"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224000","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the need for a medical exemption certificate has been effectively communicated to sufferers of diabetes by the NHS Business Service Authority and pharmacies.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225627","225627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224001","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the working group to examine the commissioning and provision of psychological therapies will examine neuro and neuropsychiatric services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225648","225648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224002","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Impact Assessment for the Standardised Packaging of Tobacco Products Regulations 2015, which derives key valuables in its cost benefit analysis from the work of Pechey et al, what account he has taken of the statements in that article that it relies on best guess estimates and that its authors have an economic or personal stake in the issue.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225624","225624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224003","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will delay implementation of standardised tobacco packaging until data on its effects on smoking prevalence in Australia is available.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225625","225625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224004","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support and guidance his Department and NHS England have made available to clinical commissioning groups to enable them to effectively commission services for smaller population groups.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225646","225646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224005","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the working group to examine the commissioning and provision of psychological therapies will be established.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225647","225647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224006","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the working group on the commissioning and provision of psychological therapies will be established; and what its scope, terms of reference and membership will be.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225661","225661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224007","2015-03-03","Department of Health","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients identified by their general practitioner as being obese have (a) received follow-up advice on how to lose or manage their weight and (b) succeeded in losing weight and maintaining their weight loss in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225670","225670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224008","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what secondary and tertiary mental health services for deaf patients are commissioned nationally by NHS England.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225660","225660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224009","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that new psychoactive substances identified by the European Monitoring Centre for Drugs and Drug Addiction are monitored by the Forensic Warning System.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225633","225633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224010","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the UK's policy will be on substantial changes to the international drugs control regime at the UN Commission on Narcotic Drugs in Vienna in March 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225649","225649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224011","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign students at schools and colleges that have lost their right to sponsor such students were removed from the UK in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225645","225645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224012","2015-03-03","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals her Department's Counter-Terrorism Referrals Unit has made to (a) Facebook, (b) Twitter, (c) Google and Youtube and (d) other websites or service providers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225636","225636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224013","2015-03-03","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many new psychoactive substances have been identified by the Forensic Early Warning System in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225637","225637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224014","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nationals of the United States are domiciled in the UK; and how many of those nationals have received visas to work (a) in the banking sector and (b) elsewhere in the financial services sector.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225596","225596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224015","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many schools and colleges that have had their right to sponsor overseas students removed have been subject to criminal proceedings in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225664","225664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224016","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-EU students who were given visas to study in the UK failed to leave the UK after their studies had ended in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225663","225663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224017","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the enquiries of the hon. Member for Chesterfield on behalf of Mr S Jackson, passed to her Department by the Prime Minister on 12 january 2015, reference JACK03010/03141925.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225507","225507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224018","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many criminal cases were abandoned between January 2014 and January 2015 as a result of diplomatic immunity.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225508","225508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224019","2015-03-05","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers of what rank retired from each police force in the North West in each year from 2009-10 to 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225526","225526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224020","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are detained in prison for immigration control purposes under the service level agreement between her Department and the National Offender Management Service; and when that agreement is due to be renewed.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225536","225536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224021","2015-03-03","Department for International Development","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on legal fees in the case of The Queen (on the application of O) and the Secretary of State for International Development.","Biography information for Rebecca Harris","Rebecca Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225572","225572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224022","2015-03-02","Department for International Development","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the numbers of internally displaced Sunni former residents of Iraqi cities taken over by ISIL.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225592","225592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224023","2015-03-02","Department for International Development","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to help the Iraqi government support the return of former residents of cities previously occupied by ISIL in Iraq who fled those cities upon occupation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225593","225593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224024","2015-03-02","Department for International Development","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the development of tax collection capacity in developing countries.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225599","225599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224025","2015-03-02","Department for International Development","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve education in Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225600","225600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224026","2015-03-02","Department for International Development","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the performance of the UK Aid Transparency Guarantee.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225654","225654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224027","2015-03-02","Department for International Development","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that environmental sustainability features within every part of the post-2015 Millennium Development Goals framework.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225653","225653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224028","2015-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much in legal aid claims was paid to Leigh Day in 2013-14.","Biography information for Rebecca Harris","Rebecca Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225672","225672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224029","2015-03-03","HM Treasury","2015-02-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many IR35 cases brought to tribunal led to (a) prosecution and (b) acquittal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225673","225673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224030","2015-03-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to promote mediation in the resolution of family and other legal disputes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225655","225655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224031","2015-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2015 to Question 223614, how many such applications by grandparents for child arrangement orders were successful in each of those financial years; and how many such orders were breached in each of those financial years.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225681","225681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224032","2015-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2015 to Question 224736, how many domestic violence court sittings took place in each magistrates court in Lancashire in 2014; and how many domestic violence trials took place in each of those courts during those sittings.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225525","225525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224033","2015-03-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review burial and cremation law.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225548","225548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224034","2015-03-02","Prime Minister","2015-02-26","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions on nuclear power policy he had with his Austrian counterpart and other representatives of the Austrian government during the European Council meeting in Brussels from 12 to 13 February 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225594","225594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224035","2015-03-02","Prime Minister","2015-02-26","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to his oral evidence to the Liaison Committee on 24 February 2015, what assessment he has made of the military threat posed by Russia in the Baltic states.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225595","225595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224036","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff transferred from Swansea Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre  to Milford Haven Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre between January 2012 and February 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225613","225613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224037","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff were employed at (a) Swansea and (b) Milford Haven Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre in (i) August 2013, (ii) February 2014, (iii) August 2014 and (iv) February 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225614","225614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224038","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many hours of shift time were staffed below risk-assessed levels at (a) Swansea and (b) Milford Haven Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre in (i) July 2013, (ii) January 2014, (iii) July 2014 and (iv) January 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225615","225615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224039","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many shifts were staffed below risk-assessed levels at (a) Swansea and (b) Milford Haven Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre in (i) July 2013, (ii) January 2014, (iii) July 2014 and (iv) January 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225616","225616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224040","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the amount of money that has been saved by the Government by making vehicle tax registration available online.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225668","225668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224041","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many hours of training Milford Haven staff have received from staff at the Swansea Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre on knowledge of the coastline currently covered by Liverpool Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225612","225612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224042","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the A595 has been closed to traffic because of (a) roadworks and (b) accidents in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225585","225585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224043","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road accidents occurred on the A595 in each of the last 10 years; and how many such accidents resulted in fatalities.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225586","225586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224044","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of likely numbers of road users on the A595 in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225587","225587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224045","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what requests his Department has received for additional funding for the A595.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225588","225588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224046","2015-03-04","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library the progress report by KPMG of its review of bus market franchising when it is issued in early March 2015.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225524","225524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224047","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will visit the Black Cat roundabout in Bedfordshire to make an assessment of the extent of the improvement works being carried out and the effect of those works on neighbouring businesses.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225546","225546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224048","2015-03-04","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to improve traffic flow and safety on the A1 between London and the A46 at Newark.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225528","225528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224049","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has made to Southern Railway about its performance.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225568","225568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224050","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has made to Network Rail about engineering works at London Bridge station and their effects on rail services into and out of that station.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225569","225569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224051","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, under what circumstances his Department may remove a franchise from a train operating company before the scheduled end of a franchise contract.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225570","225570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224052","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that adequate measures are in place to assess the toxicity of fumes entering aircraft cabins from aircraft engines; what steps he has taken to ensure the prevention of adverse effects on pilots, cabin crew and passengers caused by toxic levels of fumes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Evans","Jonathan Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225506","225506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224053","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to bring forward proposals to amend Regulation 36 of the Gas Safety (Installation and Use) Regulations 1998 to introduce MOT-style 13 month gas appliance and flue servicing duties on landlords.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225517","225517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224054","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will commission research into the reasons why the largest category of people transferred from incapacity benefit to the fit-to-work group have been people with mental health issues.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225554","225554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224055","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the scoring system in his Department's new guidelines for claimants with mental health issues to decide eligibility for support groups differentiates between men and women.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225547","225547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224056","2015-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will commission research into the effect of benefit sanctions on the (a) mental and (b) physical health of people on jobseeker's allowance or the work-related activity group of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225560","225560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224057","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many first contact notice of closure letters have been sent to (a) Segment 1 and (b) Segment 2 CSA cases in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland, (iii) England, (iv) Wales and (v) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225652","225652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224058","2015-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's most recent estimate is of the number of Child Support Agency cases within each segment of the planned case closure programme in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225674","225674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224059","2015-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2015 to Question 224963, on which dates he or his Ministerial colleagues have met a former Remploy employee since May 2010; and when any further such meetings are planned.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225675","225675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224060","2015-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2015 to Question 224791, what topics he discussed with staff during his visit to Preston Benefit Centre on 11 April 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225638","225638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224061","2015-03-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people making an application for universal credit are not registered on the real-time information system.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225640","225640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223499","2015-03-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Department issues to utility and energy companies on the supply of information of customers to credit reference agencies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225320","225320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223500","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the aggregate cost is to the public purse of designing, printing and nationwide display of the Business is Great posters; and what the objectives are of that campaign.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225334","225334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223502","2015-03-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2015 to Question 224087, which of those documents on BAFTA funding provide guidance on diversity issues.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225343","225343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223503","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to raise consumers' awareness of their rights following poor service from fact-checking websites for Government-provided services such as the EHIC card.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225352","225352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223504","2015-03-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how an institution can become a designated institution under section 129 of the Education Reform Act 1988.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225350","225350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223505","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much has been paid by the Green Investment Bank to projects in Wales in each year of that bank's operation.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225374","225374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223506","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department has had with oilfield services company Archer on the plans of that company to reduce its UK workforce by 400 people.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225401","225401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223507","2015-03-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to encourage innovation in low carbon technology in the South West of England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225384","225384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223509","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of maintaining the current level of spending on science research and development beyond 2016; and what discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues on that matter.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225412","225412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223510","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the relationship between direct air connectivity between UK airports and overseas locations and tourism from the overseas locations so connected.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225415","225415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223511","2015-03-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to increase the level of student maintenance loans in areas where the cost of living matches or exceeds the London average to the level of such loans in London.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225433","225433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223512","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution made by the direct connectivity of UK airports to emerging markets to tourism from such locations in the medium and long-term.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225416","225416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223513","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the comparative benefits to businesses of direct aviation connectivity between two locations and connectivity requiring a stopover at a hub airport.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225420","225420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223515","2015-03-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a statutory right for mothers to take breaks for breastfeeding in the workplace.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225438","225438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223516","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of overseas visitors to (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland arrive by air; and what proportion of total spending by overseas visitors such visitors account for in each nation.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225419","225419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223517","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase economic growth in Devon, Cornwall and Somerset.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225427","225427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223518","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the process is for deciding the location of the new Energy Systems Catapult.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225428","225428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223519","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the name is of each social care provider being investigated by HM Revenue and Customs for non-compliance with national minimum wage regulations.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225483","225483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223521","2015-03-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which social care providers are currently being investigated by HM Revenue and Customs for potential non-compliance with the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225484","225484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223522","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's press release of 11 February 2015, Free wifi to help rail commuters stay connected, and the speech of the Minister for the Cabinet Office at Sprint 15 of 3 February 2015, whether the free train wifi announced in that release will use the infrastructure announced in that speech.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225471","225471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223523","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 on the ability of contracting authorities to plan joint health and social care commissioning.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225456","225456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223525","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will delay implementation of the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 to ensure that appropriate guidance on trading companies exemptions, reserved contracts provisions, Article 18.2, best price-quality ratio provisions and the new light touch regime can be issued to contracting authorities in time for them to update procurement procedures.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225312","225312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223528","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the average price of a 700ml bottle of whisky is constituted by tax; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225321","225321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223529","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the contribution of the domestic spirits industry to the economy of (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225322","225322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223531","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs supported by the domestic spirits industry in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225323","225323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223532","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward proposals to ensure that all care workers receive at least the living wage for every hour that they work.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225326","225326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223533","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to devolve air passenger duty to the Northern Ireland Executive; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225328","225328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223535","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from community energy co-operatives on the decision to remove their entitlement to Enterprise Investment Scheme tax relief.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225330","225330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223536","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will update his Department's guidance on Managing Public Money, published in July 2013, to include consideration of social, economic and environmental value when government departments dispose of land assets.","Biography information for Mark Hunter","Mark Hunter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225332","225332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223537","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many mandatory reconsiderations have been requested for tax credit claims; how many of those requests have been successful; and how long on average it takes to process each such request.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225361","225361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223539","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Pensions Infrastructure Platform; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225354","225354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223540","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many section 660a status enquiries HM Revenue and Customs has made in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225344","225344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223542","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the tax yield was from Section 660a legislation in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225346","225346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223543","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many enforcement actions in respect of Section 660a legislation there have been in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225347","225347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223544","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost of off-payroll arrangements in government departments and their arm's length bodies was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225345","225345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223545","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2015 to Question 224081, how many people have been assisted by HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) in pursuing national minimum wage recovery through the civil courts on their behalf; and what the value was of wages recovered through the civil courts where HMRC has so pursued recovery in each year from 2005.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225382","225382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223546","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many investigations were commenced by HM Revenue and Customs National Minimum Wage compliance teams in each of the last five years; and how many such investigations resulted in a Notice of Underpayment being issued.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225467","225467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223548","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many enforcement actions were pursued by HM Revenue and Customs National Minimum Wage compliance teams through (a) employment tribunals and (b) civil courts in each of the last five years; and what amount was recovered through that process in each such year.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225468","225468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223549","2015-03-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many employers were publicly named by the Government for non-compliance with the National Minimum Wage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225469","225469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223550","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many fines were imposed on employers for non-compliance with the National Minimum Wage in each of the last five years; and what the value of each such fine was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225470","225470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223551","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make the Scottish Fire and Rescue Service eligible for VAT refunds.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225404","225404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223552","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2015 to Question 224081, what the average length of time was between a worker reporting non-payment of the national minimum wage to HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) and receiving the recovered wages owed to them in cases where HMRC assists with pursuing recovery through the civil courts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225383","225383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223553","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he took into account information in files relating to HSBC and tax evasion when appointing Lord Green Trade Minister in January 2011.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225449","225449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223554","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to introduce a system of grant funding for the training of professional freight drivers.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225458","225458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223556","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department carried out an impact assessment on the future implications of signing its agreement with the Swiss Confederation on co-operation in the area of taxation.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225451","225451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223557","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish in full Lord Justice Bingham's report, Inquiry into the Supervision of the Bank of Credit and Commerce International, on the closure of the Bank of Credit and Commerce International, completed in 1992.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225460","225460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223558","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what dates special advisers in his Department have sent emails that refer to HSBC in the last five years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225455","225455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223560","2015-03-02","HM Treasury","2015-02-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what dates he has met which representatives of HSBC bank since taking office.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225487","225487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223561","2015-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the value for money to the public purse of the EU's INTERREG programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225454","225454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223562","2015-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to incentivise local authorities to promote social tenants' Right to Buy.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225453","225453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223563","2015-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the appropriateness of leaseholder repair charges levied by the London Borough of Tower Hamlets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225452","225452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223564","2015-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many serving firefighters have served in that capacity for over 40 years.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225357","225357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223565","2015-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made in discussion with the Honours and Decorations Committee and the Cabinet Office on introducing a further medal or bar to the Long Service and Good Conduct Medal for firefighters that far exceed 20 years' service.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225358","225358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223566","2015-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many firefighters have been awarded a Long Service and Good Conduct Medal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225359","225359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223567","2015-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will investigate options for helping Portsmouth City Council to purchase the land at the St James' Hospital site in Milton.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225353","225353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223568","2015-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Inquiry into Anti-Semitism, published in February 2015 by the All-Party Group on Anti-Semitism, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to tackle the use of social media for anti-Semitic abuse.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225329","225329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223571","2015-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on plans to reduce funding for Libraries NI in 2015-16.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225395","225395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223572","2015-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to increase the participation of teenage girls in out-of-school sports clubs.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225397","225397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223573","2015-03-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether there is a limit on the number of stations on a digital audio multiplex aimed at the same section of the listening audience.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225381","225381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223574","2015-03-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the (a) representation of BME programming and channels available on Freeview and (b) the barriers to BME channels being on Freeview.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225472","225472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223575","2015-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2014 to Question 211346, what response the Colombian government provided to the Minister for Latin American Affairs when human rights were raised during the Minister's visit in June 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225466","225466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223576","2015-03-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2014 to Question 210962, how many armed forces personnel travelled to Colombia during 2013 in order to further the defence relationship.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225465","225465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223578","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 10 December 2014 to Questions 217147 and 217149, for what reasons providing the number of people recruited to the Cyber Reserve may undermine national security.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225462","225462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223579","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, at what rate Accelerated Incremental Progression payments have been made in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225421","225421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223580","2015-03-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2014 to Question 211346, in what ways is the issue of human rights closely examined before any military assistance to Colombia is approved; and at what level or rank is this examination conducted.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225431","225431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223582","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the armed forces have had to repay money as a result of errors in Accelerated Incremental Progression payments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225424","225424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223583","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date his Department expects to receive the recommendations of the Chief of the General Staff on whether the British Army should form a Sikh regiment; and what criteria will be used to take a decision on that matter.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225425","225425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223584","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Reservists have been recruited to the 77th Brigade of the Army; and what target his Department has set for the proportion of that Brigade to be made up of Reservists.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225426","225426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223585","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what method his Department uses to calculate money owed by members of the armed forces as a result of errors in Accelerated Incremental Progression payments.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225422","225422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223586","2015-03-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2014 to Question 211346, what expertise and advice the UK has provided on international humanitarian law and human rights during military operations at (a) seminars and conferences and (b) other events since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225432","225432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223587","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what provisions are in place to ensure that service personnel receive adequate notice when they owe money because of errors in Accelerated Incremental Progression payments.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225423","225423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223588","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Squirrel HT1/HT2, (b) T67M-2 Firefly, (c) Grob 115 Tutor, (d) Viking, (e) Vigilant, (f) AW139, (g) A109 Power, (h) Sea King HAS6, (i) Sea King HU5, (j) Merlin HM1, (k) Merlin MH2, (l) Sea King ASaC7, (m) Sea King HC4, (n) Sea King HC6CR, (o) Lynx HAS3, (p) Lynx HMA8, (q) Wildcat HMA2, (r) Hawk, (s) Grob 115 Heron, (t) Dauphin, (u) King Air, (v) Islander AL1, (w) Defender 4S AL2, (x) Defender T3, (y) Lynx AH7 and (z) Lynx AH9A are in (i) the forward fleet, (ii) sustainment and (iii) storage.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225371","225371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223589","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what military equipment has been gifted to Ukraine in the last two years; and what estimate he has made of the value of that equipment when it was gifted.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225372","225372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223590","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Typhoon, (b) Tornado GR4/4A, (c) F-35B, (d) Sentry AEW1, (e) Sentinel R1 ASTOR, (f) Shadow R.1, (g) Islander CC2/CC2A, (h) MQ-9 Predator B, (i) RC-135 Rivet Joint, (j) A330 FSTA, (k) Hercules, (l) C-17 Globemaster, (m) A400M, (n) HS125 CC3, (o) BAe 146 CC2, (p) Chinook HC4, (q) Chinook HC5, (r) Chinook HC6, (s) Merlin HC3, (t) Merlin HC3A ex RDAF, (u) Puma HC2/SA330 Puma, (v) Sea King HAR3/A, (w) A109 Power, (x) Griffin HC2, (y) S-61N, (z) AW189, (aa) Hawk T1/T1A, (bb) Hawk T2, (cc) Tucano T1, (dd) King Air, (ee) Griffin HT1 are in (i) the forward fleet, (ii) sustainment and (iii) storage.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225369","225369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223591","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Apache AH1, (b) Gazelle AH1, (c) AS365N3 Dauphin, (d) Bell 212, (e) Lynx Wildcat, (f) Squirrel HT1/HT2 and (g) Watchkeeper 450 are in (i) the forward fleet, (ii) sustainment and (iii) storage.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225370","225370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223592","2015-03-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Question 222053, by what date the documents will be placed in the Library.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225380","225380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223593","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will launch an inquiry into the conduct of the war in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225324","225324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223595","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will establish a universal youth service with ring-fenced funding from central government.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225333","225333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223596","2015-03-02","Department for Education","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether sixth form colleges can apply for academy status; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225406","225406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223597","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether primary school staff receive compulsory training on assisting students with epilepsy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225399","225399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223598","2015-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average domestic (a) electricity and (b) gas bill was in each quarter in (i) 2013, (ii) 2014 and (iii) in quarter 1, 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225356","225356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223599","2015-03-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many and what proportion of people in the Scottish Highlands and Islands are classed as living in fuel poverty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Charles Kennedy","Mr Charles Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225368","225368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223600","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Peterborough constituency received a cold weather payment in the last 12 months for which records are available; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225461","225461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223601","2015-03-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many non-financial penalties Ofgem has imposed in each year since 2001; and what each such penalty was.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225502","225502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223602","2015-03-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many fines Ofgem has imposed in each year since 2001; and what the value was of each such fine.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225501","225501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223603","2015-03-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many compensation packages for consumers Ofgem has secured in each year since 2001; and what the value was of each such package.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225500","225500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223604","2015-03-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much electricity was generated from each type of source in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225491","225491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223605","2015-03-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many seizures of illegally imported meat have been made at (a) airports and (b) seaports in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225486","225486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223606","2015-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking through the Food and Environmental Research Agency deal to support businesses in Thirsk and Malton.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225457","225457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223607","2015-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the provisions of the Dangerous Dogs Exemptions Schemes (England and Wales) Order 2015 on the owners of exempted dogs intending to go to university or who serve in the armed forces; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225447","225447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223608","2015-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she consulted with (a) the British Veterinary Association, (b) the Royal Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, (c) Dogs Trust, (d) Blue Cross and (e) the Kennel Club in drawing up the provisions of the Dangerous Dogs Exemptions Schemes (England and Wales) Order 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225446","225446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223609","2015-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons the Dangerous Dogs Exemptions Schemes (England and Wales) Order 2015 does not give full effect to the court's ruling in R (Sandhin) v Isleworth Crown Court; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225448","225448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223610","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on the long-term effects on health of monosodium glutamate in food.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225437","225437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223611","2015-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to prevent non-stun slaughter of animals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225405","225405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223612","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Nigerian government on the two recent suicide bombings in the north of that country.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225398","225398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223613","2015-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in the Maldives.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225391","225391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223614","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Czech government on the shooting of eight people in a restaurant in Uhersk Brod on 24 February 2015.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225403","225403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223615","2015-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2015 to Question 223612, whether he plans to meet his counterpart in the Philippines to discuss climate change.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225378","225378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223616","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the outcome of the Government's Balance of Competences Review on his Department's policy on EU reforms.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225414","225414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223617","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of the (a) vessels and (b) companies which have been sold licences to fish in the Falkland Islands in each of the last three years have been found guilty of criminal behaviour in other legal jurisdictions.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225445","225445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223618","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of Niger to press for further action to be taken against people perpetrating attacks on civilians and church property.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225459","225459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223619","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Taiwanese government on labour conditions on board Taiwanese-flagged vessels operating in Falkland Islands waters in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225443","225443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223620","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department has provided to the Falkland Islands government to tackle modern slavery on foreign fishing vessels operating in Falkland Islands waters.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225444","225444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223621","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of foreign nationals who have been reported as missing from foreign-flagged fishing vessels in Falkland Islands waters in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225497","225497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223622","2015-03-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent to which Hamas is attempting to rebuild its terrorist infrastructure in the Gaza Strip.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225494","225494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223623","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data his Department holds on and what assessment it has made of the effects of gambling on mental health; and how much his Department spent on counselling for people with an addiction to gambling in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225496","225496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223624","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many contracts Arriva holds for patient transport services; and what area each such contract covers.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225482","225482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223625","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans for the transfer of dialysis treatment to clinical commissioning groups to take place.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225442","225442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223626","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure equal patient access to dialysis treatment throughout the UK when the provision for dialysis treatment is transferred to clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225439","225439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223627","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who his Department consulted on the transfer of dialysis treatment to clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225440","225440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223628","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what protocols are in place for the transfer of responsibility for the provision of dialysis treatment to local clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225441","225441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223629","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2014 to Question 211702, how many finished hospital admission episodes with a primary diagnosis of asthma there were among people aged (a) under and (b) over 18 years in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225498","225498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223630","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014 to Question 202551, how many residents of care homes had an emergency admission to a hospital in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225499","225499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223631","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he and officials in his Department have had with their counterparts in other Departments on a national gambling strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225488","225488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223632","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the health effects of consanguineous marriages; and what steps he is taking to reduce them.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225464","225464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223633","2015-03-03","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2014 to Question 211703, how many people were recorded on a general practice register with a diagnosis of asthma in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225503","225503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223634","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the next phase of the evaluation of the Family Nurse Partnership.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225385","225385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223635","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Minister for Life Sciences will hold a further meeting with families of people with Duchenne muscular dystrophy on the availability of the drug Translarna.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225407","225407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223636","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support teenagers with epilepsy.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225402","225402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223637","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps the Government has taken to reduce the level of childhood obesity.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225400","225400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223638","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will change guidelines on cervical smear tests to permit GPs to conduct such tests on women outside of routine screening time frames, if the GP believes that such tests are necessary to investigate presenting symptoms.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225373","225373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223639","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects his Department to be in a position to make a decision on HPV vaccination for adolescent boys.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225307","225307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223640","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward the timeline for the review and recommendation in respect of the introduction of a universal HPV vaccination programme.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225308","225308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223641","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects a decision to be made on introducing HPV vaccinations for men who have sex with men.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225309","225309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223642","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason Public Health England is undertaking additional cost effectiveness modelling for the HPV vaccine and adolescent boys.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225305","225305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223643","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons Public Health England did not commence its cost effectiveness modelling for HPV vaccination for adolescent boys until 2015.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225306","225306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223644","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the difference in the up-take of novel oral anticoagulants and the uptake projected by NICE.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225341","225341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223645","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of IVF cycle procedures that were carried out by each West Midlands NHS trust in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225304","225304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223646","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NICE and NHS England take to ensure that (a) mandatory NICE health technology assessment guidance is fully implemented by clinical commissioning groups and (b) the up-take of innovative medicines is in line with NICE's expectations.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225342","225342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223647","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of cataract surgery procedures that were carried out by each West Midlands NHS trust in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225313","225313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223648","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of knee replacement operations that were carried out by each West Midlands NHS trust in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225315","225315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223649","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of hip replacement operations that were carried out by each West Midlands NHS trust in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225316","225316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223650","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of varicose vein surgery procedures that were carried out by each West Midlands NHS trust in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225317","225317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223651","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of breast reconstruction operations that were carried out by each West Midlands NHS trust in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225318","225318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223652","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his plans to devolve health and social care provision and expenditure in Greater Manchester, what mechanisms will be put in place to allow his Department to intervene in the event of failure of that provision.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225338","225338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223653","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which areas of health and social care provision and expenditure he plans for decision-making in Greater Manchester to be (a) devolved and (b) not devolved.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225339","225339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223654","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his plans to devolve health and social care provision and expenditure in Greater Manchester, if he will take steps to ensure that future changes to NHS provision in that area, once that devolution of powers has taken place, will be subject to public consultation.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225337","225337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223655","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his plans to devolve health and social care provision and expenditure in Greater Manchester, what safeguards he plans to put in place to ensure minimum standards of care and treatment within NHS services in that area remain when that devolution of powers has taken place.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225336","225336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223656","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the HPV vaccination programme for men who have sex with men will commence; and whether a delivery partner has been secured for that programme.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225331","225331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223657","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of people suffering from idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225325","225325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223658","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his plans to devolve health and social care provision and expenditure in Greater Manchester, if he will exclude decision-making on NHS pay and conditions from those plans.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225335","225335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223659","2015-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners there are in the prison system in Kent; and how many such prisoners have completed their sentence and are awaiting deportation.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225311","225311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223660","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 to Question 222334, by what date the documents will be placed in the Library.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225379","225379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223661","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the performance of Serco in providing accommodation and transport services for asylum seekers under the Compass contract.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225410","225410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223662","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 218892, what average length of time it takes for her Department to grant a visa after a decision is taken not to appeal a decision of the Asylum and Immigration Tribunal.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225434","225434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223663","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many sexual harm prevention orders and sexual offences prevention orders were issued in each of the last five years; and how many such orders were made after a request from a Chief of Police under section 104(5) of the Sexual Offences Act 2003.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225480","225480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223664","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there were for human trafficking offences in 2014; and how many such cases involved a victim who was a child.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225481","225481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223665","2015-03-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there were under section 14 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 in 2014.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225479","225479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223666","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are subject to sexual risk orders in each police force area.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225478","225478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223667","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Border Force sniffer dogs operate at (a) Heathrow Airport and (b) other airports and seaports in the UK to detect illegally imported meat.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225485","225485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223668","2015-03-02","House of Commons Commission","2015-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will seek information from contractors operating on the parliamentary estate on how many of their workers are employed on a zero-hours contract.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225489","225489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223669","2015-02-27","Department for International Development","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received on the situation between the government of Democratic Republic of Congo and Rwandan Hutu rebels.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225396","225396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223670","2015-03-02","Department for International Development","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much support, and under what categories, her Department provided directly to British Overseas Territories in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225390","225390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223671","2015-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) breathalysed and (b) convicted of driving under the influence of alcohol in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225377","225377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223672","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures her Department has put in place to track foreign national offenders upon release back into the community since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225366","225366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223673","2015-03-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary and the Foreign Secretary on the development of the foreign national offenders action plan.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225367","225367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223674","2015-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many courtrooms there are in (a) the High Court at the Royal Courts of Justice, (b) the County Court in Birmingham, (c) the Family Court in Birmingham and (d) the High Court in Birmingham.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225310","225310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223675","2015-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward proposals to ensure that domestic abuse victims are informed of the release from prison of their abusers regardless of how long they have served in prison.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225327","225327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223676","2015-03-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress he has made on implementation of a 24 hour coroners system.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225340","225340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223677","2015-03-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce delays in magistrates courts between a defendant's first appearance and their trial.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225436","225436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223678","2015-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of comparative per capita levels of legal aid spending in England and Wales and other jurisdictions.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225411","225411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223679","2015-03-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was paid in fines for television licensing offences in the (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225430","225430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223680","2015-02-27","Prime Minister","2015-02-25","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he carried out due diligence before recommending the appointment of Lord Green to the House of Lords in September 2010.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225450","225450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223681","2015-03-02","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2015-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what assessment the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority has made of the effect on total spend on hon. Members' travel of the discontinuation of the East Coast Rewards Scheme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225388","225388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223682","2015-02-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what representations the Electoral Commission made to (a) the Cabinet Office and (b) other bodies on the issue of the accuracy of the 2014 electoral register during the course of its compilation.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225355","225355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223683","2015-02-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-25","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Overseas Voter Day on 5 February 2015; what budget was allocated to that campaign; and how many overseas registrations resulted from that campaign.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225429","225429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223684","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons it is not a requirement to monitor and detect in real time organo-phosphate compounds in the cabin air of aircraft operating in and out of UK airports.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225418","225418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223685","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of direct flights from Scottish airports to emerging economies which have commenced since 2010.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225417","225417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223686","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of co-ordination of work by the train operating companies and Network Rail in order to ensure the smooth running of the railway.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225413","225413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223687","2015-03-09","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff employed at the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency office in Preston were made redundant when it closed; and what the total cost was of those redundancies.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225392","225392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223688","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any compensation is payable by his Department or Network Rail to Hitachi Rail Europe under the contracts between those bodies in the event of delay to the commencement of Intercity Express Programme train testing on the Great Western Main Line or the East Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225490","225490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223689","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the appropriateness of the current system for licensing sellers of mobility scooters.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225475","225475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223690","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what modelling work his Department has undertaken on road traffic flows and displaced traffic during the construction period of High Speed 2 Phase 1; and if he will publish such work.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225495","225495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223691","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with representatives of the insurance industry on products that might be offered to drivers of mobility scooters and how such products could be used to promote safety.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225476","225476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223692","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, further to the Answer of 8 January 2015 to Question 219781, for what reason action was not taken against SEAT UK for failing to submit a completed V5C/3 form.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225492","225492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223693","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will review the specificity of conditions for the eligibility to use mobility scooters.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225477","225477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223694","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people received criminal convictions for breaching a railway byelaw under Schedule 20 of the Transport Act 2000 in (a) 2014, (b) 2013 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225493","225493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223695","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of disabled people's charities on uptake of mobility scooters in the UK.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225473","225473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223696","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the potential merits of making information about qualification for disability benefits available to agencies responsible for ensuring safety on the roads in respect of mobility scooters.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225474","225474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223697","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) original and (b) revised timetable is for works carried out at the junction of the A483 and A55 roads in West Cheshire.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225319","225319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223698","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will carry out an urgent assessment of the quality of the work carried out at the junction of the A483 and A55 supervised by the Highways Agency.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225314","225314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223699","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of road traffic incidents in which a vehicle was damaged and a pedestrian or cyclist was at fault in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225348","225348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223700","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were registered for the Blue Badge scheme in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225376","225376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223701","2015-03-02","Department for Transport","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Virgin Trains and Stagecoach on the East Coast Rewards Scheme; and what representations he has received on this matter.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225389","225389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223702","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of benefit sanctions in Middlesbrough were overturned following a mandatory reconsideration in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225375","225375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223703","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of universal credit claimants likely to face hardship as a result of the seven-day waiting period before new claimants are paid.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225409","225409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223704","2015-03-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department issues to central and local government officials responsible for processing housing benefit and council tax benefit claims on withdrawal of pension fund money under the pension freedom rules that come into force in April 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225351","225351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223705","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many working-age households are better off out of work than in work in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225408","225408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223706","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department issues to jobcentres on food bank referral for families with disabled children whose benefit applications have not been processed in a timely manner.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225349","225349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223707","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effective delivery of local welfare schemes by English local authorities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225365","225365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223708","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether contractual terms for the provision of benefit assessments have transferred directly from Atos to Maximus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225360","225360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223709","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received about instances of people being sent from Jobcentre Plus to apply to the local welfare scheme instead of being offered a short-term advance of benefits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225363","225363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223710","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent through the Work Programme on (a) attachment, (b) job outcome and (c) sustainment payments for people aged (i) up to 24, (ii) 25 to 49 and (iii) 50 years and over since June 2011.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225364","225364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223711","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will promote the sharing of best practice in the administration of local welfare schemes.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225362","225362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223712","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training is provided for frontline staff of his Department on working with people with mental health issues.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225463","225463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223713","2015-03-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff are employed at his Department's offices at Palatine House, Preston; and what planned staffing levels at those offices are in each of the next three financial years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225393","225393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223714","2015-03-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff directly employed by his Department at the Carer's Allowance Unit, Palatine House, Preston earn (a) more and (b) less than the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225394","225394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223715","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what value of interim payments have been made to people affected by sanctions or delays in benefit payments.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225386","225386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223716","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral Answer of 8 December 2014, Official Report, column 638, what steps he has taken to raise awareness of interim payments for people affected by sanctions or delays in benefit payments.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225387","225387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223717","2015-03-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review the procedures for notifying his Department of a change of circumstances in the event of hospitalisation when the claimant is incapacitated and unable to contact the Disability Benefits helpline.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225435","225435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223960","2015-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken since 2010 to increase British influence around the world.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907839","907839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224570","2015-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the likelihood of a two-state solution emerging in the Middle East.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907851","907851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224571","2015-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the strategic analysis capability of his Department in relation to Russia and the Middle East.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907845","907845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224572","2015-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress in the nuclear talks between Iran and the P5+1 group of countries.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907847","907847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224573","2015-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to tackle extremist ideology and to reduce its appeal worldwide.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907848","907848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224574","2015-03-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Pakistan on discrimination and violence against people of minority faiths in that country.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907842","907842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223178","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on information given to AEA Technology in 1996 on that organisation's pension fund.","Biography information for Lord Haselhurst","Sir Alan Haselhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225080","225080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223179","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to investigate complaints made by members of the AEA Technology pension fund on information they were given by UK Atomic Energy Authority when AEA Technology was set up in 1996.","Biography information for Lord Haselhurst","Sir Alan Haselhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225081","225081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223180","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the cost to the Exchequer of restoring the pensions of AEA Technology pensioners.","Biography information for Lord Haselhurst","Sir Alan Haselhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225082","225082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223181","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will ensure that anyone who was misled by the UK Atomic Energy Agency when AEA Technology was created in 1996 is properly compensated for losses they have subsequently incurred.","Biography information for Lord Haselhurst","Sir Alan Haselhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225083","225083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223182","2015-02-26","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Insolvency Act 1986.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225120","225120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223183","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of payments by the Skills Funding Agency under the Apprenticeship Grant for Employers scheme were made within 30 days in each of the last twelve months.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225222","225222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223184","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many overseas trade missions which were attended or led by a government minister have been completed in the last twelve months; on what dates each such visit took place; and to which countries those ministers travelled on each occasion.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225223","225223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223185","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of Economic and Social Research Council research funding is spent on (a) social enterprise and (b) economics.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225233","225233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223186","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2015 to Question 222107, how many apprentices of each age group were employees of his Department, its agencies or of other government departments before their apprenticeship began.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225224","225224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223187","2015-03-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure universities better support students who are also carers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225302","225302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223188","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many full time equivalent officials of what civil service grade work on each of his Department's sector strategies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225225","225225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223189","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses have engaged with each Catapult Centre in each year since it opened.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225226","225226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223190","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to attract non-EU students to universities in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225240","225240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223191","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department has spent on advertising higher education aimed at non-EU nationals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225241","225241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223192","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to attract non-EU academic staff to seek employment at universities in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225242","225242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223193","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of participants in the Employee Shareholder Status scheme in (a) Glasgow South West constituency, (b) Glasgow city region, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225255","225255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223194","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of people who enter higher education at the age of 18 do so with BTEC qualifications as the entry criteria.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225257","225257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223195","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses are participating in the Employee Shareholder Status scheme in (a) Glasgow South West constituency, (b) Glasgow City Region, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225261","225261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223196","2015-02-27","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many new businesses were created in Esher and Walton constituency in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225268","225268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223197","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of unemployed young people did not claim jobseeker's allowance in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225266","225266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223198","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the advertising budget was for each Government department in the financial years (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13, (c) 2013-14 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225244","225244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223199","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2014 to Question 211134, how much funding has gone to each of the social enterprise incubators named; and how the social enterprise incubators based in London but with national focus realised their national mission.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225232","225232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223200","2015-02-26","Cabinet Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many pension payments to retired civil servants have been (a) missed and (b) delayed by MyCSP, in each month since September 2014.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225093","225093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223201","2015-02-26","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-02-24","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment his Department has made of the accuracy of the data provided by the Electoral Commission on the 2014 Electoral Registers used for the implementation of Individual Electoral Registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225145","225145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223202","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many voluntary disclosures of untaxed income by private landlords have HM Revenue and Customs received in each of the last five years; and what the value was of such disclosures from properties based (a) in the UK, (b) in Scotland, (c) in England, (d) in Wales, (e) in Northern Ireland and (f) overseas.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225101","225101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223203","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many landlords have made a voluntary disclosure to HM Revenue and Customs since the Let Property Campaign began; and how much previously undeclared income has been declared as a result of that campaign.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225104","225104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223204","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many prosecutions were brought for tax credit fraud in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225128","225128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223205","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total contribution to the Exchequer of the wine industry was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225129","225129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223206","2015-02-27","Cabinet Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people directly employed in the wine industry and that industry's supply chain in the UK.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225130","225130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223207","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of gin sold in the UK was produced domestically in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225131","225131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223208","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what quantity of spirits produced in the UK was exported in 2013.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225132","225132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223209","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the contribution of the English wine industry to the UK economy.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225133","225133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223210","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the tax yield was from BN66 legislation in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225152","225152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223211","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many enforcement actions in respect of BN66 legislation there have been in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225153","225153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223212","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many BN66 status enquiries HM Revenue and Customs has made in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225154","225154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223213","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he next plans to publish Treasury minutes: progress report on implementing recommendations of Public Accounts Committee.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225106","225106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223214","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much mortgage interest relief for private landlords was worth and how many recipients there were, in each of the last five years; and if he will estimate how much that relief will be worth and how many such recipients there will be in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225085","225085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223215","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, in how many cases related to tax evasion did failure to agree a rate of penalty go on appeal to the First-Tier Tribunal (Tax) or Upper Tribunal (Tax and Chancery Chamber) and result in a penalty that was (a) the same as the original amount, (b) a greater amount or (c) a lower amount in the last five years.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225251","225251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223216","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost was to his Department of the visits and press conferences for the (a) long term economic plans for Yorkshire and (b) long term economic plan for the north-west events.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225243","225243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223217","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Section 660a cases brought to tribunal led to (a) prosecution, (b) acquittal and (c) out of court settlements in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225201","225201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223218","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many successful prosecutions for breaches of national minimum wage legislation there have been since 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225245","225245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223219","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many convictions there have been as a result of prosecutions brought by HM Revenue and Customs for tax evasion in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225249","225249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223220","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cases a taxpayer settled with HM Revenue and Customs for a penalty less than that initially set by the investigating inspector in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225264","225264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223221","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what interventions his Department have made in relation to the latest pay remit for staff at the Information Commissioner's Office.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225272","225272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223222","2015-02-27","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of penalties collected by HM Revenue and Customs as a result of criminal convictions relating to tax avoidance and evasion was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225265","225265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223223","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many IR35 cases brought to tribunal led to (a) prosecution and (b) acquittal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225202","225202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223224","2015-02-26","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many BN66 cases brought to tribunal led to (a) prosecution, (b) acquittal and (c) out of court settlements in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225200","225200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223228","2015-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on advertising on Classic FM in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225228","225228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223229","2015-02-27","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on advertising on regional commercial radio stations in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225229","225229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223230","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many cases of non-compliance relating to the return of dangerous goods from Afghanistan there have been in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225219","225219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223231","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department does not plan to give evidence at the planning inquiry in respect of wind turbines and precision approach radar at French Farm, French Drove, Thorney near Peterborough in March 2015.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225253","225253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223232","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what operations vote (a) Department Expenditure Limit and (b) Annually Managed Expenditure outturn by subhead was in (i) near cash and (ii) non-cash terms for the financial years 2010-11 to 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225169","225169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223233","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value is of military equipment (a) returned to the UK, (b) destroyed in Afghanistan and (c) gifted to the Afghan government since the withdrawal of British troops from that country.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225173","225173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223234","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the new role will be of the 77th Brigade; and how many troops will be involved in that initiative.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225283","225283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223235","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to increase the number of people qualified and experienced in munitions and explosives.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225193","225193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223236","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Supplementary Estimate Provision of Defence Capability vote (a) Department Expenditure Limit and (b) Annually Managed Expenditure provision by subhead was in (i) near-cash and (ii) non-cash terms in each financial year from 2010-11.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225276","225276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223237","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Memorandum of Understanding with the Republic of Ireland on defence collaboration signed on 15 January 2015.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225275","225275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223238","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Main Estimate Operations vote (a) Department Expenditure Limit and (b) Annually Managed Expenditure provision was by subhead in (i) near-cash and (ii) non-cash terms in in each financial year from 2010-11.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225277","225277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223239","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Supplementary Estimate Operations vote (a) Department Expenditure Limit and (b) Annually Managed Expenditure provision by subhead was in (i) near-cash and (ii) non-cash terms in each financial year from 2010-11.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225278","225278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223240","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Provision of Defence Capability vote (a) Department Expenditure Limit and (b) Annually Managed Expenditure outturn by subhead was in (i) near-cash and (ii) non-cash terms in each financial year from 2010-11.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225279","225279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223241","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Main Estimate Provision of Defence Capability vote (a) Department Expenditure Limit and (b) Annually Managed Expenditure provision by subhead was in (i) near-cash and (ii) non-cash terms in each financial year from 2010-11.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225280","225280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223242","2015-02-27","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions were explosive ordnance disposal personnel deployed in Northern Ireland to deal with devices or suspect devices between 20 February 2014 and 19 February 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225158","225158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223243","2015-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he requests the Single Source Regulation Office to perform additional analysis, on the basis of information it has received or generated, but which it is not required to perform, who pays for this analysis; and what estimate he has made of the costs of that analysis to his Department.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225162","225162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223244","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure schools do not require uniforms to be bought from specialist providers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225156","225156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223245","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to reduce the costs of school uniforms.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225155","225155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223246","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what amount her Department spent on marketing (a) the Troops to Teachers scheme and (b) each other Initial Teacher Training scheme between June 2013 and 31 December 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225107","225107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223247","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of (a) the expected number of applicants for the 2015-16 and 2016-17 cohorts of the Troops to Teachers scheme, (b) the number expected to join that scheme and (c) the number expected to complete the training.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225108","225108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223248","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of the two-year extension of the Troops to Teachers scheme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225109","225109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223249","2015-02-26","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what feedback her Department has received from schools on the effectiveness of the British Armed Forces: Learning Resource 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225098","225098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223250","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received on the BUSK campaign for safe coach transport in relation to coach tour companies being contracted for long-distance school trips.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225089","225089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223251","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department issues to schools on the sleeping conditions for coach drivers on long-distance school trips.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225090","225090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223252","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when guidance on safe transport for long-distance school trips was last reviewed.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225091","225091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223253","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has issued to schools on ensuring that safe conditions apply to coach drivers contracted to provide transport for long-distance school trips.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225092","225092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223254","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of schools that opened the Autumn 2014 termly email from her Department which included a link to the British Armed Forces: Learning Resource 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225105","225105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223255","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 16 to 18 year olds are studying for BTEC qualifications at each level in (a) schools, (b) sixth form colleges and (c) and further education colleges.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225258","225258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223256","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many blocks recorded as part of the Property Data Survey Programme were in (a) good, (b) satisfactory, (c) poor and (d) bad condition.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225254","225254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223257","2015-02-27","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the summary report of the Property Data Survey Programme, published in January 2015, how many schools were rated as being (a) good, (b) satisfactory, (c) poor and (d) bad condition.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225260","225260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223258","2015-02-26","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the summary report of the Property Data Survey Programme, published in January 2015, what estimate she has made of the total cost of repairs necessary to bring the school estate in England up to good condition.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225207","225207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223259","2015-02-26","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the summary report of the Property Data Survey Programme, published in January 2015, whether the cost of maintaining, repairing or replacing a school building referred to in that report includes extra costs incurred because of the presence of asbestos.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225171","225171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223260","2015-02-26","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department has allocated for additional school places in (a) Crawley constituency and (b) West Sussex in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225168","225168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223261","2015-02-26","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary school teachers in each parliamentary constituency in the South East of England have a science degree.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225215","225215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223262","2015-02-26","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many sixth form colleges have expressed an interest in linking with Academy chains since May 2010.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225186","225186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223263","2015-02-26","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions Ministers in her Department have had with sixth form colleges on VAT exemption and linking with Academies since May 2010.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225185","225185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223264","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2014 to Question 214542, if he will place a copy of research referred to in that Answer in the Library.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225212","225212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223265","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2014 to Question 214565, whether his Department has made an estimate of the proportion of households which meet the criteria of the Affordable Warmth Group which is in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225213","225213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223266","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2014 to Question 214565, whether his Department has made an estimate of the proportion of fuel poor households which meets the criteria of the Affordable Warmth Group.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225214","225214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223267","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the oral contribution by the hon. Member for Hastings and Rye of 14 January 2015, Official Report, column 931, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the number of independent suppliers has trebled to 19 since 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225176","225176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223268","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the wholesale cost of (a) electricity and (b) gas in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225172","225172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223269","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the oral contribution by the hon. Member for Hastings and Rye of 14 January 2015, Official Report, column 931, on energy prices, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the market share of independent suppliers is 10.5 per cent.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225177","225177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223270","2015-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme accepts a boiler that has met the emissions limits set for E class fuels according to the EN303-5:2012 standard.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225246","225246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223271","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of domestic customers who are on their supplier's standard tariff.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225194","225194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223272","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding has been allocated to the power to switch campaign.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225195","225195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223273","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for how long the power to switch campaign will run.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225196","225196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223274","2015-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what emission certification dedicated to E class fuels exists under the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225287","225287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223275","2015-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether it is his policy that the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme accepts an emissions certificate where an E class fuel group is stated as one of the fuels officially approved by the manufacturers and tested by an accredited laboratory.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225288","225288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223276","2015-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether pelletized waste coffee beans or grounds are included in the definition of E class fuels for the purpose of the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225289","225289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223277","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2014 to Question 214542, in what circumstances each supplier identified by his Department requests a refundable security deposit.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225209","225209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223278","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2014 to Question 214542, which suppliers his Department has identified as requesting a refundable security deposit.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225210","225210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223279","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2014 to Question 214542, how much each of the suppliers identified by his Department requests as a refundable security deposit.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225211","225211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223280","2015-02-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many and what proportion of households in (a) England and (b) the UK used (i) pre-payment, (ii) direct debit and (iii) standard credit methods for paying for energy in each year since 2010; and what proportion of each such group of customers was categorised as fuel poor.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225102","225102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223281","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution by the hon. Member for Hastings and Rye of 14 January 2015, Official Report, column 932, on energy prices, what the evidential basis is for the statement that customers would be 100 a year worse off if prices had been frozen in October 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225149","225149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223282","2015-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution of 14 January 2015, Official Report, column 904, on energy prices, what the evidential basis is for the statement that switching rates have fallen because of the end of doorstep selling.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225148","225148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223283","2015-03-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will distribute guidance on dog waste management for both onsite and offsite disposal to ensure puppy breeders manage waste in accordance with environmental and health guidelines.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225159","225159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223284","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2014 to Question 209807, what further progress he has made in bringing to justice those responsible for the destruction of Malaysian Airlines flight MH17 on 17 July 2014.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225111","225111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223285","2015-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Cyprus on that country's proposed renewal of its military co-operation agreement with Russia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225174","225174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223286","2015-02-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to publish his Department's next six monthly report on Hong Kong.","Biography information for Sir Richard Ottaway","Sir Richard Ottaway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225227","225227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223287","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 19 January 2015 to Questions 219601 and 219602, when NHS England plans to make an accouncement regarding its plans for patients with cirrhosis from April 2015; and whether funding will be made available to support those patients to access treatment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225235","225235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223288","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 19 January 2015 to Questions 219601 and 219602, what discussions NHS England has had with stakeholders regarding its assessment of need for patients with cirrhosis from April 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225238","225238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223289","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in England have been prescribed more than 12 short-acting reliever inhalers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225239","225239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223290","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects to confirm the funding to be allocated for the continuation of the National Cancer Peer Review programme.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225189","225189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223291","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that standards of patient access, service quality and patient safety are maintained by local authorities in the commissioning of clinical sexual health services.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225188","225188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223292","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the workforce development strategy is for (a) GPs and (b) other healthcare professionals in the field of musculoskeletal disorders.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225217","225217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223293","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of differences in genetic susceptibility to obesity.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225250","225250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223294","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children and (b) adults in the civilian population in England have been fitted with recreational prosthetics in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225192","225192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223295","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will hold discussions with medical bodies on funding for developing a cure for the common cold.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225284","225284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223296","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to assist wounded veterans with their care expenses.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225286","225286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223297","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide funding to ensure that vaccines that are not resistant to flu bug virus are available.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225285","225285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223298","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department will publish the Report by Sir Stuart Rose on NHS Leadership.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225236","225236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223299","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many asthma patients in England have been prescribed short-acting reliever inhalers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225234","225234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223300","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the consultancy reports he has commissioned into the challenged local health economy of (a) Staffordshire, (b) Eastern Cheshire, (c) South West London, (d) North East London, (e) Cumbria, (f) Mid Essex, (g) Cambridge and Peterborough, (h) Leicestershire, (i) Northamptonshire, (j) East Sussex and (k) Devon has been completed; and when copies of each completed report were delivered to (i) the project's Joint Programme Board, (ii) NHS England, (iii) the Trust Development Authority, (iv) Monitor and (v) his Department.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225293","225293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223301","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the expected target dates are for completion of the reports commissioned from consultants into the challenged local health economy of (a) Staffordshire, (b) Eastern Cheshire, (c) South West London, (d) North East London, (e) Cumbria, (f) Mid Essex, (g) Cambridge and Peterborough, (h) Leicestershire, (i) Northamptonshire, (j) East Sussex and (k) Devon; and when he expects copies of reports to be delivered to (i) the project's Joint Programme Board, (ii) NHS England, (iii) the Trust Development Authority, (iv) Monitor and (v) his Department.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225294","225294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223302","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which consultancy firm has been commissioned to review the challenged local health economy of (a) Staffordshire, (b) Eastern Cheshire, (c) South West London, (d) North East London, (e) Cumbria, (f) Mid Essex, (g) Cambridge and Peterborough, (h) Leicestershire, (i) Northamptonshire, (j) East Sussex and (k) Devon; and when each such firm started its work in each area.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225295","225295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223303","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the availability in obtaining dispensing appliance contractor licenses on patients with complex conditions.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225281","225281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223304","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the ease with which small and medium-sized businesses can obtain a dispensing appliance contractor licence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225282","225282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223305","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the burns review in the South East; and which hospitals are affected by that review.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225296","225296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223306","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for asthma medications were issued in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225247","225247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223307","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average length of stay in hosptial was for people admitted with a primary diagnosis of asthma in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225248","225248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223308","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many short-acting reliever inhalers for the treatment of asthma have been prescribed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225263","225263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223309","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2015 to Question 223818, what progress his Department has made in discussions with the Royal British Legion on how a disregard may be applied for the War Pension scheme under social care charging rules in future.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225112","225112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223310","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review regulations applying to the licensing of the drug Avastin for use in eye conditions, in response to recent research on that drug's safety and efficacy compared to licensed alternatives.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225113","225113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223311","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost of hospital stay was for people admitted with a primary diagnosis of asthma in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225150","225150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223312","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of mental health services for children and young people in South Kent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225146","225146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223313","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the use of 3D printing in research, design and production of recreational prosthetics.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225147","225147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223314","2015-03-04","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which mental health and acute NHS trusts in England provide nurseries for staff; how many nursery places each trust provides in each such case; and what the average cost per place, per hour is in each such trust.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225141","225141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223315","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Government is doing to support endoscopy units to ensure that there is sufficient capacity in resources and staff for the roll-out of the bowel scope screening programme.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225126","225126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223316","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have (a) been invited to take part in and (b) taken part in (i) the bowel scope screening programme and (ii) the faecal occult blood test programme to date.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225127","225127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223317","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the review of the first year's operation of the framework for sexual health improvement in England.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225142","225142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223318","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when vaccinations for human papillomavirus for men who have sex with men will be implemented.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225143","225143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223319","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans are in place for an audit of the commissioning process for sexual health services.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225144","225144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223320","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on the NHS Choices Winter Health Advice campaign; and for what purpose that expenditure has been incurred.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225119","225119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223321","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what type of proton therapy machine NHS England plans to install in (a) Manchester and (b) London.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225099","225099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223322","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the results of the 2014 National Cancer Peer Review programme cycle will be published.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225122","225122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223323","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the support available to people with epilepsy.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225124","225124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223324","2015-02-27","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve (a) access to specialists and (b) investment in medical research for epilepsy.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225125","225125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223325","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2015 to Question 222678, how many claims for clinical negligence involving treatment for trigeminal neuralgia were submitted to the NHS Litigation Authority in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225134","225134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223326","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2015 to Question 222680, which NHS trusts reported the patient incidents referred to in that Answer in 2013 and 2014.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225135","225135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223327","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria NHS England has to decide which non-commissioned hospitals providing stereotactic radiosurgery are permitted to treat NHS patients.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225136","225136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223328","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by what funding mechanism NHS England pays for the treatment of NHS patients receiving stereotactic radiosurgery at non-commissioned hospitals.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225137","225137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223329","2015-03-02","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS England non-commissioned hospitals providing gamma knife stereotactic radiosurgery are funded to treat NHS patients.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225138","225138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223330","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the (a) 15 million convergence funding allocated for specialised augmentative and alternative communication services and (b) 7.5 million convergence funding allocated for specialised environmental control services is forecast to have been spent by the relevant specialised services by the end of the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225096","225096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223331","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS clinical reference groups are chaired by employees of NHS England or people receiving financial reimbursement from NHS England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225086","225086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223332","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when it is planned for the revised NHS England service specification D01/S/b Complex Disability Equipment Communication Aids (Specialised AAC services), published as Interim for adoption from 01/10/14, to be approved by the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225097","225097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223333","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on which specialised augmentative and alternative communication providers have hired speech and language therapists since signing contracts with NHS England area teams; and how many such therapists have been hired by each such provider.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225094","225094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223334","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were sent abroad for proton therapy in each of the last five years; how many such patients were children in each of those years; and what the annual cost was to the NHS in each of those years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225084","225084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223335","2015-02-26","Department of Health","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which specialised augmentative and alternative communication providers have signed contracts, or variations of contract, with the appropriate NHS England Area Team; and on what date was each such contract or variation signed.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225095","225095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223336","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations the Government has received on the practices of UK Services and Support Ltd in relation to charges for passport applications; and what steps have been taken in response to those representations.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225157","225157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223337","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many further submissions under rule 353 of the Immigration Rules were made in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225163","225163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223338","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to which Home Office Reporting Centre further submissions under rule 353 of the Immigration Rules were initially made in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225164","225164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223339","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police stations have (a) been in operation and (b) closed in each police force area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225088","225088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223340","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the (a) total cost of training police officers in the use of water cannons and (b) cost of such training to each police force.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225114","225114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223341","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that biometric data is deleted with minimal delay when arrests are made unlawfully or incorrectly.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225115","225115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223342","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the arrangements to send out the status letter, biometric residence permit, National Insurance number and the NASS35 form simultaneously to people newly-granted refugee status.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225206","225206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223343","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people departing the UK did so with a matching API data record in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225203","225203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223344","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what proportion of people departing the UK was matching API data recorded in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225197","225197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223345","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average police helicopter response times have been for each police force in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225259","225259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223346","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the National Extremism Tactical Co-ordination Unit had a meeting with the Consulting Association in 2008; and if she will publish any minutes or documents relating to that meeting.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225291","225291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223347","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any police force currently has operational staff working within trade unions.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225292","225292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223348","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish all of the information her Department holds on Special Demonstration Squad activity within trade unions between 1996 and 1998.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225290","225290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223349","2015-03-02","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on renewing the visa concession for Syrian internationals studying at UK higher education institutions.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225301","225301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223350","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consultation her Department carried out with Liverpool City Council in advance of the recent decision by her Department to make Liverpool the place failed asylum seekers must go to lodge their final appeals.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225237","225237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223351","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on in what locations British citizens are fighting conflicts abroad; and what estimate she has made of the number of citizens in each such destination.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225178","225178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223352","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how reductions in the budget of the National Police Air Service will be distributed between police forces in North Wales and the North West of England.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225170","225170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223353","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time is for people granted refugee status from discontinuation of S95 support to the start of mainstream benefits.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225216","225216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223354","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of further submissions made under rule 353 of the Immigration Rules were (a) accepted as fresh claims and (b) rejected with no right of appeal in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225190","225190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223355","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) grants and (b) refusals of international protection her Department made in cases where further submissions under rule 353 of the Immigration Rules were accepted as fresh claims for each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225191","225191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223356","2015-02-26","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015 to Question 222300, when she plans to announce the content of the inserts to be made by Member States in the Directive identifying the national authority to which appeals and reviews must be lodged and the time limits for doing so; which that national authority is; and what the time limits are.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225187","225187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223357","2015-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of offences under section 3(1) of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 in England in each year from 1997 to 2014.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225303","225303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223358","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the preventative and early intervention measures trialled in the foreign national offenders action plan.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225270","225270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223359","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what comparative assessment her Department has made of the costs of managing foreign national offenders in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225269","225269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223360","2015-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what comparative information his Department holds on pay rates of the Information Commissioner's Office and other independent regulators and ombudsmen with similar functions for staff at the same grade.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225273","225273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223361","2015-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average percentage pay rise was of Executive Team staff at the Information Commissioner's Office since June 2014; and what average pay increase has been proposed for non-executive staff excluding buy-out of contractual progression.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225274","225274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223362","2015-02-27","Home Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to develop and standardise its approach to Foreign National Offenders casework since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225256","225256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223363","2015-03-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to his Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 217622, what the resource requirements are for each planned stage of the court reform programme; what the planned (a) start and (b) finish time is for each stage of the programme; and what the planned staff allocation is for each planned stage of the programme.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225118","225118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223364","2015-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many section 1 dogs have been exempted under section 4A or 4B of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 in England in each year from 1997 to 2014.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225161","225161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223365","2015-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people have been (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under section 2 of the Dogs Act 1871 in England in each year from 1997 to 2014.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225160","225160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223366","2015-03-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many domestic violence trials in each magistrates' and Crown court in Lancashire in 2014 (a) collapsed and (b) were postponed due to the complainant not being present.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225139","225139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223367","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which 10 local authorities had the greatest proportional drop in electoral registration between 2013 and 2014.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225165","225165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223368","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how much the Electoral Commission plans to spend on television advertising to encourage registration; and how it monitors the effectiveness of such campaigns.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225166","225166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223369","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what representations the Electoral Commission has received about monitoring and improving household canvasses from (a) hon. Members and (b) other bodies and individuals.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225167","225167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223370","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what estimate the Electoral Commission has made of the cost per registration of 16 and 17 year olds who are encouraged to register primarily through (a) television adverts and (b) Bite the Ballot school visits.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225199","225199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223371","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what research, actions and advice the Electoral Commission undertook to ensure that (a) students and (b) people living in Houses of Multiple Occupation and other mobile groups did not fall off the electoral register in the run up to Individual Electoral Registration; and what assessment the Commission has made of the success of such actions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225198","225198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223372","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what advice the Electoral Commission gave to Electoral Registration Officers on (a) maximising the registration of home movers and (b) sending voter registration forms to all households.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225204","225204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223373","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the Electoral Commission has sufficient data to recommend whether the end of the transition to individual electoral registration should be brought forward to December 2015.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225181","225181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223374","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what interim assessments the Electoral Commission has made of the accuracy of the data on registration rates collected in the run-up to the introduction of individual electoral registration; and what procedures were in place to enable concerns about that data to be raised.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225180","225180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223375","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the reasons for the recent increase in voter registration in East Devon.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225179","225179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223376","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, whether the local authorities which did not take sufficient action to conduct a household canvass in 2014 did not take sufficient action to conduct a household canvass in a previous year.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225175","225175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223377","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, when the Electoral Commission first knew of the problems with the registration software used by Electoral Registration Officers; and what steps the Commission has taken to overcome those problems.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225183","225183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223378","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the effects of its handling of the introduction of Individual Electoral Registration on (a) public perception of the integrity of the Commission and (b) public confidence in the Commission.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225182","225182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223379","2015-02-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-24","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what progress the Electoral Commission has made in differentiating in online registration between people who are already registered and people newly on register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225184","225184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223380","2015-02-26","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria are used to decide which local authorities receive monies from the challenge fund allocation; what weighting is given to highways management efficiency; and how information used in the process of decision is verified.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225218","225218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223381","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of Network Rail's Control Period 5 projects have had a cost determination under the Office of Rail Regulation's Enhancement Cost Adjustment Mechanism (ECAM); how many such projects remain to be assessed; how many of Network Rail's ECAM submissions have missed their deadline; and how many ECAM submissions have been referred back to Network Rail by the Office of Rail Regulation for further development.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225297","225297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223382","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the response times for tug boats assisting shipping incidents on the west of Scotland have been in the last year.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225221","225221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223383","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what records are available to Network Rail regarding the location of buried trackside signalling cables on the Great Western Main Line.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225299","225299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223384","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent to date on (a) Reading Station Area Resignalling and Remodelling, (b) East West Phase 1, (c) the Northern Hub, (d) Transpennine electrification, (e) Great Western Main Line electrification and (f) Midland Main Line electrification.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225298","225298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223385","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the performance of Network Rail's principal contractor on the North West electrification project; and what estimate he has made of the number of working hours spent redoing completed work on the lines included in that project.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225300","225300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223386","2015-02-26","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many railway stations in (a) Nottinghamshire, (b) England and (c) the UK are not compliant with disability access guidelines and requirements.","Biography information for Mark  Spencer","Mr Mark Spencer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225208","225208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223387","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the review his Department has commissioned KPMG to conduct on bus market dynamics will assess the Tyne and Wear bus market.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225116","225116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223388","2015-03-03","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether KPMG has been given unrestricted access to commercially sensitive data held by his Department for its inquiry into bus market dynamics.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225117","225117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223389","2015-02-26","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the contribution of Baroness Williams of Trafford of 11 February 2015, Official Report, House of Lords, column 1333, that targeted local bans on pavement parking outside London would be more effective than a blanket ban and with reference to the Answer of 12 November 2013, Official Report, column 576W, on parking: pedestrian areas, that his Department does not collect information on local parking enforcement and pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221436, that his Department does not hold information on local authority traffic regulation orders, what the evidential basis is for the statement by Baroness Williams.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225151","225151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223390","2015-02-27","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many planned possessions have been cancelled by Network Rail since 1 January 2015; and on how many such occasions were train and freight operators consulted in advance.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225087","225087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223391","2015-02-26","Department for Transport","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from local authorities in support of using traffic regulation orders to enforce a prohibition on the footway.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225121","225121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223392","2015-02-27","Women and Equalities","2015-02-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when her Office plans to publish the results of its survey to mark the twentieth anniversary of the Beijing Declaration and Platform for Action.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225123","225123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223393","2015-02-27","Women and Equalities","2015-02-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent progress she has made on implementing the recommendations of the Committee on the Elimination of Discrimination against Women on the UK's record on women's rights and services.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225100","225100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223395","2015-02-27","Women and Equalities","2015-02-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the Governments objectives are for the fifty ninth session of the Commission on the Status of Women; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225271","225271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223397","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2015 to Question 224391, what targets his Department has for the timeliness of processing benefits.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225267","225267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223398","2015-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has set any targets for Maximum to deal with the backlog of legacy work capability assessments queries which will be transferred from Atos on 2 March 2015.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225205","225205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223399","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individuals in Peterborough constituency have participated in the work choice scheme in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225262","225262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223400","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the extent of partnership working between work programme providers and local NHS and public health bodies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225220","225220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223401","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to implement the commitments in Fuller Working Lives - a framework for action, published by his Department in June 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225231","225231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223402","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount of funding provided by his Department to a local authority is for personal budgeting support when universal credit is implemented in a local authority area.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225230","225230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223403","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individuals have (a) applied for and (b) been granted assistance through the access to work programme in Peterborough constituency in each year since 2007; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225252","225252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223404","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of disability living allowance have been required to make repayments to his Department after continuing to claim the benefit whilst hospitalised for medical treatment in 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225110","225110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223405","2015-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many prosecutions have been brought for benefit fraud in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225103","225103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223406","2015-03-04","HM Treasury","2015-02-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff employed at the Tax Credit Office in Preston are currently paid (a) more and (b) less than the living wage.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225140","225140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223594","2015-03-02","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to use state schools to encourage social mobility.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907805","907805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224283","2015-03-02","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the relative effectiveness of the different routes into teacher training.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907801","907801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/224284","2015-03-02","Department for Education","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations she has received on reforms to A and AS-levels.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907804","907804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/225031","2015-03-04","Wales Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the First Minister on promoting exports by Welsh businesses.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907777","907777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/225032","2015-03-04","Wales Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the effects on Wales of the Government's long-term economic plan.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907781","907781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/225033","2015-03-04","Wales Office","2015-02-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of trends in the rate of child poverty in Wales since 2010.","Biography information for Martin Caton","Martin Caton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907779","907779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222849","2015-02-25","Attorney General","2015-02-23","To ask the Attorney General, how many apprentices employed by (a) the Law Officers' Departments and (b) its executive agencies and associated bodies are aged (i) 16 to 18, (ii) 19 to 24 and (iii) 25 years or older; and how many of those apprentices employed in each form of body and of each age group were previously employed by the Government.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225060","225060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222851","2015-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to Question 222042.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 225006","225006"
