"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532990","2016-07-07","Northern Ireland Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of which policy areas within her Department's remit will be affected by the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41975","41975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532991","2016-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Article 2 of the North Atlantic Treaty will be on the agenda of the forthcoming NATO summit.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41870","41870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532992","2016-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to fulfil Article 2 of the North Atlantic Treaty.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41900","41900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532993","2016-07-07","Scotland Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether an Act of Parliament would be required to allow a further binding referendum on Scottish independence.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41892","41892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532994","2016-07-07","Scotland Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of which policy areas within his Department's remit will be affected by the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41976","41976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532995","2016-07-11","Cabinet Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the potential merits of using the electoral registration data relating to the recent EU referendum as baseline data for the boundary review of parliamentary constituencies.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41951","41951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532996","2016-07-11","Department for Transport","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what savings his Department's focussed shared service centre has made in each year since its creation.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41866","41866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532997","2016-07-07","Department for Transport","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of which policy areas within his Department's remit will be affected by the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41977","41977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532998","2016-07-07","Wales Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of which policy areas within his Department's remit will be affected by the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41978","41978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532999","2016-07-11","Wales Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of legislation currently in force applies to Wales only.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41954","41954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533000","2016-07-07","Wales Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what plans he has to ensure that the Government commits to providing  the same level of funding to Wales after the UK leaves the EU that is received from the EU.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41923","41923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533001","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential policy implications for his Department of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41913","41913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533002","2016-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people diagnosed with myalgic encephalomyelitis have taken early retirement after receiving that diagnosis.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41950","41950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533003","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 31 May 2016 to Question 37766, if he will assess the potential merits of collating information about vaccinations given to people claiming or receiving payment under the vaccine damage payments scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41943","41943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533004","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families accessed support from the Child Support Agency in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) the North West and (c) the UK in (i) 2011 and (ii) 2012.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41944","41944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533005","2016-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to increase the take-up of advice by people accessing pension freedoms.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41936","41936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533006","2016-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 13 of the Health and Safety Executive (HSE) Business Plan 2016-17, what steps the HSE plans to take to meet the proposed nine per cent reduction to its funding by 2019-20.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41890","41890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533007","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse is of a claim for (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment and support allowance which is (i) refused at initial assessment, (ii) refused at mandatory reconsideration and (iii) successful at tribunal.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41873","41873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533008","2016-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of auto-enrolment to pension schemes for people who are casual or seasonal workers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41855","41855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533009","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of which policy areas within his Department's remit will be affected by the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41979","41979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533886","2016-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential policy implications for his Department of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for John Nicolson","John  Nicolson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905756","905756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/534971","2016-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support people with disabilities and health conditions who are looking for work.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905772","905772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/535664","2016-07-13","Wales Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of inward investment in Wales.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905793","905793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/535665","2016-07-13","Wales Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent progress the Government has made on a North Wales growth deal.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905792","905792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/535666","2016-07-13","Wales Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will take steps to strengthen Wales' international business links.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905797","905797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/535667","2016-07-13","Wales Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on the economy in Wales of upgrading the M4 relief road.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905796","905796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/535668","2016-07-13","Wales Office","2016-07-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on the economy in Wales of upgrading the M4 relief road.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905791","905791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532385","2016-07-06","Attorney General","2016-07-04","To ask the Attorney General, how much has been paid to officials of the Law Officers' Departments as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments in (a) each of the last five years and (b) 2016 to date; how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence; how many staff received such incentivised additional payments; from which budgets such payments were made; and at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41800","41800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532386","2016-07-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41799","41799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532387","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with representatives of the UK steel industry on the implications of the outcome of the EU referendum for that industry; and what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on support for the steel industry of the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41714","41714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532388","2016-07-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure Northern Ireland benefits from the Catapult programme.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41766","41766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532389","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many women started businesses in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) the Liverpool City Region and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41774","41774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532390","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department provides to female entrepreneurs in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) the Liverpool City Region and (c) England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41776","41776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532391","2016-07-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership and other international trade negotiations.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41652","41652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532392","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to negotiate access to the Digital Single Market for British online retailers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41680","41680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532393","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost to the economy of the (a) UK and (b) North East of the UK leaving the EU and businesses being unable to access the Digital Single Market.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41682","41682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532394","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that digital consumer rights are not lost in the process of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41681","41681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532395","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings he has had with manufacturers in the North East on the (a) immediate effect of the result of the EU referendum and (b) short to long-term effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41685","41685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532396","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to protect employment levels in the North East from the potential (a) immediate effect of the UK voting to leave the UK and (b) the short to long-term effect of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41686","41686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532397","2016-07-06","HM Treasury","2016-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which companies the Government retains golden shares in for the purpose of limiting overseas ownership; and what the terms are of such shares.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41666","41666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532398","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects to answer Question 39267, tabled by the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion on 3 June 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41740","41740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532399","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether officials from the Welsh Government have been identified to take part in the establishment of expanded trade negotiation functions in his Department as a result of the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41710","41710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532400","2016-07-07","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what support the Government plans to provide to veterans of the Iraq Conflict who are concerned by the findings of the Chilcot Report and its implications for their service records.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41744","41744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532401","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government has taken to improve the performance of the Civil Service Pension Scheme since the publication of the National Audit Office report, Investigation into Members' experience of civil service pension administration, published in February 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41705","41705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532402","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many retired civil servants have (a) not received an annual benefit statement and (b) received such a statement late from MyCSP in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41660","41660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532403","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many retired civil servants have not received pension payments from MyCSP for which they are eligible in (a) each of the last 12 months and (b) each month since MyCSP has been processing such payments.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41661","41661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532404","2016-07-07","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to provide similar support for injured veterans of the Iraq conflict following the publication of the Chilcot Report to that provided to the next of kin of people who lost their lives in that conflict.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41752","41752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532405","2016-07-07","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2016 to Question 38697, what steps his Department has taken to provide injured veterans of the Iraq conflict with free copies of the Chilcot Report.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41753","41753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532406","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many retired civil servants have received late pension payments from MyCSP in (a) each of the last 12 months and (b) each month since that company has been processing such pension payments.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41662","41662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532407","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many cases marked as urgent are currently waiting resolution by MyCSP.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41658","41658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532408","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants have pension records that are incomplete or incorrect.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41659","41659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532409","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many telephone calls MyCSP has received in each month since September 2014; and how many of those calls were abandoned before being answered in each of those months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41656","41656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532410","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2016 to Question 40722, if his Department will review its official guidance on the keeping of travel records of Ministers and departmental officials; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41734","41734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532411","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many retired civil servants have been adversely affected by the performance of MyCSP since that company has been responsible for the processing of pension payments to those people; and if he will take steps to guarantee that no retired civil servant will suffer financial loss as a result of the performance of that company.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41657","41657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532412","2016-07-07","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the petition on the change.org website, entitled Restore truthful politics - create an independent office to monitor political campaigns, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of creating such an office; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41771","41771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532413","2016-07-07","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to ensure that questions that would enable local authorities to ascertain the number of (a) veterans and (b) service personnel living in their areas are included in the 2021 census.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41702","41702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532414","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41801","41801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532415","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many divorces involving people aged over 50 years of age took place in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41823","41823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532416","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information the Government holds on the incidence of relationship break-up among people aged over 50 years of age in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41824","41824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532417","2016-07-06","HM Treasury","2016-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41815","41815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532418","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to provide funding for youth employment in the North West in the event of funding currently received from the EU Youth Employment Initiative being withdrawn.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41698","41698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532419","2016-07-07","HM Treasury","2016-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government intends to replace or substitute any loss of funding to the Welsh Government for the South Wales Metro as a result of the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41712","41712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532420","2016-07-06","HM Treasury","2016-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the automatic application to Northern Ireland of any change in corporation tax in Great Britain.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41791","41791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532421","2016-07-06","HM Treasury","2016-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reverse plans to close HM Revenue and Customs offices in Northern Ireland following the UK vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41792","41792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532422","2016-07-07","HM Treasury","2016-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the (a) regulation of the insurance industry and (b) implementation of the Solvency II Directive.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41683","41683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532423","2016-07-07","HM Treasury","2016-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the transposition of the Basel III reform measures into UK law.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41690","41690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532424","2016-07-07","HM Treasury","2016-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential economic effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41696","41696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532425","2016-07-06","Church Commissioners","2016-07-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether the Church of England has plans for educational projects to commemorate the First World War in addition to existing centenary events.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41707","41707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532426","2016-07-06","Church Commissioners","2016-07-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps are being taken by the Church of England to tackle human trafficking.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41718","41718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532427","2016-07-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to announce the result of the Government's consultation on supported housing; and whether he expects supported housing to be included in the Local Housing Allowance cap.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41717","41717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532428","2016-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2016 to Question 40188, on Kingston upon Hull City Council, what the source is for the comment that the response from the Leader of Hull City Council was in response to a point made by the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41703","41703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532429","2016-07-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will respond to the National Housing Federation's recommendation of 29 June 2016 that supported housing providers should register with an independent regulator in order to receive access to extra housing benefit.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41759","41759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532430","2016-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the population of (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency and (b) the Liverpool City Region was homeless in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41775","41775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532431","2016-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take into account the views of local communities and Lancashire County Council when deciding whether to reverse the council's decision not to allow fracking.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41784","41784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532432","2016-07-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41802","41802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532433","2016-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the potential savings to the public purse from applying the Local Housing Allowance cap to supported housing; and whether he has carried out an impact assessment for that policy.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41715","41715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532434","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data is held by local authorities on suspected abuse of the elderly by social carers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41646","41646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532435","2016-07-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41803","41803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532436","2016-07-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has made representations to the Information Commissioner's Office management and directors on ensuring that terms of pay and conditions for staff of that office are being upheld and that wage increases are proportionate for all staff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41767","41767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532437","2016-07-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the Royal British Legion on their Count Them In campaign.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41765","41765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532438","2016-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the implications of the outcome of the EU referendum for the EU Maritime Headquarters at Northwood.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41713","41713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532439","2016-07-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41804","41804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532440","2016-07-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if the Government will establish an independent inquiry into deaths at Deepcut Barracks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41833","41833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532441","2016-07-06","Ministry of Defence","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many crimes have been committed by members of the cadet forces in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41834","41834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532442","2016-07-07","Department for Education","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will provide emergency funding to academies in Gloucestershire while the review of education funding is pending to cover additional costs associated with changes in the level of (a) teachers' pay, (b) national insurance contributions and (c) pension costs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41743","41743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532443","2016-07-07","Department for Education","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) childcare places are available for three and four year olds and (b) eligible children there are in (i) England and (ii) Copeland constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41694","41694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532444","2016-07-07","Department for Education","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department expects to confirm to childcare providers the rates to be paid to them when delivering 30 hours free childcare per week for three and four year olds.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41695","41695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532445","2016-07-07","Department for Education","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the process is for (a) ensuring that religious education is taught to all pupils in all schools and (b) reporting schools that are not teaching religious education.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41691","41691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532446","2016-07-07","Department for Education","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to ring-fence the funding rate paid to providers of free childcare for eligible three and four year olds.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41677","41677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532447","2016-07-06","Department for Education","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, (a) how much has been paid to officials of her Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41805","41805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532448","2016-07-07","Department for Education","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the ability of childcare providers in (a) England and (b) Copeland constituency to provide the additional hours necessary to extend free childcare for three and four year olds.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41693","41693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532449","2016-07-07","Department for Education","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants have been trained by local authorities in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41746","41746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532450","2016-07-07","Department for Education","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants were employed in schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41747","41747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532451","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to reduce air pollution in (a) Liverpool and (b) Merseyside since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41772","41772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532452","2016-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that houses with multiple occupation that are let on a room-by-room basis are not exempt from minimum energy efficiency standards.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41798","41798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532453","2016-07-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2016 to Question 41211, what steps she plans to take to ensure that heat networks provide value for money for customers.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41789","41789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532454","2016-07-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) help to buy, (b) shared ownership and (c) social housing new build properties participate in a district heating system.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41790","41790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532455","2016-07-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, (a) how much has been paid to officials of her Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41806","41806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532456","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many areas will be involved in the badger cull in 2016; and what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of that cull.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41638","41638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532457","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average cost is of (a) the current bovine TB skin test and (b) the gamma interferon test; and what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of each of those tests.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41639","41639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532458","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) tuberculin skin tests and (b) gamma interferon tests have been conducted in each year since 2010; and how many cases of bovine TB have been detected by each method.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41640","41640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532459","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to adopt the gamma interferon test as the primary standardised test to detect TB in cattle.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41674","41674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532460","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on fishery funding.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41668","41668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532461","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on fishing quotas.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41669","41669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532462","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on movement of animals across international borders.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41670","41670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532463","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on biodiversity.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41671","41671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532464","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on subsidies to farmers.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41672","41672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532465","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the main reasons for delays in basic farm payments were in the most recent year for which information is available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41745","41745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532466","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, (a) how much has been paid to officials of her Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41807","41807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532467","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons Northern Irish beekeepers are prevented from registering on BeeBase.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41796","41796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532468","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support beekeepers whose colonies are at risk from fatal diseases.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41793","41793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532469","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many big cat sightings have been reported in each year from (a) 2000 to 2010, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41777","41777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532470","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to produce data on the reduction in single-use plastic carrier bag usage in England for the period ending 6 April 2016.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41748","41748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532471","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's policy is on banning wild animals from being used in circuses.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41749","41749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532472","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the extension of the prison sentence from four years to nine years of Sheikh Ali Salman in Bahrain; and what representations he has made to the government of Bahrain on that extension.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41724","41724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532473","2016-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on efforts to free the Seamen Guard Ohio crew.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41797","41797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532474","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to recognise the mass killings of Armenian Christians by the Ottoman Empire as genocide.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41788","41788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532475","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41808","41808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532476","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage the government of Burma to establish an independent investigation into the destruction of buildings in a mosque compound in the Bago Region in central Burma.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41817","41817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532477","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on steps taken by the government of Saudi Arabia to investigate the possible use of UK-supplied BL-755 cluster munitions in northern Yemen.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41818","41818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532478","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the government of Iran on the cases of (a) Kamal Foroughi and (b) Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41820","41820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532479","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will urge the government of Iran to apply without discrimination Article 58 of the Islamic Penal Code to permit Kamal Foroughi's early release.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41821","41821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532480","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to prevent or reduce the incidence of female genital mutilation in Nigeria.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41822","41822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532481","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of support provided by the Turkish government to refugees and asylum seekers in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41819","41819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532482","2016-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether UK Ministers plan to participate in discussions initiated by the French government on the Middle East peace process.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41741","41741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532483","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33305, whether his Department had sight of the evidence submitted to the Ombudsman in Bahrain regarding Mr Mohamed Ramadan's case when preparing that Answer.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41676","41676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532484","2016-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the (a) UK's and (b) EU's sanctions policy for Russia.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41678","41678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532485","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement will be considered an exclusive competence of the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41750","41750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532486","2016-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the French government on Israel and Palestine since the conference organised by the French government.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41637","41637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532487","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the market cost was of drugs provided through prescriptions in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41651","41651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532488","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to tackle suspected abuse of the elderly by social carers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41647","41647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532489","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS clinical staff that work part-time are additionally registered as agency staff.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41739","41739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532490","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of making yoga available through the NHS for treatment and recovery; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41737","41737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532491","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS clinical staff work part-time.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41738","41738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532492","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to review the decision to remove peptide receptor radionuclide therapy treatments from the Cancer Drugs Fund list.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41736","41736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532493","2016-07-07","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the guidelines are for remuneration of chairs of clinical commissioning group governing bodies.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41751","41751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532494","2016-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that the hon. Member for Walsall North receives a reply to his letter of 3 May 2016 to the Chief Executive of the Medical Research Council on behalf of a constituent.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41725","41725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532495","2016-07-07","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evidence his Department is taking into account to decide whether (a) consultant-led and (b) midwife-led maternity services should be withdrawn at West Cumberland Hospital.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41689","41689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532496","2016-07-07","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been treated by the NHS for gambling addictions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41726","41726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532497","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for personalised medicines for inoperable cancers to be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41831","41831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532498","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce avoidable deaths in people below 70 years of age.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41832","41832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532499","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on trends in the prominence of relationship break-up as a contributory cause of suicide over the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41825","41825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532500","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government plans for TEV-48125 to be made available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41826","41826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532501","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether new treatments for high-risk neuroblastoma are planned for availability on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41830","41830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532502","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of potential savings to the public purse that would accrue from a reduction in the incidence of chronic pain.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41828","41828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532503","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has allocated to (a) assess the extent of and (b) treat chronic pain.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41829","41829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532504","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps NHS England has taken to assist in reducing the incidence of chronic pain.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41827","41827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532505","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41809","41809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532506","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to support the development of clinician-led neuromuscular networks across England.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41778","41778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532507","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has held with NHS ambulance trusts on undertaking collaborative work with Muscular Dystrophy UK to increase health professionals' knowledge of care for people with muscular dystrophy and neuromuscular conditions.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41779","41779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532508","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that UK access to emerging treatments for (a) muscular dystrophy and (b) other neuromuscular conditions is maintained in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41780","41780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532509","2016-07-07","Cabinet Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency and (b) the Liverpool City Region have been (i) diagnosed with and (ii) died from lung cancer in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41773","41773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532510","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress has been made on the Competition Market Authority's investigation into claims that generic drug procurement costs are being artificially increased by suppliers.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41768","41768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532511","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the effect on NHS resources was in each of the last three years of charging people with long-term health conditions for prescription drugs.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41761","41761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532512","2016-07-07","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average total remuneration was of chairs of clinical commissioning group governing bodies in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41732","41732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532513","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if NHS England-appointed Maternity Choice and Personalisation pioneers will take steps to improve outcomes in high-risk multiple pregnancies.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41720","41720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532514","2016-07-07","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will adopt the recommendations of the All Party Parliamentary Group on Primary Care and Public Health in its Inquiry Report into NHS England's Five Year Forward View: behaviour change, information and signposting, published in March 2016, that reports of self-care pilots and evidence-based initiatives in the NHS should be sent to the Self Care Forum for upload to its best practice portal.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41701","41701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532515","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England plans to review individual maternity-related strategic transformation plans to see how each local area plans to improve outcomes in high-risk multiple pregnancies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41722","41722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532516","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England plans to include the measurement of outcomes in multiple pregnancies in annual reporting for clinical commissioning groups which commission maternity services.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41721","41721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532517","2016-07-07","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the immigration health surcharge for visa applications on the number of visas applied for; how much funding has been raised by that surcharge since its introduction; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41770","41770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532518","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of refugees that her Department plans to relocate to Coventry under the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation Scheme in each of the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41723","41723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532519","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will set up a website to provide up-to-date advice for EU citizens who are resident in the UK on their status following the vote for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41716","41716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532520","2016-07-07","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of the number of illegal immigrants in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41697","41697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532521","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to fulfil its commitment to accept unaccompanied refugee children following the UK vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41781","41781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532522","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are subject to immigration reporting restrictions; what the nature of those restrictions are; and what the rate of compliance with those restrictions is.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41782","41782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532523","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) how much has been paid to officials of her Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41810","41810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532524","2016-07-07","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on funding of the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41728","41728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532525","2016-07-07","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who will be relocated through the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme in the next 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41729","41729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532526","2016-07-07","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the effect of the abolition of the Agricultural Wages Board in 2013 on the proportion of migrants working in the agricultural sector; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41688","41688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532527","2016-07-07","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the systems for measuring levels of illegal immigration in other countries; and whether such systems could be applied to the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41687","41687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532528","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to increase the number of Border Force officials at Edinburgh Airport.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41663","41663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532529","2016-07-11","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to uphold the Vienna Convention on the Law of Treaties 1969 allowing existing EU citizens already living and working in the UK to retain their existing rights throughout and following negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41704","41704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532530","2016-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to extend the provisions preventing squatting in residential buildings to non-residential premises.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41664","41664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532531","2016-07-07","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of reports from members of the public on possible illegal immigration have (a) been investigated and (b) resulted in enforcement action in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41679","41679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532532","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the operation of the Border Force.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41655","41655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532533","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national offenders have been living in the community for (a) less than six months, (b) between six months and one year, (c) between one and two years, (d) between two and three years, (e) between three and four years, (f) between four and five years and (g) over five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41649","41649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532534","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many spousal visas have been granted in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41650","41650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532535","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the numbers of people arriving at UK border control points classed as international passengers.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41653","41653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532536","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many spousal visas were revoked in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41641","41641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532537","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many revoked spousal visas have led to the deportation of the spouse concerned in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41642","41642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532538","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of immigration marriage fraud have led to (a) an investigation and (b) a subsequent deportation in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41643","41643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532539","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions have been made for bigamy or polygamy without consent in each of the last eight years; and how many such prosecutions led to a subsequent revoking of immigration status and deportation.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41644","41644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532540","2016-07-06","Home Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many vessels believed to have been attempting to enter the UK have Border Force officials intercepted in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41645","41645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532541","2016-07-06","Department for International Development","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will increase the proportion of the UK aid budget spent on water and sanitation.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41648","41648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532542","2016-07-07","Department for International Development","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the total budget for the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme will be funded by her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41730","41730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532543","2016-07-07","Department for International Development","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to identify potential recipients of overseas development assistance currently given to (a) the European Development Fund, (b) the European Commission Humanitarian Aid and Civil Protection department and (c) the European Investment Bank as a result of the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41711","41711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532544","2016-07-06","Department for International Development","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve access to water and sanitation.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41708","41708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532545","2016-07-06","Department for International Development","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, (a) how much has been paid to officials of her Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41811","41811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532546","2016-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41812","41812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532547","2016-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of prison inspections in providing an accurate reflection of the work of prison service staff.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41794","41794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532548","2016-07-07","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the level of alcohol dependency in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41699","41699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532549","2016-07-07","Department of Health","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to develop (a) interventions for people with alcohol problems before they commit criminal offences and (b) support for people with alcohol problems within the criminal justice system; and if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings of research by Professor Newbury-Birch of Teesside University, published in June 2016, on alcohol and the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41700","41700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532550","2016-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many decisions taken  on claims for (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payments have been appealed in (i) St Helens North constituency and (ii) Merseyside in each of the last five years; and how many of those appeals have been successful.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41733","41733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532551","2016-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons the abolition of section 225 of the Criminal Justice Act 2003 was not applied retrospectively for prisoners serving sentences for imprisonment for public protection.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41769","41769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532552","2016-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans further court closures in Greater London in the next 10 years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41673","41673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532553","2016-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on international co-operation on policing and justice matters.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41654","41654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532554","2016-07-06","Northern Ireland Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much of the 500 million designated to shared education and housing from the Fresh Start deal has been spent to date.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41795","41795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532555","2016-07-06","Northern Ireland Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent steps she has taken to address the outstanding legacy issues from the Troubles in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41754","41754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532556","2016-07-06","Northern Ireland Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive and government of the Republic of Ireland on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41758","41758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532557","2016-07-06","Northern Ireland Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, (a) how much has been paid to officials of her Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41813","41813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532558","2016-07-06","Prime Minister","2016-07-04","To ask the Prime Minister, what process will be used to trigger Article 50 of the Treaty on the European Union.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41667","41667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532559","2016-07-06","Scotland Office","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the cost was of his Department's communications team in each year since 2007; and what the projected costs are for 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41719","41719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532560","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to endorse automated cone laying and retrieval for road maintenance worker safety.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41764","41764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532561","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2016 to Question 40586, which key stakeholders his Department has met to discuss the potential contents of the secondary legislation and guidance needed to complement the Bus Services Bill.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41755","41755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532562","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of buses on the road in England that he expects to be in compliance with the Public Service Vehicle Accessibility Regulations by 2017.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41757","41757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532563","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 8 of the Bus Services Bill Impact Assessments, how much public money has been spent on incentivising bus operators to share real-time punctuality data with local authorities through an uplift to the Bus Service Operators Grant.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41756","41756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532564","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that there are sufficient motorcycle instructors to meet demand.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41762","41762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532565","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of the recommendations and conclusions of the report of the Institute for Mechanical Engineers, UK freight: in for the long haul, published in June 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41763","41763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532566","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse has been of making the bus registration process digital.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41760","41760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532567","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41814","41814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532568","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2016 to Question 41437, what his policy is on establishing a statutory independent body representing bus users to complement the work of non-statutory non-profit organisations, such as Bus Users UK.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41735","41735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532569","2016-07-07","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will support the introduction of high-bioethanol blends into petrol to maintain future jobs in the bioethanol industry.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41692","41692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532570","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2016 to Question 41125, on shipping exhaust emissions, what ongoing assistance his Department is providing to support current and future research into such technologies.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41675","41675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532571","2016-07-06","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2016 to Question 41126, on shipping: energy, what penalties were given to each of the 24 vessels identified with deficiencies relating to energy efficiency; and how many Port State Control inspections have been carried out at each port since that requirement became mandatory.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41709","41709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532572","2016-07-07","Department for Transport","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to promote increased awareness among cyclists of other road users and pedestrians; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41731","41731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532574","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to publish child poverty statistics at a regional level.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41727","41727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532575","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of universal credit on the number of children living in (a) absolute and (b) relative poverty.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41742","41742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532576","2016-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) value of programmes commissioned by his Department's Dynamic Purchasing System in (i) St Helens North constituency, (ii) Merseyside and (iii) the North West since that system was introduced.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41706","41706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532577","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish updated mortality statistics for employment and support allowance, incapacity benefit and severe disablement allowance.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41684","41684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532578","2016-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for the consultation on attendance allowance.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41665","41665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532579","2016-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how much has been paid to officials of his Department as an additional incentive for working overtime on top of their normal overtime payments, (b) how much has been offered to any individual staff member for a one-off occurrence, (c) how many staff received such incentivised additional payments, (d) from which budgets such payments were made and (e) at which Ministerial or official level the business cases or payment approval for such payments was made in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41816","41816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532580","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants living in Hove constituency were reimbursed for travel to Brighton Assessment Centre in 2015.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41783","41783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532581","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment claims which a tribunal ruled should be paid are reinstated within six to eight weeks.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41785","41785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532582","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is for a personal independence payment claim to resume after the claimant has successfully challenged a stop to their claim; what administrative stages his Department undertakes before resuming such payments; and what steps he is taking to ensure that the time taken to resume such payments is within service standards.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41786","41786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532583","2016-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether people claiming attendance allowance can access Motability.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41787","41787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533372","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent support her Department has given to lamb farmers.","Biography information for Chris Davies","Chris Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905717","905717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533426","2016-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2016-07-04","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will make an assessment of the effect of extending the franchise for Scottish Parliament elections to 16 and 17 year olds on the level of youth engagement in the electoral process.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905700","905700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533487","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Government has to help more children access and understand nature.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905726","905726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533488","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to encourage more women to work in the food and farming industries.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905730","905730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533489","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the National Wildlife Crime Unit in tackling wildlife crime and protecting endangered animals.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905727","905727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533490","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Government has to help more children access and understand nature.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905731","905731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533491","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the decline in the bee population.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905729","905729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/533492","2016-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress is being made on ensuring that government departments buy more British food.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905732","905732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531443","2016-07-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking in response to the result of the EU referendum to ensure that investment in the Hartlepool steel pipe mills is made.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41624","41624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531444","2016-07-05","Department for International Trade","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government plans to meet with the (a) Australian, (b) New Zealand and (c) Canadian governments to discuss the potential effect on trade with those countries of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41618","41618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531445","2016-07-05","Cabinet Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government plans to establish a Department for Trade.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41617","41617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531446","2016-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of local authority-owned properties which have been sold under the Right to Buy scheme and subsequently let by private landlords.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41636","41636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531447","2016-07-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has had discussions with his European counterparts on funding for the universal service obligation.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41596","41596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531448","2016-07-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings he has had with mobile telephone providers on the implications of the outcome of the EU referendum for roaming charges; and what assessment he has made of whether roaming charges for UK citizens travelling in the EU will remain at their current level.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41597","41597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531449","2016-07-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has met with representatives of Vodafone to discuss the implications of the outcome of the EU referendum for the location of its headquarters in London.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41598","41598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531450","2016-07-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department is making in respect of EU (a) Directives which are passed and not yet implemented and (b) Regulations which will be adopted before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41599","41599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531451","2016-07-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on implementation of the Digital Economy Act 2010.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41600","41600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531452","2016-07-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of requiring at least 50 per cent of the licence fees raised in each region to be spent in that region on programme commissioning.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41604","41604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531453","2016-07-05","Department for Education","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to publish a response to the finding of the National Union of Teachers survey, published in March 2016, that 70 per cent of school leaders believed that a lack of school funding was affecting education standards in their schools.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41603","41603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531454","2016-07-06","Department for Education","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in Key Stage 1 in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire were taught in classes of more than (i) 30 or (ii) 35 in the academic year beginning September 2015.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41627","41627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531455","2016-07-06","Department for Education","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which primary schools in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire were were full or over capacity in the academic year beginning September (i) 2014 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41628","41628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531456","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) air pollution, (b) water pollution, (c) protection of species and habitats and (d) waste management.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41631","41631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531457","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on food standards and food safety.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41632","41632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531458","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on British fisheries.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41633","41633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531459","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on rural payments.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41634","41634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531460","2016-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on employment in the food manufacturing and farming sector.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41635","41635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531461","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to paragraph 19 of the concluding observations on the fifth period report of Israel by the UN Committee against Torture, published in May 2015, what steps he is taking to encourage the Israeli government to adopt the recommendations of that committee relating to documentation of suspect interrogations.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41623","41623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531462","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to work with Israel to support the formulation of the criminal offence of torture in that country.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41620","41620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531463","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department most recently raised the case of Giulio Regeni with the Egyptian government.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41610","41610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531464","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Israeli counterpart on ending the practice of administrative detention in that country.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41622","41622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531465","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the British embassy in Tel-Aviv is taking to monitor the case of Palestinian circus performer Mohammad Faisal Abu Sakha.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41621","41621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531466","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Iranian government on the alleged political imprisonment of orphanage worker Maryam Zaragaran.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41616","41616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531467","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if a representative from his Department will travel to Egypt to meet Egyptian authorities to discuss the murder of Giulio Regeni.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41607","41607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531468","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 June 2016 to Question 38785, what the content was of the three most recent representations the Government has made to the Saudi Arabian government relating to religious freedom.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41601","41601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531469","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress the Government has made on its response to the murder of Giulio Regeni.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41611","41611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531470","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to implement the ban on menthol cigarettes in the UK after 2020; and what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of that ban on the quality of life of smokers.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41615","41615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531471","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has visited the maternity department at the West Cumberland Hospital.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41625","41625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531472","2016-07-06","Cabinet Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many births there were at West Cumberland Hospital in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41626","41626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531473","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 22462, if he will place in the Library a copy of NHS England's report on individual funding requests for palivizumab.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41629","41629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531474","2016-07-06","Department of Health","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Cumbria Success Regime on consultant-led maternity services at the West Cumberland Hospital.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41630","41630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531475","2016-07-05","Home Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps are being taken (a) to improve cyber security and (b) prevent hacking as part of proposals for members of the public to submit identification photographs for official documents to HM Passport Office using their own digital services.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41608","41608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531476","2016-07-05","Home Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether HM Passport Office has trialled and tested the professional photo trade association ICAO compliant Digital ID Photo Sending Service proposal to mitigate identification fraud, photo rejections, poor image quality and cyber security threats.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41619","41619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531477","2016-07-05","Home Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to seek professional photographic trade association (a) accreditation, (b) sanction and (c) support for proposals to encourage digital identification photographs to be used in passport applications.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41609","41609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531478","2016-07-05","Home Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost was to HM Passport Office of handling and processing rejected passport applications in each of the last three years; and on what those costs were incurred.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41613","41613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531479","2016-07-05","Home Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passport applications were rejected by HM Passport Office because of the quality of the identification photo supplied in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41612","41612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531480","2016-07-05","Home Office","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports were reported as containing fake identification photos in the (a) last and (b) previous 12 months.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41614","41614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531481","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a new Junction 25A on the M1.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41602","41602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531482","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has received a copy of the report by IPPR North, entitled Gateways to the northern powerhouse: A northern ports strategy, published in June 2016.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41605","41605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531483","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to support the UK freight sector.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41606","41606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531484","2016-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on allowing unregistered charities to advertise vacancies on Universal Jobmatch.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41594","41594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/531485","2016-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many unregistered charities are registered and able to post vacancies on Universal Jobmatch.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41595","41595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530641","2016-07-04","Attorney General","2016-06-30","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Ministerial Correction of 24 June 2016 to Question 40180, on Gurpal Virdi, (a) when the Crown Prosecution Service (CPS) became aware that the Metropolitan Police had documentary evidence of the age of the complainant arrested on 7 November 1986 by PC Markwick and (b) whether the CPS asked for a statement by the arresting officer.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41555","41555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530642","2016-07-04","Attorney General","2016-06-30","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Ministerial Correction of 24 June 2016 to Question 40180, on Gurpal Virdi, how many statements of fact by the complainant were contradicted by (a) Tom Makins and (b) police or court records; and which police or court records confirmed the age of the complainant in November 1986.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41556","41556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530643","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the ability of firms to recruit skilled workers.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41525","41525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530644","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of (a) the number of free trade and other agreements which the UK will need to renegotiate as a result of the outcome of the EU referendum and (b) the resources which will be required to renegotiate such agreements.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41526","41526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530645","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on the Government's ability to negotiate trade agreements.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41527","41527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530646","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what engagement his Department has had with the Accelerated Access Review (AAR); and whether the AAR plans to investigate expediting the delivery of new drugs and devices to tackle MRSA and antimicrobial resistance.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41572","41572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530647","2016-07-05","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make arrangements for opposition party leaders or their nominated representatives to be granted advance sight of the conclusions of the Chilcot Report prior to that Report's publication.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41592","41592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530648","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Government officials with trade negotiating skills are currently based in Brussels.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41516","41516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530649","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the European and Global Issues Secretariat is part of the new EU Unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41517","41517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530650","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the Government's (a) expertise and (b) capacity to carry out trade deals as a result of the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41518","41518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530651","2016-07-04","Department for International Trade","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the Government's capability of negotiating trade agreements.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41519","41519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530652","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he plans to take to ensure that attracting trade and investment into the UK will be a key priority of the new EU unit.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41507","41507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530653","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the new EU Unit recruits people with an appropriate level of expertise.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41521","41521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530654","2016-07-05","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure that there is cross-party input into discussions with the devolved parliamentary bodies and administration in the process of negotiating the UK exit from the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41505","41505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530655","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister's oral statement of 27 June 2016, Official Report, column 23, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure cross-party input at each stage of formulating national goals and strategy.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41501","41501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530656","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to encourage Government-funded agencies and departments to move their offices outside London.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41502","41502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530657","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on advertising in the last six months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41554","41554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530658","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41567","41567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530659","2016-07-05","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to promote the Prime Minister's Points of Light awards; and how much was spent (a) overall and (b) on staff costs related to the distribution of those awards in each year since their launch.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41549","41549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530660","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on future levels of recruitment of civil servants.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41528","41528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530661","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on the future of the Union of the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41529","41529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530662","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the economic effect of the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41530","41530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530663","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made on the potential effect on levels of employment of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41533","41533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530664","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made on the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on the cost of (a) household products, (b) food and (c) cars.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41531","41531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530665","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate the Government has made on the potential effect on government income of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41532","41532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530666","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK-Malawi tax treaty on work to alleviate poverty and support economic growth in Malawi.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41520","41520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530667","2016-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on house prices.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41535","41535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530668","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government has made on the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on EU development funding for the regions of England.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41534","41534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530669","2016-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the amount owed by the Government to the government of Iran for Chieftain tanks bought by that government but never delivered; and if he will take steps to return that amount to the government of Iran.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41562","41562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530670","2016-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Chieftain tanks sold to the government of Iran but which remained undelivered were later sold to the government of Iraq.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41563","41563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530671","2016-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the use during the Iran-Iraq war of Chieftain tanks sold by the UK to the government of Iraq; and whether those tanks had previously been purchased by the government of Iran.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41564","41564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530672","2016-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether funds were received into the public purse from the sale of the same Chieftain tanks to Iraq which had already been sold through International Military Services but never delivered to the government of Iran.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41565","41565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530673","2016-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to return the funds owed to the government of Iran for the purchase of Chieftain tanks through International Military Services which were never delivered.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41566","41566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530674","2016-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the contribution of steel production to the resources of the armed forces.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41506","41506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530675","2016-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on the UK's role in NATO.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41536","41536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530676","2016-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on the UK's ability to work with allies in Syria and Iraq to fight Daesh.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41537","41537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530677","2016-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs that will be supported at BAE Systems in Samlesbury by the F-35 programme; and for how long those jobs will be supported.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41579","41579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530678","2016-07-05","Department for Education","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to encourage employers to provide work experience opportunities to people in full-time education.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41558","41558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530679","2016-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the number of trees that have been felled to be used as biofuel or biomass in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41523","41523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530680","2016-07-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the number of trees that have been planted to be used in biofuel or biomass in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41578","41578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530681","2016-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on flood defence funding.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41538","41538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530682","2016-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to make available funding at the same level as currently received from the Common Agricultural Policy in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41551","41551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530683","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) the USA and (b) the EU on corruption in the Palestinian authority.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41570","41570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530684","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on the Government's global diplomatic standing.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41539","41539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530685","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of China on the persecution of Christians and other faith groups.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41584","41584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530686","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the recommendations of the UN Committee against Torture Review of Israel, adopted on 12 May 2016 by that Committee, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on transferring responsibility for prisoner healthcare to that country's Ministry of Health.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41590","41590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530687","2016-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Israel on the (a) immediate release or (b) prompt charge and fair trial of Eteraf Al-Rimawi.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41591","41591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530688","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will withdraw his proposal to replace bursaries for nurses, midwives and allied health professionals with student loans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41588","41588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530689","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the announcement in paragraph 1.97 of the March 2016 Budget, on funding for child prosthetics, (a) by what mechanisms people can access, (b) who is able to apply for, (c) what the criteria is for accessing, (d) how many people have received and (e) who is responsible for distributing such funding.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41561","41561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530690","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on continued access to emerging treatments for muscular dystrophy and other rare neuromuscular conditions.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41576","41576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530691","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his Ministerial colleagues on Article 5.3 of the WHO Framework on Tobacco Control.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41522","41522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530692","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the tobacco industry on the Government's commitment to tackle the illicit trade in tobacco products and its potential effect on public health policy.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41509","41509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530693","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on the potential effect of the Government's commitment to tackle the illicit trade in tobacco products on public health policy.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41508","41508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530694","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the Government's response to the Choice Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41571","41571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530695","2016-07-05","Home Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to extend or give effect to the provisions in the Immigration Act 2016 in respect of (a) residential tenancies, (b) transfer of responsibility for unaccompanied children and (c) limitations on local authority support for people who have been refused asylum, adult migrant care leavers and other migrants.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41574","41574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530696","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the tobacco industry on the Government's commitment to tackle the illicit trade in tobacco products.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41557","41557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530697","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the outcome of the EU referendum on levels of (a) inward and (b) outward migration.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41543","41543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530698","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on the Government's role in (a) tackling the refugee crisis in Europe and (b) Operation Sophia in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41544","41544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530699","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on the Government's ability to tackle terrorism.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41545","41545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530700","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on national security.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41542","41542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530701","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of introducing an Australian-style points immigration system.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41540","41540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530702","2016-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents reported to the police online reporting portal True Vision in June 2016 took place in (a) Nottingham and (b) Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41510","41510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530703","2016-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents reported to the police online reporting portal True Vision have taken place in (a) Nottingham and (b) Nottinghamshire in June 2016.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41511","41511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530704","2016-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents reported to the police online reporting portal True Vision after 23 June 2016 took place in (a) Nottingham and (b) Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41512","41512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530705","2016-07-05","Home Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library copies of any correspondence with Ministers of the Scottish Government since the passing of the Immigration Act 2016 relating to that Act.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41575","41575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530706","2016-07-04","Department for International Development","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, under what circumstances it is her Department's policy to enact its action plan for Burundi.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41503","41503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530707","2016-07-04","Department for International Development","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when her Department plans to deploy additional funding and resources to Burundi.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41504","41504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530708","2016-07-04","Department for International Development","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, to which UN agencies staff of her Department have been seconded in connection with her Department's work in Burundi.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41513","41513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530709","2016-07-04","Department for International Development","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the level of seniority is of staff of her Department who have been seconded to UN agencies in connection with her Department's work in Burundi.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41514","41514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530710","2016-07-04","Department for International Development","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff of her Department have been seconded to UN agencies in connection with her Department's work in Burundi.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41515","41515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530711","2016-07-04","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on arrangements at the border between Ireland and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41541","41541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530712","2016-07-04","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what administrative arrangements have been made within her Department to respond to the result of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41552","41552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530713","2016-07-04","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what arrangements she plans to put in place to ensure the best possible co-ordination between her Department and the Northern Ireland Executive in response to the result of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41553","41553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530714","2016-07-04","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the proposed closures of electoral offices in Northern Ireland on voter registration and turnout.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41568","41568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530715","2016-07-04","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the effect on Northern Ireland of postponing the decision on extra runway capacity in South East England.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41569","41569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530716","2016-07-04","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the proposed closure of regional electoral offices in Northern Ireland, what steps she plans to take to ensure that all people in Northern Ireland will be able to continue to exercise their right to vote.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41573","41573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530717","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on EU development funding for Scotland.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41546","41546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530718","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish his accessibility action plan for public transport.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41550","41550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530719","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reports his Department has received on differences between actual and published driving test waiting times in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41559","41559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530720","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to reduce driving test waiting times in the last 12 months; and what data the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency has collected to assess the effectiveness of such steps.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41560","41560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530721","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make an assessment of the provision of bus services serving Sabden in Lancashire; and what steps his Department is taking to protect bus services serving rural communities.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41524","41524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530722","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what work his Department has conducted with Transport for London on the Sarah Hope Line.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41548","41548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530723","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the accuracy of the driving test waiting times published by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41577","41577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530724","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the viability of reopening Chatburn railway station in the Ribble Valley.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41580","41580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530725","2016-07-04","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps the Government has taken to encourage the level of (a) public transport use and (b) cycling in (i) Northern Ireland and (b) other constituent parts of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41585","41585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530726","2016-07-04","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on proposals to reduce air passenger duty on short to medium haul flights.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41586","41586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530727","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to advise people in the UK of their continuing rights to travel freely within the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41587","41587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530728","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to substantially reduce the number of heavy goods vehicles on the roads around Euston; and if he will make it his policy to encourage the use of rail to transport excavated and construction materials in that area during the development of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41593","41593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530729","2016-07-04","Department for Transport","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on plans in the Road Investment Strategy for a new smart motorway between junctions 23 and 25 of the M1.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41583","41583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530730","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of the outcome of the EU referendum on EU development funding for Wales.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41547","41547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530731","2016-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what change there has been in the proportion of (a) pensioners and (b) children living in low income households in the North East of England in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41589","41589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530732","2016-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of implementing a single asbestos disease-related benefit.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41581","41581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/530733","2016-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will take steps to reduce the number of forms associated with asbestos-related benefits.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41582","41582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529784","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Government plans to enter into talks with non-EU countries on initiating free trade agreements.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41458","41458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529785","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications of the EU referendum result for his plans to implement the EU-Canada Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41487","41487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529786","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications of the EU referendum result for his plans to agree and implement the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41488","41488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529788","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of whether parliamentary approval is required for implementation of the EU-Canada Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41468","41468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529789","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of leaving the EU on university research.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41480","41480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529790","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what criteria his Department plans to use to decide which companies may place bids for the Land Registry.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41495","41495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529791","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what selection criteria were used to appoint the head of the EU Unit.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41464","41464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529792","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2016 to Question 39672, if he will provide a breakdown of the costs associated with the Independent Commission on Freedom of Information.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41465","41465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529793","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether a value for money assessment was carried out prior to the setting up of the Independent Commission on Freedom of Information.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41447","41447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529794","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has for the revised UK-Malawi tax treaty to be signed and ratified.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41434","41434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529795","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which tax treaties his Department has under review or plans to review in the near future.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41435","41435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529797","2016-07-04","HM Treasury","2016-06-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2016 to Question 41169, whether his Department has made (a) an assessment of the potential merits and (b) an estimate of the potential costs of limiting taxation of pensions to the basic rate.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41463","41463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529798","2016-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to tackle increases in levels of street homelessness in (a) Bristol and (b) England.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41466","41466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529799","2016-07-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the local newspaper industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41443","41443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529800","2016-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the ongoing costs of keeping local authority data on the sale of higher value council homes up-to-date.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41440","41440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529801","2016-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of processing and validating local authority data on the sale of higher value council homes.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41441","41441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529803","2016-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what account he has taken of the Government's policy to end unabated coal in framing National Planning Policy Framework guidelines on the approval of new coal extraction projects.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41498","41498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529804","2016-07-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many voucher codes have been issued to date to households in Na h-Eileanan an Iar constituency under the national satellite broadband subsidy scheme; and what proportion of those codes has led to an order.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41475","41475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529808","2016-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38675, how many veterans who have applied for the Legion d'Honneur award are yet to receive that award.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41450","41450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529809","2016-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many nuclear warheads the UK currently retains.","Biography information for Mr Ronnie Campbell","Mr Ronnie Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41453","41453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529810","2016-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 39746, what the original purchase cost was of the Voyager aircraft that has been adapted.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41446","41446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529811","2016-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports the Government has received on the existence of evidence of the use of banned weapons by Russian forces in Syria; and what representations he has made to the Russian government on that matter.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41467","41467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529812","2016-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current timetable is for the completion and publication of the national shipbuilding strategy headed by Sir John Parker.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41500","41500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529814","2016-07-04","Department for Education","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the level of funding for secondary schools per pupil was in each of the last six years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41483","41483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529815","2016-07-04","Department for Education","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what real-terms funding she has allocated to schools in Birmingham for each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41496","41496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529816","2016-07-04","Department for Education","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department places any limits on (a) the pay of academy chains' chief executives and (b) payments to consultants.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41484","41484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529817","2016-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on ensuring that the Government's policy on unabated coal is reflected adequately in the National Planning Policy Framework guidelines.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41497","41497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529819","2016-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of leaving the EU on the UK's ability to meet its climate change targets.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41478","41478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529820","2016-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 June 2016 to Question 40996, what statistics the Government collects on the number of hunting trophies from endangered or threatened species which are brought in to the UK; and how the Government defines the sustainable hunting of such species.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41469","41469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529821","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 24771, what further assessment he has made of the conclusions of the Final Report of the UN Panel of Experts on Yemen.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41476","41476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529822","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any UK embassies in Europe are temporarily closed.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41477","41477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529823","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the EU institutions on the job security of UK citizens employed by those institutions.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41481","41481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529824","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications of UK withdrawal from the EU for UK pensions and healthcare provision for UK citizens (a) currently residing in other EU member states and (b) wishing to retire to other EU member states.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41482","41482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529825","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on cooperation with Ireland on matters under the Joint Statement Regarding Co-Operation on Measures to Secure the External Common Travel Area Border.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41433","41433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529826","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what humanitarian assistance the UK is providing to Taiz in Yemen; and whether his Department is engaging in negotiations to end the blockade of that city.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41485","41485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529827","2016-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will reaffirm its commitment to ensuring Gibraltar remains British sovereign territory as long as it is the will of the inhabitants of Gibraltar.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41451","41451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529828","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received about his Department's participation in the seventh conference of the parties to the WHO framework convention on tobacco control in November 2016.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41448","41448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529829","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's priorities are for the 7th Conference of the Parties to the World Health Organisation Framework Convention on Tobacco Control to be held in November 2016.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41439","41439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529830","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his (a) EU and (b) non-EU counterparts on tackling antimicrobial resistance.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41454","41454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529831","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Ministers of his Department have had with their counterparts in the devolved administrations on development of new antibiotics and encouraging innovation in such development through reform of evaluation and reimbursement mechanisms.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41456","41456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529832","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to minimise the number of cancelled operations caused by bed shortages.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41491","41491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529833","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cancelled operations were caused by bed shortages in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41492","41492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529834","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of alcohol consumption across the last 25 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41493","41493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529836","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many paediatric audiology services have registered for the Improving Quality in Physiological Services accreditation scheme to date.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41471","41471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529837","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many paediatric audiology services have (a) been allocated a date and are awaiting an assessment visit by UKAS inspectors under the Improving Quality in Physiological Services accreditation scheme and (b) failed to gain accreditation after their initial assessment visit, since the accreditation began in 2012.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41472","41472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529838","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has met the key deliverable in the 2014-15 NHS England business plan to ensure that more than 70 per cent of all scientific and diagnostic services are part of accreditation programmes.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41473","41473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529840","2016-07-04","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many paediatric audiology services have reached the level required, using the Self-Assessment and Improvement Tool, to be eligible to apply for accreditation under the Improving Quality in Physiological Services scheme.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41474","41474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529841","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress the Metropolitan Police Service has made on piloting and evaluating the use by police officers of body-worn cameras; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41479","41479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529842","2016-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many successful prosecutions there have been under the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41499","41499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529843","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes in the number of back office staff on the time spent on administrative duties by frontline police officers in (a) Avon and Somerset and (b) England.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41489","41489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529844","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to change visa requirements for EU citizens who wish to travel, study and work in the UK.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41445","41445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529845","2016-07-04","Home Office","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle the illicit trade in tobacco products.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41449","41449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529846","2016-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions there have been under legislation on female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41490","41490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529847","2016-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many convictions there have been for dog fighting in each of the last two years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41494","41494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529848","2016-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many work capability assessment appeals there were in Wales in the last three years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41459","41459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529849","2016-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost to the public purse was of an appeal hearing for a work capability assessment in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41460","41460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529850","2016-07-04","Prime Minister","2016-06-29","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to respond to the letter on Syria from Medics Under Fire which was delivered to 10 Downing Street on 20 May 2016.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41486","41486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529851","2016-07-04","Department for Transport","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve bus passenger safety.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41455","41455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529852","2016-07-04","Department for Transport","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on implementation of the Single European Sky programme.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41452","41452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529854","2016-07-04","Department for Transport","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what processes his Department plans to follow to determine the sums to be allocated from Local Growth Funding for the period from 2017-18 to 2020-21 in response to proposals for cycling and walking projects submitted before 22 July 2016 by local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41442","41442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529855","2016-07-04","Department for Transport","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish its cycling and walking investment strategy.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41436","41436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529856","2016-07-04","Department for Transport","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the process for bus passengers to register complaints.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41437","41437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529857","2016-07-04","Department for Transport","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on establishing a statutory independent body representing bus users.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41438","41438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529858","2016-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people transferred from working tax credit to (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41444","41444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529859","2016-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discretion his Department has to waive rules on non-payment of housing benefit to people with savings over a prescribed amount for (a) looked after adults, (b) vulnerable adults and (c) adults with disabilities.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41457","41457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529860","2016-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the quality of work capability assessments.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41461","41461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529861","2016-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answers of 29 January 2016 to Question 23225 and of 28 April 2016 to Question 35312, what progress his Department has made on bringing forward changes to secondary legislation provisions of the Pensions Act 2014 relating to Pension Protection Fund capping.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41462","41462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529862","2016-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has issued to officials of his Department on processing disability benefit claims from people who are on the organ transplant waiting list.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41470","41470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532615","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how he plans to implement the General Practice Forward View published by NHS England in April 2016.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905667","905667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532616","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Government has made on supporting women with perinatal mental health issues.","Biography information for Amanda Solloway","Amanda Solloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905670","905670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532617","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people diagnosed with lung diseases.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905669","905669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532618","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how NHS England plans to ensure that implementation of the cancer strategy published by the Independent Cancer Taskforce in July 2015 includes sufficient provision for people with rarer cancers.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905674","905674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532619","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to improve the provision of mental health services.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905671","905671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532620","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on improving cancer survival rates.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905673","905673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/532621","2016-07-05","Department of Health","2016-06-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on payments for people affected by contaminated blood.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905672","905672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529202","2016-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to secure the jobs of employees of HM Land Registry if its transition to the Government's preferred contract-based privatisation model goes ahead.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41344","41344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529203","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to prevent the dumping of Chinese steel in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41369","41369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529204","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that the investment in the long-products steel works in Teesside will be secure in the event of the UK exiting the EU.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41417","41417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529205","2016-07-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2016 to Question 40727, if his Department will increase the number of its employees based in Coventry in the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41420","41420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529206","2016-06-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to raise the rate of the national minimum wage for people under 25 to the rate of the national living wage.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41424","41424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529207","2016-06-30","Cabinet Office","2016-06-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate the amount lost to cyber fraud in the public sector in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41391","41391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529208","2016-06-30","Cabinet Office","2016-06-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what powers the National Cyber Security Centre will have to ensure that key infrastructure providers act on the advice it gives.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41399","41399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529209","2016-06-30","Cabinet Office","2016-06-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to ensure (a) that all Government services are available through the gov.uk website and (b) that that website remains operational at all times.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41400","41400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529210","2016-06-30","Cabinet Office","2016-06-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of staff the Government plans to recruit to form the new EU Unit.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41341","41341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529211","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister's Oral Statement of 27 June 2016, Official Report, column 23, what the terms of reference are for the new EU Unit.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41355","41355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529212","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister's Oral Statement of 27 June 2016, Official Report, column 23, how much funding has been allocated to the new EU Unit.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41356","41356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529213","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has to consult opposition parties on and during the process of negotiating the UK exit from the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41357","41357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529214","2016-07-04","Cabinet Office","2016-06-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government took before 23 June 2016 to prepare for a potential vote to leave the EU in the referendum.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41349","41349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529215","2016-06-30","HM Treasury","2016-06-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria his Department uses to decide when and how to negotiate the UK's tax treaties with other countries.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41359","41359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529216","2016-06-30","HM Treasury","2016-06-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department publishes on its process of reviewing and revising the UK's tax treaties  with other countries.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41340","41340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529217","2016-06-30","HM Treasury","2016-06-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to ensure stability in the housing market and increase the confidence of property developers since the EU referendum of 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41396","41396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529218","2016-06-30","HM Treasury","2016-06-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to encourage financial institutions to maintain their London operations and employment levels.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41397","41397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529219","2016-07-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2016 to Question 40701, what estimate he has made of the number of housing association properties sold through right-to-buy which have been replaced since the launch of that policy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41421","41421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529220","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with local authorities on the definition of higher value for the purposes of sales of higher value council homes under the Housing and Planning Act 2016.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41386","41386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529221","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library a copy of his recent request to local authorities for information about those bodies' housing stock to help determine the sale of higher value council homes.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41387","41387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529222","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance he provides to local councils to help them secure faster build-out rates from new developments.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41343","41343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529223","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of housing association tenants who will take up the option of right-to-buy in each year until 2019-20.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41384","41384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529224","2016-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what support the Government plans to provide to communities in (a) West Cumbria and (b) Somerset (i) during and (ii) after the construction of new nuclear development in those areas.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41365","41365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529225","2016-07-05","Department for Transport","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission research into improving pedestrian safety on pavements and to determine whether accidents occur more often on tarmacadam or on concrete slab surfaces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41370","41370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529226","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will set out the (a) number, (b) nature, (c) date of and (d) grounds of decisions Ministers in his Department have made to disagree with local authority proposals for housing development in their areas since 2010.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41407","41407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529227","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects the first sale of higher value council housing allowed by the Housing and Planning Act 2016 to take place.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41385","41385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529228","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what methodology he plans to use to determine the market rents of social housing properties for the purposes of the pay to stay policy.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41413","41413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529229","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish secondary legislation on the sale of higher value council homes under the Housing and Planning Act 2016.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41388","41388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529231","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, under which legislative provisions he took his decision on Ipswich Council's planning application for the development of the Ravenswood affordable housing scheme.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41432","41432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529232","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons he has not allowed Ipswich Council's recent proposal for the Ravenswood affordable housing development.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41389","41389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529233","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities will be affected by the sale of higher value council homes under the Housing and Planning Act 2016.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41411","41411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529234","2016-06-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answers of 8 February 2016 to Questions 25834 and 25835, whether a final decision has been made on the retention of business rates generated by new nuclear development in Copeland by the billing authority.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41428","41428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529235","2016-06-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will investigate reports that BT is installing and charging for telephone lines for customers who have not requested one and who are only customers of fibre optic services.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41401","41401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529236","2016-06-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will provide additional funding for broadband provision to difficult to reach properties in (a) rural and (b) urban areas which have not been provided with access under the Universal Service Obligation to date and where Openreach fibre rollout has been delayed for more than a year.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41347","41347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529237","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many veterans applied through his Department for the Legion d'Honneur in each month from July 2014 to June 2016.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41348","41348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529238","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the projected increase in defence expenditure during the current Parliament his Department expects to spend on (a) equipment and (b) the maintenance of equipment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41362","41362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529239","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has received representations from Amnesty International on photographs alleged to show UK-produced cluster munitions dropped in Yemen.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41376","41376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529240","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training is provided to officials of his Department working on his Department's Saudi Armed Forces Programme and the Saudi Arabia National Guard Communications Project on responding to whistleblowers from the private sector.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41364","41364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529241","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many applications for the Legion d'Honneur had been processed by the Personnel and Training, Defence Services Secretary, Commemorations department but had not yet been processed by the French authorities by 24 June 2016.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41371","41371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529242","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information the Government holds on stockpiles of cluster munitions in countries other than the UK.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41378","41378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529243","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the additional cost of repairing the F35 in the USA rather than the UK during its lifetime; and if he will take steps to allow the electronics of the F35 to be repaired in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41408","41408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529244","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the average time between veterans applying for the Legion d'Honneur and subsequently receiving the award.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41404","41404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529245","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Europe of 8 June 2016, Official Report, column 138WH, what assessments were last carried out on (a) whether the Saudi-led coalition in Yemen were targeting civilians and (b) respect for and compliance with international humanitarian law; and if he will place in the Library copies of documentation used in such assessments.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41410","41410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529246","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK ground personnel based in Saudi Arabia have witnessed the (a) movement, (b) transport or (c) storage of cluster munitions in that country.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41426","41426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529247","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) of his Department's civilian staff based in the UK, (b) military personnel based in the UK, (c) of his Department's civilian staff based in Saudi Arabia and (d) military personnel based in Saudi Arabia were employed by the (i) Saudi Arabian National Guard Communications Project and (ii) Ministry of Defence Saudi Armed Forces Project on 1 April in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41412","41412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529248","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of overall repair costs of an F35 during its operational lifetime.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41392","41392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529249","2016-06-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what evidence he has received on the possible use of cluster munitions in Yemen by Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41423","41423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529250","2016-06-30","Department for Education","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps her Department has taken to encourage students at Key Stage 3 to take up modern foreign languages.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41402","41402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529251","2016-06-30","Department for Education","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that computer coding is taught to children from an early stage in their education.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41405","41405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529252","2016-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2016 to Question 40363, what estimate she has made of the cost of energy imports by the UK in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41418","41418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529253","2016-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to her speech of 18 November 2015 on a new direction for UK energy policy, when the terms of reference of the review into coal will be published; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41414","41414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529254","2016-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assistance her Department provides to UK-based companies seeking to export energy and fuel; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41415","41415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529255","2016-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent progress has been made on her Department's market stabilisation Contract for Difference policy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41416","41416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529256","2016-07-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2016 to Question 40279, what forecast the Oil and Gas Authority has made of the proportion of UK energy consumption to be supplied by other countries in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41419","41419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529257","2016-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what public consultation the Forestry Commission has carried out on the future ownership and use of the Cannon Hill plantation in Ferndown, Dorset.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41372","41372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/529258","2016-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is the policy of the Forestry Commission to sell the Cannon Hill plantation in Ferndown, Dorset for development.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 41373","41373"
