"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885226","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to establish an independent air safety regime after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136091","136091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885227","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of establishing a new UK civil aviation system after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136092","136092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885228","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether UK aircraft maintenance companies will be able to continue to perform maintenance checks on EU27 aircraft after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136093","136093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885229","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from representatives of pharmaceutical companies on the legal status of cannabis for medical treatments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136094","136094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885230","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to support UK small and medium-sized businesses in procurement competitions to supply (a) goods and (b) services for the construction of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136095","136095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885231","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 105717, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending statutory adoption leave to people who are self-employed.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136096","136096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885232","2018-04-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the merits in terms of (a) value for money and (b) reducing errors of separating the production of health reports from decision making.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136097","136097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885233","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Mental Health and Inequalities on 22 March, Col 488, what recent discussions he has had with BioMarin, the manufacturer of Kuvan, on the pricing of that drug.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136098","136098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885234","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what services are available for new patients at the Whittington Health NHS Trust clinic specialising in the treatment of chronic urinary tract infections.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136099","136099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885235","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish the subcontracting management fees for all further education providers for 2016-17.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136100","136100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885236","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were granted entry to reside in the UK on the basis of ties to a family member in the UK in each of the last seven years; how many of those people were under the age of 25; and how many applications were made on that basis in that same period.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136101","136101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885237","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discounted rates for dental treatment are available for people on the basis of (a) protected characteristics, (b) pregnancy and (c) low income.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136102","136102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885238","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many representations he has received on the level of noise pollution caused by traffic from people living in the London Borough of Southwark in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136103","136103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885239","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of breast pumps in (a) maternity and (b) neo-natal units.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136104","136104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885240","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that all (a) maternity and (b) neo-natal units have an adequate provision of breast pumps.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136105","136105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885241","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking in response to the finding of the National Maternity Review that 90 per cent of women stopped breastfeeding before they wanted to.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136106","136106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885242","2018-04-23","Cabinet Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for how many deaths the consumption of an excess of prescription drugs was the primary cause between 2012 and 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136107","136107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885243","2018-04-23","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the change in the ratio of investments in stocks and shares ISAs to cash ISAs has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136108","136108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885244","2018-04-23","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Government's timetable is for setting out its plans arising from its consultation on the impact of VAT and air passenger duty on tourism in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136109","136109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885245","2018-04-19","Women and Equalities","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 22 December 2017 to Question 120358, on Access to Elected Office for Disabled People Fund, what the timetable is for publishing the evaluation of the Access to Elected Office Fund which was completed in June 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136110","136110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885246","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date the Government (a) first identified (i) the Him Shinshar weapons bunkers near Homs as a chemical weapons equipment and storage facility, (ii) the Him Shinsar weapons storage site and former missile base near Homs as a location of Sarin and precursor production equipment and (iii) the Barzeh branch of the Syrian Scientific Studies and Research Centre in northern Damascus as a centre for the research and development of Syria’s chemical and biological weapons programme and (b) reported that information to the Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136111","136111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885247","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with key infrastructure providers on the steps they are taking to protect themselves from cyber-attack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136112","136112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885248","2018-04-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with key infrastructure providers on the steps they are taking to protect themselves from cyber-attack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136113","136113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885249","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with key infrastructure providers on the steps they are taking to protect themselves from cyber-attack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136114","136114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885250","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with key infrastructure providers on the steps they are taking to protect themselves from cyber-attack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136115","136115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885251","2018-04-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with key infrastructure providers on the steps they are taking to protect themselves from cyber-attack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136116","136116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885252","2018-04-19","Wales Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with key infrastructure providers on the steps they are taking to protect themselves from cyber-attack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136117","136117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885253","2018-04-19","Scotland Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with key infrastructure providers on the steps they are taking to protect themselves from cyber-attack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136118","136118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885254","2018-04-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with key infrastructure providers on the steps they are taking to protect themselves from cyber-attack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136119","136119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885255","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her oral contribution of 16 April 2018, Official Report, Column 27, on Windrush Children (Immigration Status), what plans she has to review the management of the immigration directorate in her Department.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136120","136120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885256","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the relationship between changes in the (a) number of officers in the West Midlands Police Force Area and (b) level of recorded crime in the area covered by that police force.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136121","136121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885257","2018-04-19","Department for International Trade","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what contact he has had with businesses in Coventry South constituency in connection with trade with the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136122","136122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885258","2018-04-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many new start-ups there have been in the media and culture sector in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136123","136123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885259","2018-04-19","Attorney General","2018-04-17","To ask the Attorney General, how many IT systems which his Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all his Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136124","136124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885260","2018-04-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many IT systems which his Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all his Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136125","136125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885261","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many IT systems which his Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all his Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136126","136126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885262","2018-04-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many IT systems which his Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all his Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136127","136127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885263","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many IT systems which his Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all his Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136128","136128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885264","2018-04-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many IT systems which his Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all his Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136129","136129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885265","2018-04-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many IT systems which his Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all his Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136130","136130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885266","2018-04-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many IT systems which his Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all his Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136131","136131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885267","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many IT systems which his Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all his Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136132","136132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885268","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many IT systems which her Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps she is taking to ensure that all her Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136133","136133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885269","2018-04-19","Department for International Development","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many IT systems which her Department uses are more than (a) three, (b) five and (c) eight years old; and what steps she is taking to ensure that all her Department's IT systems are updated promptly.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136134","136134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885270","2018-04-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress the cross-Whitehall workstream has made since January 2018 on realising the opportunities to regulate (a) social, (b) environmental, (c) energy, (d) consumer and (e) product standards differently after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136135","136135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885271","2018-04-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he is able to intervene in circumstances in which Virgin Media fails to provide telecommunication services to a charitable organisation within a reasonable timeframe.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136136","136136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885272","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of students leaving a free school pursued a STEM subject at university in each year since 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136137","136137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885273","2018-04-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the document EU Exit Analysis Cross Whitehall Briefing, dated January 2018, what assumptions were made when modelling for the impact on gross value added in the agriculture sector of exiting the EU under a Free Trade Agreement scenario.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136138","136138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885274","2018-04-23","Department for International Trade","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 134889, on Export Controls, for what reason his Department sifts licence applications into three categories.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136139","136139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885275","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 135034, for how many days each of the four requests to visit Yarl’s Wood Immigration Removal Centre was under consideration by the Minister for Immigration before being granted.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136140","136140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885276","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Minister of State for Immigration plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Warley of 13 March 2018 regarding Miss Shouqat Harrum.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136141","136141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885277","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 134853, whether her Department plans to introduce transitional arrangements for Turkish business people who have been in the UK for up to four years under the European Community Association Agreement with Turkey visa scheme to allow them to apply for indefinite leave to remain after four years in the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136142","136142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885278","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department provided from the Places of worship: security funding scheme to (a) churches, (b) gurdwaras and (c) mosques in the 2017-18 allocation; and whether such funds will be renewed on an annual basis.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136143","136143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885279","2018-04-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made in response to the 2015 recommendation of the All-Party Parliamentary Group against Antisemitism on creating a database of symbols slogans and flags that may be illegal because the organisations that use them incite hatred.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136144","136144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885280","2018-04-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he has taken to establish codes of conduct for social media companies and industry bodies on the treatment of antisemitic content on their platforms.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136145","136145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885281","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what advice his Department gives to pregnant women on folic acid.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136146","136146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885282","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her oral contribution of 16 April 2018, Official Report, column 27, on Windrush Children (Immigration Status), how many staff she plans to deploy to the dedicated team to help people to evidence their right to be here and to access the necessary services.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136147","136147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885283","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her oral contribution of 16 April 2018, Official Report, column 27, on Windrush Children (Immigration Status), how she plans to recruit staff to work in the dedicated team to help people to evidence their right to be here and to access the necessary services.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136148","136148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885284","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her oral contribution of 16 April 2018, Official Report, column 27, on Windrush Children (Immigration Status), whether the staff she plans to deploy to the dedicated team to help people to evidence their right to reside in the UK and to access the necessary services will be (a) new Civil Service recruits or (b) reassigned from within her Department.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136149","136149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885285","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions his Department has had with (a) representatives of the universities sector and (b) the Home Office on ensuring that British-born children of immigrants are not deterred from applying to university by the application fee for such children to register as British citizens.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136150","136150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885286","2018-04-19","Department for International Development","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department provides to support programmes to improve the economy of Egypt.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136151","136151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885287","2018-04-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance his Department is giving to the Egyptian armed forces.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136152","136152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885288","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequate availability of the HPV vaccine throughout the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136153","136153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885289","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce incidences of bowel cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136154","136154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885290","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people by (a) age and (b) gender have been diagnosed with bowel cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136155","136155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885291","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average life expectancy is for people diagnosed with bowel cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136156","136156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885292","2018-04-23","Department for International Development","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking in the preparation of its Voluntary National Review of progress against the Sustainable Development Goals to secure the active involvement of local authorities and civil society organisations.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136157","136157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885294","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed as having glaucoma in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136159","136159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885295","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the employment of 3,000 new midwives by the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136160","136160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885296","2018-04-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy to relocate interpreters regardless of where they have assisted British military personnel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136161","136161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885297","2018-04-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the safety of interpreters is monitored when they are no longer employed by the UK Government.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136162","136162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885299","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce (a) infection and (b) disease after tonsil removal operations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136163","136163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885300","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with an STI in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136164","136164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885301","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the incidence of STIs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136165","136165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885302","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prevent addiction to Xanax.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136166","136166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885303","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a regulatory requirement for Ofsted to inspect children’s homes before they reopen.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136167","136167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885304","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department provides on how multi-academy trust board minutes and other records should be stored in instances where (a) a previous academy board is replaced and placed under new sponsorship and (b) an academy trust closes.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136168","136168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885305","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether (a) Ofsted, (b) the Education and Skills Funding Agency, (c) the Regional Schools Commissioner and (d) his Department had sight of board minutes from the Manchester Creative Studio or the Collective Spirit Free School in Oldham prior to the re-brokering of the Collective Spirit Multi-Academy Trust.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136169","136169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885306","2018-04-23","Wales Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on plans to bring forward a Public Health (Minimum Price for Alcohol) (Wales) Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136170","136170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885307","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what strategy has been put in place to co-ordinate the entry into service of 7,000 new rail vehicles in control period (CP) 5 and early CP6 and the upgrading of rail infrastructure in order to maximise the benefits of that new rolling stock to passengers.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136171","136171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885308","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the capability of the UK rail network infrastructure to fully realise the benefits of the new rail vehicles due to enter service in CP5 and early CP6 which will be electric.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136172","136172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885309","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which (a) Department and (b) Minister will be responsible for making the final decisions on projects within the Rail Network Enhancements Pipeline.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136173","136173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885310","2018-04-19","Department for International Development","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the total amount of aid is that the UK plans to send to Yemen in 2018.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136174","136174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885311","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Police Information Notices were issued in London by ethnicity in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136175","136175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885312","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect on the credit rating of claimants of Support for Mortgage Interest of that benefit being converted into a loan.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136176","136176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885313","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools by type of school are rated as (a) requires improvement or (b) inadequate in each regional schools commissioner area.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136177","136177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885314","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to contact claimants of Support for Mortgage Interest that do not have a telephone number.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136178","136178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885315","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) failed and (b) unsuccessful contacts with claimants of Support for Mortgage Interest there have been.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136179","136179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885316","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of Support for Mortgage Interests are part of the home ownership for people with long-term disabilities scheme.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136180","136180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885317","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools by type of school have improved from (a) inadequate or requires improvement to (b) good or outstanding in each regional schools commissioner jurisdiction area in each year since regional schools commissioners were established.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136181","136181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885318","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people with Parkinson’s disease were held in custody by the police in 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136182","136182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885319","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools by type of school have moved from (a) good or outstanding to (b) inadequate or requires improvement in each regional schools commissioner jurisdiction area in each year since regional schools commissioners were established.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136183","136183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885320","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what policies the police have in place to help support (a) staff with Parkinson’s disease and (b) people with Parkinson’s disease being held in custody.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136184","136184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885321","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what legislation is in place to prevent discrimination against (a) housing benefit and (b) universal credit recipients in the private rented sector; and what assessment has been made of the adequacy of that legislation.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136185","136185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885322","2018-04-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the aerospace industry on ensuring that goods, products, and services will be able to swiftly cross the UK-EU border after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136186","136186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885323","2018-04-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) representatives of the defence manufacturing industry on ensuring that goods, products, and services will be able to swiftly cross the UK-EU border after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136187","136187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885324","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the funding arrangements for new pre-registration dental hygiene and dental therapy students who are starting courses on or after 1 August 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136188","136188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885325","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment has been made of the equity of the cost to consumers of Flood Re insurance cover.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136189","136189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885326","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has assessed the potential merits of producing a strategy to support research into the barriers and motivations affecting BAME organ, blood and stem cell donation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136190","136190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885328","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that UK driving licence holders are able to use those licences in EEA countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136191","136191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885329","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has in place to ensure the efficiency of border arrangements for the import of components in complex supply chains from non-EU countries.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136192","136192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885330","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to prevent work-related mental illness in the police force.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136193","136193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885331","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many real-time continuous glucose monitoring devices were used (a) in each clinical commissioning group and (b) across England in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136194","136194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885332","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the variation in (a) access and (b) uptake of insulin pumps across England.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136195","136195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885333","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has been made of the variation in (a) access and (b) uptake of testing strips for people with diabetes across England.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136196","136196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885334","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of people with diabetes in England are given a choice of their preferred glucose monitor.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136197","136197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885335","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of local NHS formularies in delivering best outcomes for people with diabetes.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136198","136198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885336","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what (a) guidance and (b) incentives are provided to GPs to ensure people with Type 1 Diabetes have access to proven technologies to support self-management.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136199","136199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885337","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with NICE on undertaking its appraisal of technology for Type 1 Diabetes.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136200","136200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885338","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using artificial pancreas to improve outcomes for people with Type 1 Diabetes.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136201","136201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885339","2018-04-23","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent estimate she has made of the proportion of pupils attending integrated schools in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136202","136202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885340","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure a friction-free border for non-EU (a) imports and (b) exports at UK ports.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136203","136203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885341","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the maintenance of commercial air services after 30 March 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a Withdrawal and Future Partnership Agreement.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136204","136204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885342","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has received an application for consent to hydraulic fracturing in respect of Preston New Road, Lancashire.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136205","136205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885343","2018-04-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the ability of the UK to substitute domestically produced (a) food and (b) fish for imports once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136206","136206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885344","2018-04-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that a UK fishing policy will be in place after April 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136207","136207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885345","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to complete the bulk pension transfer of employees working in Devonport Dockyard; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136208","136208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885346","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to respond to and resolve the case of Ms Jeorga Thompson of Prenton, Birkenhead.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136209","136209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885347","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps his Department has taken to control smuggling at the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136210","136210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885348","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2018 to Question 130566, what guidance is provided to Jobcentre staff to ensure that the work requirements they prescribe do not necessitate medical treatment.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136211","136211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885349","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many home visits were made by work coaches in respect of universal credit claimants with complex needs prior to making a referral to a decision-maker on whether or not to consider a sanction in 2017-18.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136212","136212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885350","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria or guidance is used by work coaches when deciding whether a home visit is necessary in respect of universal credit claimants with complex needs prior to making a referral to a decision-maker on whether or not to consider a sanction.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136213","136213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885351","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department had with Preston City Council on the external cladding installed on the exterior of properties in the Fishwick, St Matthews and Town Centre wards under the Community Energy Saving Programme; and what assessment has been made of whether properties are unsafe to reside in due to risk of fire or mould.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136214","136214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885352","2018-04-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people (a) were convicted of, (b) received custodial sentences for and (c) received community orders for driving or attempting to drive with excess alcohol at each magistrates court in Lancashire and Cumbria in each month of 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136215","136215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885353","2018-04-23","Prime Minister","2018-04-17","To ask the Prime Minister, for what reasons the meeting at 10 Downing Street with (a) Jeff Silvester and (b) Zack Massingham of AggregateIQ was not reported in the Cabinet Office Transparency data; and if she will publish the (a) date of the visit, (b) who issued them with the invitation to the meeting, (c) who attended that meeting and what the purpose of that meeting was.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136216","136216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885354","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 135108 on Govia Thameslink Railway: Compensation, how much compensation (a) has been paid and (b) is due to be paid to his Department by Network Rail.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136217","136217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885355","2018-04-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Government's plastic deposit return scheme on small retailers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136218","136218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885356","2018-04-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions his Department has had with unions representing prison officers on the new pension scheme since its introduction in 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136219","136219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885357","2018-04-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers in England and Wales have retired (a) at and (b) before the age of 60 for health reasons in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136220","136220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885358","2018-04-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what consultation his Department carried out with prison officers, trades unions and healthcare professionals before introducing the new pension scheme for prison officers in 2015 which raised the age of retirement to 67 years of age.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136221","136221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885359","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost of subsidies and financial incentives provided from the public purse has been by scheme for electric vehicles and plug-in hybrid electric vehicles in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136222","136222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885360","2018-04-23","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what revenues have been collected from VAT on electric vehicle sales and plug-in hybrid electric vehicles in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136223","136223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885361","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with local authorities on the provision of funding in revenue support grants for infrastructure to support electric vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136224","136224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885362","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of reintroducing wolves into the UK; whether his Department has any plans to support the reintroduction of such animals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136225","136225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885363","2018-04-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to retain any Tornado GR4 aircraft in service beyond 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136226","136226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885364","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the implications are of recent Iranian cyber attacks on universities in the UK and US on the level of cyber threat posed by that country to the UK more generally.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136227","136227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885365","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made representations to the Iranian Government on restrictions being applied to people in that country on access to the internet and social media; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136228","136228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885366","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of people who will lose their homes as a result of the ending of the Support for Mortgage Interest for claimants in receipt of Employment and Support Allowance.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136229","136229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885367","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure that businesses receive any refunds or rebates from HMRC in a timely manner.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136230","136230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885368","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to streamline the real-time submissions process to support the payment of refunds from HMRC to employers.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136231","136231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885369","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC has recently made an assessment of the effectiveness of its procedures for businesses obtaining refunds from either (a) the Construction Industry Scheme and (b) statutory overpayments.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136232","136232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885370","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what resources he plans to commit his Department and its agencies to provide to improve patient safety and engage with health professionals to raise awareness of the potential health risks for women of child-bearing age taking Sodium Valproate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136233","136233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885371","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2018 to Question 134583, on Martin Selmayr,  what communications his Department had with the UK Commissioner to the EU on the appointment of Professor Dr Martin Selmayr as Secretary General of the European Commission prior to that appointment.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136234","136234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885372","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to have in place a customs system to deal with trade on WTO terms.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136235","136235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885373","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that nursing students who have received incorrect payments from the Student Loans Company are not forced to leave their courses on account of reductions to their payments in the new term.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136236","136236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885374","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of nursing students who have received incorrect payments from the Student Loans Company and who have been told that money will as a result be deducted from their future payments.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136237","136237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885375","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Commonwealth citizens who arrived in the UK before 1973 have been (a) deported, (b) placed in immigration detention and (c) denied recourse to public funds since 2012.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136238","136238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885376","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information holds on the number of passenger (a) arrivals and (b) departures at Nuneaton railway station in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Jones","Mr Marcus Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136239","136239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885377","2018-04-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether England is projected to meet its share of the UK's targets for reducing waste sent to landfill sites.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136240","136240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885378","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reason the Government ceased to make available waste infrastructure credits in relation to incineration; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136241","136241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885379","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to introduce any proposals in the revised National Planning Policy framework to make changes to the Waste Planning Policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136242","136242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885380","2018-04-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will assess the potential merits of introducing no-fault divorce settlements in helping couples to settle disputes outside court.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136243","136243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885381","2018-04-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding his Department has allocated to each regional delivery partner of the National Citizen Service programme in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136244","136244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885382","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to publish its Waste and Resources Review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136245","136245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885383","2018-04-19","Department for International Trade","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March to Question 132109 on trade remedies, if he will publish the schedule of meetings which took place at each of the 60 visits.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136246","136246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885384","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Questions 134800, 134801, 134802, 134803 and 134804, on Visas: Skilled Workers, if she will publish the data requested.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136247","136247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885385","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department holds the data requested in Questions 134800, 134801, 134802, 134803 and 134805.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136248","136248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885386","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 117198, on Incinerators, for what reason the UK's on-stream incineration capacity is underused compared with the permitted capacity; and for what reason there is a similar difference in the East of England.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136249","136249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885387","2018-04-23","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the agenda for the Financial Action Task Force plenary meeting in June 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136250","136250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885388","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to promote the recycling of waste instead of using (a) landfill and (b) incineration.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136251","136251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885389","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 134308 on Engineers and Scientists: Visas, if she will place that data in the Library.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136252","136252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885390","2018-04-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of tourism funding from the public purse was allocated to London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136253","136253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885391","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many investigations of breaches of section 1112 of the Companies Act 2006 have been undertaken by Companies House; and how many of those investigations (a) led to companies being dissolved and taken off the register and (b) resulted in Companies House referring the case to prosecutors.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136254","136254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885392","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many elective operations were cancelled in (a) November 2017, (b) December 2017 and (c) January 2018; and how many and what proportion of those operations have not yet been rearranged.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136255","136255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885393","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many wards are currently closed under the framework to support winter pressures in 2017-18.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136256","136256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885394","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average length of time taken was to rearrange elective procedures that were cancelled as a result of the winter pressures.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136257","136257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885395","2018-04-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the average length of custodial sentence for each type of offence given by each magistrate court in England and Wales.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136258","136258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885396","2018-04-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of defendants being remanded in custody was by each type of offence for each magistrate court in England and Wales.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136259","136259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885397","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the NHS to meet the target for referral to treatment in less than 18 weeks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136260","136260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885398","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the NHS next to meet its target relating to A&E waiting times of less than four hours.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136261","136261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885399","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has conducted any impact assessments on the effect on the British education system of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136262","136262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885400","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has conducted any impact assessments on the effect on the healthcare system in the UK of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136263","136263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885401","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133769, what specific steps her Department is taking to encourage social media companies to tackle online hate crime.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136264","136264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885402","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on the environment of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136265","136265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885403","2018-04-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to negotiate bilateral alternatives to the EU Mobility Partnerships.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136266","136266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885404","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March to Question 134845 on English Language: Refugees, how much funding the Government has allocated to accredited English language teaching for refugees in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136267","136267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885405","2018-04-23","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers in Wales were prosecuted for non-payment of the national living wage in each quarter of 2017.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136268","136268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885406","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start children’s centres there are there in England.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136269","136269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885407","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the organisations that submitted applications to run the Reception Baseline Assessment.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136270","136270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885408","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children using Sure Start Children's Centres in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136271","136271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885409","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of Sure Start centres offer a referral-only service.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136272","136272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885410","2018-04-23","Cabinet Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which (a) external data analysts and (b) data collection companies his Department has used in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136273","136273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885411","2018-04-23","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which (a) external data analysts and (b) data collection companies his Department has used in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136274","136274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885412","2018-04-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether her Department has assessed the viability of online voting in Northern Ireland elections.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136275","136275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885413","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which (a) external data analysts and (b) data collection companies his Department has used in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136276","136276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885414","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Algerian Government on the closure of places of Christian worship in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136277","136277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885415","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons his Department does not offer a subject knowledge enhancement grant to people training as religious education teachers; and if he will take steps to offer such grants for people wishing to train as teachers in that subject.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136278","136278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885416","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what advice his Department provides to early years settings on (a) identifying and (b) removing asbestos from premises.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136279","136279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885417","2018-04-19","Department for International Trade","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with Invest Northern Ireland on the use of UK Embassies to promote Northern Ireland as a location for foreign direct investment.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136280","136280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885418","2018-04-19","Department for International Trade","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many people were employed in his Department dealing with trade negotiations in (a) March 2016 and (b) March 2018.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136281","136281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885419","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many diplomats of the Russian Federation in the UK are based in locations outside London.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136282","136282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885420","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the fairness of the 2018 Egyptian Presidential election.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136283","136283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885421","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department holds information on the number of families with no recourse to public funds who have been offered support under Section 17 of the Children's Act 1989 in (a) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (b) London and (c) England in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136284","136284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885422","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers conducted street patrols in (a) Lewisham and (b) London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136285","136285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885423","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to reintroduce prescriptions for gluten-free products for children who have coeliac disease.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136286","136286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885424","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made any recent assessment of the adequacy of support available to the children of parents with no recourse to public funds.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136287","136287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885425","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to prohibit the practice of cross-border hiring by private hire vehicles; and if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a statutory definition of cross-border hiring.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136288","136288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885426","2018-04-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which (a) external data analysts and (b) data collection companies his Department has used in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136289","136289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885427","2018-04-19","Department for International Development","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which (a) external data analysts and (b) data collection companies her Department has used in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136290","136290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885428","2018-04-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which (a) external data analysts and (b) data collection companies his Department has used in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136291","136291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885429","2018-04-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which (a) external data analysts and (b) data collection companies his Department has used in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136292","136292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885430","2018-04-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) external data analysts and (b) data collection companies his Department has used in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136293","136293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885431","2018-04-23","Women and Equalities","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what correspondence there has been between her Department and the Speaker of the House of Commons on whether a decision to re-open the Access to Elected Office scheme has been made.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136294","136294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885432","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Stop Start, published by the Sutton Trust on 16 April 2018, if he will make an assessment on the implications for his policies on the recording of sure start centre closures as a result of the findings in that report.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136295","136295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885433","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 134639, on Children: Day Care, what the technical issues were that were experienced by parents when applying for tax-free childcare through the online service; and what caused those issues.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136296","136296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885434","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the planned effective operational date is for the Government's dedicated national security unit to tackle fake news and disinformation.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136297","136297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885435","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the staffing complement is by grade of the Government's dedicated national security unit to tackle fake news and disinformation.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136298","136298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885436","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Stop Start, published by the Sutton Trust on 16 April 2018, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits of introducing a national register of children’s centres which sets minimum levels of Sure Start provision.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136299","136299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885437","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the number of Windrush citizens who have been (a) denied and (b) charged for NHS treatment; and what steps she is taking together with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care to rectify that matter.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136300","136300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885438","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to conduct a consultation on children's centres.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136301","136301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885439","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 904765, Official Report, column 21, if she will publish (a) the evidential basis for the contract for the printing of passports being estimated as saving £120 million and (b) details of that proposed contract; over what time period those savings are estimated to accrue; and what proportion of the cost of the contract those estimated savings represent.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136302","136302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885440","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of children living in the London Borough of Lewisham who spent time in a police station as a place of safety as a result of a mental health condition in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136303","136303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885441","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people living in (a) Lewisham Deptford constituency and (b) the London Borough of Lewisham have (i) been detained for immigration purposes and (ii) successfully appealed a Home Office decision to detain them for immigration purposes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136304","136304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885442","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary school children have been off-rolled by their school in (a) the London Borough of Lewisham, (b) London and (c) England in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136305","136305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885443","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the GP to patient ratio for (a) Lewisham Clinical Commissioning Group and (b) other clinical commissioning groups in London; and if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of those GP to patient ratios.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136306","136306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885444","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to (a) correct its guidance concerning personal independence payment daily living activity 9 in respect of visual impairment being considered insufficient in itself to score points in respect of engaging with others and (b) identify cases incorrectly assessed on that basis.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136307","136307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885445","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department's guidance for assessors and decision-makers in relation to personal independence payment mobility activity 1 which reflecting regulations which the High Court has found to be ultra vires and to discriminate against claimants who cannot plan or follow a journey because they experience overwhelming psychological distress is still in use; and when it is planned for that guidance to be withdrawn and new guidance issued.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136308","136308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885446","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the status is of her Department's guidance for personal independence payment daily living activity 6 which states that visual impairment is not sufficient in itself to score points in respect for help with dressing; what steps her Department is taking to identify cases incorrectly assessed on that basis; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136309","136309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885447","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the Dorset (Structural Changes) (Modification of the Local Government and Public Involvement in Health Act 2007) Regulations 2018 disapply the provision in Section 7(3) of the Local Government and Public Involvement in Health Act 2007 to require consultation with every local authority affected before making an order under Section 7(1)(a) of that 2007 Act.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136310","136310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885448","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the amendments to the Local Government and Public Involvement in Health Act 2007 proposed in the Dorset (Structural Changes) (Modification of the Local Government and Public Involvement in Health Act 2007) Regulations 2018 are retrospective; and whether analogous retrospective provisions are also proposed for other local government areas in England.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136311","136311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885449","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason (a) he has not used and (b) does not intend to use his powers under Section 2 of the Local Government and Public Involvement in Health Act 2007 to invite proposals from local authorities in Dorset for single tier local government.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136312","136312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885450","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the evidential basis is for the statement in his letter of 27 March 2018 to the hon. Member for Christchurch that the draft of the Dorset (Structural Changes) (Modification of the Local Government and Public Involvement in Health Act 2007) Regulations 2018 have been developed and worked up with all nine councils in Dorset; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136313","136313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885451","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133811, on local government finance, for what reason he is not able to make the information requested available immediately; and if he will place a copy of that information in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136314","136314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882246","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people in receipt of the upper rate of employment support allowance who have died of motor neurone disease since October 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135350","135350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884155","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-04-16","What assessment she has made of the level of crime and the effectiveness of crime reporting by police forces.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904758","904758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884156","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-04-16","Whether she has made an assessment of the effectiveness of measures to tackle the illegal trade in the drug commonly known as Spice.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904761","904761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884157","2018-04-16","Home Office","2018-04-16","What plans she has to change the operation of the Tier 2 work visa.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904763","904763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884866","2018-04-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what requirements his Department places on bidders to demonstrate the potential effect of their winning a contract on (a) UK employment and (b) the UK economy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135854","135854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884867","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of students whose classes have been cancelled as a result of the recent strikes by university staff.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135855","135855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884868","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the UK will have completed all preliminary steps to allow ratification of the WHO Framework Convention on Tobacco Control Protocol to Eliminate Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products before 2 July 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135856","135856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884869","2018-04-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women aged between 60 to 65 are in receipt of employments benefits by type of benefit.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135857","135857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884870","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support the implementation of UN Security Council resolution 2401.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135858","135858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884871","2018-04-18","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what additional rights are accorded by the UK Government to people in Northern Ireland who choose to assert their right to Irish citizenship.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135859","135859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884872","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland authorities on social security and employment procedures after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135860","135860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884873","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to support off-grid households to connect to the gas network.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135861","135861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884874","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the amount of export sales by companies with over 250 employees based in Northern Ireland has been with (a) the Republic of Ireland and (b) Great Britain in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135862","135862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884875","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has received representations on the level of availability of interpreters willing to travel for judicial proceedings in Northern Ireland; and if he will take steps to ensure the provision of interpreters from England and Wales for such proceedings in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135863","135863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884876","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the £200 self-contribution that disabled students in higher education must make to access funding for computer equipment, if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of the British Assistive Technology Association’s suggestion that the contribution is reviewed and students are able to have that charge added to their student loan.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135864","135864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884877","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the £200 self-contribution that disabled students in higher education must make to access funding for computer equipment, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of that charge on the ability of disabled students to (a) access essential equipment and (b) continue with their education.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135865","135865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884878","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the repayment of advances is included in the 40 per cent cap on what can be deducted from universal credit claimants’ monthly awards.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135866","135866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884879","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether there is a requirement on the part of decision-makers to take into account a claimant's wider financial situation when deductions and recoveries are taken from universal credit claimants in part 4 of their monthly award letter.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135867","135867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884880","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) evidence is required to be produced by decision-makers and (b) claimant consent is required in determining that it is in a universal credit claimant’s best interest that more than 40 per cent of a claimants' standard allowance should be taken in repayments.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135868","135868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884881","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discretion is available to decision-maker if a claimant of universal credit reports that (a) deductions and (b) recoveries are causing financial detriment.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135869","135869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884882","2018-04-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of theatres that have closed in the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135870","135870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884883","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that social media companies are complying fully with the Data Protection Act 1998 and associated General Data Protection Regulations.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135871","135871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884884","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people who use online platforms are aware of the nature and volume of their data that is retained by the companies responsible for those platforms as a result of that use.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135872","135872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884885","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department will review Approved Document B as a result of his Department's findings, Analysis of fires in buildings of timber framed construction, England, 2009-10 to 2011-12, published in December 2012 which states that fires in timber frame constructions are more extensive than fires in other forms of construction; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135873","135873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884886","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for the implementation of planned changes to pay Pension Credit to the youngest member of a couple rather than the youngest.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135874","135874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884887","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 129958, what information his Department holds on the qualification levels held by children's residential care staff in England.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135875","135875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884888","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to review tax rates applicable to the telecommunications industry for SMEs investing in broadband fibre.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135876","135876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884889","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC has made an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a reliable mechanism which (a) makes clear the whereabouts of important documentation relating to tax credit claims, (b) acknowledges the submission of online renewals and (c) does not suspend payments until it can be proved that claimants have received and then failed to respond appropriately to the necessary paperwork.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135877","135877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884890","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's Serious Violence strategy policy paper published on 9 April 2018, from which of her Department's budgets will the funding announced for a Serious Violence strategy be allocated; and whether such allocation of funds will effect the budgets of other existing programmes led by her Department.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135878","135878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884891","2018-04-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support was given to families who infant feed with formula milk during the Thames Water water supply disruption in March; and what steps he is taking to improve the response to future water shortages.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135879","135879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884892","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people excluding those on student visas have been granted leave to remain in the UK with no recourse to public funds since 2010.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135880","135880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884893","2018-04-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to make an assessment of the potential merits of legislative proposals to remove prison sentences for the non-payment of council tax in line with other forms civil debt sentencing.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135881","135881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884894","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether there is a formal process in place for patients who receive Continuing Health Care funding to challenge a decision of Decision Support Tools that move them from funded health care into social care.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135882","135882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884895","2018-04-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress the Government has made on updating Consolidated Guidance on the use of torture.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135883","135883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884896","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on promoting the use of digital currencies; and what impact assessment has been carried out on the economic benefits of regulating that sector.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135884","135884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884897","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the availability of judicial legal remedies below High Court level for disabled people to challenge the under-occupancy penalty on the grounds of discrimination.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135885","135885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884898","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference the Written Statement of 15 March 2018, Employment and Support Allowance, HCWS 549, which external organisations her Department has been engaging with that provide support and advice to claimants in order to ensure that as many people as possible are aware of corrections that may be necessary as a result of underpayments that may have occurred due to how a proportion of Incapacity Benefit claims were transitioned to Employment and Support Allowance between 2011 and 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135886","135886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884899","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many applicants for NHS Continuing Healthcare died before a decision was made on their case by the relevant clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135887","135887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884900","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS Continuing Healthcare assessments have taken place after a claimant has died to establish whether that claimant's family or estate are entitled to claim that funding retrospectively.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135888","135888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884901","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on the plan for the trans-Pennine tunnel.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135889","135889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884902","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what advice the Sports Ground Safety Association provided to his Department on the  application by West Bromwich Albion to introduce a safe standing area at that club's stadium.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135890","135890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884903","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure the efficacy of capacity assessments for people with learning disabilities to look after a child.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135891","135891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884904","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the criteria are for capacity tests used for a person's suitability to look after a child; and what guidance his Department has issued on the use of that criteria.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135892","135892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884905","2018-04-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, (a) how many calls the ACAS helpline received and (b) what the budget was for ACAS Helpline Services in 2017-18.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135893","135893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884906","2018-04-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) Government funding, (b) annual spending and (c) total staff head count was for ACAS in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135894","135894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884907","2018-04-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) Government funding (b) annual spending and (c) total staff head count was for the Health and Safety Executive in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135895","135895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884908","2018-04-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many referrals were made to enforcement agencies from the ACAS helpline in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135896","135896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884909","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that plans to phase out of fossil fuel powered vehicles does not increase greenhouse gas emissions associated with the (a) manufacture and (b) distribution of new vehicles; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135897","135897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884910","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how the Government plans to ensure that the environmental effects of vehicle battery manufacture, use and disposal are minimised; and if he will he make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135898","135898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884911","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Government has to encourage manufacturers to recycle material recovered from fossil fuel powered vehicles to help develop (a) new and (b) existing industries; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135899","135899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884912","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that non-UK EU citizens are aware that they will need to apply for settled status if they wish to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135900","135900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884913","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to (a) write to all eligible non-UK EU citizens and (b) use advertising to inform such citizens that they must apply for settled status if they wish to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135901","135901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884914","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in the UK were born in Commonwealth countries and arrived in the UK before 1971.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135902","135902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884915","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of people who work in the NHS who were born in Commonwealth countries and arrived in the UK before 1971.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135903","135903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884916","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to establish a fast-track citizenship system for people who have lived in the UK for more than 40 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135904","135904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884917","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to provide free legal advice to Commonwealth citizens who have lived in the UK since before 1971 and who now may face deportation because of a lack of documentation.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135905","135905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884918","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the evidence cited by the Minister for Housing, the hon. Member for Esher and Walton in the Sunday Times article of 8 April 2018, that immigration has increased house prices.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135906","135906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884919","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans to fit vertical launch cruise missiles on (a) Type 26 and (b) Type 31 frigates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135907","135907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884920","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a module for vertical launch missiles is planned for inclusion as part of the specification for the Type 31 frigate.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135908","135908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884921","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the A38 between Plymouth and Exeter to be upgraded to Highway England’s Expressway standard.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135909","135909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884922","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that banks maintain records for longer than five years in response to possible legal actions on the mis-selling of (a) tailored business loans and (b) other financial products to small businesses.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135910","135910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884923","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential opportunities High Speed 2 provides to members of the UK railway supply chain to increase their international export profile.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135911","135911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884924","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of implementing a requirement that UK-based suppliers are formally considered in the procurement of all (a) systems and (b) sub-systems required for the delivery of High Speed 2 Phase 1.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135912","135912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884925","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to ensure there is (a) transparency, (b) fairness and (c) integrity in the work of the Financial Conduct Authority; and whether he plans to take any further steps to ensure those criteria are met.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135913","135913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884926","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the outcomes of the 2018 Plenary meeting of Intergovernmental Science-Policy Platform on Biodiversity and Ecosystem Services.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135914","135914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884927","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what arrangements he plans to make for continued co-operation with EU member states on international biodiversity issues after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135915","135915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884928","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what arrangements he plans to make for continued UK involvement in the EU Circular Economy programme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135916","135916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884929","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on campaigns to promote the cessation of smoking in (a) 2016-17 and (b)  2017-18; and what funding he plans to allocate to such campaigns in 2018-19.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135917","135917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884930","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set out total spending by NHS Commissioners on private health providers in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135918","135918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884931","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what total spending by NHS Commissioners was on private mental health treatment in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135919","135919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884932","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what total spending by NHS Commissioners was on private providers carrying out elective procedures in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135920","135920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884933","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS contracts were secured by private providers in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135921","135921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884934","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of NHS contracts were secured by (a) NHS, (b) private and (c) other providers in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135922","135922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884935","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what was the value of NHS contracts secured by Virgin Care in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135923","135923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884936","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospital trusts have merged in the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135924","135924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884937","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department has provided for research on tackling antibiotic-resistant bacteria in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135925","135925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884938","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the number of homeowners who have participated in the electric vehicle homecharge scheme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135926","135926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884939","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps he has taken to encourage more local authorities to take up electric car charge-point funding.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135927","135927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884940","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much gift aid was claimed by fundraising platforms through fees in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135928","135928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884941","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of trends in the use of electric and hybrid vehicles on the National Grid over the next ten years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135929","135929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884942","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many councils charge for collecting garden waste for recycling.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135930","135930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884943","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK citizens who have returned to the UK after living in territories claimed by ISIL have been stripped of their citizenship.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135931","135931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884944","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the performance assessments of Local Enterprise Partnerships.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135932","135932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884945","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers conducted street patrols in the (a) West Midlands and (b) Coventry in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135933","135933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884946","2018-04-19","Prime Minister","2018-04-16","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she plans to discuss the case of Jagtar Singh Johal  during her bilateral meeting with Narendra Modi, at the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135934","135934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884947","2018-04-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in drug-related deaths of prisoners in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135935","135935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884948","2018-04-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many fewer full-time (a) male and (b) female service personnel there were at the most recent date for which data is available compared with 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135936","135936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884949","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that student nurses do not experience hardship as a consequence of administrative errors in the provision of maintenance loans.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135937","135937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884950","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many vacant positions there are for (a) nurses and (b) doctors in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135938","135938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884951","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2017 to Question 111966, on Wakefield City Academies Trust, how many of the schools formerly within the Wakefield City Academies Trust have been placed with new trusts.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135939","135939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884952","2018-04-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases there have been in which people have been declared fit for work and then went on to win their appeal against her Department in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135940","135940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884953","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the schools formerly within the Academies Enterprise Trust and awaiting re-brokering have been placed with new trusts.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135941","135941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884954","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students have applied for the disabled student's allowance in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135942","135942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884955","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been paid out to disabled students allowances in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135943","135943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884956","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has plans to include provision for a tunnel under the widened section of the M1 south of Junction 25 to accommodate the restoration of the Derby and Sandiacre canal.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135944","135944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884957","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 135187, how much of the £26 million funding for school breakfast clubs will be allocated in the 2019-20 financial year.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135945","135945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884958","2018-04-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether staff at her Department have instructed local authorities to cease paying housing enefit to all residents in receipt of personal independence payments pending a review into all claims for such payments.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135946","135946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884959","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of bus drivers have undertaken disability awareness training.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135947","135947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884960","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure compliance with EU regulation 181/2011 by which disability awareness training for bus drivers has been a legal requirement since March 2018.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135948","135948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884961","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to report annually on the proportion of bus drivers that have undertaken disability awareness training.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135949","135949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884962","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has plans to allocate additional resources for the expansion of surface access to regional airports, including (a) Stansted and (b) Luton.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135950","135950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884963","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has he made of the effectiveness of the use of airport capacity at regional airports.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135951","135951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884964","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a national concessionary bus fare structure for 16-18 year olds.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135952","135952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884965","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what procedures are in place for Ministers to respond appropriately to correspondence from children and young people.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135953","135953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884966","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what procedures are in place for Ministers in all Government departments to respond to written Welsh correspondence in that language.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135954","135954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884967","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to Israeli counterparts in advance of the high court hearing on the demolition of school buildings in Khan al-Ahmar which is due to take place on 25 April 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135955","135955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884968","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Written Statement of 31 January 2018 on Police Funding, HCWS439, which refers to an increase in total investment in the police system of up to £450 million including £270 million from increases in the precept, for what reason the press release, entitled Serious Violence Strategy funding: rebuttals and clarifications, of 10 April 2018 refers to a comprehensive settlement that will increase police funding by £460 million for 2018-19 including £280 million drawn from increased precept contributions.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135956","135956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884969","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the press release of 9 April 2018, entitled Home Secretary launches serious violence strategy, which projects are to be allocated the £40 million of her Department's funding referred to; and how much each such project will receive.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135957","135957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884970","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133851, and with reference to the statement in the Defence Intelligence and Security Centre document dated 11 January 2012, published by the Digital, Culture, Media and Sport Committee on 28 March 2018, that SCL were cleared to routine access of UK secret information, whether (a) Cambridge Analytica and (b) SCL Group Limited or as formerly named Strategic Communication Laboratories Limited have, since 2010, had access to UK or international partners’ information classified as confidential or above; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135958","135958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884971","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2017 to Question 135188, on Social Mobility Commission: Public Appointments, which Minister is responsible for the process of appointing the Chair of the Social Mobility Commission.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135959","135959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884972","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his article in the Sunday Times on 15 April 2018, entitled Chemical weapons can never be tolerated, if he will publish the full risk assessment made of the risks posed to civilians of the destruction of the Him Shinshar site near Homs by British missiles.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135960","135960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884973","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the news article entitled Amber Rudd denies seeing leaked Home Office violent crime report, published by The Guardian on Monday 9 April 2018, whether (a) the Minister of State for Policing and the Fire Service (b) her special advisers and (c) special advisers to Ministers in her Department had seen the leaked report.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135961","135961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884974","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the news article entitled Amber Rudd denies seeing leaked Home Office violent crime report, published by the Guardian on Monday 9 April 2018, whether her private office viewed the leaked report mentioned in that article before publishing the Serious Violence Strategy.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135962","135962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884975","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the international community is taking to bring about further pressure on the Assad regime to allow humanitarian aid to reach civilians in areas either under his Government's control or which are theatres of ongoing conflict.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135963","135963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884976","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of cases involving domestic abuse in the family courts special protection measures were implemented in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135964","135964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884977","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of cases involving domestic abuse in the criminal courts special protection measures were implemented in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135965","135965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884978","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of cases involving domestic abuse in the family courts separate entrances and exits were utilised as a special protection measure in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135966","135966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884979","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of cases involving domestic abuse in the family courts video links were utilised as a special protection measure in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135967","135967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884980","2018-04-18","Department for International Development","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to (a) promote and (b) help meet the targets set for tackling global disability contained within the Sustainable Development Goals, 4, 8, 10, 100 and 17.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135968","135968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884981","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many and what proportion of inquests legal aid was granted in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135969","135969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884982","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of inquests into the death of military service personnel legal aid was granted for representation at the inquest or pre-inquest hearing in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135970","135970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884983","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,with reference to the news article entitled Amber Rudd denies seeing leaked Home Office violent crime report, published by the Guardian on Monday 9 April 2018, for what reason analysis produced by the Home Office on the effect of the reduction in police resources on serious violence was omitted from the Serious Violence Strategy.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135971","135971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884984","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of inquests into a death in custody or in the course of arrest legal aid was granted for representation at the inquest or pre-inquest hearing in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135972","135972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884985","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of inquests involving public bodies legal aid was granted for representation at the inquest or pre-inquest hearing in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135973","135973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884986","2018-04-19","Department for International Development","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether measures to meet the Sustainable Development Goals on global disability are planned for discussion during the 2018 Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in London.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135974","135974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884987","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has made representations to Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman and the Government of Saudi Arabia on the bombing of an Internally Displaced Person Camp in Hodeidah, Yemen, on 3 April 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135975","135975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884988","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made representations for an independent investigation as called for by the UN Secretary General into the shooting of Palestinian protestors in Gaza by Israeli forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135976","135976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884989","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the total sleep-in back pay liability for providers in (a) North Wiltshire constituency and (b) Wiltshire County Council.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135977","135977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884990","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the criteria are for the assessment of applications to use the data compiled by the Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135978","135978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884991","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the criteria used to assess applications for the use of Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey data differs from (a) other mental health-related datasets and (b) other physical health-related datasets in the UK Data archive.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135979","135979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884992","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many applications to use the Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey data have been (a) submitted and (b) granted.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135980","135980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884993","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the Roads to Zero strategy.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135981","135981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884994","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Zero Emissions Vehicle Summit announced by the Prime Minister in December 2017 is planned to be held.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135982","135982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884995","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on the (a) procurement and (b) design of LED street lighting.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135983","135983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884996","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who arrived in the UK from Commonwealth Countries before 1971 have been deported, removed, or left the country through the Assisted Voluntary Departure Service.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135984","135984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884997","2018-04-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish any Government reports that assess the suitability of safe standing in the Scottish Premier League.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135985","135985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884998","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to extend to the annuity market the freedom that people have to access their pensions.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135986","135986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/884999","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to help enable people with annuities to access liquidity from their products as a result of changes to their financial circumstances.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135987","135987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885000","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings Ministers or officials of his Department have had with pharmaceutical companies at which medical cannabis was discussed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135988","135988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885001","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many self-assessment tax payers have been audited by HMRC in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135989","135989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885002","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many self-assessment tax payers have been fined by HMRC for under-reporting in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135990","135990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885003","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people have died within (a) six months, (b) one year, (c) two years and (d) more than two years after they were issued with a DS1500.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135991","135991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885004","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's policy is on encouraging working class students to attend university.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135992","135992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885005","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to take steps to (a) introduce and (b) support courses to improve computer literacy.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135993","135993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885006","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has plans to issue body worn video cameras to all (a) police officers and (b) detectives.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135994","135994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885008","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are registered self-employed.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135996","135996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885009","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are receiving the state pension in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135997","135997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885010","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has a policy on supporting food manufacturers to sell their produce abroad.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135998","135998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885011","2018-04-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will assess the effectiveness of (a) protections in law for workers from penalisation for whistle-blowing and (b) incentives to ensure that workers are not dissuaded from raising matters of improper conduct relating to their place of work.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135999","135999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885012","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2018 to Question 121792, on Immigrants: Commonwealth, if she will publish the number of Commonwealth citizens legally residing in the UK who have been (a) deported and (b) detained in error by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136000","136000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885013","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce the successful bidder for the new Southeastern franchise.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136001","136001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885014","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women are still held in prison on indeterminate public protection sentences by (a) offence and (b) original length of sentence.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136002","136002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885015","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans are in place to support women and men on indeterminate public protection sentences in meeting the requirements for their release.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136003","136003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885016","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Ghana and (b) the US Administration on the Ghana - US Military Cooperation Agreement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136004","136004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885017","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women sentenced to Imprisonment for Public Protection have been recalled since their release.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136005","136005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885018","2018-04-19","Department for International Trade","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will list the (a) meetings and discussions (i) Ministers and (ii) officials in his Department have had with the Legatum Institute and (b) outcomes of those discussions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136006","136006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885019","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fake pet passports were (a) identified and (b) removed from circulation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136007","136007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885020","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what security features have been built into pet passports to prevent fake passports from being used to bring animals into the UK.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136008","136008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885021","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the security features contained within pet passports.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136009","136009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885022","2018-04-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what training is provided to carrier staff, Pet Travel Scheme (PETS) staff and Animal and Plant Health Agency staff to ensure that they are able to identify fake pet passports used for animals travelling under the PETS.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136010","136010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885023","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of incorporating water safety and drowning prevention into the national curriculum.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136011","136011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885024","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many water related fatalities there were in (a) the North East and (b) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136012","136012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885025","2018-04-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 128419, on the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012, on what date the post-implementation review is planned to be completed; and what the reasons are for the review not meeting its original timetable.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136013","136013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885026","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2018 to Question 132681, on Youth Social Action Review, whether the Minister of Sport and Civil Society has met with the Chair of the Independent review of full-time social action since that report's publication.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136014","136014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885027","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timetable is for the review of the Financial Ombudsman Service to begin.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136015","136015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885028","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who will chair the independent review of the Financial Service Ombudsman; and what steps he plans to take to ensure the independence of the Chair of that review.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136016","136016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885029","2018-04-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133509, on Social Security Benefits: Medical Examinations, how many assessment reports the Department has deemed unacceptable and returned to (a) Independent Assessment Services and (b) Centre for Health and Disability Assessments for reworking in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136017","136017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885030","2018-04-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many health assessment reports her Department has received from the (a) Independent Assessment Services and (b) Centre for Health and Disability Assessments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136018","136018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885031","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the scope is of the independent review into the Financial Ombudsman Service.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136019","136019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885032","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timetable is for the independent review of the Financial Service Ombudsman to report.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136020","136020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885033","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to withdraw the pre-qualification questionnaire passport from Virgin Trains.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136021","136021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885034","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that train operating companies comply with consumer data legislation.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136022","136022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885035","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the profit accrued by train operating companies from schedule 8 payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136023","136023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885036","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) set-up and (b) running costs were for the Government's (i) twitter account @youdecide2014, (ii) website www.youdecide2014.uk, (iii) facebook page @youdecide2014 and (iv) Buzzfeed user YouDecide2014.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136024","136024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885037","2018-04-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to Joint Service Publication 464 Section IX,  what discussions he has had with CarillionAmey on service family accommodation complaints procedure.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136025","136025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885038","2018-04-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent meetings her Department has had with (a) football fan groups, (b) representatives of Premier League football clubs, (c) representatives of English Football League clubs, (d) the Football Association, Scottish Football Association and Football Association of Wales and (e) Celtic Football Club on safe standing in football grounds.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136026","136026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885039","2018-04-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, by what date he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Rochdale dated 26 February 2018 on songbirds in Cyprus, reference number IW/0029.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136027","136027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885040","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were billed by the NHS each year on the grounds of non-UK citizenship in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136028","136028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885041","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment the Government made prior to the introduction of the hostile environment immigration policy of that policy's potential effect on Commonwealth migrants who have been long-term residents of the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136029","136029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885042","2018-04-19","Wales Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 135100 on Ports: Wales, whether the (a) Government (b) Welsh Government and (c) Port Authorities will provide funding for the additional infrastructure required at Welsh ports as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136030","136030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885043","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of response times to 999 calls in (a) Lincoln, (b) Lincolnshire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136031","136031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885044","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the pay offer to NHS nurses includes public health nurses employed by local authorities.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136032","136032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885045","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the transparency of publicly-funded medical research and development.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136033","136033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885046","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the (a) pay and (b) terms and conditions of public health nurses employed by local authorities will remain comparable to nurses working directly for the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136034","136034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885047","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether public health nurses employed directly by local authorities will be included in the local government pay award; and whether those nurses will receive pay rises comparable to nurses in the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136035","136035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885048","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that medicines developed from public research are (a) accessible and (b) affordable.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136036","136036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885049","2018-04-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for free and fair elections in Malaysia of the re-drawing of parliamentary constituency boundaries in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136037","136037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885050","2018-04-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will (a) prohibit the removal by departmental officials of documents from a person's universal credit journal and (b) ensure that in cases of official error the journal record is amended through the addition of a revising letter.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136038","136038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885051","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the clarity of Government guidance for private companies on the charging of VAT on loans.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136039","136039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885052","2018-04-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on freedom of speech and expression in Malaysia of the Anti-Fake News Bill recently passed by the Malaysian Parliament.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136040","136040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885053","2018-04-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications of provisions in the Anti-Fake News Bill recently passed by the Malaysian Parliament, which apply to reporting by foreign media organisations, for the ability of the BBC World Service to operate freely in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136041","136041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885054","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many individual patient funding requests have been approved for the use of Kuvan.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136042","136042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885055","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ensure that funding is provided for the training and recruitment of chronic urinary tract infection specialists in the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136043","136043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885056","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the progress of investigations by UK authorities into financial crimes related to the 1MDB fund in Malaysia; what requests for information have been made to the Malaysian authorities during the course of those investigations; and what responses have been received to such requests.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136044","136044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885057","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received on the reopening to new patients of the Lower Urinary Tract Services Clinic in north London.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136045","136045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885058","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the annual cost to the NHS of treating chronic urinary tract infections.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136046","136046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885059","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Indian counterpart on recent protests against the ruling of that country’s Supreme Court on the Scheduled Castes and Scheduled Tribes Act of 1989 dated 20 March 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136047","136047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885060","2018-04-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Indian Supreme Court’s ruling of 20 March 2018 on the Scheduled Castes and Scheduled Tribes Act of 1989 on (a) levels of caste-based discrimination and violence in India and (b) the ability of any victims of such discriminatory or violent acts to seek legal redress in that country’s courts.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136048","136048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885061","2018-04-18","Department for International Trade","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress he plans to make on increasing food and drink exports to India in advance of the next India-UK Joint Economic and Trade Committee.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136049","136049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885062","2018-04-18","Department for International Trade","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a business-led Joint Working Group on Food and Drink as part of the India-UK Joint Trade Review.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136050","136050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885063","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to appoint the independent chair of the review into the Teaching Excellence Framework.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136051","136051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885064","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Minister of State for Apprenticeships and Skills has held meetings with the panel of apprentices that reports to the Board of the Institute for Apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136052","136052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885065","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications his Department received for the Panel of Apprentices in 2017-18.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136053","136053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885066","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to allocated funding for the UK's participation in the European Apprentice Network after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136054","136054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885067","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which companies are responsible for train maintenance on the West Coast Main Line; and by whom those companies are owned.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136055","136055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885068","2018-04-19","Home Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her article in The Daily Telegraph of 7 April 2018, we are determined to tackle violent crime, and there are enough officers on the streets to do so, if she will publish the statistical data on which the levels of knife crime were cited.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136056","136056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885069","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding his Department has provided to trusts that are taking over schools from the Wakefield City Academy Trust.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136057","136057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885070","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to encourage NHS England to develop specialist services for Lyme disease patients.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136058","136058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885071","2018-04-19","Cabinet Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many apprentices his Department directly employs; and how many of this apprentices have been placed within each group in his Department.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136059","136059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885072","2018-04-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in February 2016, what progress his Department has made in implementing recommendation 24.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136060","136060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885073","2018-04-19","Treasury","2018-04-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in February 2016, what progress his Department has made in implementing recommendation 10.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136061","136061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885074","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in February 2016, what progress his Department has made in implementing recommendations 26, 28, and 29.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136062","136062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885075","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department is making on fully automating delay repay procedures for rail passengers using smartcards.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136063","136063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885076","2018-04-19","Department for Transport","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the business case presented to his Department by Shropshire Council for funding of the NW Relief Road for Shrewsbury.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136064","136064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885077","2018-04-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he decided to seek legal authority through secondary legislation to amend retrospectively the Local Government and Public Involvement in Health Act 2007 in respect of proposals for single tier local government; and what consultation was carried out prior to the publication of the draft Regulations.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136065","136065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885078","2018-04-19","Department for Education","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government plans to take to reduce the need for schools to pay for the advertising of school staff vacancies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136066","136066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885079","2018-04-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library a copy of the notes of the meeting held between officials of his Department and Section 151 Officers from Dorset Councils in June 2016 when the 20-year harmonisation period was discussed.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136067","136067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885080","2018-04-19","Leader of the House","2018-04-16","To ask the Leader of the House, what the policy of the Government is on the use of secondary legislation to amend primary legislation with retrospective effect; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136068","136068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885081","2018-04-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance he has issued to Dorset Councils under the provisions of Section 3(5)(b) of the Local Government and Public Involvement in Health Act 2007 on what a proposal for single tier local government in Dorset should seek to achieve and the matters to be taken into account.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136069","136069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885082","2018-04-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the relevance and usefulness of the advice provided to UK citizens travelling to Cameroon by his Department.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136070","136070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882144","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether a business which did not use her Department's employer checking service when requested by a job applicant would be in breach of Home Office rules on recruitment and selection.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135202","135202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882145","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Civil Aviation Authority will publish its report on its investigation on allocated airline seating.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135204","135204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882146","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Southeastern rail franchise operates a daily cap on delay repay claims.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135205","135205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882147","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will instruct Highways England to carry out a survey of the drainage pipes buried in the verges of the M6 where it runs close to Galgate.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135206","135206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882148","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Questions 134201, 134202 and 134203, on Prisoners: Hepatitis, if he will publish the Health and Justice Indicators of Performance data for the number of prisoners by prison that have (a) been tested for hepatitis C, (b) been diagnosed with hepatitis C and (c) received treatment for hepatitis C.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135207","135207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882149","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Questions 134202 and 134203, on Prisoners: Hepatitis, for what reason 48 per cent of prisoners diagnosed with hepatitis C in the first quarter of 2017-18 have yet to be referred to specialist care to have their infection treated.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135208","135208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882150","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS spends on mental health services in England; and what proportion of that amount is spent on community eating disorder services for adults.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135209","135209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882151","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to strengthen the evidence base of open access youth work and non-formal learning opportunities for young people.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135210","135210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882152","2018-04-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to select a person to review the operation of sections 6 to 11 of the Justice and Security Act 2013; and what the timetable is for that appointment to be announced.","Biography information for Mr Kenneth Clarke","Mr Kenneth Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135211","135211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882153","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the use of personal fitness trackers on the prevention of cardio-vascular conditions.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135212","135212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882154","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that clinical commissioning groups provide access to medical nutrition for all patients in their area for whom it is recommended by clinical guidelines.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135213","135213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882155","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable for negotiations on the new pharmaceutical price regulation scheme is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135214","135214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882156","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations her Department has received on the effect of Progress 8 on schools in white working class areas with high levels of deprivation.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135215","135215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882157","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to amend the methodology for Progress 8 to take account of its effect in schools in white working class areas with high levels of deprivation.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135216","135216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882158","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people aged under 18 years of age who were convicted of drug offences outside their local area were also found to be carrying weapons.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135217","135217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882159","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of integrating nutrition and hydration into clinical pathways for patients.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135218","135218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882160","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential savings to the public purse from the integration of nutrition and hydration into clinical pathways.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135219","135219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882161","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC shares information on the amendment of tax returns or other taxation errors of non-UK citizens with UK Visas and Immigration.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135220","135220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882162","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of wearable health monitoring devices to preventative health care.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135221","135221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882163","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help local councils improve support for carers in (a) Brigg and Goole constituency and (b) rural communities.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135222","135222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882164","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of adults who do not have (a) basic, (b) intermediate and (c) advanced digital literacy.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135203","135203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882165","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what improvement plan agreements the Government has made with Interserve since that company's profit warning in September 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135279","135279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882166","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter of 26 September 2017 from the hon. Member for Poplar and Limehouse on the case of Mrs Justina Ugisomi Saliu, the wife of Mr John Pattison.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135280","135280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882167","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of hours worked by officials of his Department on assessing and dealing with the effects of Carillion entering liquidation and the transfer of Government contracts formerly held by that company.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135281","135281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882168","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2018 to Question 132514, if he will publish the monthly scorecards for each prison in which Amey is responsible for maintenance since such scorecards were first recorded.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135282","135282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882169","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to (a) designate hedgehogs as a protected species and (b) ensure that planning guidance takes into account the need to preserve hedgehog habitats.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135283","135283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882170","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of unlicensed charity bag collections.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135284","135284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882171","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what meetings he has had with representatives of blood cancer patients to discuss the availability of treatment options on the NHS for patients diagnosed with relapsed acute lymphoblastic leukaemia.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135285","135285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882172","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of treatment options for patients with relapsed acute lymphoblastic leukaemia in the (a) UK and (b) EU countries.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135286","135286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882173","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has conducted an assessment of the (a) performance and (b) effectiveness of the national modern slavery helpline.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135287","135287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882174","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of (a) the accuracy of NICE's calculation of the wider value of (i) rare disease and (ii) rarer cancer treatments and (b) the extent to which NICE accounts in that calculation for (A) additional medical benefits, (B) wider economic consequences and (C) social impact costs.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135288","135288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882175","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 119731 on Pneumoccocol Diseases: Vaccination, whether NHS England is responsible for funding the vaccination of adults who have undergone stem cell transplantation under paragraph 4.2 of the NHS public health functions agreement 2017-18: Service specification no.8 Pneumococcal immunisation programme.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135289","135289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882176","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 134095 on Department for Transport: Hedgehogs, what steps he is taking as species champion for the native hedgehog to make hedgehogs a protected species.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135290","135290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882177","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the charity sector on reducing the use of single-use plastic bags in door-to-door collections.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135291","135291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882178","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department holds on the number of people aged under 18 years of age convicted for drug related offences outside the local authority area where they live.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135292","135292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882179","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for the National County Lines Co-ordination Centre to be fully operational.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135293","135293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882180","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 132826 on Nuclear Power: Consultants, if he will set out (a) the title of each report that he plans to publish and the timetable for doing so and (b) the title of each report that he does not plan to publish and in each case the reasons why.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135294","135294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882181","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military airstrikes were carried out by the RAF in Syria in ach month between March 2017 and March 2018.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135295","135295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882182","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress had been made on the Multi Role Vehicle (Protected) Group (a) 1 and (b) 2 contracts.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135296","135296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882183","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received representations from (a) hon. Members, (b) NGOs or (c) members of the public on the protection of the Sami community in Scandinavia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135254","135254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882184","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had any discusisons with his Norwegian, Finnish or Swedish counterparts on the welfare of the Sami people and the protection of their culture.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135255","135255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882185","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information the Government holds on the proportion of UK businesses that (a) own their own premises and (b) rent their premises.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135256","135256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882186","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of removing from business rates (a) new investment in plant and machinery and (b) all plant and machinery.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135257","135257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882187","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people who have ten year personal independence awards have had a planned intervention in advance of the original end date of their claim in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135258","135258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882188","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter of 28 March 2018 from the hon. Member for Croydon North a visa enquiry on behalf of a constituent.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135259","135259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882189","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons personal independence payment claimants who undergo reviews 12 months in advance of their award ending have their payments stopped immediately should they fail those reviews.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135260","135260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882190","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Written Ministerial Statement of 25 January 2018 on energy policy, HCWS428, if he will ask the Infrastructure and Projects Authority to assess the financial resilience of Cuadrilla Resources Ltd, including its ability to fund decommissioning costs, as part of the Government's consideration of that company's application for consent to fracture its first horizontal well at Preston New Road, Lancashire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135261","135261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882191","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of eating disorder specialists in the area of adult eating disorder treatment and care.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135262","135262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882192","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of patients living with HIV who (a) were offered and (b) received an annual health assessment for cardiovascular disease, renal impairment, diabetes and bone health in each NHS England region in the last year for which figures are available; and what plans he has to ensure that all people living with HIV (i) are offered and (ii) attend an annual health assessment to manage co-morbidities.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135263","135263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882193","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of recording the time of birth on birth certificates; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135264","135264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882194","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many local authorities applied for the modern slavery pilot scheme; and how were successful applicants selected.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135265","135265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882195","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of visits to the Universal Credit website result in claimants successfully accessing the service following the (a) creation and (b) re-use of a verified account.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135266","135266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882196","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the campaign being run in schools by ITV and INEOS to promote the Daily Mile required the approval of his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135267","135267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882197","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of children under the age of 18 who are living in the London Borough of Lewisham and have undergone female genital mutilation (a) in the UK and (b) abroad in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135268","135268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882198","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of children under the age of 18 who are living in the London Borough of Lewisham who have been subjected to a forced marriage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135269","135269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882199","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average net weekly household income was for people in (a) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (b) London, (c) England, and (d) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135270","135270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882200","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils (a) attained and (b) exceeded the minimum standard for reading at (i) key stage 1 and (ii) key stage 2 in Lewisham, Deptford constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135271","135271"
