"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173385","2015-01-16","Department for Education","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children of what ages went missing from care in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220561","220561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173386","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on making defibrillators available to all schools at a reduced price.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220531","220531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173387","2015-01-16","Department for Education","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools opened a new sixth form in the last four years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220526","220526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173388","2015-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Written Statement HCWS183 of 13 January 2015, on Nuclear Decommissioning Authority, what estimate he has made of the costs to the public purse of the removal of Nuclear Management Partners as the management of Sellafield and their replacement with a new management structure; and whether these costs will be paid from his Department's budget.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220614","220614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173389","2015-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Written Statement HCWS183 of 13 January 2015, on Nuclear Decommissioning Authority, if he will appoint representatives of non-governmental organisations to the board of the Site Licence Company for Sellafield.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220615","220615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173390","2015-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans he has to update the Electricity Market Reform Delivery Plan projection of 2.4-4GWp of large-scale solar photovoltaic capacity by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220653","220653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173391","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make funds available to Community Impact Bucks for 2015-16 and 2016-17 to replace the funding that has been withdrawn from Action with Communities in Rural England from March 2015.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220538","220538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173392","2015-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what responsibilities and obligations were inherited by the Environment Agency from predecessor bodies for the maintenance of particular flood defences in Lancaster and Fleetwood; and whether those responsibilities and obligations remain in place.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220549","220549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173393","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to publish a consultation document for the 2015 review of the Greyhound Regulations (England) 2010.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220577","220577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173394","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what groups and organisations she plans to consult in the 2015 review of the Greyhound Regulations (England) 2010.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220578","220578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173395","2015-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to announce whether Natural England's Variation Orders of 2012 extending the boundaries of the Lake District and Yorkshire Dales national parks will be confirmed.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220639","220639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173396","2015-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with landowners concerning measures to improve the habitat of the grey partridge.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220590","220590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173397","2015-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to stop the spread of Pacific oysters; and what discussions she has had with the (a) Northern Ireland Executive and (b) other devolved administrations on that matter.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220589","220589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173398","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to encourage the consolidation of developments in religious freedom in Turkey.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220606","220606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173399","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote freedom of religion internationally.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220566","220566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173400","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage an end to clashes between Indian and Pakistani troops in Kashmir.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220570","220570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173401","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the South Korean authorities about (a) North Korean progress towards viable nuclear weapons and (b) protecting UK companies from North Korean hacking.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220567","220567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173402","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise at the UN the recent killings by Boko Haram in Baga and surrounding villages in Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220541","220541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173403","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on reports made to the UN by Morocco as required of an administering power of Western Sahara.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220646","220646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173404","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's obligations are as a guarantor of the 1960 Treaty of Guarantee in relation to Cyprus.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220624","220624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173405","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Nigerian authorities about the promotion of (a) reintegration into society of and (b) other support for victims of Boko Haram in Nigeria.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220609","220609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173406","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to encourage better protection of religious minorities in Egypt.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220608","220608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173407","2015-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many incidents caused by Boko Haram in Nigeria involved British citizens in the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220630","220630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173408","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if in the Government's role as a guarantor of the 1960 Treaty in relation to Cyprus he will make representations to the UN facilitated process for a comprehensive settlement on the confiscation of property owned by Turkish  Cypriots in Vasiliko in order to facilitate oil and gas exploitation in Northern and Southern Cyprus.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220625","220625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173409","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of deaths caused by infection with HIV or hepatitis C through exposure to contaminated blood and blood products.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220665","220665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173410","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual (a) salary and (b) pension contribution is of the Chief Executive of the NHS Trust Development Agency; what performance-related measures the salary package for that post includes; and what steps his Department takes to monitor the performance of that Chief Executive.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220636","220636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173411","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has received any adverse notifications from the Penrose Inquiry relating to people in Scotland infected with hepatitis C and HIV acquired from exposure to contaminated blood and blood products.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220642","220642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173412","2015-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to his written statement HCWS183 of 13 January 2015, on Nuclear Decommissioning Authority, what plans he has to involve the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's national stakeholder forum and the Sellafield site stakeholder committee in the transition to the new management arrangements for Sellafield.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220616","220616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173413","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2014 to Question 220083, on breast cancer: drugs, when he expects the roundtable event his Department is planning to take place; and whether NICE's report on its feedback will be published after that event.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220660","220660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173414","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on the long-term use of locum consultants to run dermatology services in England.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220539","220539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173415","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many antibiotics were prescribed by out-of-hours dentists in each quarter of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220536","220536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173416","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many consultant dermatologists with (a) permanent contracts, (b) agency contracts and (c) other contractual or financial arrangements worked in the NHS on 13 January 2015.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220537","220537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173417","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include affective disorders in prescribed specialist services.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220530","220530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173418","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what target NHS Property Services had for revenue raising in each year since it was established; and how much revenue it raised in each such year.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220525","220525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173419","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what requirements there are on members of the Committee on Safety of Medicines to declare relevant interests.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220533","220533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173420","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has for NHS Blood and Transplant to extend the collection of ethnic origin data to all sources of organ donation registration.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220527","220527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173421","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to sustain Kidney Research UK's Peer Education Programme in Birmingham once the funding from his Department ends.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220528","220528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173422","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will remove Circle UK from his list of preferred partners to run NHS trusts.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220517","220517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173423","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many consultant dermatologist training posts have been funded in each financial year since 2010; and what assessment he has made of the sufficiency of that number.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220562","220562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173424","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vacant consultant dermatologist posts there were in the NHS on 13 January 2015.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220553","220553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173425","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress he has made in preventing the Ebola virus spreading in the UK.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220593","220593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173426","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will have discussions with NICE on the future availability in the NHS of the cancer drugs (a) Eribulin, (b) Avastin, (c) Kadcyla, (d) Afinitor, (e) Tykerb and (f) Perjeta; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220587","220587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173427","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is adequate public consultation and discussion before a decision is taken by Parliament on permitting mitochondrial transfer.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220591","220591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173428","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to introduce a statutory requirement for care providers to publish an annual report on their internal complaints procedures.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220638","220638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173429","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals to make it a statutory requirement for care providers to make clients aware of the Local Government Ombudsman complaints procedure.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220637","220637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173430","2015-01-15","Cabinet Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of citizens of EU member states in Eastern Europe who are resident in the UK.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220596","220596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173431","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people not holding UK passports of what (a) nationality and (b) age entered Northern Ireland through the land border with the Republic of Ireland in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220569","220569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173432","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to prevent irregularities in illegal immigration to the UK across the land border with Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220568","220568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173433","2015-01-16","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidelines her Department provides for timescales for completing a disclosure and barring check.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220573","220573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173434","2015-01-16","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance is provided to police forces on timescales for responses to referrals from the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220574","220574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173435","2015-01-16","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to help the Northern Ireland Executive and the Police Service of Northern Ireland to tackle drug smuggling in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220523","220523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173436","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement of 26 June 2014, Official Report, column 35W, on potential miscarriages of justice, what progress Mark Ellison has made in his review; and how many cases have been referred to the Criminal Cases Review Commission for its consideration of whether cases should be referred to the appellate courts.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220515","220515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173437","2015-01-16","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to encourage local authorities to participate in the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220662","220662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173438","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the additional costs incurred by her Department in connection with policing Black Friday.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220654","220654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173439","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information she holds on the reasons why the Independent Police Complaints Commission has not published its report on the actions of South Yorkshire Police at Orgreave coke works in 1984.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220601","220601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173440","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will request the Independent Police Complaints Commission announces when it plans to report on its investigations into the actions of the South Yorkshire Police at Orgreave coke works in 1984.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220600","220600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173441","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the value is of assets on her Department's balance sheets as a result of the use of returnable capital.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220627","220627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173442","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what budget her Department allocated to the CDC Group in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13, (e) 2013-14, (f) 2014-15 and (g) 2015-16 respectively.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220613","220613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173443","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the £1.8 billion allocated by her Department to economic development programmes has been spent to date.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220652","220652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173444","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the £1.8 billion allocated by her Department for economic development programmes is expected to be non-fiscal expenditure; and what the purposes of that expenditure will be.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220651","220651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173445","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who will represent the (a) UK and (b) EU at each of the international meetings in 2015 that will work on the post-2015 Sustainable Development Goals process.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220550","220550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173446","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the European Commission will be responsible for negotiating the post-2015 Sustainable Development Goals on behalf of Member States.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220552","220552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173447","2015-01-16","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the composition of the EU negotiation team for the post-2015 Sustainable Development Goals will be; and how many UK representatives at each level of seniority will be permanently appointed to that team.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220551","220551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173448","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much has been returned of the amount her Department invested into projects with predicted returns in the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220617","220617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173449","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much money her Department has allocated to each of the pillars of the strategic framework for economic development.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220620","220620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173450","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will update her Department's Development Tracker so it is possible to filter projects by economic development.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220621","220621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173451","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, by how much her Department has reduced public sector net borrowing as a result of its increased use of returnable funds.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220619","220619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173452","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether all projects and spending from the funds earmarked in the strategic framework for economic development has been added to her Department's Development Tracker.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220618","220618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173453","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much from her Department's budget planned for the strategic framework for economic development has been paid to commercial companies.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220623","220623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173454","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoner claims for damage for possessions or injury sustained during acts of concerted indiscipline were settled in each year since 2010; what the total value of those claims was in each such year; what the largest single amount paid to a prisoner under such a claim was in each such year; and to what type of incident each of those payments related.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220585","220585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173455","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff claims relating to assaults by prisoners were settled in each year since 2010; what the total value of those claims was in each such year; and what the largest single amount paid to a staff member under such a claim was in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220584","220584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173456","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoner claims relating to assaults by fellow prisoners were settled in each year since 2010; what the total value of those claims was; and what the largest single amount paid to a prisoner under such a claim was in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220582","220582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173457","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoner claims relating to assaults by staff were in each year since 2010; what the total value of those claims was in each such year; and what the largest single amount paid to a prisoner under such a claim was in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220583","220583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173458","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are unlawfully at large having escaped since June 2010 from escorts conducted under the Prison Escort and Custody Services contract where the prisoner had not previously been received into NOMS' custody; and of what offence those prisoners had been convicted or charged.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220581","220581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173459","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions for racially or religiously aggravated offences there were in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220512","220512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173460","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answers of 12 January 2015 to Questions 220031 and 220032 on shared services staff in Newport, which departments have signed up to the arrangement.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220540","220540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173461","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals are in UK (a) young offender institutions and (b) secure children's homes.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220661","220661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173462","2015-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the naming of specific companies in the Criminal Justice (Electronic Monitoring) (Responsible Person) Order 2014 is legal under EU competition law.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220670","220670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173463","2015-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of changes to the budget of the Police Service of Northern Ireland on frontline policing.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220520","220520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173464","2015-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to help the Northern Ireland Executive and the Police Service of Northern Ireland to tackle drug smuggling in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220524","220524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173465","2015-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when and where she last met the Chief Executive of Invest NI.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220522","220522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173466","2015-01-16","Prime Minister","2015-01-13","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to his Answer to Question 68 of his evidence to the Liaison Committee on 16 December 2014, HC 887, whether Ministers have reported back on any failure to implement any of the 25 recommendations of the Extremism Taskforce.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220659","220659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173467","2015-01-16","Prime Minister","2015-01-13","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to Answer of 9 January 2015 to Question 219820, for what reason that Answer refers to a section of a transcript which does not name the Minister responsible for each of the 25 recommendations of the Extremism Taskforce.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220658","220658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173468","2015-01-16","Home Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the fifth bullet point of paragraph 301 of the Report of the Task Force on Tackling Radicalisation and Extremism, published in December 2013, how many people have been excluded since that recommendation was made.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220655","220655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173469","2015-01-16","Prime Minister","2015-01-13","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to Answer of 9 January 2015 to Question 219820, for what reasons his Answer refers to a section of a transcript which does not contain the 25 recommendations made by the Extremism Taskforce; and how many of these recommendations have been fully implemented.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220656","220656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173470","2015-01-16","Prime Minister","2015-01-13","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to Answer of 9 January 2015 to Question 219820, for what reason that Answer refers to a section of a transcript which does not name the Minister responsible across Government for overseeing the implementation of the Extremism Taskforce.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220657","220657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173471","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the reduction in journey time from Rochester to London that will result from the new station in Rochester and the improvements to signalling on that route being undertaken by Network Rail.","Biography information for Mark Reckless","Mark Reckless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220626","220626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173472","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reports he has received on the incident involving the nuclear materials transport ship Parida that ran into difficulties between Scrabster and Antwerp in early October 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220603","220603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173473","2015-01-16","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what personnel or aircraft support the Government has recently provided following the disappearance of Malaysia Airlines flight MH17 on 17 July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220519","220519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173474","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2015 to Question 219323, how many hectares of land as mapped in the High Speed 2 Phase One environment statement have been allocated for (a) woodland, (b) wetland and (c) grass and habitat creation.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220563","220563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173475","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the A63 Castle Street Improvement Scheme.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220564","220564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173476","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to contact the families of the seafarers serving on the bulk carrier Cemfjord; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220543","220543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173477","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with representatives of the (a) Cyprus ship registery, (b) ship management company and (c) ship owner on the sinking of the Cemfjord in the Pentland Firth on 3 January 2015.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220546","220546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173478","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the Marine Accident Investigation Branch to produce initial findings from its investigation into the causes of the sinking of the bulk carrier Cemfjord in the Pentland Firth on 3 January 2015.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220544","220544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173479","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how the (a) Northern Lighthouse Board and (b) Maritime and Coastguard Agency responded to the sinking of the Cemfjord in the Pentland Firth on 3 January 2015.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220545","220545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173480","2015-01-16","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the results of the most recent mobile telephone usage survey will be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220576","220576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173481","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what arrangements are in place for the rescue of ships carrying nuclear materials from British ports that run into operational difficulties off the coast of the UK; and whether any ports are designated safe havens for such vessels.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220604","220604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173482","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his policy completely to abolish air passenger duty.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220598","220598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173483","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the emergency tug provision in the UK for lending assistance to ships carrying hazardous cargoes that become distressed.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220605","220605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173485","2015-01-16","Women and Equalities","2015-01-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking with other Government departments to support and encourage women entrepreneurs.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220535","220535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173486","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2014 to Question 216270, whether the average payment made by the Social Fund Funeral Payment scheme is intended to cover the whole cost of a simple, respectful, low-cost funeral; by what methodology he has assessed the total cost of such a funeral; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220516","220516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173487","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to prevent immigrants from claiming benefit for children living abroad.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220595","220595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173488","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the abolition of the Independent Living Fund on previous claimants of that fund in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220599","220599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173489","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy that people on benefits who undertake temporary work placements can have their benefits reinstated immediately and do not wait six weeks.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220571","220571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173490","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Labour Market Statistics, table BEN01, published in December 2014, what assessment he has made of the reasons why the number of claimants of employment and support allowance and other incapacity benefits was higher in May 2014 than in May 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220554","220554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173491","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what conclusions his Department has drawn from the Universal Credit in-work conditionality pilots which started in 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220555","220555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173492","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sub-contractors were engaged in the Work Programme at the most recent stocktake of that programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220556","220556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173493","2015-01-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) pensioners, (b) people of working age in work, (c) unemployed people of working age, (d) social housing sector tenants and (e) private sector housing tenants were receiving housing benefit in (i) Peterborough constituency and (ii) Peterborough City Council area in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220586","220586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173494","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount of annual housing benefit payments per applicant was in (a) Glasgow North constituency, (b) the city of Glasgow and (c) Scotland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220572","220572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173495","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value of hardship payments issued to sanctioned jobseekers' allowance claimants was in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220565","220565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173496","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people (a) were eligible for and (b) participated in the Work Programme in Cumbernauld, Kilsyth and Kirkintilloch East constituency in each month since October 2012.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220612","220612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173497","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much housing benefit was paid to applicants in (a) Glasgow North constituency, (b) the city of Glasgow and (c) Scotland in each year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220641","220641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173498","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many hardship payments were made to sanctioned jobseeker's allowance claimants in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220640","220640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173499","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the capacity within the citizens advice network to deal with Pensions Wise enquiries.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220611","220611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173500","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many agents offering guidance through the Pensions Wise scheme will be based outside London.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220610","220610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173501","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people who will reach state pension age within 12 months from the start of the single tier pension who will be eligible to receive state pension at the full rate; and what proportion of the total number of recipients those people will be.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220631","220631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173502","2015-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of (a) women and (b) men who will reach state pension age within 12 months from the start of the single tier pension who will be eligible to receive state pension at the full rate.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220632","220632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173503","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what training agents offering guidance through the Pensions Wise scheme will be given before dealing with enquiries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220633","220633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173504","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people who will seek to use the Pensions Wise service in the financial year 2015-16.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220634","220634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173505","2015-01-16","HM Treasury","2015-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, where the agents offering guidance through the Pensions Wise scheme will be based.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220635","220635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173506","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will publish a list of the high charging pension schemes referred to by the Independent Project Board in its report, Defined contribution workplace pensions: The audit of charges and benefits in legacy schemes, published in December 2014.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220645","220645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173507","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the research finding reported in the evaluation of the Work Programme published by his Department in December 2014, that differential pricing has had little impact in driving provider behaviour in the way they segmented customers and prioritised support; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220671","220671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173905","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that Bradford has enough school places.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907048","907048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174306","2015-01-19","Department for Education","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many cluster academies there are in (a) Northamptonshire, (b) the Borough of Kettering and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907056","907056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174883","2015-01-21","Wales Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps he is taking to improve transport links between Wales and England.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907068","907068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174884","2015-01-21","Wales Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on improving transport links to Wales.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907072","907072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174885","2015-01-21","Wales Office","2015-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the progress of the roll-out of superfast broadband in Wales.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907071","907071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173034","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many equality impact assessments his Department produced in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220343","220343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173035","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much tuition fee income was raised from students studying STEM subjects at UK universities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220344","220344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173037","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average response rate of initial teacher training students trained in universities to the National Student Survey was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220372","220372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173040","2015-01-14","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Bank of England on the continuation of quantitative easing.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220360","220360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173041","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse is of exempting intra-company transfer workers from overseas from paying national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220351","220351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173042","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many equality impact assessments his Department completed in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220342","220342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173044","2015-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of solar farm planning applications (a) received planning approval and (b) were called in in (i) 2013 and (ii) 2014.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220333","220333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173045","2015-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of UK land was registered on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220373","220373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173048","2015-01-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the average (a) download and (b) upload speed in East Lancashire was on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220325","220325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173049","2015-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the Government has to commemorate the anniversaries of VJ and VE Days in 2015.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220353","220353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173051","2015-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the UK next plans to host UN World Press Freedom Day.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220379","220379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173052","2015-01-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of work to increase broadband line speeds (a) from below 2 mbps to 10 mbps and (b) above 10 mbps to date.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220396","220396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173053","2015-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress the Ministry Defence Police has made on establishing a strength of 2,400 officers by April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220380","220380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173054","2015-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to invest in the upgrade of the A400M aircraft for use in special operations; what lessons his Department learned from the time taken to upgrade the C130J aircraft for that role in terms of (a) foregone capability and (b) increased costs; what estimate he has made of the (i) ability of the A400M to withstand an attack in comparison with the C130J and (ii) comparative cost of keeping the C130J in service for this role and introducing an upgraded A400M; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220423","220423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173055","2015-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Ministry of Defence Police were tasked in support of border controls for the UK Border Agency in northern France during 2013.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220378","220378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173057","2015-01-14","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage schools to (a) report and (b) support victims of child abuse.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220323","220323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173059","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary school children have received funding through the pupil premium in (a) Bradford East constituency and (b) Bradford.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220371","220371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173060","2015-01-14","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to increase the number of primary school teachers who have one or more science A-Levels.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220374","220374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173061","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to provide telephone helplines for schools to use to contact the Education Funding Agency.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220369","220369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173063","2015-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the timetable is for the forthcoming Comprehensive Review of solar feed-in-tariffs consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220331","220331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173065","2015-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of people employed in the UK solar photovoltaic industry.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220334","220334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173066","2015-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many solar CfD bids were received during the first auction; and what total NWp is represented by all bids.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220332","220332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173068","2015-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 524W, on Supply Estimates, which elements of the roll out of smart meters are being funded by his Department.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220385","220385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173069","2015-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 524W, on Supply Estimates, what proportion of the total cost of the roll out of smart meters is being met from the public purse; and what criteria his Department used to decide on that proportion.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220386","220386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173070","2015-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken to protect bass fish stocks during spawning in January 2015 since meetings with EU officials on 16 December 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220356","220356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173072","2015-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support British dairy industry producers whose payments by First Milk have been delayed.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220358","220358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173073","2015-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the use of green waste as compost.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220327","220327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173074","2015-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of efforts to reintroduce the short-haired bumblebee Bombus subterraneus to the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220328","220328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173075","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts about press freedom.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220359","220359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173076","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Russian government on the human rights implications of the decision to ban transgender people and other groups from driving.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220363","220363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173078","2015-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Palestinian Authority on its accession to the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220361","220361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173080","2015-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department recognises Morocco as the administering power in the non-self-governing territory of Western Sahara.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220367","220367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173081","2015-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his new Sri Lankan counterpart on protecting the Tamil and Muslim minority communities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220383","220383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173083","2015-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government took to ensure that the recent election in Sri Lanka was free and fair; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220384","220384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173084","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost of the Healthcare Travel Costs Scheme has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220375","220375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173086","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have used the Healthcare Travel Costs Scheme in each of the last five years; and how many such claimants claimed on behalf of a child under the age of 16.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220376","220376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173087","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on expanding the scope of the Healthcare Travel Costs Scheme to include (a) primary care services and (b) visits of close relatives.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220377","220377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173089","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any of the new marginal tariff payments proposed by NHS England for specialised services activity will be zero.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220364","220364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173090","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complex social discharges there were in each of the last four years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220357","220357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173092","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of private health companies which have taken on contracts to run GP practices have left the contract before completing it in (a) England and (b) Birmingham in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220336","220336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173093","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what legal costs the NHS has incurred relating to admissions to the NHS from private hospitals in the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220337","220337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173095","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pensioners gave up their right to the state pension to enter social care in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220352","220352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173096","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any member of the governing body of the Bedfordshire Clinical Commissioning Group has a financial interest in a private health provider.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220329","220329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173098","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS of admissions from private hospitals was in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220338","220338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173099","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any member of the governing body of the Rushcliffe Clinical Commissioning Group has a financial interest in a private health provider.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220330","220330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173101","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of GP practices are privately owned; and what research he has conducted on differences between privately owned and NHS GP practices in hospital admission rates, cancer survival rates, waiting times and other measures of quality.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220339","220339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173103","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital admissions have occurred as a result of injuries caused by e-cigarettes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220321","220321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173104","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many diagnoses of sciatica were made in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220322","220322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173107","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with familial hypercholesterolaemia in (a) England and (b) each local commissioning organisation in the last year.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220394","220394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173108","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients with long-term medical conditions in (a) England, (b) Greater Manchester, (c) Tameside and Glossop and (d) Stockport visited A&E before they were able to visit a GP or walk-in centre in the last three months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220381","220381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173109","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the number of patients admitting themselves to A&E for a pre-existing medical condition before they reach the top of a waiting list for the same issue, in (a) England, (b) Greater Manchester, (c) Tameside and Glossop and (d) Stockport in the last three months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220382","220382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173112","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many equality impact assessments her Department produced in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220340","220340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173113","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the top 10 nationalities granted study visas, other than student visitors, were in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220354","220354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173115","2015-01-14","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will revoke the entry ban into the UK on the US broadcaster Michael Alan Weiner, also known as Michael Savage.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220335","220335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173117","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the effect of revoking the visa sponsorship licence granted to Youth With A Mission on that organisation.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220370","220370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173118","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which directorate of her Department provides the budget for the electronic visa waiver scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220365","220365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173120","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the costs and benefits of the electronic visa waiver scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220366","220366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173121","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2014 to Question 213652, what progress her Department has made on developing proposals for a blanket ban on the sale of new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220368","220368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173122","2015-01-15","Department for International Development","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2014 to Question 207136, to the hon. Member for Brighton, Kemptown, what recent progress has been made on the outcomes of the Girl Summit of July 2014.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220355","220355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173124","2015-01-14","Department for International Development","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to monitor the effectiveness of the International Development (Gender Equality) Act 2014 in reducing gender inequality.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220326","220326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173129","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release of 6 May 2014, Justice for victims of banned drivers, when he plans to publish the new review of driving offences.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220345","220345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173130","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many punishments of removal from wing were given to children at HM Young Offender Institution Feltham in each month in 2014; and how many children were punished with removal from wing following an adjudication in that institution in each of those months.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220346","220346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173131","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the ethnicity was of children held in the segregation unit at HM Young Offender Institution Feltham in each month in 2014.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220347","220347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173132","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children held on the segregation unit at HM Young Offender Institution Feltham had an identified mental health issue in each month in 2014.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220348","220348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173133","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers were employed at the children's site at HM Young Offender Institution Feltham in each month in 2014.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220349","220349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173134","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times children have been subject to single unlock at HM Young Offender Institution Feltham in each month in 2014; and how many children were subject to single unlock at that institution in each of those months.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220350","220350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173135","2015-01-15","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the UK Government Financial Package to Northern Ireland under the Stormont House Agreement, how much of the up to £500 million new capital funding will be to support (a) shared and (b) integrated education.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220362","220362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173136","2015-01-14","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress she has made on establishing a separate mediation intervention group in relation to the Ardoyne parades issue.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220397","220397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173137","2015-01-14","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how residents affected by the plans for High Speed 2 will be informed of the appointment of a residents commissioner.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220387","220387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173138","2015-01-14","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when communities will be informed about (a) the likely start date for construction works for High Speed 2 (Phase 1) in their area and (b) the length of time such construction works are planned to take.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220393","220393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173139","2015-01-14","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what disruption there will be to services on the West Coast Mainline during the construction of High Speed 2; and how long such disruption is expected to last.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220395","220395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173140","2015-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effects of the benefits cap on reducing employment in Pendle constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220324","220324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173141","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many equality impact assessments his Department produced in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220341","220341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173142","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students are studying STEM subjects at UK universities in the 2014-15 academic year; and if he will estimate the number of such students in each of the next five academic years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220412","220412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173143","2015-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will instruct HM Revenue and Customs to investigate non-compliance with the national minimum wage in the care sector.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220434","220434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173144","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his latest estimate is of the RAB charges on (a) fees and (b) maintenance loans to students at UK universities studying STEM subjects.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220411","220411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173145","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of City Link on subcontractors reliant on City Link.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220437","220437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173146","2015-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the statement by his Department to the Today programme on 7 January 2015, what steps his Department is taking to name and shame care providers who do not pay the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220433","220433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173147","2015-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the oral Answer of 8 January 2015, Official Report, columns 382-3, which organisations and businesses he consulted prior to adopting the Government's position of opposing the product safety and market surveillance package at the European Council; and if he will meet Steelite International to discuss mandatory country of origin marking.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220473","220473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173148","2015-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students in England and Wales graduated in STEM subjects in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220475","220475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173149","2015-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to prevent poorly manufactured or dangerous e-cigarettes being imported into the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220478","220478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173150","2015-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the reduction in the student opportunity allocation on the ability of financially-disadvantaged students to access higher education.","Biography information for Rebecca Harris","Rebecca Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220479","220479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173151","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which overseas visits undertaken by HRH The Duke of York since 2011 were carried out partly or wholly on behalf of his Department; which countries were visited and what official events took place during each such visit; and what the cost to the public purse of (a) travel and (b) other expenses was of each such visit.","Biography information for Norman Baker","Norman Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220482","220482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173152","2015-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate he has made of the average unit costs of (a) the face value of student loans, (b) the resource costs of student loans, (c) teaching grants through the Higher Education Funding Council for England, (d) maintenance grant and (e) access spending by institutions in respect of additional students entering higher education in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220487","220487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173153","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to provide (a) funding and (b) other support for a reception hosted by HRH The Duke of York at the World Economic Forum to be held in Davos from 21 to 24 January 2015.","Biography information for Norman Baker","Norman Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220484","220484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173154","2015-01-14","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to reduce the level of business rates on small shopkeepers of Beckenham constituency.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220495","220495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173155","2015-01-14","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a sales tax on companies which operate in the UK and locate their headquarters overseas.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220496","220496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173156","2015-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the £2 per ton levied by the Coal Board for restoration on every ton of coal sold prior to the privatisation of the coal industry was paid to his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220505","220505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173157","2015-01-14","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints received by HM Revenue and Customs regarding non-payment of the national minimum wage by domiciliary care providers in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 led to formal investigations being carried out.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220466","220466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173158","2015-01-14","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints were received by HM Revenue and Customs regarding non-payment of the national minimum wage by domiciliary care providers in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220435","220435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173159","2015-01-15","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to grant tax relief to those who fund their own social care costs and are not entitled to any direct financial assistance from the Government.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220403","220403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173160","2015-01-14","HM Treasury","2015-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has made to the Financial Policy Committee of the Bank of England and the Financial Conduct Authority on problems faced by mortgage holders wishing to port their mortgage.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220400","220400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173161","2015-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion, to Question 218133, to which policies he was referring as the Government's broader social inclusion and integration policies.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220410","220410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173162","2015-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in (a) Lewisham, Deptford constituency and (b) the Borough of Lewisham have been assisted by the (i) Help to Buy equity loan and (ii) Help to Buy mortgage guarantee schemes; and what the (A) range and (B) average value has been of mortgages so assisted.","Biography information for Dame Joan Ruddock","Dame Joan Ruddock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220449","220449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173163","2015-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much of his Department's budget was allocated to (a) Wirral and (b) Birkenhead constituency in 2013-14.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220441","220441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173164","2015-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) value and (b) start and finish date is of each contract for foreign military sales procured by UK defence staff based in the US in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220401","220401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173165","2015-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2014 to Question 217097, when he expects (a) the review of the results of that survey to be completed and (b) the survey to be placed in the Library.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220491","220491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173166","2015-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's data protection policy is on (a) surveillance footage and (b) monitoring of on-line networking sites of people who have served in the armed forces and are compensation claimants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220492","220492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173167","2015-01-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many military compensation claimants have been subject to surveillance in each year since 2008; in what proportion of such compensation claim cases surveillance footage was used; what the cost of undertaking such surveillance was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220493","220493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173168","2015-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2014 to Question 217721, when the catering arrangements were extended to assist with Op SHADER; what choices were in place on 4 December 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220500","220500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173169","2015-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 219981, what arrangements were put in place to inform qualifying servicemen and women of their eligibility to receive the UN Special Service medal for the Sarajevo Airlift; whether they are allowed to wear that medal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Robertson","Sir Hugh Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220485","220485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173170","2015-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 219980, what rules relating to the wearing of medals govern those UK servicemen and women who served in (a) Sarajevo and (b) other areas of the former Yugoslavia that were subject to both UN and NATO mandates.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Robertson","Sir Hugh Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220486","220486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173171","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which overseas visits undertaken by HRH The Duke of York since 2011 were carried out partly or wholly on behalf of her Department; which countries were visited and what official events took place during each such visit; and what the cost to the public purse of (a) travel and (b) other expenses was of each such visit.","Biography information for Norman Baker","Norman Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220481","220481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173172","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2014 to Question 219636, whether she expects to provide an update on the management of asbestos in schools before the end of February 2015.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220503","220503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173173","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of her Department's budget was allocated to (a) Wirral and (b) Birkenhead constituency in 2013-14.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220439","220439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173174","2015-01-14","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the study of STEM subjects by girls; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220427","220427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173175","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many nursery school places have been created in (a) Bradford East constituency and (b) Bradford since 2008.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220444","220444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173176","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2014 to Question 906346, what live data health services and local authorities are permitted to share with children's centres.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220445","220445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173177","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary school children in (a) Bradford East constituency and (b) Bradford have received funding through the pupil premium.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220443","220443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173178","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which children's centres there were in the 10 per cent most deprived wards in England in (a) 2010 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220447","220447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173179","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children in (a) care and (b) need who have parents who misuse alcohol or drugs.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220448","220448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173180","2015-01-15","Department for Education","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve educational standards and opportunities at non-local education authority schools in (a) Tameside and (b) Stockport.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220450","220450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173181","2015-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department will publish its response to its consultation on transferability of rooftop solar photovoltaic which was launched in 2014.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220464","220464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173182","2015-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department plans to publish its response to its consultation on the transferability of rooftop solar photovoltaic consultation, published in November 2014.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220399","220399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173183","2015-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on the Waste to Bioeconomy roadmap; and whether her Department plans to provide any assistance to local authorities in relation to anaerobic digestion.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220477","220477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173184","2015-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish by 16 January 2015 the Shale Gas Rural Economy Impacts report; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Baker","Norman Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220483","220483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173185","2015-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress has been made in deregulating the consent process for river maintenance pilots; and what plans she has to start new pilot schemes (a) along the Thames in Berkshire and (b) elsewhere.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220494","220494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173186","2015-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the 50 largest landowners in the UK received from the Single Farm Payment scheme in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220432","220432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173187","2015-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress by Burma towards establishing democracy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220428","220428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173188","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the Middle East peace process.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220414","220414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173189","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority on recent reports of violations of the ceasefire agreement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220415","220415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173190","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations Ministers in his Department have made to the Saudi Arabian government on (a) freedom of the press, (b) religious freedom, (c) the rule of law and (d) cruel and inhumane treatment.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220417","220417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173191","2015-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to improve UK-Burmese diplomatic relations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220465","220465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173192","2015-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts in the Lebanese government on the removal of restrictions placed on Syrian refugees seeking to enter Lebanon.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220497","220497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173193","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Palestinian Authority counterparts on the closure of the administrative checkpoint at the Erez Crossing.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220488","220488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173194","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Palestinian Authority counterparts on the smuggling of weapons and other contraband into Gaza.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220489","220489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173195","2015-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2014 to Question 217644, on Ukraine, what criteria were used to establish EU policy objectives on non-recognition of the illegal annexation by (a) Russia of Crimea and (b) Israel of East Jerusalem and the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220480","220480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173196","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of kidney disease.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220457","220457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173197","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on screening for testicular cancer.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220476","220476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173198","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health visitors were employed in Warrington in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220454","220454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173199","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many district or community nurses were employed in Warrington in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220455","220455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173200","2015-01-20","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the Cancer Drugs Fund was spent on pancreatic cancer drugs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220490","220490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173201","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) professionally-qualified clinical staff other than locum doctors, (b) doctors other than locum doctors and qualified nursing, midwifery and health visiting staff, (c) HCHS doctors other than locum doctors and (d) qualified nursing, midwifery and health visiting staff were employed in each NHS trust in May (i) 2010 and (ii) 2014.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220474","220474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173202","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will allocate additional funding to assist towards delivering the new cystic fibrosis ward at King's College Hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220498","220498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173203","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's strategy is for addressing the disproportionally higher incidence of kidney disease from BAME communities.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220499","220499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173204","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of his Department's budget was allocated to (a) Wirral and (b) Birkenhead in 2013-14.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220440","220440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173205","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken in the last two months to reduce instances of delayed discharge at NHS healthcare providers in England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220405","220405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173206","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the adequacy of the number of escalation beds available to NHS healthcare providers in winter 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220406","220406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173207","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the adequacy of the capacity of A&E services in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220407","220407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173208","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received from NHS healthcare providers on the number of elective operations cancelled in the last two months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220408","220408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173209","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received from NHS healthcare providers on instances of delayed discharge at hospitals in England in the last month.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220404","220404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173210","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2014 to the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion, to Question 218766, by what date he plans to make a decision on whether to introduce standardised packaging of tobacco products; and what the reason is for the time taken to reach that decision.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220413","220413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173211","2015-01-14","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the health entitlements within the NHS are of British national missionaries and aid workers who are not ordinarily resident in, but retain housing and other links to, the UK.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220429","220429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173212","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Government's response to the Health Select Committee's Fifth Report of 2008-09 on the use of management consultants in the NHS and the Department of Health, HC 28, whether his Department initiated talks with the Management Consultancies Association (MCA) on its members' engagement with the NHS; and what formal meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with the MCA since then.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220467","220467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173213","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people from BAME backgrounds in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency and (b) the North West have registered on the organ donation register.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220458","220458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173214","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people from BAME backgrounds in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency and (b) the North West are currently on the organ donation waiting list.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220459","220459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173215","2015-01-15","Department of Health","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department has provided to Kidney Research UK's Peer Education Programme.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220460","220460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173216","2015-01-14","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many investigations into modern slavery have been made in each police force area in 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220425","220425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173217","2015-01-14","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much of her Department's budget was allocated to (a) the Wirral and (b) Birkenhead in 2013-14.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220426","220426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173218","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign nationals who have been convicted of a crime outside the UK and who currently live in the UK are being supervised by email by probation officers based in their native country.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220468","220468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173219","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to allow more refugees fleeing the conflict in Syria to enter the UK.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220402","220402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173220","2015-01-14","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests were made last year as a result of alleged crimes committed using social media.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220431","220431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173221","2015-01-15","Home Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219411, if she will discuss with the Secretary of State for Education the reasons for that Department's decision to update categorisation of the ethnicity of school pupils from January 2016.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220409","220409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173222","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of driving while disqualified were subsequently convicted of (a) committing further road offences, (b) causing serious injury and (c) causing death while driving in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220416","220416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173223","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2015 to Question 219263, what substances are covered by the heading Other in the table placed in the Library.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220446","220446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173224","2015-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of his Department's budget was allocated to (a) the Wirral and (b) Birkenhead in 2013-14.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220424","220424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173225","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what new additional capacity in the adult prison estate is (a) planned or (b) under construction; which prisons are so affected; how many additional units are being created through such work; and when each additional space will come on stream.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220452","220452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173226","2015-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the expected capacity of the adult (a) male and (b) female prison system will be in (i) June 2015, (ii) January 2016, (iii) June 2016, (iv) January 2017, (v) June 2017, (vi) January 2018, (vii) June 2018, (viii) January 2019, (ix) June 2019 and (x) January 2020.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220451","220451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173227","2015-01-14","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, of what land and in what locations adjacent to the High Speed 2 route, HS2 Ltd has facilitated the acquisition; and from which third parties.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220392","220392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173228","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which organisations and individuals were invited to make a submission to the consultation, Changing merchant shipping regulations: weighing of goods vehicles and emergency equipment lockers, published on 16 June 2014; and which organisations and individuals (a) who were and (b) who were not so invited made a submission to that consultation.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220470","220470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173229","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) employees and (b) secondees have been appointed by HS2 Ltd since October 2014; and what the pay grade and salary scale of each such person is.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220422","220422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173230","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average per metre bored tunnel cost is of the Crossrail tunnels.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220418","220418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173231","2015-01-14","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who will sit on the Need to Sell panel; and whether any of that panel will be employees or secondees of HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220389","220389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173232","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent on High Speed 2 during the period 1 January to 31 December 2013; and what budgeted spend was under each cost heading for (a) 2013 and (b)1 January to 31 December 2014.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220420","220420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173233","2015-01-14","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many petition response documents have been issued to those who have submitted petitions on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220390","220390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173234","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average tunnel boring machine advance rate is for the Crossrail tunnels.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220421","220421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173235","2015-01-14","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the High Speed 2 Wigan (Golborne) spur will be reconsidered; and when he will announce a decision on this matter.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220391","220391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173236","2015-01-14","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list (a) the contracts, (b) the value of those contracts and (c) payments made between (i) his Department and (ii) HS2 Ltd and (A) Alstom, (B) Atkins, (C) Bechtel, (D) Costain, (E) Hitachi, (F) Keolis, (G) Parsons Brinckerhoff, (H) the Rail Industry Association, (I) Siemens, (J) Laing O'Rourke, (K) Bombardier, (L) Young Rail Professionals, (M) National Skills Academy and (N) Railway Engineering in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220388","220388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173237","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether a High Speed 2 Residents' Commissioner has now been appointed; and when the Residents' Charter will be in operation.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220419","220419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173238","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his latest estimate is of the number of existing platforms at Euston station which will have to be taken out of use to permit construction of a London terminus for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220501","220501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173239","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when HS2 Ltd will start consultation on new design proposals for Euston station to comply with the Environmental Impact Assessment Directive.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220506","220506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173240","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department will announce revised plans for Euston station to accommodate High Speed 2.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220507","220507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173241","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the results of the Old Oak Common consultation will be published.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220508","220508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173242","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) employees and (b) secondees have been appointed by HS2 Ltd since October 2014.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220509","220509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173243","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Marine Accident Investigation Branch is taking to investigate the sinking of the cargo vessel, Cemfjord, in the Pentland Firth.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220502","220502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173244","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the recovery of bodies from the sunken cargo vessel, Cemfjord, in the Pentland Firth.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220510","220510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173245","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the length of time taken by the emergency towing vessel to respond to the foundering of the Cemfjord in the Pentland Firth.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220511","220511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173246","2015-01-15","Department for Transport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when driving or motorcycle tests in Na h-Eileanan an Iar constituency have been postponed in the last 12 months; what the reason was for each such postponement; and what the period was in each case until the next opportunity for learner drivers to sit the test.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220504","220504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173247","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency have waited more than six months for a personal independence payment application to be determined in the last three years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220456","220456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173248","2015-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have appealed against child maintenance decisions since the introduction of the mandatory reconsideration period.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220436","220436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173249","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 28 of his Department's Work Programme Evaluation published in December 2014, what guidance his Department gives Work Programme providers on best practice in cases where the costs of support for those with greatest need exceed the payments available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220442","220442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173250","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of his Department's budget was allocated to (a) Wirral and (b) Birkenhead constituency in 2013-14.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220438","220438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173251","2015-01-14","Cabinet Office","2015-01-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what account he has made of the performance of the launch of MyCSP; what targets have been set for the delivery of this service; and whether they have been met to date.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220398","220398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173252","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria are employed to assess applicants for personal independent payments (PIPs); and what steps are being taken to ensure that those in need do not lose access to the payment following the switchover from disability living allowance to PIPs.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220469","220469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173253","2015-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average time is taken to resolve those benefit cases subject to mandatory discrimination which are not resolved in the first 30 days.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220430","220430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173254","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has issued guidance on the evaluation of Innovation Fund projects to support separated families.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220471","220471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173255","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who in the past (a) had nil assessments and (b) were in the first tranche of old case closures would be eligible for payments under the current child maintenance system.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220472","220472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173256","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for a personal independence payment are still awaiting determination in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220453","220453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173257","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2014 to Question 906491, when he will publish data on how many victims of domestic violence are using the exemption to the child maintenance application fee.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220461","220461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173258","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost per case is under the new child maintenance system.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220462","220462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173259","2015-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the £2,000 tax free childcare allowance is available to those on universal credit.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220463","220463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173372","2015-01-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to support culture and the arts.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907010","907010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173373","2015-01-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of creative industries to the economy.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907005","907005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173484","2015-01-15","Women and Equalities","2015-01-12","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to tackle homophobic bullying.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907021","907021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/173860","2015-01-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to increase women's participation in sport and physical activity.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907011","907011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172864","2015-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he intends to reply to the letter dated 25 November 2014, from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms C Gazelet, forwarded from the Department for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220258","220258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172865","2015-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he takes to ensure that equipment for which arms export licences to Saudi Arabia have been granted is not used for internal repression.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220307","220307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172866","2015-01-13","Department for Transport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with businesses on the effects on vehicle leasing companies of the Protection of Freedoms Act 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220310","220310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172867","2015-01-14","Attorney General","2015-01-09","To ask the Attorney General, what amount each Government department has spent on external legal fees relating to each case involving substantive judicial review hearings since May 2010; and what the outcome of the proceedings was in each such case.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220247","220247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172868","2015-01-13","HM Treasury","2015-01-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any resources or staff of his Department were used in the drafting of or analysis for the document A Cost Analysis of Labour Party Policy, published by the Conservative Party on 5 January 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220253","220253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172869","2015-01-13","HM Treasury","2015-01-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2015 to Question 203110, what the total cost of administering his Department's employee check-off service is; and which organisations contribute financially towards that service.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220266","220266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172870","2015-01-14","HM Treasury","2015-01-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funds are currently managed by the Pool Re scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220318","220318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172871","2015-01-14","HM Treasury","2015-01-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the anticipated dividend payment to the Government and the insurance industry from the assets managed in the Pool Re scheme in 2014-15 is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220319","220319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172872","2015-01-14","HM Treasury","2015-01-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has for the division of dividends on the assets held by the Pool Re scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220320","220320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172873","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals relating to development on green belt land have been recovered for a decision by the Secretary of State in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220268","220268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172874","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, from which local authorities planning appeals were recovered in 2014.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220269","220269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172875","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals related to Gypsy and Traveller sites were recovered for a decision by the Secretary of State in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220271","220271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172876","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals were recovered from local authorities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220270","220270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172877","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals related to wind energy projects were recovered for a decision by the Secretary of State in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220296","220296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172878","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many recovered planning appeals he has upheld in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220297","220297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172879","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many recovered planning appeals he has refused in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220298","220298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172880","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals have been recovered from local authorities which have no local plan or whose plan (a) dates from earlier than 2004 and (b) is not compliant with the National Planning Policy Framework; and how many such appeals resulted in a refusal decision.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220299","220299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172881","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning appeals have been recovered from local authorities which have an adopted local plan which (a) dates from later than 2004 and (b) is compliant with the National Planning Policy Framework; and how many such appeals resulted in a refusal decision.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220300","220300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172882","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of homes planned for in development applications which were refused by the Secretary of State in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220301","220301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172883","2015-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with the London Borough of Redbridge on gravel extraction in Aldborough Hatch.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220245","220245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172884","2015-01-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2014 to Question 218397, on broadband: urban areas, to which 28 cities his Department has written.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220287","220287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172885","2015-01-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on the Government Art Collection in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220313","220313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172886","2015-01-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to prevent households which do not have a television receiving correspondence from the TV licensing Authority threatening them with legal action.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220311","220311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172887","2015-01-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the County Durham, Oxfordshire, Hampshire, Essex and Wokingham phase 2 broadband projects produced coverage maps of their broadband implementation plans at a full 7-digit postcode level.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220308","220308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172888","2015-01-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which recommendations in the Independent Library Report for England, published in December 2014, he (a) accepts and (b) rejects.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220312","220312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172889","2015-01-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 16 December 2014 to Question 217969, which four cities were considered and rejected in wave 1; which six cities were considered and rejected in wave 2; and for what reasons each city in each wave was rejected.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220292","220292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172890","2015-01-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the recommendations of the Independent Library Report for England, published in December 2014, what estimate he has made of the cost of providing WiFi in all public libraries.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220293","220293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172891","2015-01-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what work his Department has done with local authorities in County Durham, Oxfordshire, Hampshire, Essex and Wokingham to identify, in relation to the broadband rollout, (a) alternative solutions, (b) joint working and fair capital contributions from suppliers and (c) other opportunities to promote competition and value for money.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220294","220294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172892","2015-01-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the (a) County Durham, (b) Oxfordshire, (c) Hampshire, (d) Essex and (e) Wokingham phase 2 broadband projects received bids or offers from suppliers other than BT.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220295","220295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172893","2015-01-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much of the cost of phase 2 broadband projects in (a) County Durham, (b) Oxfordshire, (c) Hampshire, (d) Essex and (e) Wokingham will be met by (i) BT, (ii) BDUK and (iii) the relevant local authority.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220290","220290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172894","2015-01-14","Department for Education","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department's Annual Report and Accounts for 2013-14 will be published; and what the reasons are for the time taken to publish that report.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220261","220261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172895","2015-01-13","Department for Education","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with (a) the Read On. Get On. campaign and (b) members and supporters of that campaign on improving the reading ability of primary school children.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220283","220283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172896","2015-01-13","Department for Education","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that every child can read by the time they finish primary school.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220284","220284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172897","2015-01-13","Department for Education","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to support parents in bolstering the cognitive development of their children before they reach primary school.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220285","220285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172898","2015-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the cost of energy for homes not connected to mains gas or electricity.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220250","220250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172899","2015-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of changes introduced by her Department to the EU pet travel scheme which came into force on 29 December 2014 on illegal imports of puppies to the UK from other EU countries; what discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on abuse of the PETS system to illegally import puppies for sale; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220249","220249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172900","2015-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Saudi Arabian government on the public flogging of Raif Badawi on 9 January 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220263","220263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172901","2015-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the extent of persecution of Christians in (a) Nigeria and (b) Iran.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220309","220309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172902","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff have been made redundant and subsequently re-employed by NHS organisations on a (a) permanent and (b) fixed-term contract basis since the provisions of the Health and Social Care Act 2012 came into force.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220252","220252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172903","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of recent research on the treatment of rheumatoid arthritis carried out by Professor Paul-Peter Tak of the Academic Medical Centre, Amsterdam.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220305","220305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172904","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP practices informed NHS England they would (a) reduce their opening hours and (b) not offer face-to-face appointments at any point over the 2014-15 Christmas and New Year period.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220302","220302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172905","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance NHS England gave GP practices on opening hours during the 2014-15 Christmas and New Year period.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220303","220303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172906","2015-01-16","Department of Health","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution of regulated complementary and alternative medical practitioners to reducing demands on the NHS.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220251","220251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172907","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many admissions to hospital through A&E with an alcohol-related diagnosis involving people (a) under and (b) over the age of 18 there were in each NHS hospital trust in the East of England in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220254","220254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172908","2015-01-14","Home Office","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment criteria are used for the Syrian vulnerable persons relocation scheme.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220264","220264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172909","2015-01-14","Home Office","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) total cost and (b) cost in each principal category of expenditure was of the Police and Crime Commissioner elections in 2012; and in which months of 2012 costs for each of the principal items were incurred.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220265","220265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172910","2015-01-14","Home Office","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) longest time taken has been to process a Syrian refugee through the Syrian vulnerable persons relocation scheme up to their relocation in the UK.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220306","220306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172911","2015-01-14","Home Office","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps that do not require legislation have been taken by her Department in response to its review of new psychoactive substances since its publication; and what further such steps she plans to take before the end of the present Parliament (a) overall and (b) relating to head shops.","Biography information for Norman Baker","Norman Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220314","220314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172912","2015-01-14","Home Office","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for implementation of each of the recommendations of her Department's review of new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Norman Baker","Norman Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220315","220315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172913","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many foreign exchange transactions involving less than £2 million her Department has made to Bangladesh in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220275","220275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172914","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many foreign exchange transactions involving less than £2 million her Department has made to India in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220276","220276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172915","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many foreign exchange transactions involving less than £2 million her Department has made to Ethiopia in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220277","220277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172916","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many foreign exchange transactions involving less than £2 million her Department has made to Tanzania in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220281","220281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172917","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, for what reasons her Department is increasing its allocation of non-humanitarian funding to the Caribbean from 2013-14 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220282","220282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172918","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many foreign exchange transactions involving less than £2 million her Department has made to Nigeria in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220278","220278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172919","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many foreign exchange transactions involving less than £2 million her Department has made to Pakistan in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220279","220279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172920","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many foreign exchange transactions involving less than £2 million her Department has made to Afghanistan in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220280","220280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172921","2015-01-14","Department for International Development","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2014 to Question 216682, what the top five countries were to which payments under £2 million were made in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220288","220288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172922","2015-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) convictions and (b) fixed penalty notices there have been in respect of people arrested for speeding offences in Suffolk (i) in total and (ii) on the (A) A143 and (B) A14 in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220273","220273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172923","2015-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers (a) work in each prison and (b) are authorised to work in each prison at the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220267","220267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172924","2015-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the Government spent on legal fees in the case Gudanaviciene & Ors, R (on the application of) v The Director of Legal Aid Casework & Or [2014] EWCA Civ 1622 (15 December 2014).","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220248","220248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172925","2015-01-13","Scotland Office","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with (a) the Scottish Government and (b) his ministerial colleagues on the sustainability of employment and exploration levels in the North Sea oil and gas industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220246","220246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172926","2015-01-13","Department for Transport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2014 to Question 217210, how much funding his Department has allocated to each district and unitary council in (a) Suffolk, (b) Bedfordshire, (c) Cambridgeshire, (d) Essex, (e) Hertfordshire and (f) Norfolk for road improvement in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220289","220289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172927","2015-01-13","Department for Transport","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress his Department has made on increasing the use of renewable energy in transport in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220304","220304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172928","2015-01-13","Cabinet Office","2015-01-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many payments for jobseeker's allowance were terminated (a) as a result of employment and (b) for other reasons in (i) Suffolk, (ii) Bedfordshire, (iii) Cambridgeshire, (iv) Essex, (v) Hertfordshire and (vi) Norfolk in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220274","220274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172929","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of benefit fraud which was attributable to identity fraud for each benefit in (a) Suffolk, (b) Bedfordshire,(c) Cambridgeshire, (d) Essex, (e) Hertfordshire and (f) Norfolk in each year since 2005 for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220272","220272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172930","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 25 November 2014, from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr M A De Barrus.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220259","220259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172931","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 26 November 2014, from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr A Farooqi.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220260","220260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172932","2015-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent on in-work housing benefit for migrant workers from the European Economic Area who have arrived in the UK within the last (a) six months, (b) 12 months and (c) 24 months.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220286","220286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172933","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment of proposed changes to the widowed parent's allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220244","220244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172934","2015-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the performance metrics for jobcentres.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220262","220262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172935","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in England who have waited more than (a) 30 days, (b) 60 days, (c) 90 days, (d) 120 days, (e) 150 days, (f) 180 days and (g) one year for a personal independence payment application to be completed.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220255","220255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172936","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Dudley who have waited more than six months for a personal independence payment application to be completed.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220256","220256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172937","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Dudley who are waiting for a personal independence payment application to be completed.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220257","220257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172938","2015-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what incentives jobcentres have to sanction benefit claimants.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220291","220291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172939","2015-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many benefit sanctions have been overturned on appeal because the claimant met the reasonableness test because of (a) domestic violence, (b) mental health conditions or disorders, (c) bullying or harassment in the workplace, (d) homelessness, (e) losing a work experience opportunity, other than for a reason of gross misconduct, (f) travelling time, (g) break-up of the family, (h) short notice caring commitments for the elderly, sick or children, (i) domestic emergency, (j) family bereavement, (k) learning difficulties, poor numeracy or literacy, (l) legal constraints and (m) temporary changes in circumstances in (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12, (iv) 2012-13, (v) 2013-14 and (vi) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220316","220316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172940","2015-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sanctions relating to each benefit have been overturned on appeal in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13, (e) 2013-14 and (f) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220317","220317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172739","2015-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions there have been for driving while disqualified in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220161","220161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172740","2015-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received from universities about the future viability of Initial Teacher Training courses and university education departments.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220155","220155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172741","2015-01-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on the changes to the budget of the Tradeshow Access Programme by UK Trade & Investment in November 2014.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220213","220213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172742","2015-01-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what forecast he has made of the value of export sales for UK companies generated by attendance at overseas exhibitions through the use of the Tradeshow Access Programme during the life of that programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220214","220214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172743","2015-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on mail volumes to the universal service provider in the HA postcode area of London of end-to-end competition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220228","220228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172744","2015-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans for the Skills Funding Agency to have a data sharing agreement in place with London Work Programme providers so that referrals to Skills support for Work Programme participants in Employment can commence.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220236","220236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172745","2015-01-12","Cabinet Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what consideration he has given to adopting a Welsh language policy for his Department.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220150","220150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172746","2015-01-12","Cabinet Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he last visited the Emergency Contingencies Planning College, The Hawkhills, Easingwold; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220144","220144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172747","2015-01-13","HM Treasury","2015-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2014 to Question 217619, when the hon. Member for Walsall North will receive a reply to his letter of 10 November 2014, reference MC2014/04463; and what the reason was for the time taken to respond.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220231","220231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172748","2015-01-12","HM Treasury","2015-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will arrange for the Chief Executive of HM Revenue and Customs to provide a substantive response to the letter of 13 November 2014 from the hon. Member for Hartlepool on behalf of his constituent, Mr McGovern.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220216","220216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172749","2015-01-12","HM Treasury","2015-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to keep under review HM Revenue and Customs' conduct when dealing with taxpayers who seek additional time to pay as a consequence of Accelerated Payments Notices.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220189","220189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172750","2015-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to promote service in the Reserves.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220143","220143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172751","2015-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to whom his Department has sold Minley Manor and for what price; how many bidders there were for that site; whether those bidders were asked to improve their offers; when the sale was completed; and what covenants were put in place relating to that sale.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220165","220165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172752","2015-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on introducing the Armed Forces Covenant in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220197","220197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172753","2015-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to promote the Reserves in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220198","220198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172754","2015-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will introduce a time limit by which investigations undertaken by the Service Complaints Commissioner must be concluded.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220229","220229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172755","2015-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the Service Complaints Commissioner provides full disclosure of complaints and how they are determined to interested parties.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220230","220230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172756","2015-01-12","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed changes to identity checks on applicants to register as voters on people with the protected characteristic of gender reassignment; whether he has sought legal advice on the compatibility of those proposed changes with (a) the Equality Act 2010 and (b) the Human Rights Act 1998; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220157","220157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172757","2015-01-12","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-08","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with the York, North Yorkshire and East Riding Local Enterprise Partnership on infrastructure funding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220145","220145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172758","2015-01-13","Department for Education","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many trainee secondary school chemistry, physics and mathematics teachers there are in each region of England.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220153","220153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172759","2015-01-13","Department for Education","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish her Department's quality grade of academy sponsors.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220154","220154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172760","2015-01-12","Department for Education","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether construction budgets for studio schools include the cost of specialist teaching equipment related to the school's specialism.","Biography information for Nadhim Zahawi","Nadhim Zahawi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220159","220159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172761","2015-01-13","Department for Education","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons the National College of Teaching and Leadership has withdrawn Initial Teacher Training students from future National Student Surveys.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220156","220156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172762","2015-01-13","Department for Education","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary school teachers in each parliamentary constituency in the South West have a science degree.","Biography information for Stephen Gilbert","Stephen Gilbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220221","220221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172763","2015-01-13","Department for Education","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children (a) in receipt of free school meals, (b) with a statement of special educational needs, (c) from a BME community and (d) looked after by a local authority received a place in a grammar school in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220222","220222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172764","2015-01-12","Department for Education","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219314, what information her Department holds on when children born outside the UK who are then reported to be in private fostering arrangements entered the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220174","220174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172765","2015-01-12","Department for Education","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to reduce disparities between local authorities in meeting the six-week regulation for visits of children within the first year of a private fostering arrangement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220175","220175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172766","2015-01-12","Department for Education","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219314, whether her Department holds figures for the countries of origin of children who are reported to be in private fostering arrangements born outside the UK.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220173","220173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172767","2015-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2014 to Question 208622, if she will reconsider her decision not to publish the Shale Gas Rural Economy Impact Report.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220152","220152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172768","2015-01-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent representations he has received on regulations relating to hydraulic fracturing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220147","220147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172769","2015-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will request that the Marine Management Organisation review catch limits for skate and ray for vessels under 10 metres calculated using data from January 2014, when persistent bad weather prevented smaller fishing vessels putting to sea.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220166","220166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172770","2015-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support UK dairy farmers who are producing milk without the use of intensive indoor practices.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220168","220168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172771","2015-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which fish species have been overfished in 2013-14.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220169","220169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172772","2015-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress she has made on implementation of point 7, on constantly improving standards of animal health and welfare, in the dairy industry growth plan, Leading the Way, published in June 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220185","220185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172773","2015-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will meet the Chairman and Board of First Milk to discuss the effect of that body's recent announcements on milk prices, delays in payments and increased capital levy contributions on the viability of farmers who supply it.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220191","220191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172774","2015-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the announcement by the Marine Management Organisation (MMO) on 7 January 2015, on January 2015 catch limits, from which industry bodies the MMO received feedback; which fisheries representatives contacted the MMO; and how many members each such organisation represents.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220194","220194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172775","2015-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will assess the potential merits of giving additional powers to the Environment Agency to respond in instances where landfill site owners ignore advice on tipping waste in severe weather.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220208","220208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172776","2015-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will assess the potential merits of giving additional powers to the Environment Agency to enable it to take punitive action against landfill site operators who ignore advice not to tip during severe weather resulting in waste, dust and other potentially hazardous materials being blown off site.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220209","220209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172777","2015-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's policy is on EU renegotiation of quotas to get a better deal for cane sugar importers.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220210","220210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172778","2015-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that cane sugar importation from African and Caribbean countries is protected when EU beet sugar quotas are lifted in 2017.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220211","220211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172779","2015-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to protect cane sugar refiners (a) in East London and (b) elsewhere in the UK following the lifting of beet sugar quotas in 2017.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220212","220212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172780","2015-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2014 to Question 214438, when she plans to publish the triennial review of the Maritime Management Organisation.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220243","220243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172781","2015-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to support the petition from British survivors of thalidomide damage to the EU Commissioner for Health and MEPs which seeks to secure a fair level of compensation for the costs and losses arising from the damage done to them by thalidomide.","Biography information for Lord Young of Cookham","Sir George Young","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220224","220224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172782","2015-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the finding by UNHCR that there were 40 killings of human rights defenders in Colombia in the first nine months of 2014, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in that country.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220207","220207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172783","2015-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of the Republic of Congo as to the safety and protection of the British missionary, Ms Maud Kells.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220199","220199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172784","2015-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps are being taken to ensure that the Chagossians are taken to the Chagos Islands as soon as possible, since the cancellation by his Department of their scheduled annual trip in November 2014.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220171","220171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172785","2015-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what consideration he has given to adopting a Welsh language policy for his Department.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220149","220149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172786","2015-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when and for what reasons permission was given to representatives of the Zoological Society of London to travel to the Chagos Islands.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220170","220170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172787","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many inspections of approved independent places for the termination of pregnancy have been carried out to ensure compliance with the revised Procedures for the Approval of Independent Sector Places for the Termination of Pregnancy and his Department's Guidance in Relation to the Requirements of the Abortion Act, both published in May 2014.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220158","220158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172788","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures his Department has in place to ensure that independent-sector providers of abortion services comply with the requirements of the Procedures for the Approval of Independent Sector Places for the Termination of Pregnancy, published in May 2014.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220148","220148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172789","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has for the future funding of dental services in Mid Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220206","220206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172790","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the studies recommended by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority's expert review panel in the publication, Scientific review of the safety and efficacy of methods to avoid mitochondrial disease through assisted conception: update, published in March 2013 on mosaicism in human morulae have been concluded; and in which peer-reviewed journal his Department plans to publish the findings of those studies.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220195","220195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172791","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department allocated to projects aimed at increasing walking between (a) 2005 and 2010 and (b) 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220190","220190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172792","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for talking therapy in Birmingham.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220193","220193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172793","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department collects separate figures on the numbers of locum, temporary, part-time and agency GPs hired on the latest GP contracts.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220176","220176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172794","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the current GP contract allows a GP who is classified as a part-time GP with an FTE of less than 1.0 to be employed also as a locum or agency doctor.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220177","220177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172795","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the proposed NHS England National Obesity Plan will include specific measures relating to diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220178","220178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172796","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what organisations will be responsible for the implementation of the nationwide obesity plan, announced by NHS England in December 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220179","220179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172797","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to put contingency arrangements in place to ensure support for recipients of mitochondrial donation techniques in the event of failure or abnormal development in the resulting child.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220183","220183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172798","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of whether eggs used in the creation of embryos through maternal spindle transfer or pronuclear transfer have had their mitochondrial or nuclear genes altered in the process.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220181","220181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172799","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for public safety in relation to his policy on mitochondrial transfer of the study by Professor John Zhang et al, published in Fertility and Sterility, Vol 80, Suppl. 3, September 2003.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220182","220182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172800","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies were absent from work through sickness in December 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220225","220225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172801","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to raise awareness of mesothelioma and its cause by (a) exposure to asbestos and (b) other causes.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220226","220226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172802","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the experiment on mitochondrial DNA carry-over on non-human primate model into the possible heteroplasmy of tissues in the foetus, recommended by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority's expert panel in its publication Scientific review of the safety and efficacy of methods to avoid mitochondrial disease through assisted conception, published April 2011, has been concluded; and in which peer-reviewed journal he plans to publish the results of that experiment.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220220","220220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172803","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms are in place for engagement and joint working between NICE and the Scottish Medicines Consortium for (a) sharing best practice in the early access of medicines in the UK, (b) avoiding duplication in the licensing of medicines and (c) promotion of the UK for inward investment into research, clinical trials and manufacture of medicines.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220215","220215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172804","2015-01-12","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on increases in attendances at A&E departments.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220204","220204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172805","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the experiment on vitrifying zygotes created through pronuclear transfer, recommended by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority's expert panel in its publication Scientific review of the safety and efficacy of methods to avoid mitochondrial disease through assisted conception, published in April 2011, has been concluded; and in which open access peer-reviewed journal he plans to publish the results of that experiment.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220217","220217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172806","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the experiments on human embryonic stem cells derived from blastocysts that are heteroplasmic for abnormal mitochondrial DNA (mtDNA) and blastocysts created through maternal spindle transfer and pronuclear transfer where the oocytes had abnormal mtDNA, recommended by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority's expert panel in its publication Scientific review of the safety and efficacy of methods to avoid mitochondrial disease through assisted conception, published April 2011, has been concluded; and in which peer-reviewed journal he plans to publish the results of those experiments.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220218","220218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172807","2015-01-13","Department of Health","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the experiment involving the use of induced pluripotent stem cells derived from patients carrying different mitochondrial DNA mutations, recommended by the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority's expert panel in its publication Scientific review of the safety and efficacy of methods to avoid mitochondrial disease through assisted conception, published April 2011, has been concluded; and in which peer-reviewed journal he plans to publish the results of that experiment.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220219","220219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172808","2015-01-13","Home Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219411, what policy considerations led to the decision to retain the Census 2001 framework.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220227","220227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172809","2015-01-13","Home Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the current number of police officers employed as crime prevention officers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220223","220223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172810","2015-01-13","Home Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fines relating to performance have been levied on providers of the COMPASS service in each of the past two years; how many such fines were levied on each provider in each year; what those fines were for; and what the amount was of each fine.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220186","220186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172811","2015-01-12","Home Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to introduce the use of drunk tanks by the police to alleviate pressure on A&E departments at weekends.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220180","220180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172812","2015-01-12","Cabinet Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of recent trends in rural crime; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220146","220146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172813","2015-01-12","Home Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether every police force has an action plan in place to ensure that domestic violence is dealt with quickly and fairly.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220167","220167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172814","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what amount from the funds allocated by her Department to the International Climate Fund has been disbursed in each year since that fund's inception.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220233","220233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172815","2015-01-13","Department for International Development","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to page 169 of her Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, what the equivalent value of Departmental Expenditure Limit Capital was in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220232","220232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172816","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses were recommended by the Financial Services Ombudsman to award consumers fair compensation above the £100,000 limit in each year from 2001 to 2011.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220188","220188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172817","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses were recommended by the Financial Services Ombudsman to award consumers fair compensation above the £150,000 limit in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220187","220187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172818","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on removing the compensation limit set by the Financial Services Ombudsman.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220196","220196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172819","2015-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date the Legal Aid Agency introduced a prescribed time period of 24 months for evidence relating to domestic violence cases.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220160","220160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172820","2015-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to Question 217807, tabled on 9 December 2014, when he plans to answer Question 213688, tabled on 6 November 2014.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220162","220162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172821","2015-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it remains the policy of his Department not to fund Christmas parties for staff.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220163","220163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172822","2015-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to answer Question 217822, tabled on 9 December 2014.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220164","220164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172823","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses were instructed by the Financial Services Ombudsman to award consumers the maximum compensation of £150,000 in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220172","220172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172824","2015-01-12","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220203","220203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172825","2015-01-12","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the cost to her Department was of the Parades Commission in 2013-14.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220202","220202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172826","2015-01-12","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with Ministers in the Northern Ireland Executive on securing adequate resources for the Police Service of Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220201","220201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172827","2015-01-12","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she had with the Secretary of State for Transport before the decision of that Department to display the Union flag on driving licences only in England, Scotland and Wales.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220200","220200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172828","2015-01-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-01-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of postal voters did not transfer to the individual electoral register in each (i) local authority and (ii) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220192","220192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172829","2015-01-12","Department for Transport","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which main contractors were responsible for engineering work north of King's Cross station during the Christmas 2014 period.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220205","220205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172830","2015-01-13","Department for Transport","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his Written Statement of 8 January 2015, WS175, on Rail in the North: Rolling Stock, how long he expects the lease for the new rolling stock to run; and which rolling-stock leasing company will provide the new rolling stock.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220239","220239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172831","2015-01-13","Department for Transport","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his Written Statement of 8 January 2015, WS175, on Rail in the North: Rolling Stock, what estimate he has made of the total cost of leasing the new rolling stock; and what proportion of that cost will be borne by (a) his Department and (b) train operating companies in each year until the end of the lease.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220238","220238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172832","2015-01-13","Department for Transport","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his Written Statement of 8 January 2015, WS175, on Rail in the North: Rolling Stock, what the average age is of the new rolling stock; and whether the new rolling stock meets the requirements in the Persons of Reduced Mobility Specification for Interoperability.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220240","220240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172833","2015-01-13","Department for Transport","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his Written Statement of 8 January 2015, WS175, on Rail in the North: Rolling Stock, whether it is his policy that the operator of Northern Rail and TransPennine Express services after the new franchise commences will be required to continue using that rolling stock.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220241","220241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172834","2015-01-13","Department for Transport","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his Written Statement of 8 January 2015, WS175, on Rail in the North: Rolling Stock, how many seats are available on Northern Rail and TransPennine Express; how many seats will be available once the new rolling stock comes into service; when he expects this rolling stock to be put into service; and how long he expects such rolling stock to remain in service.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220242","220242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172835","2015-01-12","Department for Transport","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to restrict access to DVLA vehicle ownership records by private parking companies which have a high failure rate in the appeals process.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220151","220151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172836","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 122 of work programme evaluation: operation of the commissioning model, finance and programme delivery, published by his Department on 18 December 2014, for what reasons the performance management approach applied in the Work Programme was replaced by a more prescriptive system.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220235","220235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172837","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of differential pricing on provider behaviour in the Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220237","220237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172838","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 28 of work programme evaluations: operation of the commissioning model, finance and programme delivery, published by his Department on 18 December 2014, what assessment he has made of the finding that only a small proportion of subcontractors were positive about the commerical attractiveness of their contracts with the primes.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220234","220234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/172839","2015-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who the (a) Chair and (b) other members are of the Universal Credit Programme board.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 220184","220184"
