"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134885","2019-07-01","Women and Equalities","2019-06-26","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of making an employer legally liable if they fail to protect their staff from sexual harassment at work.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269629","269629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134886","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that BAME women receive the specialist help they need after suffering domestic abuse.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269630","269630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134887","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that all pensioners claim all of the pension credit they are entitled to.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269631","269631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134888","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that constituents with learning disabilities or autism, in Newcastle-under-Lyme, are able to access inpatient facilities close to home.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269659","269659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134889","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the median advance payment awarded to people awaiting their first payment of universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269644","269644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134890","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools are allocated to each of the teaching school alliance hubs.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269621","269621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134891","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what is the median repayment period for advance payments awarded to people awaiting their first payment of universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269645","269645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134892","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria his Department used to decide the regions that are pilots for the new teaching school alliance hubs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269622","269622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134893","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of repayment schedules for advance payments awarded to people awaiting their first universal credit claim have been timetabled to (a) one to three months, (b) four to six months, (c) seven to nine months and (d) 10-12 months by Jobcentre Plus district in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269646","269646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134894","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2019 to Question 254153 on prescriptions: universal credit, when the new NHS prescription form will be introduced; and whether the new form will be used throughout the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269647","269647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134895","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to allow a wider range of support workers to distribute and sign parents' application forms to increase the take-up of healthy start vouchers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269648","269648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134896","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of veterinary research funded by the Horserace Betting Levy Board on the welfare of horses since 2000.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269623","269623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134897","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Horse Welfare Board in improving the standards of welfare in horseracing.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269624","269624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134898","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment (a) his Department and (b) the Animal Plant and Health Agency have made of the effectiveness of the measures taken by the British Horseracing Authority in countering and containing the ongoing outbreak of equine influenza in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269625","269625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134899","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS long-term plan, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on healthcare delivery of reducing the number of clinical commissioning groups to match the number of sustainability and transformation partnerships.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269781","269781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134900","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS long-term plan, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) merits and (b) demerits of reducing the number of clinical commissioning groups to match the number of sustainability and transformation partnerships.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269782","269782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134901","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS long-term plan, what consultation his Department has conducted on the potential merits of reducing the number of clinical commissioning groups to match the number of sustainability and transformation partnerships.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269783","269783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134902","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS long-term plan, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on local accountability in planning and commissioning health services of reducing the number of clinical commissioning groups to match the number of sustainability and transformation partnerships.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269784","269784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134903","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to (a) monitor and (b) evaluate the merit of mergers between clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269785","269785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134904","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) disability and (b) work capability assessments were carried out with a home visit in 2018-19 in each DWP Region.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269649","269649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134905","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what role he plans Genomics England to play in the NHS Genomic Medicine Service after the completion of the 100,000 Genomes Project.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269786","269786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134906","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which organisation Genomics England is accountable to.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269787","269787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134907","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to evaluate the 100,000 Genomes Project.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269788","269788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134908","2019-07-01","Department for International Development","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions he has had with representatives of the World Food Programme on the suspension of aid in Sana’a and other areas where aid is at risk of diversion.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269632","269632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134909","2019-07-01","Department for International Development","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support he is providing to the World Food Programme to (a) import equipment into Yemen and (b) secure visas for that country its staff without delay.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269633","269633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134910","2019-07-01","Department for International Development","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support his Department is providing to the World Food Programme to operate in Government-controlled areas in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269634","269634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134911","2019-07-01","Department for International Development","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to prevent pollution from the transport of barrels of oil along the coast of Hodeidah.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269635","269635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134912","2019-07-01","Department for International Development","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle the level of bureaucracy that impedes the operations of UN agencies and other international organisations in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269636","269636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134913","2019-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent an escalation of violence in al-Hodeidah Governorate.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269637","269637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134914","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps her Department is taking to deter foreign military vessels from entering UK territorial waters.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269668","269668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134915","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Poseidon MRA Mk1 (P-8A) will be operational.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269669","269669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134916","2019-07-01","Department for International Trade","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he has taken to enhance UK trade with Montenegro after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269670","269670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134917","2019-07-01","Northern Ireland Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she has taken to ensure that Northern Ireland has good governance in the absence of a devolved Administration.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269671","269671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134918","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps her Department is taking to minimise the time taken to dispose of retired nuclear submarines.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269672","269672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134919","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2019 to Question 262315 on Wakefield City Academies Trust: Deloitte and Touche, what services were provided by Deloitte LLP under its contract in relation to the closure of Wakefield City Academies Trust.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269696","269696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134920","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has plans to establish a statutory greyhound race betting levy to improve the welfare of racing greyhounds.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269673","269673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134921","2019-07-01","Department for International Trade","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress he has made on ensuring transitional arrangements for the UK to replace the EU's trade agreement with Georgia; and whether he has plans to enhance that agreement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269674","269674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134922","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Second report of the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Committee of Session 2015–16, Greyhound welfare published on 10 February 2016 and its recommendation that regulations should be extended beyond racetracks to cover standards at trainers’ kennels, if he will amend the Welfare of Racing Greyhound Regulations 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269675","269675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134923","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time is for treatment for transgender people (a) under 18 years old and (b) over 18 years to transition in each of the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269693","269693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134924","2019-07-01","Department for International Trade","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he has taken to negotiate a free trade deal with Grenada after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269676","269676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134925","2019-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to discuss human rights issues in Hong Kong at the next G20 meeting.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269677","269677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134926","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of access to treatment for people that reach the age of 18 while on the waiting list to transition gender.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269694","269694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134927","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives from social media companies to tackle hate speech against transgender people on their platforms.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269695","269695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134928","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that pupils are aware of the non-Jewish victims of the Holocaust.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269678","269678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134929","2019-07-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce trends in the number of pubs closing each year.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269679","269679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134930","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle plagiarism among students at university.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269680","269680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134931","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is (a) taking and (b) plans to take to help tackle the number of extreme lslamists operating on (a) Twitter and (b) other social media platforms.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269681","269681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134932","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage more school leavers to pursue a career in the technology sector.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269682","269682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134933","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more school leavers to pursue a career in the maritime industry.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269683","269683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134934","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Director of Public Prosecutions on ensuring more effective prosecutions of cases involving violent criminals.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269684","269684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134935","2019-07-01","Attorney General","2019-06-26","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with the Director of Public Prosecutions on ensuring more effective prosecutions of cases involving individuals supporting terrorism abroad.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269685","269685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134936","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to improve tourist information facilities at Gatwick airport and other entry points to the UK.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269711","269711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134937","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of protection available to prison officers who are not trained in the use of PAVA spray.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269686","269686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134938","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who identify at Yezidi have been granted asylum under the Syrian Refugee Programme.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269712","269712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134939","2019-07-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress he has made in discussions with the Home Secretary on a two-year, multi-entry touring visa for UK musicians in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269789","269789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134940","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he has made in negotiations with the European Commission on ensuring that musicians’ (a) instruments and (b) equipment can move freely between the UK and the EU when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269790","269790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134941","2019-07-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on ensuring the maintenance of the European Health Insurance Card for UK citizens when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269791","269791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134942","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) Tazidis and (b) Christians from Iraq that have been granted asylum in the UK since 2014.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269707","269707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134943","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the level of greenhouse gas emissions of the decision to exclude electrification from the scope of the Western Phase of the East West Rail project.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269713","269713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134944","2019-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on the recommendation of the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights to establish a fact-finding mission to (a) monitor, (b) verify and (c) report on the situation in Sudan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269731","269731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134945","2019-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help ensure that people guilty of human rights violations and abuses in relation to peaceful demonstrations in Sudan are held accountable for their actions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269732","269732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134946","2019-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for bilaterial relations of the report of the people's tribunal into forced organ harvesting from prisoners of conscience in China.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269733","269733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134947","2019-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold discussions with the Quebec Government on Bill 21 on the wearing of religious symbols by public officials at work.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269734","269734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134948","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of adult male suicides.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269603","269603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134949","2019-07-01","Cabinet Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on immigrants who have died by suicide within the first three years of moving to the UK.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269604","269604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134950","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the revenue forgone to the public purse from the recalculation of the Sovereign-Grant from 15 per cent to 25 per cent of the Crown Estate profits for the financial years 2017-18 to 2027-28.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269792","269792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134951","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the suicide risk among (a) immigrants and (b) each ethnic minority group.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269605","269605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134952","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the difference between the expenditure of the Royal Household and the amount of the Sovereign Grant allocated in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269793","269793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134953","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the £37.8 million spent by the Sovereign on property maintenance was spent on (a) Buckingham Palace, (b) St James's Palace, (c) Windsor Castle, (d) Hampton Court Mews, (e) Windsor Home Park and (f) Kensington Palace.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269794","269794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134954","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the vacancy rate is for nurses in (a) the NHS and (b) social care.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269596","269596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134955","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of current staffing levels in the NHS.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269597","269597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134956","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the quantity of UK plastic waste that has been returned from countries overseas; what steps he is taking to dispose of that waste; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269660","269660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134957","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has with Cabinet colleagues on requiring schools to be energy independent.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269661","269661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134958","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the merits of private sector ownership of electricity networks.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269795","269795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134959","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the re-nationalisation of electricity networks on the level of personal pensions.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269796","269796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134960","2019-07-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of investment in carbon capture usage and storage to help reach the Government's net zero by 2050.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269797","269797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134961","2019-07-01","Department for International Trade","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Open Individual Export Licences for crowd control equipment to the Hong Kong SAR issued on (a) 27 July 2015, (b) 15 January 2016, (c) 15 April 2016 and (d) 9 May 2016 are extant.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269699","269699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134962","2019-07-01","Department for International Trade","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the suspension mechanism that applies to (a) extant and (b) pending licences is applicable to licences for Hong Kong.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269700","269700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134963","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of women taking up careers in STEM.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269798","269798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134964","2019-07-01","Church Commissioners","2019-06-26","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, if the Commissioners will make an estimate of the number of thefts of lead from church buildings in (a) the diocese of St Albans and (b) England in (i) 2018 and (ii) 2019 to date.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269594","269594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134965","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her Written Statement of 20 December 2018, HCWS1224, what progress she has made on the introduction of light touch reviews for people with long-term health conditions who are in receipt of personal independence payment.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269799","269799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134966","2019-07-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the Government's policy is on planning permission for the creation of additional opencast coal mines.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269800","269800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134967","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support the Government provides to vehicle rental companies to transition their fleet to electric vehicles.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269801","269801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134968","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the BBC on proposals to reduce the availability of BBC 3 and BBC 4 television channels for people living outside the UK.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269602","269602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134969","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support his Department provides to local councils to ensure that young refugees are protected by an adequate level of safeguarding.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269802","269802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134970","2019-07-01","Wales Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the funding package announced for the 2022 Commonwealth Games in Birmingham, what assessment he has made of the Barnett consequential for Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269651","269651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134971","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the level of alcohol-related mortality rates in each National Statistics Socio economic classification in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269652","269652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134972","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) children and (b) schools have covered the Battle of Cable Street at Key Stage 3 in the 2018-19 academic year.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269714","269714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134973","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to undertake a review of IR35 legislation ahead of the introduction of Off-Payroll tax.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269715","269715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134974","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to tackle stakeholders' concerns on the Check Employment Status for Tax tool ahead of the introduction of the Off-Payroll tax.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269716","269716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134975","2019-07-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking as part of the loneliness strategy to ensure that community cohesion is considered in the assessment process for prospective Garden Communities.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269717","269717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134976","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what restrictions cover flights by United States Air Force planes over south Lincolnshire to protect residents against disturbance caused by (a) noise and (b) vibrations.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269638","269638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134977","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what safety measures have been implemented to protect (a) pilots and (b) local residents when United States Air Force planes fly over south Lincolnshire.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269639","269639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134978","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the United States Air Force is accountable for accidents caused by its planes in UK airspace.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269640","269640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134979","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether her Department plans to facilitate a dialogue between the United States Air Force and local residents on the frequency of flights over south Lincolnshire.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269641","269641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134980","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests were made for hate crimes against people with learning disabilities in (a) 2018 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Mr Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269642","269642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134981","2019-07-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that second-hand electrical products sold online meet the relevant safety standards.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269803","269803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134982","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there were for hate crimes against people with learning disabilities in (i) 2018 and (ii) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Mr Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269643","269643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134984","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the June 2019 report of the Children’s Commissioner, we need to talk: access to speech and language therapy, if he will meet with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care to discuss the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of that report.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269600","269600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134985","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference the June 2019 report of the Children’s Commissioner, We need to talk: access to speech and language therapy, if he will meet with NHS Clinical Commissioners to discuss the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of that report.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269601","269601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134986","2019-07-01","Department for International Trade","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the implications for his Department's policy on the sale of arms to Saudi Arabia are of the Court of Appeal ruling on 20 June 2019 in R (on the application of Campaign Against Arms Trade) v. The Secretary of State for International Trade.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269653","269653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134987","2019-07-01","Department for International Trade","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the implications of the Court of Appeal ruling on 20 June 2019 in R (on the application of Campaign Against Arms Trade) v. The Secretary of State for International Trade are for his Department's policy on existing licences to export arms to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269654","269654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134988","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has carried out an impact assessment of the effect of reduced access to cash among vulnerable groups including (a) disabled people, (b) BAME people and (c) people on low incomes.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269741","269741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134989","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the status is of the Government's response to each recommendation in the Lammy Review.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269804","269804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134990","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2019 to Question 262421 on prisoners: education, how his Department assesses the range of courses that should be delivered without collecting information on the courses the Parole Board recommends prisoners complete.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269805","269805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134991","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2019 to Question 264474 on prisons: private sector, how he defines funded posts.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269806","269806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134992","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 June 2019 to Question 265568 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service: Staff, if he will publish the information by staff band.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269807","269807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134993","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2019 to Question 263817 on Courts and Probation: ICT, if he will publish the cost to the public purse of the IT systems failures in probation services and the courts in January 2019 once those discussions with suppliers have concluded.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269808","269808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134994","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2019 to Question 264468 on courts: staff, whether his Department holds data relating to the staff service length prior to 2011.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269809","269809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134995","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2019 to Question 264474 on Prisons: Private Sector, how many sufficiently trained and experienced (a) prison custody officers and (b) other staff have contractors at each establishment told the Government they require to maintain safe and decent prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269810","269810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134996","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2019 to Question 259342 on Prisons: Contracts, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of HMP Altcourse’s innovative approach to violence reduction on levels of (a) prison-on-prisoner assaults, (b) prisoner-on-staff assaults, (c) serious prison-on-prisoner assaults and (d) serious prisoner-on-staff assaults between 2010 and 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269811","269811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134997","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answers of 18 June 2019 to Question 264474 on Prisons: Private Sector and of 11 June 2019 to Question 259342 on Prisons: Contracts, whether HMPPS Controllers are required to keep a record of the number of prison custody officers certified to act as such at establishments for which they have responsibility.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269812","269812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134998","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has carried out an impact assessment of regional disparities in access to cash.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269742","269742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134999","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children were recorded as being of no fixed abode on arrival in custody in each custodial institution that holds children in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269813","269813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135000","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women were recorded as being of no fixed abode on arrival in custody in each custodial institution that holds women in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269814","269814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135001","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2019 to Question 256426 on Prisons: Crimes of Violence, how many (a) assailants, (b) suspected assailants and (c) victims there have been in respect of such incidents in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269815","269815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135002","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have died in custody while under an imprisonment for public protection sentence with an initial tariff of less than five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269816","269816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135003","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2019 to Question 251425 on Prisons: Contracts, what the shortfall in staffing levels was at HMP Rye Hill that required the issuing of a Rectification Notice in March 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269817","269817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135004","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2019 to Question 251425 on Prisons: Contracts, what increases were made to staffing levels at HMP Doncaster to enable the closure of the Rectification Notice in July 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269818","269818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135005","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2019 to Question 251425 on Prisons: Contracts, what the staffing levels were at HMP Doncaster at the time the contractual improvement notice of March 2015 was issued.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269819","269819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135006","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment of the effect of reduced access to cash on small businesses.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269743","269743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135007","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2019 to Question 251425 on Prisons: Contracts, what increase in staffing levels was required as part of the contractual improvement notice issued in March 2015 at HMP Doncaster.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269820","269820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135008","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he is having with fin tech providers on delivery of financial services to people and businesses affected by lack of access to cash.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269821","269821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135009","2019-07-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timeline is for the proposed leasehold reform as set out in the Written Statement entitled Housing Policy Update, published on 2 July 2018, HCWS818.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269822","269822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135010","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase access to cash in areas without ATMs.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269823","269823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135011","2019-07-01","Department for International Development","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of work to support the distribution of snake anti-venom products in developing countries; and whether his Department supports any such project.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269701","269701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135012","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for the personal independence payment were refused on the first assessment in 2018; and how many of those applications that were refused were subsequently (a) considered again and (b) granted under Mandatory Reconsideration.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269702","269702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135013","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government will recognise July as International Group B Strep Awareness Month; and what progress has been made on improving (a) prevention and (b) awareness of group B streptococcus .","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269598","269598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135014","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has for a peer-reviewed analysis of the effectiveness of badger culling in reducing the incidence of Bovine Tuberculosis in cattle herds in areas where badger culling schemes has been running for three years or more.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269824","269824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135015","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training and guidance her Department provides to Jobcentre Plus Work Coaches and other staff in her Department on (a) the specific vulnerabilities of women at risk of, or experiencing, sexual exploitation and (b) specialist services that staff may refer to that support women to exit prostitution.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269825","269825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135016","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Home Department, what steps he has taken to commission specialist services that aim to support women to exit prostitution and enter the workplace.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269826","269826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135017","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what her Department's policy is on screening new recruits to identify the risk of sudden cardiac death.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269662","269662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135018","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information the Department holds on the number of NHS Clinical Commissioning Groups that follow the NICE 2017 guideline, NG77, on cataract surgery.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269606","269606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135019","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times his Department has issued a Certificate of Lawfulness to Network Rail for entry to a tenanted railway arch under section 14 of the Railway Regulation Act 1842 in the last five years in (a) London and (b) England.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269827","269827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135020","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to promote best practice across Clinical Commissioning Groups on the NICE 2017 guideline, NG77, on cataract surgery.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269607","269607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135021","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to launch a three-year spending review before the summer recess; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269828","269828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135022","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for financial planning by local authorities of the uncertainty of the timing of the next spending review.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269829","269829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135023","2019-07-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department is aware of any large-scale fire tests carried out in other EU Member States on High Pressure Laminate cladding since June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269830","269830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135024","2019-07-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has asked private manufacturers to disclose the large-scale fire tests they have carried out on High Pressure Laminate cladding since June 2017.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269831","269831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135025","2019-07-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has asked manufacturers of High Pressure Laminate cladding to disclose the result of large-scale fire tests they have carried out on High-Pressure Laminate cladding since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269832","269832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135026","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has spent or plans to spend on converting schools to academies in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21, (e) 2021-22, (f) 2022-23 and (g) 2023-24.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269833","269833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135027","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2019 to Question 267289, which programmes have been funded within the budget lines provided in that Answer; and how much funding has been (a) allocated to and (b) spent by each programme.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269834","269834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135028","2019-07-01","Prime Minister","2019-06-26","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she had discussions at the EU Council on 20-21 June 2019 with her EU27 counterparts on the evidence to the European Parliament's Brexit Steering Group submitted by the campaign group New Europeans in respect of the 2019 European elections; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269835","269835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135029","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) community rehabilitation companies and (b) the Probation Service on the use of algorithms in the probation system.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269689","269689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135030","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with Police and Crime Commissioners in England and Wales on the use of algorithms in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269690","269690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135031","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether her Department has had discussions with the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the UK Steel charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269724","269724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135032","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if she will sign her Department up to the UK Steel charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269725","269725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135033","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the pay band is of the joint chief executive of the mid-Essex Broomfield, Basildon and Southend hospitals.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269663","269663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135034","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answers of 30 January 2019 to Question 214478 and of 26 February to Question 223137, if he will (a) discuss that difference in clinical practice with the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists and (b) ask that college to review its clinical guidelines.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269708","269708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135035","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) ambulances, (b) doctors, (c) paramedics and (d) emergency medical technicians were operationally available for the East of England Ambulance Service NHS Trust on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269664","269664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135036","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many GPs are operating at One Riverside Medical Centre Practice in Hullbridge, Essex; and how many patients are registered at that practice.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269665","269665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135037","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the pay is of the managing directors of (a) mid-Essex Broomfield hospital, (b) Basildon hospital and (c) Southend hospital.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269666","269666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135038","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to additional blue light emergency patient transfers between hospitals proposed in the mid/south Essex sustainability and transformation plan, what estimate has been made of the number of additional emergency transfers each day; in which financial year the contract for those transfers is due to be let; which element of the NHS will fund that contract; whether the contract will be let competitively; and whether the East of England Ambulance Service NHS Trust has the capacity to service that contract.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269667","269667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135039","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department holds data on pupil absence in primary schools in England which is cross-tabulated by school week, year group and reason for absence.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269836","269836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135040","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department holds data on teacher sickness absence in primary schools in England in each school week.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269837","269837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135041","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information he holds on when probate will be granted in the case of Carol Rosalind Green who died on 24 September 2018; and if he will make an assessment of the effect the time taken to grant probate on the ability of the executors to complete the sale of the deceased person's property.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269608","269608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135042","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the public purse of (a) the decision by NICE in May 2019 to enable people with spinal muscular atrophy to access new drugs and (b) enabling all people with relevant conditions to access those drugs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269609","269609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135043","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people with spinal muscular atrophy will be eligible for access to NHS drugs for treatment following the 15 May 2019 announcement by NICE; what his policy is on people who have been excluded from that access; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269610","269610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135044","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason the announcement by NICE on 15 May 2019 that it would facilitate access by people with spinal muscular atrophy to a new drug for prescription on the NHS was followed several weeks later by an announcement that the drug would be available only to a specific group of those people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269611","269611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135045","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what processes he has in place to enable relatives with lasting power of attorney registered with the Public Guardian to apply for pension credit on behalf of those for whom they are responsible; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269612","269612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134113","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent research on the effects on levels of public health of emissions of (a) PM2.5, (b) PM1 and (c) PM0.1 from waste incinerators (i) he has undertaken and (ii) has formed the basis of an assessment of the implications for his policies.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268356","268356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134222","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure a coordinated response across Government on tackling climate change.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268601","268601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134439","2019-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment there has been of the risk that A24 traps pose to hedgehog populations.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269077","269077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134440","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average cost to the NHS is of carrying out a cataract operation.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268959","268959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134441","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC has plans to publish its correspondence with (a) tax payers and (b) agents.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269070","269070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134442","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the transfer of Network Rail's System Operator responsibilities to the devolved regional routes on the effectiveness of Network Rail; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269065","269065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134443","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 June 2019 to Question 265489 on Personal Independence Payment, for what reason recent correspondence on casework enquiries to hon. Members states that waiting times for personal independence payments mandatory reconsiderations are 10 to 12 weeks in County Durham and table 7D, entitled MR clearance time (median calendar days), normal rules, by year of clearance, region and local authority of her Department's quarterly statistical publication, Personal Independence Payment: April 2013 to April 2019 states that such waiting times are 39 median calendar days.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269031","269031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134444","2019-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on supporting the UK car industry through the Government's transition to zero emissions policy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269032","269032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134445","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the UK rail network is electrified.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269033","269033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134446","2019-07-01","Northern Ireland Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking with the Secretary of State for Justice to ensure the construction of the new Magilligan Prison in the absence of devolved Government in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268995","268995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134447","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid in fines by people who submitted tax returns after the deadline of 31 January in each year since 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268996","268996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134448","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the number of (a) fixed-term and (b) permanent school exclusions by local authority area for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269043","269043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134449","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made in the past year in combating the use of drones to supply illegal drugs to prisoners.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268997","268997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134450","2019-07-01","Northern Ireland Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which Department is responsible for allocating funding from the apprenticeship levy in Northern Ireland in the absence of a devolved Administration.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268998","268998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134451","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of the 2019 Loan Charge on the (a) mental health and (b) livelihoods of people affected by that Charge.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268968","268968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134452","2019-06-27","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the results of the recent fire tests on non-ACM cladding demonstrated; how many blocks those tests found to be affected; and when those blocks will be made safe in the same way as blocks affected by ACM cladding.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268957","268957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134453","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to invest in ESOL provision for (a) refugees and (b) migrants.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269044","269044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134454","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many committal orders have been issued under each category for (a) the Child Maintenance Service and (b) the Child Support Agency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269080","269080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134455","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have received compensation for being assaulted by a fellow prisoner in each of the last three years, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269059","269059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134456","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department plans to use to assess the effectiveness of its new guidance issued on Blue Badges for people with (a) dementia and (b) other hidden disabilities.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269103","269103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134457","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has plans to collect data on the number of people with dementia that have been (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful in applying for a Blue Badge.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269104","269104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134458","2019-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the accuracy of the data in relation to tree (a) felling and (b) restocking and the associated granting of felling licences.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269071","269071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134459","2019-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to increase (a) the transparency of the UK timber market and (b) the publication of data on timber production.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269072","269072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134460","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason the application of Capital Gains Tax relief on trees from which private owners of established conifer woodland benefit after the first 10 years.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269073","269073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134461","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to respond to the recommendations in the report entitled, Elitist Britain 2019, published by the Social Mobility Commission in June 2019.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268988","268988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134462","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of the introduction of minimum unit pricing of alcohol in Scotland on the level of alcohol consumption in Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269105","269105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134463","2019-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the Government's price cap for standard variable tariffs on trends in the level of the average household energy bill.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269106","269106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134464","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints Stanley Job Centre has received in relation to disabled access throughout the building in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269005","269005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134465","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department has issued to staff at Stanley Job Centre in relation to disabled access in advance of arranging appointments with claimants.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269006","269006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134466","2019-07-01","Cabinet Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2019 to Question 266672 on Political Parties: Finance, for what reason the Government considers Section 10 of the Political Parties and Elections Act 2009 to be unworkable.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268969","268969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134467","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has held with the (a) Scottish Government and (b) British Transport Police on tackling crime on Scotland's railways.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269107","269107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134468","2019-07-01","Cabinet Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has received representations from the Electoral Commission on the workability of section 10 of the Political Parties and Elections Act 2009.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268970","268970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134469","2019-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the publication of the Defence Technology Framework.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269007","269007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134470","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment of the potential effect of the planned cessation of ring-fencing of the Public Health Grant in 2020 on the (a) quality of drug treatment and (b) rate of drug-related deaths.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269034","269034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134471","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of universal credit on armed forces veterans.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269108","269108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134472","2019-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to increase the maximum sentence available under the Animal welfare (Service Animals) Act 2006.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268962","268962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134473","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government has taken to implement its response to the Indexation and equalisation of the Guaranteed Minimum Pension in public service pension schemes consultation for people reaching state pension age after December 2018.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268958","268958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134474","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department's proposed aviation strategy will include the potential effect of the operation of radar on the implementation of the offshore wind sector deal.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269045","269045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134475","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Government's offshore wind sector deal, published in March 2019, whether his Department has allocated funding to help the renewable energy sector mitigate the effect of aviation radar on the development of offshore wind sites.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269046","269046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134476","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has issued strategic guidance to (a) NATS and (b) the Civil Aviation Authority on the future procurement of aviation radar systems in relation to the effect of those systems on the deployment of new (a) onshore and (b) offshore wind sites.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269047","269047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134477","2019-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2019 to Question 266880 on Yemen: Military Intervention and with reference to the news article entitled, The Saudis couldn’t do it without us: the UK’s true role in Yemen’s deadly war, published by The Guardian on 18 June 2019 in which a senior UK diplomatic source stated that the UK was a party to the conflict in Yemen, for what reason the Answer stated that the UK is not part of the coalition operating in Yemen but did not state whether the UK is a party to the conflict.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269109","269109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134478","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the value for money achieved through (a) the sale of Network Rail arches to Telereal Trillium and Blackstone Property Partners and (b) Network Rail’s re-purchase of some railway arches.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269095","269095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134479","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of railway arches owned by (a) Network Rail and (b) Telereal Trillium and Blackstone Property Partners.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269096","269096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134480","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that Network Rail's sale of railway arches was fully scrutinised; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Network Rail maintains its obligations to protect railway lines above property owned by another company.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269097","269097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134481","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential for conflict between Network Rail’s role in providing public infrastructure and acting as a private landlord.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269098","269098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134482","2019-07-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social and Care on the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement on the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268963","268963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134483","2019-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much and what proportion of fees paid by banks to the Post Office Limited have been paid to sub-postmasters in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269081","269081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134484","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to raise the maximum prize limit for Society Lotteries to £1 million.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268964","268964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134485","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the changes in a claimant's circumstances that would result in natural migration from legacy benefits to universal credit.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268991","268991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134486","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many unsuccessful claims for universal credit there were in Alyn and Deeside constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268992","268992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134487","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of unsuccessful claims for universal credit were as a result of (a) a claimant's lack of digital skills and (b) inadequate support for that claimant.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268993","268993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134488","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of natural migrations to universal credit from legacy benefits were as a result of (a) a trigger for natural migration, (b) claimant error, (c) official error, (d) incorrect advice from staff or contractors and (e) inadequate advice from third party advisers.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268994","268994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134489","2019-06-27","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of his Department's preparations for the UK leaving the EU on 31 October 2019 without a deal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269015","269015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134490","2019-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on intelligence sharing between the UK and EU of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269016","269016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134491","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the provision of healthcare for UK citizens in the EU of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269017","269017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134492","2019-06-27","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish his Department's no deal preparation documents.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269018","269018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134493","2019-07-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps he has taken to reduce the (a) level and (b) risk of homelessness among young people.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269037","269037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134494","2019-06-27","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on using Border Force technology to solve the customs issues when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269019","269019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134495","2019-06-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with representatives from the BBC on the BBC's decision to charge people aged over 75 for TV licences.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269020","269020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134496","2019-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of banning shark fin imports.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269024","269024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134497","2019-06-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the growth of technology firms in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269021","269021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134498","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the changes to IR35 off-payroll rules on the public sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269110","269110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134499","2019-06-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has consulted on safe standing in English football stadiums.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269022","269022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134500","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of whether the Check Employment Status for Tax tool is fit-for-purpose ahead of the roll-out of the off-payroll rules to the private sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269111","269111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134501","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to tackle stakeholder's concerns regarding the roll-out of the off-payroll rules to the private sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269112","269112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134502","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to support contracting and the flexible economy following the roll out of IR35.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269113","269113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134503","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to pause the roll-out of the off-payroll tax to the private sector.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269114","269114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134504","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Court of Appeal hearing on 24 June 2019, how many women have been forced to have an abortion, as decided in their best interests, by NHS trusts in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269115","269115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134505","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which NHS trust was involved in the case on forced abortion heard at the Court of Appeal on 24 June 2019.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269116","269116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134506","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the case heard at the Court of Protection on 21 June 2019 and Court of Appeal on 24 June 2019 on forced abortion, what the total cost of that case was to the NHS trust.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269117","269117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134507","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the case heard at the Court of Protection on 21 June 2019 and Court of Appeal on 24 June 2019 on forced abortion, what guidance is provided to NHS trusts on deciding whether to take legal action in the best interests of patients.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269118","269118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134508","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to prepare for the consequences of data spillages.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268999","268999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134509","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Answer of 24 April 2019 to Question 243336 on Domestic Abuse and Stalking, how many police forces in the UK have undertaken Domestic Abuse Matters training developed by the College of Policing and SafeLives.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268965","268965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134510","2019-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people work in the defence sector by constituency.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269025","269025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134511","2019-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide a breakdown of the workforce employed by the defence sector by (a) profession and (b) qualifications.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269026","269026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134512","2019-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the contribution of the defence sector to the (a) Welsh and (b) UK economy.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269027","269027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134513","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of incidents of stalking of women in England and Wales that were initially dismissed by police in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268966","268966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134514","2019-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide a breakdown of defence spending by constituency.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269028","269028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134515","2019-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of creating a defence diversification agency to ensure the sustainability of the defence sector.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269029","269029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134516","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to encourage women to attend mammography screening.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268967","268967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134517","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2019 to Question 252573, whether that his Department has taken steps to check the scientific veracity of the new Abortion and Abortion Care Factsheet for schools.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269030","269030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134518","2019-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department first became aware that HM Treasury had received tax receipts derived from the interest on frozen Libyan assets held in UK banks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269000","269000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134519","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people are studying medicine as a second degree; and what proportion of those students did not apply for study grants or financial support for their first degree.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269099","269099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134520","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on reducing air passenger duty on domestic flights from Northern Ireland's airports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269001","269001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134521","2019-07-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that tax receipts derived from the interest on frozen Libyan assets held in UK banks are used to compensate the victims of Libyan state-sponsored violence committed by the IRA; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269002","269002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134522","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many civil penalties relating to failure to undertake tasks required for universal credit compliance have been issued in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269119","269119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134523","2019-06-27","Northern Ireland Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress she has made on bringing forward legislative proposals to implement the recommendations of the Hart report into historical institutional abuse in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269003","269003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134524","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much revenue has been received from civil penalties relating to failure to undertake tasks required for universal credit compliance in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269120","269120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134525","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many civil penalties have been passed to debt collection agencies by her Department in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269121","269121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134526","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total monetary amount is of civil penalties which have been passed to debt collection agencies by her Department in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269122","269122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134527","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax was taken by HM Treasury on the interest accrued on Libyan assets frozen in UK banks in each of the years since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269004","269004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134528","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department has received from debt collection agencies in respect of civil penalties in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269123","269123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134529","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many payments of the child element of universal credit have been ceased due to a child being in hospital for over six months in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269124","269124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134530","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the protection and restoration of peat moss in achieving net carbon neutrality for the UK.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268974","268974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134531","2019-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his Department's policy to protect remaining areas of peat moss in the UK from development.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268975","268975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134532","2019-06-27","Home Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he plans to include officers from Humberside Police on the National Police Air Service.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269090","269090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134533","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the equality of availability of shared policing resources across all relevant police forces.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269091","269091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134534","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who is responsible for monitoring compliance by transport companies with the law on disability access.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269078","269078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134535","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on securing the recognition by EU countries of UK certificate of professional competence driving qualifications in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269094","269094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134536","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of the loss of a force-specific police helicopter on the quality of air support in the Humberside area.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269092","269092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134537","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of fixed wing aircraft compared to helicopters in providing air support to police operations.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269093","269093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134538","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is his policy that the (a) Department or (b) rail franchise operator announces (i) extensions, (ii) direct awards and (iii) other changes to franchise agreements.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269066","269066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134539","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June to Question 266855 on Future Large Aircraft, what the cost to the public purse is of the anticipated work programme to improve the reliability of the A400M; what the planned length of time is for the completion of that programme; what the key features are of that programme; and whether that work programme will take place at RAF Brize Norton.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269009","269009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134540","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether she has plans to cancel the Warrior Capability Upgrade Programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269010","269010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134541","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June to Question 265492: BBC, what his policy is on funding public service broadcasting in the (a) North East of England and (b) Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269035","269035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134542","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Typhoon aircraft have been delivered to the RAF; and how many Typhoon aircraft on order are (a) Tranche 1, (b) Tranche 2 and (c) Tranche 3 aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269011","269011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134543","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his legal settlement with Eurotunnel cost in (a) VAT and (b) departmental officials' time.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269067","269067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134544","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what requirements for troops to parachute from the A400M were included in the original specification for that aircraft; whether the A400M has been cleared to deliver that capability; on how many occasions the A400M has delivered that capability; and what assessment she has made of potential technical issues that would prevent the parachuting of troops from the A400M.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269012","269012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134545","2019-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking in response to the Court of Appeal's ruling on the legality of British sales of arms to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268978","268978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134546","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many A400M aircraft have been (a) ordered by and (b) delivered to (i) the RAF, (ii) the Luftwaffe, (iii) the Spanish Air Force, (d) the Italian Air Force and (e) other nations air forces.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269013","269013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134547","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) neighbourhood police officers and (b) police officers in visible frontline roles there were in each police force area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269125","269125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134548","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons contain an electronic gate with at least one safety feature disengaged; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269060","269060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134549","2019-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps she is taking to (a) protect the mental health and (b) treat mental health issues of members of the armed forces during training.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269082","269082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134550","2019-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps she is taking to (a) protect the mental health and (b) treat mental health issues of members of the armed forces during service in combat zones.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269083","269083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134551","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that veterans with mental health problems receive the treatment they need.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269084","269084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134552","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2019 to Question 266839 on Prescriptions: Fees and Charges, how his Department monitors the National Health Service Business Services Authority in relation to appeals against wrongly issued prescription penalty charge notices.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269036","269036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134553","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what monitoring is taking place on university campuses to ensure compliance with the International Holocaust Remembrance Association definition of anti-semitism.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269079","269079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134554","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department has issued to foreign-owned banks trading in the UK on the regulation of the use of bank accounts by people on the UN sanctions list.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269061","269061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134555","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2019 to Question 266153 on Hawk Aircraft, how many times have Hawk T1 aircraft been given over to advanced jet training since July 2016.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269014","269014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134556","2019-07-01","Cabinet Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the senior civil service that were privately educated.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268971","268971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134557","2019-07-01","Cabinet Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what data his Department holds on the educational background of civil servants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268972","268972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134558","2019-07-01","Cabinet Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of senior civil servants that were educated at (a) Oxford and (b) Cambridge University.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268973","268973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134559","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2019 to Question 267348, whether hybrid HS2 trains will stop at Wigan Station.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269126","269126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134560","2019-07-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether she plans to hold discussions with the Government of Saudi Arabia on future UK arms sales to that country; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268960","268960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134561","2019-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the criteria are for exclusion on medical grounds for recruits to GCHQ.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269127","269127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134562","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the implications for the aims of the Online Harms White Paper of the adoption of new technical standards to bypass the blocking of online content; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268954","268954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134563","2019-07-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to reduce the number of households living temporarily in bed and breakfasts, private hostels, short-stay houses of multiple occupancy and guesthouses.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268955","268955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134564","2019-07-01","Cabinet Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of applications for GovTech catalyst funding were successful in each funding round.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269128","269128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134565","2019-07-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people living temporarily on license agreements in privately-owned (a) bed and breakfast accommodation, (b) hostels, (c) short-stay house in multiple occupation and (d) guesthouses were placed by local authorities in discharge of a statutory homelessness duty.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268956","268956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134566","2019-07-01","Home Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the need for new police stations in Newton-le-Willows and St Helens; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269085","269085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134567","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of apprenticeship starters were eligible for free school meals in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) the North West and (c) England in each quarter of each academic year since 2014.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269086","269086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134568","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of people entering higher education by age 19 in (a) 2018-19 and (b) each of the last five academic years were eligible for free school meals in (i) St Helens North constituency, (ii) the North West and (iii) England.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269087","269087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134569","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of apprenticeship starts that were eligible for free school meals started (a) intermediate, (b) advanced and (c) higher apprenticeships in (i) St Helens North constituency, (ii) the North West and (iii) England in the first quarter of the academic year (A) 2018-19, (B) 2017-18, (C) 2016-17, (D) 2015-16 and (E) 2014-15.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269088","269088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134570","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many businesses in (a) St Helens North constituency and (b) the North West hired apprentices in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269089","269089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134571","2019-06-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to promote coastal tourism in the UK; and what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on tourism of the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268989","268989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134572","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement, Government review confirms local authorities will continue to commission public health services, published by his Department on 7 June 2019, when he plans to publish the proposals in relation to the review of the commissioning arrangements for sexual and reproductive health set out in paragraph 2.4 of the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269039","269039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134573","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor for the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with banks on the potential effect on rural communities of the removal of free cash machines from high streets.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268990","268990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134574","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement, Government review confirms local authorities will continue to commission public health services, published by his Department on 7 June 2019 and paragraph 2.4 of the NHS Long Term Plan, in what form will the consultation into the proposals to improve co-commissioning developed in relation to the commissioning arrangements for sexual and reproductive health be conducted.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269040","269040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134575","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 2.4 of the NHS Long Term Plan, what public consultation his Department undertook with the sexual and reproductive health sector on the review of the commissioning arrangements for sexual and reproductive health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269041","269041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134576","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of the Public Health Grant in (a) the current Spending Review Period and (b) the next Spending Review on the (i) level of quality of drug treatment services and (ii) number of drug-related deaths.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269042","269042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134577","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Check Employment Status for Tax Tool ahead the roll-out of the Off-Payroll rules to the private sector.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268953","268953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134578","2019-07-01","Department for International Development","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much money was paid by organisations contracted by his Department to deliver aid projects to consultants in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268961","268961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134579","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consultation his Department undertook in determining the membership of the Economic Crime Strategy Board.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269129","269129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134580","2019-07-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) non-molestation orders, (b) occupation orders and (c) injunctions were granted in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269023","269023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134581","2019-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many local authority checks have been undertaken on non multi-boarding dog boarding hosts since the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (England) Regulations 2018 were published.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268976","268976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134582","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consultation his Department undertook in determining private sector representation on the Economic Crime Strategy Board.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269130","269130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134583","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether representatives from (a) academic institutions and (b) civil society were invited to sit on the Economic Crime Strategy Board.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269131","269131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134584","2019-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average cost is of a premise check for a non multi-boarding dog boarding host since the implementation of the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities Involving Animals) (England) Regulations 2018.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268977","268977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134585","2019-07-01","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what role the chief executive officers and chief executives from (a) Barclays, (b) Lloyds and (c) Santander will perform in determining the UK’s operational response to economic crime.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269132","269132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134586","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new universal credit claimants received an additional two weeks' housing benefit in each month since April 2018.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269068","269068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134587","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what sums her Department expended on funding the additional two weeks' of housing benefit for new universal credit claimants in each month since April 2018.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269069","269069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134588","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people had their benefit payments reduced to (a) less than £6 per day, (b) less than £5 per day and (c) zero due to the imposition of sanctions by her Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269074","269074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134589","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what percentage of people aged over 65 receive some form of social care.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269075","269075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134590","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of schoolgirls aged between 11 and 18 participated in at least 30 minutes of sport at least once a week in 2018.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269076","269076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134591","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Research and analysis entitled, Supporting mental health in schools and colleges conducted by his Department, what steps the Government has taken to increase the provision of counselling services in schools.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269133","269133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134592","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that schools in Yorkshire and the Humber achieve the England average for the number of Ofsted schools ranked good.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269134","269134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134593","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department has allocated to further education colleges in low-income communities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269135","269135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134594","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the Government’s policy is on the use of isolation booths for discipline in schools; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the use of isolation booths.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269136","269136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134595","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the money retained by private schools as a result of the VAT exemption on private school fees in 2017-18.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269137","269137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134596","2019-06-27","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to reduce homelessness in lower layer super output areas.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269138","269138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134597","2019-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps the Government is taking to support a peaceful conclusion to the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269139","269139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134598","2019-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support a diplomatic resolution to the stand-off between the United States of America and the Islamic Republic of Iran.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269140","269140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134599","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department provides to local authorities to ensure that those authorities have access to fully trained animal welfare inspectors to enforce the Animal Welfare Act 2006.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269141","269141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134600","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2019 to Question 266845, on antidepressants what assessment he has made of the potential merits of developing a policy to monitor the proportion of patients prescribed antidepressants who do not take that medication for the prescribed length of time.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268979","268979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134601","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the proportion of children who have experienced adverse childhood experiences in each National Statistics Socio-economic classification.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268980","268980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134602","2019-07-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the diagnosis rates of dementia in each local authority area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268981","268981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134603","2019-07-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of investment in the automotive manufacturing industry in the UK relative to the EU average in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268982","268982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134604","2019-07-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the proportion of people with long-term mental ill health who are in paid employment.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268983","268983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134605","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the proportion of claimants of employment support allowance that have a mental illness as their primary impairment.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268984","268984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134606","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people with long-term mental health conditions that have become unemployed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268985","268985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134607","2019-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what level of charges Approved Enforcement Agencies may add to original financial penalties imposed by criminal courts, and whether his Department has plans to change that level.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269100","269100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134608","2019-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the level of charges added by Approved Enforcement Agencies to the original financial penalties imposed by criminal courts in each of the last four quarters.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269101","269101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134609","2019-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the expected savings to the public purse through service contracts with Approved Enforcement Agencies.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269102","269102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134610","2019-06-27","Cabinet Office","2019-06-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the proportion of public sector workers that have reported mental ill health in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268986","268986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134611","2019-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the expected savings to the public purse of outsourcing warrants of arrest work to Approved Enforcement Agencies.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269142","269142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134612","2019-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much Approved Enforcement Agencies will be paid for carrying out warrants of arrest work on behalf of his Department.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269143","269143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134613","2019-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full time equivalent Civilian Enforcement Officers are in post.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269144","269144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134614","2019-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full time equivalent vacancies for Civilian Enforcement Officers there are.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269145","269145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134615","2019-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date the most recently appointed Civilian Enforcement Officer commenced employment.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269146","269146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134616","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with HM Treasury on the application of 20 per cent VAT on e-publications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269038","269038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134617","2019-06-27","Department for International Development","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of depression in developing countries.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268987","268987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134618","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) improve the quality of and (b) increase access to public health care in (i) Stevenage and (ii) Hertfordshire.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269050","269050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134619","2019-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps the Government has taken to ensure that (a) mothers and (b) people with primary care responsibilities have access to flexible working.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269051","269051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134620","2019-06-27","Department for International Development","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment his Department has made of the humanitarian situation in (a) Idlib and (b) Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269052","269052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134621","2019-06-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps his Department has taken to tackle the spread of disinformation and fake news online.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269053","269053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134622","2019-06-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle social isolation in older people through the digital sector.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269054","269054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134623","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department taking to fund performing arts education for young people under 18 years-old.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269055","269055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134624","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help people recently recovered from long-term illness find and return to work.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269056","269056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134625","2019-06-27","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much money from the public purse was spent by local authorities in England on services (a) promoting and (b) providing services for children and young people’s mental health in 2018-19.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269147","269147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134626","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data his Department holds on Government expenditure on mental health provision for children and young people (a) under the age of 18; (b) from 18 to 25 years old in 2018-19.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269148","269148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134627","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS appointments have been missed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269057","269057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134628","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the annual cost to the public purse was of missed NHS appointments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269058","269058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134629","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Government Loneliness Strategy, what progress his department has made on convening a rural stakeholder group to (a) advise and support the work of Government Departments and (b) help support the communication of initiatives and good practice at a local level.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269062","269062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134630","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Loneliness Strategy, what steps his Department is taking with the Loneliness Action Group to (a) share learning on loneliness and (b) ensure the effective implementation of that strategy.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269063","269063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134631","2019-07-01","Department for Transport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken with the Loneliness Action Group to improve the transport network as part of the Government's loneliness strategy, published in October 2018.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269064","269064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134632","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department plans to take to help people over 75 with a long-term complex illness such as dementia to pay for a TV licence from June 2020.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269149","269149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134633","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance his Department plans to provide to carers who work with people over 75 to help those people pay for a TV licence from June 2020.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269150","269150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134634","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed changes to the TV licence for people over 75 on the accommodation for residential care concessionary TV licence; and what guidance his Department plans to provide to residential care homes on the effect of the change on that licence.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269151","269151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134635","2019-07-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the removal of free TV licences for people aged over 75 on people with sight impairments.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269152","269152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134636","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy for his Department to procure only plastic free period products for schools.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269008","269008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134637","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure co-operation with the EU on tackling air pollution after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269048","269048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134638","2019-07-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment,Food and Rural Affairs what steps he is taking to promote cross-departmental collaboration on adopting World Health Organisation standards for fine particulate matter.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269049","269049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1132411","2019-06-19","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average length of time between death and cremation by region in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18 and (c) 2018-19; and what steps he is taking to reduce that time.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 265571","265571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1133993","2019-06-26","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a salary sacrifice car scheme for teachers in state schools.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268486","268486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1133994","2019-06-26","Department for Transport","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the DVSA's Theory Test for cars and motorcycles, which ten questions within that Test candidates most frequently answered (a) correctly and (b) incorrectly in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268487","268487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1133995","2019-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to change the qualifying criteria for the enhanced mobility component of personal independence payment to allow claimants with dwarfism to access specially adapted mobility vehicles.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268488","268488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1133996","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made in compensating victims of historical abuse at Aston Hall, Derbyshire.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268489","268489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1133997","2019-06-26","Treasury","2019-06-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department taking following the collapse of London Capital & Finance to ensure that mini-bond holders in Crewe and Nantwich will be properly compensated.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268490","268490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1133998","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of legislation regulating body modification following the prosecution of Brendan McCarthy.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268491","268491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1133999","2019-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to tackle anthropogenic climate change and global warming.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268492","268492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134000","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to encourage members of the Commonwealth to share the same goals in tackling anthropogenic climate change and global warming.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268493","268493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134001","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he took to raise concerns on USA withdrawing from the Paris Climate Agreement during President Trump's recent visit.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268494","268494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134002","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has any plans to reintroduce blood glucose test strips on prescription for Type 2 diabetics.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268495","268495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134003","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure all Type 2 diabetics have access to a glucose monitoring blood test every three months as standard.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268496","268496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134004","2019-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ban the export of live animals from the UK for fattening and slaughter.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268497","268497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134005","2019-06-27","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department continues to pursue deportation proceedings in cases in which people have been found to have been trafficked under section 22 of the Human Trafficking and Exploitation (Criminal Justice and Support for Victims) Act (Northern Ireland) 2015.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268498","268498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134006","2019-06-26","Northern Ireland Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the merits of the Northern Irish Government’s model of providing independent guardians to all separated and trafficked children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268499","268499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134007","2019-06-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the BBC on the proposed removal of free television licences for people aged over 75.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268373","268373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134008","2019-06-26","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to implement the Augar recommendations to deliver a fairer higher education system.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268374","268374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134009","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on a universal credit claimant’s health and well-being of the ability to repay hardship payments.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268345","268345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134010","2019-06-27","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of whether out-of-country appeals are appropriate for students to challenge visa revocations as a result of allegations of cheating in the TOEIC English language test.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268346","268346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134011","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will commit to bringing forward a national sexual health strategy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268500","268500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134012","2019-06-24","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timeframe is for his receiving a report from the University of Bristol on prostitution in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268396","268396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134013","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to prevent listeria in food in hospitals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268501","268501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134014","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to prevent heart disease in young people aged 17-30.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268502","268502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134015","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that wounded soldier health and rehabilitation bills are paid for by the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268503","268503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134016","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when electrical stimulation for arthritis pain will be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268504","268504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134017","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what advice is available to people travelling overseas for dental or cosmetic surgery.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268505","268505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134018","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will list the (a) criteria and (b) timelines for products to be considered in (i) the current round and (ii) future review rounds of the Accelerated Access Collaborative route.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268506","268506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134019","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how products selected by the Accelerated Access Collaborative will be funded.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268507","268507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134020","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether all products considered by the Accelerated Access Collaborative will have to be cost-neutral to the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268508","268508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134021","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Accelerated Access Collaborative has to prioritise products which help control hospital-acquired infections.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268509","268509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134022","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the Accelerated Access Collaborative plans to balance its focus on (a) medicines, (b) diagnostic tools and (c) digital services.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268510","268510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134023","2019-06-26","Treasury","2019-06-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he will take to ensure that dementia care is adequately funded in the next Spending Review.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268511","268511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134024","2019-06-26","Treasury","2019-06-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on funding for dementia care.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268512","268512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134025","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what standards his Department uses to set acceptable levels of (a) vibration, (b) noise and (c) dust and air quality in construction projects funded by his Department; and when those applicable standards were (i) set and (ii) last reviewed.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268446","268446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134026","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the construction of Ealing Fields High school, what his Department's policy is on provision of compensation for (a) structural and (b) non-structural damage caused by construction of Departmental projects.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268447","268447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134027","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of Local Cycling and Walking Infrastructure Plans in delivering their goals.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268426","268426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134028","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how rates of testicular cancer diagnosis in the UK compare with ratse in other G20 countries over the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268427","268427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134029","2019-06-27","Cabinet Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the transparency data entitled Cabinet Office ministerial meetings January to March 2019, published on 21 June 2019, if he will publish the (a) organisations and (b) individuals that attended (i) Roundtable discussion on Digital Transformation in Government on 12 February 2019; (ii) Roundtable on digital innovation in government on 17 January 2019; (iii) Discussion on Strategic Approach to Public Appointments on 21 January 2019; (iv) Roundtable on digital innovation in government, 24 January 2019; (v) Discussion of ongoing Civil Service Compensation scheme negotiations on 28 January 2019; (vi) Discussion on Strategic Approach to Public Appointments on 28 January 2019; (vii) Discussion of ongoing Civil Service Compensation scheme negotiations on 6 February 2019; (viii) Discussion on Public Appointments Events on 6 February 2019; (ix) Roundtable discussion on Workforce issues across the Public Sector on 12 February 2019; (x) Discussion on government outsourcing and innovation on 12 February 2019; (xi) Discussion on the work of the Government Digital Service on 19 February 2019; (xii) Discussion on Digital Accessibility on 19 February 2019; and (xiii) Discussion on Govtech and digital innovation in government on 26 February 2019.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268379","268379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134030","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the NHS Diabetes Prevention Programme.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268428","268428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134031","2019-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing more support for farmers to control weeds without using synthetic herbicides.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268430","268430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134032","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make available the scoring data of the respective bids for grant funding from the Holiday Activities and Food Programme 2019.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268442","268442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134033","2019-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children in receipt of disability living allowance in the Yorkshire and Humber region were required to transition to personal independence payment upon turning 16 years of age, whilst still in full-time education.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268513","268513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134034","2019-06-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the total cost incurred to the public purse has been of the CyberEssentials programme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268514","268514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134035","2019-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what analysis her Department has conducted on the psychological effect on children of transitioning at 16 years of age from disability living allowance to personal independent payment while in full-time education.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268515","268515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134036","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the availablity of (a) critical and (b) short shelf-life medicines in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268516","268516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134037","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason his Department decided to charge visa applicants £5.48 for email inquiries.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268417","268417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134038","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money in cash terms his Department raised from levying a £5.48 charge on email visa enquiries in 2018.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268418","268418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134039","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money in cash terms his Department raised from levying an additional £1.37 per minute on top of the standard network charge on telephone visa enquiries in 2018.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268419","268419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134040","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa or settlement applicants paid for the priority service in 2018; and how many of those applicants received a response within one working day.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268420","268420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134041","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the criteria his Department use to assess the performance of VFS Global in handling visa and settlement applications.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268421","268421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134042","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish his Department’s most recent assessment of VFS Global’s performance in meeting targets in relation to their handling of visa and settlement applications.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268422","268422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134043","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will provide in cash terms the value of the charge levied upon visa and settlement applicants for having documents (a) scanned and (b) photocopied by his Department.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268423","268423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134044","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the contract held between his Department and VFS Global on handling visa and settlement applications.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268424","268424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134045","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans to renew the contract held between his Department and VFS Global in relation to handling visa and settlement.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268425","268425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134046","2019-06-27","Department for Transport","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the increase in use of electric scooters on roads.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268469","268469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134047","2019-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the effect of plasticulture on the environment; and what support his Department is giving to farmers to tackle plastic waste within their businesses.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268406","268406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134048","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were detained (a) in total and (b) for more than 24 hours in short-term holding facilities at (i) Heathrow and (ii) Gatwick airport in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268348","268348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134049","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made implementing the recommendations of the Independent Monitoring Boards to improve conditions in short-term holding facilities.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268349","268349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134050","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people currently in Immigration Removal Centres claim to be under 18 years old.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268350","268350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134051","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his policy is on detaining in Immigration Removal Centres people who claim to be under 18 years old but whose age is disputed by his Department.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268351","268351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134052","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reporting locations there are for asylum seekers in each local authority area.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268352","268352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134053","2019-06-26","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his policy is on increasing the number of reporting locations for asylum seekers.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268353","268353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134054","2019-06-26","Cabinet Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have died from cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268517","268517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134055","2019-06-26","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been withdrawn from school to be home educated in Gloucestershire in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and how many of those children (a) before or (b) subsequent to their withdrawal have had an Education, Health and Care Plan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268354","268354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134056","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to respond to the letter of 26 April 2019 from the hon. Member for Glasgow East, reference DL3281.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268518","268518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134057","2019-06-26","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information he holds on the progress that LocatED has made on finding and purchasing a site for the Swift Secondary Academy in Walsall North in partnership with Windsor Academy Trust.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268519","268519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134058","2019-06-26","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the funding allocated to build the Swift Secondary Academy in Blakenall ward in partnership with Windsor Academy Trust remains in place.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268520","268520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134059","2019-06-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to make it easier and quicker for (a) local and (b) combined authorities to take ownership of unused brownfield sites through compulsory purchase with adequate compensation for owners to bring them back into economic use for (i) homes and (ii) employment and remove derelict properties from local communities.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268521","268521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134060","2019-06-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing in Walsall a pilot scheme to streamline the process of bringing unused brownfield sites back into public use.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268522","268522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134061","2019-06-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that shared home ownership is affordable in London.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268523","268523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134062","2019-06-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the Starter Homes programme on levels of shared ownership.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268524","268524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134063","2019-06-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of what consumer protections are required as private providers enter the shared ownership market.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268525","268525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134064","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with Whirlpool on its online system for the reporting by consumers of tumble dryers which require modification for reasons of safety; and what his understanding is of the timescales involved for consumers once they have made such a report.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268526","268526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134065","2019-06-26","Department for International Trade","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Chartered Institute of Building's report entitled from China Road to Silicon Road, published May 2019, and its finding that China’s Belt and Road Initiative could deliver a $178 billion boost to UK GDP, what assessment he has made of the potential merits for the UK of formally joining the Belt and Road Initiative.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268527","268527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134066","2019-06-26","Department for International Trade","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential benefit to the UK construction sector of China's Belt and Road Initiative.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268528","268528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134067","2019-06-26","Department for International Trade","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions his Department has had with the UK construction sector on the skills that sector can provide to the Belt and Road Initiative (BRI); and what assessment he has made of the importance of the BRI to future UK-China international partnerships.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268529","268529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134068","2019-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the Government has made to commemorate the 75th anniversary of Victory over Japan Day in 2020.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268438","268438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134069","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2019 to Question 264333, how many and what proportion of individual claims for universal credit were not paid (a) on time and (b) in full in each for the last six months for which information is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268397","268397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134070","2019-06-26","Treasury","2019-06-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what safeguards his Department has put in place to prevent online VAT fraud.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268530","268530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134071","2019-06-26","Treasury","2019-06-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HMRC takes in responding to complaints on online VAT fraud; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of HMRC's response to such complaints.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268531","268531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134072","2019-06-26","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how long the funding commitments are for the (a) Primary Sports Premium and (b) Healthy Pupils Capital Fund.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268532","268532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134073","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of unpaid overtime in the TV, film and radio production industries; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure companies in those industries pay their employees for overtime worked.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268533","268533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134074","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the continued smooth import and export of continence products and similar medical devices in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268443","268443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134075","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what role has recently been played by Deloitte, and at what cost, in the development by NHS Improvement of proposals to introduce a centralised NHS procurement system for products and services; and what steps are being taken to ensure that the introduction of such a system does not lead to a restriction on the freedom of medical practitioners to prescribe any continence product on the Medicines Tariff that they consider to be the most appropriate product for the individual patient.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268444","268444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134076","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the (a) Health Care Supply Association, (b) main trade associations for suppliers of continence products and (c) organisations representing patients who use continence products have been consulted on the development by NHS Improvement of proposals to introduce a centralised NHS procurement system for products and services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268445","268445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134077","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department will publish the Green Paper on prevention.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268534","268534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134078","2019-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employers have signed up to the Government’s voluntary reporting framework on disability, mental health and wellbeing since it was launched in November 2018.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268535","268535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134079","2019-06-27","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to EU Settlement Scheme Statistics, May 2019: Experimental Statistics, how any applications have been received from the West Midlands.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268536","268536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134080","2019-06-27","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to EU Settlement Scheme Statistics, May 2019: Experimental Statistics, page 4, if he will provide a breakdown of the proportion of applicants by nationality.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268537","268537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134081","2019-06-27","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the May EU Settlement Scheme, May 2019: Experimental Statistics, how many of the pre-settled status application conclusions were due to the applicant not having five years’ continuous residence.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268538","268538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134082","2019-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with (a) Ofcom, (b) Ofwat and (c) Ofgem on incentives for innovation and research and development in their sectors and how that relates to the 2.4 per cent GDP spend on R&D target.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268539","268539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134083","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2019 to Question 264335, how many of the 77,952 calculations that were disputed by claimants related to late reporting of wages by employers to HMRC.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268398","268398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134084","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to improve response times to recommendations for endovascular thrombectomy treatment for severe strokes which can be administered only within 24 hours.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268413","268413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134085","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has in place to increase the number of specialists trained in endovascular thrombectomy treatment.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268414","268414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134086","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason endovascular thrombectomy treatment is provided 24/7 only at Stoke-on-Trent hospital and St George's hospital in London; and what steps he plans to take to widen the provision of that service.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268415","268415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134087","2019-06-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason not all health trusts provide endovascular thrombectomy treatment.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268416","268416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134088","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many new NHS hospital facilities specifically for secondary and acute care in England (a) have been built, (b) are under construction and (c) are planned for completion between 2015 and 2025; what the (i) location and (ii) estimated capital value is of each of those new hospital facilities, including those that are valued at less than £100 million; and what the proportion of financing for each project is (A) public and (B) private financing.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268474","268474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134089","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, who will be attending the economic crime strategy board meeting on 10 July 2019.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268540","268540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134090","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what elements of the economic crime strategy will be discussed at the economic crime strategy board meeting on 10 July 2019.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268541","268541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134091","2019-06-27","Treasury","2019-06-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether extending the failure to prevent criminal offence for bribery to other economic crimes, such as fraud and money laundering, will be discussed at the economic crime strategy board meeting on 10 July 2019.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268542","268542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134092","2019-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies previously registered as non-resident for corporation tax purposes in countries other than Luxembourg provided an address in Luxembourg to the Land Registry in May 2019.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268475","268475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134093","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department allocated from the apprenticeship budget to (a) apprenticeship levy paying employers, (b) top up payments to apprenticeship levy paying employers, (c) non-apprenticeship levy paying employers, (d) ongoing costs of apprenticeships already in training prior to 1 April 2017, (e) English and maths qualifications, (f) incentive payments for 16- to 18-year-old apprentices and (g) additional support for apprentices that are care leavers or have special needs in financial year (i) 2017-2018 and (ii) 2018-19.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268543","268543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134094","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of applications for (a) universal credit and (b) job seekers allowance were rejected on the Habitual Residency Test in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268476","268476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134095","2019-06-27","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for asylum in the UK were made by unaccompanied minors that arrived in the UK by their own means since 2016.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268477","268477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134096","2019-06-27","Home Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that unaccompanied children in other EU Member States with family in the UK are informed for their rights to apply for family reunification under EU Regulation 604/2013.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268478","268478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134097","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  what estimate he has made of the number of children under the age of 16 that smoke who smoke in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268429","268429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134098","2019-06-26","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to ensure that businesses understand the value of the new T Level qualifications before their implementation in 2020.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268544","268544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134099","2019-06-26","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to promote technical and vocational education and training in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268545","268545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134100","2019-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions,  how many people in receipt of (a) employment support allowance and (b) personal independence payments are (i) autistic and (ii) have autistic spectrum disorders.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268546","268546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134101","2019-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of (a) employment support allowance and (b) personal independence payments have (a) Autism and (b) autistic spectrum disorders in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268547","268547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134102","2019-06-27","Prime Minister","2019-06-24","To ask the Prime Minister, what meetings she held with the Chancellor of Germany between 1 and 6 July 2018.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268548","268548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134103","2019-06-27","Prime Minister","2019-06-24","To ask the Prime Minister, what records were kept of meetings she held with European heads of state in the 12 months to 6 July 2018.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268549","268549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134104","2019-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support adults with Autism gain employment.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268550","268550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134105","2019-06-27","Cabinet Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has plans to give prisoners in England the right to vote.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268431","268431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134106","2019-06-26","Treasury","2019-06-24","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Financial Conduct Authority survey of defined benefit pension advice published on 19 June 2019, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of advice provided by the financial services industry on the potential merits of transferring out of defined benefit pension schemes.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268448","268448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134107","2019-06-27","Department for International Trade","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2019 to Question 265577 on UK Export Finance, how many hon. Members attended each of those briefings.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268551","268551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134108","2019-06-27","Department for International Trade","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2019 to Question 265577 on UK Export Finance, whether his Department plans to hold further breakfast briefings.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268552","268552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134109","2019-06-27","Department for International Trade","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the recent Court of Appeal ruling on arms exports to Saudi Arabia and criterion 2c of the Consolidated EU and National Arms Export Licensing Criteria which states that licences should not be granted if there is a clear risk the equipment to be exported might be used in a serious violation of international humanitarian law, if he will suspend arms sales to (a) Bahrain and (b) the United Arab Emirates.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268343","268343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134110","2019-06-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of doses of flu vaccine required in winter 2019-20 and (b) proportion of those doses which will need to be sourced from outside the UK; and what plans he has in place to ensure the adequate supply of flu vaccine in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268344","268344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134111","2019-06-27","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with which EU member states the UK has concluded a reciprocal agreement on the right of each other's citizens to (a) vote and (b) stand as candidates in local elections after the UK leaves the EU; and with which EU member states are discussions ongoing.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268553","268553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134112","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children (a) are on the home education register and (b) have been removed from school by their parents or guardians in each local authority area in the South West in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268355","268355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134114","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children who are being educated at home but who are not listed in the Home Education register in each South-west Authority in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268357","268357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134115","2019-06-26","Department for Transport","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) Civil Aviation Authority and (b) European Aviation Safety Agency on the imposition by Airbus of flight speed restrictions on H175 helicopters used to transport offshore oil and gas workers.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268479","268479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134116","2019-06-26","Department for Transport","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of recent news reports of a crack in the tailpiece of a H175 helicopter operated by NHV from Aberdeen to offshore oil and gas installations; and what steps he is taking to reassure offshore workers about the safety of H175 models.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268480","268480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134117","2019-06-26","Department for Transport","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Civil Aviation Authority’s Safety review of offshore public transport helicopter operations in support of the exploitation of oil and gas, CAP1145, will be completed.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268481","268481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134118","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the effect on offshore oil and gas workers of flight speed restrictions imposed on H175 helicopters operating in the North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268482","268482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134119","2019-06-27","Prime Minister","2019-06-24","To ask the Prime Minister, what meetings were held between her and the Chancellor of Germany in the 12 months to 6 July 2018.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268554","268554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134120","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the date of a universal credit claim is protected in the contract Citizen's Advice have with her Department to support such claims.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268555","268555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134121","2019-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have been sanctioned in universal credit at (a) Shettleston and (b) Laurieston Jobcentres in each of the last 12 months; and for what reasons.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268556","268556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134122","2019-06-26","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support (a) schools and (b) local authorities in providing additional services to help young people with early signs of mental ill health.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268557","268557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134123","2019-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Ugandan Ambassador to the UK on press freedom and civil liberties in that country.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268432","268432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134124","2019-06-27","Department for Education","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that schools and colleges follow guidance on exam procedure to minimise the risk of security breaches.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268433","268433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134125","2019-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress made in England, Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland on meeting the 2011 Bonn Challenge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268399","268399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134126","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the role that carbon capture and storage technology could play in reducing emissions in the (a) heavy industry, (b) transport, (c) power and (d) heating sectors.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268483","268483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134127","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the role carbon capture and storage technology can play in decarbonising the transport sector.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268484","268484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134128","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of potential UK capacity to supply bioenergy that can generate negative emissions through bioenergy with carbon capture and storage (BECCS).","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268485","268485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134129","2019-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of supporting the export of carbon capture, usage and storage technologies.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268558","268558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134130","2019-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2019-06-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the findings of the June 2019 report by the Prison Reform Trust, Prison: the facts, what steps his Department is taking to (a) tackle overcrowding and (b) improve conditions in prisons.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268434","268434"
