"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147971","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to create a regulator for online political advertising.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293488","293488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147972","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Brazilian counterpart on the increase in deforestation of the Brazilian Amazon over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293489","293489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147973","2019-10-07","Cabinet Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September to Question 286366 and with reference to page 10 of the Government Transformation Strategy, which Minister made the decision to extend the objective of appointing a Chief Data Officer from by 2020 to in 2020; and on what date that decision was made.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293725","293725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147974","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Russian counterpart on the release of the Ukrainian student Serhiy Rusynov, who has been held for almost a year held by Russian backed separatists in Donbas.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293490","293490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147975","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all schools teach every part of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293491","293491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147976","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of people prosecuted for illegal waste exports in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293492","293492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147977","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will introduce independent regulation of the media to protect people from invasive and unethical journalism.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293499","293499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147978","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to ban the (a) production and (b) use of polystyrene plastic packaging in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293493","293493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147979","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress (a) his Department and (b) the NHS has made since February 2017 on preventing and reducing neonatal sepsis.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293705","293705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147980","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of obligating all retailers to ensure that the packaging of products sold can be recycled locally before stocking those products.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293494","293494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147981","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question 290603, what support is available to people who would otherwise be eligible for benefits and who are undergoing long-term hospital care to pay for (a) mortgages, (b) rents and (c) other personal and care charges to help ensure that they do not lose their unit of accommodation while in NHS-funded care.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293432","293432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147982","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will fund the improvement to junctions on the A14 with the A1156 (East of Ipswich) and A12 (North), the A1189, the A1214 and A12 (South) and the A1156 (West of Ipswich) as requested by the New Anglia LEP and associated organisations.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293735","293735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147983","2019-10-07","Cabinet Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office,  what progress he has made on the establishment of the Office for Tackling Injustices; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293689","293689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147984","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2019 to Question 281772 on Teachers: Pay Settlements, from which Departmental budget the £105 million transferred into the Teachers' Pay Grant in the current financial year was drawn.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293690","293690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147985","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many meetings Ministers in his Department have held with Ministers in the Cabinet Office on the National Data Strategy in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293726","293726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147986","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of trends in the level of remuneration for chief executives in the charity sector in the last five years.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293706","293706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147987","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the latest timetable and scope of improvements being planned to TransPennine Services on the Huddersfield Rail line; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293566","293566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147988","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Integrated Communities Action Plan published in February 2019, whether his Department has facilitated meetings between the Anti-Muslim Hatred Working Group and Independent Press Standards Organisation to help them to develop guidance for editors and journalists to tackle unnecessary negative portrayals of Muslims in the media.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293516","293516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147989","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding her Department has allocated to the (a) creation and (b) implementation of the Government Data Strategy.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293727","293727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147990","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department will review the cost of train fares.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293736","293736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147991","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what dedicated emergency support her Department has put in place to help and advise Thomas Cook members of staff who have lost their jobs.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293716","293716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147992","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employees of Thomas Cook who have lost their jobs following the company's collapse have been offered alternative employment opportunities as of 2 October 2019.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293717","293717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147993","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to provide pension protection for Thomas Cook staff.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293718","293718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147994","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of supermarkets on the sale of endangered fish species.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293476","293476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147995","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Ofgem is able to collate accurate data on the installation of solar power units.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293680","293680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147996","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Department has taken to ensure that women who are unable to use alternative forms of HRT have access to HRT patches.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293445","293445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147997","2019-10-07","Cabinet Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to ensure that the London Living Wage is paid by all Government Departments and their contractors.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293677","293677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147998","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has departmental responsibility for local welfare assistance schemes.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293545","293545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147999","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department is responsible for allocating funding for local welfare assistance schemes.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293546","293546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148000","2019-10-07","Cabinet Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings (a) members of the Cabinet and (b) their predecessors have had with EU officials in each of the last twelve months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293498","293498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148001","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what further steps the Government is taking to reduce the use of single-use plastics; and what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of levies to further reduce the use of plastics.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293681","293681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148002","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of local health providers on medical staff vacancies at Bedford Hospital NHS Trust; and how many and what proportion of vacancies there are in each discipline.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293685","293685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148003","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the funding announced for the merger of Bedford Hospital Trust and Luton and Dunstable University Hospital Trust will be allocated to improving infrastructure and facilities at Bedford Hospital.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293686","293686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148004","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 6 and 9 September to Questions 282507, 282510, 282514, 282515, 282516, 282517, 282518, 282519, 282520, 282521, 282522, 282523, 282524, 282525, 282527, 282528 and 282529, what (a) programmes and (b) deliverables were included in the Food, sustainable and competitive farming programme under the heading Food and Farming; and if she will publish the (i) Resource Departmental Expenditure Limit, (ii) Capital Departmental Expenditure Limit and (iii) Annually Managed Expenditure funding allocated to each of those programmes for 2019-20.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293609","293609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148005","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with Bedfordshire Clinical Commissioning Group and East London Foundation Trust on plans to reinstate inpatient mental health beds in Bedford.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293687","293687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148006","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of EU citizens who have been in UK over five years have been given pre-settled status.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293606","293606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148007","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much has been spent on diagnostic equipment for cancer including MRI and CT scanners at Bedford Hospital NHS Trust in each year since 2010; and what the average spend on diagnostic equipment for cancer was per capita year in each of those years.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293688","293688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148008","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of non-UK EU citizens who have been granted pre-settled status have resided in the UK for over five years.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293607","293607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148009","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 6 and 9 September to Questions 282507, 282510, 282514, 282515, 282516, 282517, 282518, 282519, 282520, 282521, 282522, 282523, 282524, 282525, 282527, 282528 and 282529, what specific programmes and deliverables to tackle waste and promote recycling are included under which headings; and if she will publish the (a) Resource Departmental Expenditure Limit, (b) Capital Departmental Expenditure Limit and (c) Annually Managed Expenditure funding allocated to each of those programmes for 2019-20.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293610","293610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148010","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 6 and 9 September to Questions 282507, 282510, 282514, 282515, 282516, 282517, 282518, 282519, 282520, 282521, 282522, 282523, 282524, 282525, 282527, 282528 and 282529, what specific funding for National Parks is included under which headings; and if she will publish the (a) Resource Departmental Expenditure Limit, (b) Capital Departmental Expenditure Limit and (c) Annually Managed Expenditure funding allocated to National Parks for 2019-20.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293611","293611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148011","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 6 and 9 September to Questions 282507, 282510, 282514, 282515, 282516, 282517, 282518, 282519, 282520, 282521, 282522, 282523, 282524, 282525, 282527, 282528 and 282529, what air quality programmes and deliverables are included under which headings; and if she will publish the (a) resource departmental expenditure limit, (b) capital departmental expenditure limit and (c) annually managed expenditure funding allocated to air quality programmes and deliverables for 2019-20.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293612","293612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148012","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, who the successful supplier was in the tender for the Express Freight Service.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293608","293608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148013","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that the ability of refugees and people seeking asylum to reunite with family members in the UK under the Dublin III Regulation will be safeguarded in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293719","293719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148014","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to protect the rights of families to reunite under the Dublin Regulation in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293720","293720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148015","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on families who are eligible to be reunited under the provisions of the Dublin III Regulation.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293721","293721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148016","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many take charge requests under the Dublin III Regulation were accepted in the first six months of 2019.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293722","293722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148017","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were transferred to the UK under Article (a) 8, (b) 9 (c) 10, (d) 11 and (e) 12 of the Dublin III Regulation in the first six months of 2019.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293723","293723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148018","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) recruit and (b) retain GPs.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293549","293549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148019","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the number of cases where children who have experienced potentially irreversible brain injury have been able to receive ventilation at home after a tracheostomy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293507","293507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148020","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) target and (b) average time taken is between the completion of an immigration tribunal and the implementation of that tribunal's decision.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293550","293550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148021","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the regional consistency of treatment where children who have experienced potentially irreversible brain injury are able to receive ventilation at home after a tracheotomy.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293508","293508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148022","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 6.1 of the Report of the Liverpool Community Health Independent Review by Dr Bill Kirkup, published in January 2018, what steps NHS Improvement has taken to implement the recommendation that when approving Trust Board appointments, NHS Improvement should take note of the level of experience of appointees and level of risk in the Trust and should ensure a system of support and mentorship for Board members where indicated.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293465","293465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148023","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether financial considerations are involved when decisions are made by NHS trusts on the possibility of brain injured children receiving ventilation at home following a tracheostomy.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293509","293509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148024","2019-10-07","Treasury","2019-10-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many retail bank branches there are per head of population.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293551","293551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148025","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with developers to encourage them to build on brownfield sites.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293552","293552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148026","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the proportion of home ownership was in (a) England, (b) Surrey and (c) Woking constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293553","293553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148027","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the strength of the UK's diplomatic relations with Egypt.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293554","293554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148028","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the UK's role in global ocean conservation.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293555","293555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148029","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in what capacity NHS Improvement gave advice to the Blackpool Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust between June 2019 and September 2019 on the appropriateness of the Trust (a) discussing the possibility of merging services and provision between the Trust and the East Lancashire Hospitals NHS Trust and (b) the potential for the East Lancashire Trust's Chief Executive, Kevin McGee, to operate as the permanent Chief Executive of both trusts.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293466","293466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148030","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of demand for local authority-provided children’s services.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293556","293556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148031","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many people have participated in the National Citizen Service in each local authority area in Surrey in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293557","293557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148032","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of lifting the ban on direct flights from the UK to Sharm El Sheikh airport in Egypt.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293558","293558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148033","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of lifting the UK flight ban to Sharm el Sheikh.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293559","293559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148034","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support the mental health of veterans.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293560","293560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148035","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to recruit and retain service personnel.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293561","293561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148036","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to maintain the capabilities of UK defence manufacturing.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293562","293562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148037","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the support provided by UK armed forces to the Bahamas following Hurricane Dorian.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293563","293563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148038","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to review the funding of sixth form colleges.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293564","293564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148039","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to protect UK shipping in the Strait of Hormuz.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293565","293565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148040","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what cognisance NHS Improvement took of the oral contribution of the Minister for Health of 27 June 2018, Official Report, column 1002, on irregularities of process that had taken place including at NHS Improvement in respect of the appointment process for the Chair of the Blackpool Trust, Pearse Butler, when advising the Chair of the Trust between June 2019 and September 2019 on those matters.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293467","293467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148041","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what consultation NHS Improvement had with hon. Members whose constituencies fall within the area served by the Blackpool Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust on their discussions and advice to the Trust between June 2019 and September 2019 on (a) the possibility of merging services and provisions and (b) on allowing the East Lancashire Trust's Chief Executive Kevin McGee to operate as the permanent Chief Executive of both trusts.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293468","293468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148042","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with NHS Improvement on its progress in implementing the Kirkup governance report, published in February 2018.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293469","293469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148043","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the annual report and accounts for the Air Travel Trust Fund for the year ending March 2019 have not been published on the CAA website.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293737","293737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148044","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the Air Travel Trust Fund’s insurance policies.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293738","293738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148045","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost of insurance premiums on insurance and reinsurance policies for the Air Travel Trust Fund was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293739","293739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148046","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to Reducing UK emissions - 2019 Progress Report to Parliament, published by the Committee on Climate Change on 10 July 2010, for what reasons 21 of the 56 risks and opportunities identified in the UK’s Climate Change Risk Assessment have no formal actions in the National Adaptation Programme.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293517","293517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148047","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the levels of excess payments are on (a) insurance and (b) reinsurance policies taken out by the Civil Aviation Authority to cover payouts from the Air Travel Trust Fund.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293740","293740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148048","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the UK Government plans to seek membership of or co-operator country status with the European Environment Agency in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293518","293518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148049","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations the UK Government has received on the UK’s relationship with the European Environment Agency from (a) the Scottish Government, (b) the Welsh Government and (c) the Northern Ireland Executive.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293519","293519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148050","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the value is of the (a) insurance and (b) reinsurance that the Air Travel Trust Fund has that covered the collapse of Thomas Cook; and which insurance companies underwrite that insurance.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293741","293741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148051","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on the monitoring, measuring and reporting of environmental outcomes in the event that the UK ends its membership of the European Environment Agency.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293520","293520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1148052","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much money he expects to recover from credit and debit card companies in relation to the costs incurred after the collapse of Thomas Cook.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293742","293742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147086","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department first received a communication from the hon. Member for Plymouth Moor View on the (a) continuation and (b) termination of his role at Crucial Academy Ltd.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292099","292099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147342","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the number of women that did not receive Hormone Replacement Therapy as a result of shortages of those therapies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292433","292433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147396","2019-10-03","Leader of the House","2019-10-01","To ask the Leader of the House, with reference to the debate on EU Settlement Scheme: Looked-after Children and Care Leavers on 3 September 2019, whether he has plans to bring forward the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 (Legal Aid for Separated Children) (Miscellaneous Amendments) Order 2019 for debate.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292994","292994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147397","2019-09-03","Leader of the House","2019-10-01","To ask the Leader of the House, with reference to the debate on EU Settlement Scheme: Looked-after Children and Care Leavers on 3 September 2019, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on the provision of time for a debate on the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 (Legal Aid for Separated Children) (Miscellaneous Amendments) Order 2019.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292995","292995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147398","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for eye care appointments.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292821","292821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147399","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Single Energy Area for Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland will continue in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292933","292933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147400","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will place in the Library each estimate that has been provided  to Government since January 2019 on the potential reduction in the flow of food between the EU and the UK in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement if the Government (a) takes and (b) does not take steps to mitigate the reduction in those flows.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292934","292934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147401","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will place in the Library each estimate that has been provided to Government since January 2019 on the potential reduction in medicine flows from the EU to the UK in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a Withdrawal Agreement if the Government (a) takes and (b) does not take steps to mitigate those reductions.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292935","292935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147402","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how her Department plans to support new programmes that would have been eligible for Rural Development Programme funding after 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292936","292936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147403","2019-10-07","Wales Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how his Department plans to support new programmes that would have been eligible for Rural Development Programme funding after 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292937","292937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147404","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that NHS England's reduction of single-use plastics in healthcare do not prevent best practice in approaches to catheterisation.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292878","292878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147405","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to investigate allegations made by whistleblower Jon Wedger against the Metropolitan Police.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292945","292945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147406","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of allowing British National (Overseas) passport holders to live and work in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292899","292899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147407","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of detainees abroad who hold a British National (Overseas) passport who have been provided with consular assistance in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292900","292900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147408","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the findings of the Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders Motor Industry Facts 2019 report that in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal 52.6 per cent of UK produced cars are exported to the EU, what steps the Government plans to take to support the automotive industry in the event that the UK leave the EU without a deal and exports of those cars are subject to a 10 per cent tariff in line with WTO rules.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292865","292865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147409","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to undertake a review of the legislation on pavement parking.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292982","292982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147410","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the (a) terms of reference and (b) timeframe is for the National Bowel and Bladder Product trial undertaken by NHS England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292926","292926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147411","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the National Bowel and Bladder product trial undertaken by NHS England does not result in a restriction of the full range of medical devices available for clinicians to prescribe through Part IX of the Drug Tariff.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292927","292927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147412","2019-10-07","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution of the Exchequer Secretary to the Treasury of 30 September 2019, Official Report, column 981, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the housing sector of short positions against the pound in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292970","292970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147413","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) ECMT and (b) short-term ECMT international road haulage permits have been (i) applied for, (ii) approved and (iii) refused each month in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292930","292930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147414","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 274650 on Large Goods Vehicles: EU Countries, which bilateral agreements he expects to be (a) revived and (b) reinstated.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292931","292931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147415","2019-10-07","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer, what his Department's base case planning assumptions were before that document was published.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292787","292787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147416","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what sectors his Department plans to prioritise for support in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292788","292788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147417","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on UK ports of the UK leaving the EU under the Government's worst case planning assumptions.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292789","292789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147418","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what preparations her Department for policing operations in relation to traffic management in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292790","292790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147419","2019-10-07","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding his Department has allocated to Operation Kingfisher.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292791","292791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147420","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to implement the recommendation in the National Childbirth Trust's Hidden Half campaign to add a maternal six week postnatal check to the GP contract.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292971","292971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147421","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September to Question 290725 on Kilroot Power Station, when she plans to undertake a strategic assessment of the asset life of individual power stations to assess future power generation requirements and strategy.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292947","292947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147422","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the revised commissioning date is for Hinkley Point C nuclear power station; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292948","292948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147423","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish a response to EDM 2723 on Joint All Party Parliamentary Group Report on Visa Problems for African visitors to the UK.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292938","292938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147424","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Bishop of Truro’s Independent Review for the Foreign Secretary of FCO Support for Persecuted Christians, what progress he has made with his counterparts at the UN on enhancing the protections afforded to (a) Christians and (b) other minority religions in the Middle East.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292976","292976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147425","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Cabinet plans to discuss the recommendations of the Bishop of Truro’s Independent Review for the Foreign Secretary of FCO Support for Persecuted Christians.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292977","292977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147426","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish his Departments papers in relation to the release of political prisoners from Chile in 1975.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292862","292862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147427","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many GCSE entries for arts subjects there were from students in Mansfield constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292989","292989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147428","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding her Department has allocated to Powerchair Football in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292990","292990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147429","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding he has allocated to repair roads in Mansfield constituency in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292991","292991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147430","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to increase public awareness of the symptoms of bowel cancer.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292992","292992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147431","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what funding his Department has made available to (a) local authorities and (b) councils to comply with website content accessibility guidelines.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293001","293001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147432","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle delays in the supply of HRT medications.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292912","292912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147433","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the provision of Hormone Replacement Therapy.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292913","292913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147434","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 July 2019 to Question 280282, on HIV infection, if he will place in the Library the number of finished consultant episodes in relation to (a) primary and (b) secondary diagnoses of HIV infection in (i) England and (ii) each English region in each year since 1989; and if he will provide that information in the format used in the Answer of 19 March 2015 to Question 227661.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292914","292914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147435","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the revised Joint Spatial Plan for South Gloucestershire will not effect the building of affordable homes in the Filton and Bradley Stoke area.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292887","292887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147436","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on transgender people of the shortage of Hormone Replacement Therapy medication.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292915","292915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147437","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason there was a delay in Omar Barghouti being informed of the approval of his visa to travel to the UK from the Occupied Palestinian Territories in September 2019 after that visa was approved.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292826","292826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147438","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with (a) representatives of clinical commissioning groups and (b) families on increasing the uptake of childhood immunisation.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292816","292816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147439","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has assessed the potential effect on public health of allowing children who have not received the MMR vaccine to start primary school in September 2019.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292817","292817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147440","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps her Department is taking to tackle Internet Service Provider monopolies.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292888","292888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147441","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to prevent children who have not received the MMR vaccine from attending school.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292818","292818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147442","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households in (a) Wallasey constituency, (b) Wirral and (c) Merseyside are living in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292836","292836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147443","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the mean funding is per pupil for SEND provision in (a) Wallasey constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the North West in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292837","292837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147444","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was of providing free television licences to people over the age of 75 for qualifying residents in (a) Wallasey constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the North West in 2018-19.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292838","292838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147445","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will (a) bring forward legislative proposals to require local authorities to provide food waste bins and (b) allocate funding to local authorities to provide those waste bins.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292993","292993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147446","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle (a) falling rates of childhood vaccination and (b) anti-vaccine misinformation.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292848","292848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147447","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many meetings she had with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June 2019 to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292859","292859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147448","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many advance benefit payments were made to people in (a) Wallasey constituency and (b) Wirral in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292839","292839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147449","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many tonnes of carbon dioxide were displaced by renewable (a) electricity and (b) heat generation in (i) the UK, (ii) England, (iii) Scotland and (iv) Wales in (A) 2016, (B) 2017 and (C) 2018.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292949","292949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147450","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in the US Administration on the creation of accidental Americans through the US Foreign Account Tax Compliance Act.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292963","292963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147451","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to support a UN-enforced arms embargo against Myanmar.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292885","292885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147452","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 291081 on Cybercrime: Skilled Workers, for what reason the Answer did not include information on whether a target has been set for the number of people to be assisted by the third round of funding from the Cyber Skills Immediate Impact Fund.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292998","292998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147453","2019-10-07","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 01 October 2019 to Question 291474 on Get Ready for Brexit Advertising, when the Government plans to publish regular spending figures for the Get Ready for Brexit advertising campaign.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292985","292985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147454","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 May 2019 to Question 254811 on Electronic Training Aids, when the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ban the use of electronic shock collars.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292895","292895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147455","2019-10-07","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department, when he plans to respond to the letter of 10 December 2018 from the hon. Member for North Durham to the Financial Secretary to the Treasury on Landfill Tax Fraud.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292856","292856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147456","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken since the judgment issued by Mr Justice Swift in May 2019 that the tactile voting device for blind people was unlawful.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292863","292863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147457","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is a fully accessible voting option for blind voters, following the judgment in May 2019 by Mr Justice Swift that the tactile voting device was unlawful.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292864","292864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147458","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the green paper on funding social care.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292928","292928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147459","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has made of the effect on young drivers of pay-as-you-drive car insurance.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292996","292996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147460","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of knife crime in (a) Slough constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292978","292978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147461","2019-10-07","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps are being taken to ensure (a) asylum support payments and (b) other welfare payments will (i) be available to and (ii) provide adequate support to those most vulnerable to (A) rising food prices and (B) food supply disruption in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292997","292997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147462","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce incidences of knife crime in (a) Slough constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292979","292979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147463","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 September 2019 to Question 290332 on Department of Health and Social Care: Energy Supply, what initiatives are included in the on-going programme to reduce emissions; and what the timeframe is for the implementation of each of those initiatives.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292896","292896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147464","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve transport links between the Isle of Wight and Portsmouth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292983","292983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147465","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has his Department made of the effect on the (a) economic prosperity (b) well-being of people on the Isle of Wight of improved transport links between the Isle of Wight and Portsmouth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292984","292984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147466","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 September 2019 to Question 290332 on Department of Health and Social Care: Energy Supply, whether the criteria used by Crown Commercial Services to select an energy supplier for Government Departments and public bodies includes an assessment of the environmental policies of a supplier; and what recent steps Crown Commercial Services has taken to reduce CO2 emissions from energy use in the (a) supply of and (b) demand for energy.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292897","292897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147467","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has he made of the financial effect on low-income families of the cost of a school uniform.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292980","292980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147468","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 272140 on Right of Abode: Veterans, when her Department plans to make a decision on whether to grant right of abode to former British-Hong Kong servicemen.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292939","292939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147469","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the trends in the level of GP trainees.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292981","292981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147470","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to submit a resolution to the UN Security Council requiring members of the Myanmar military responsible for the persecution of Christians and Muslims to be investigated by the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292866","292866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147471","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Myanmar counterpart on the repression of Kachin Christians in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292867","292867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147472","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Ukrainian counterpart on that country's prospective membership of NATO.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292868","292868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147473","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether her Department has authorised the sale of telecommunications equipment to (a) Saudi Arabia and (b) the UAE for use by the armed forces of those countries to direct operations of their front-line troops in conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292869","292869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147474","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish the Memorandum of Understanding between the UK and Brazilian Governments on the £20 million of investment allocated from the Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292870","292870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147475","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of the Government’s investment in Brazil out of the Prosperity Fund has been allocated to programmes that strengthen environmental protections in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292871","292871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147476","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of the Government’s investment in Brazil out of the Prosperity Fund has been allocated from Official Development Assistance.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292872","292872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147477","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish the amount of money the Government plans to invest in Brazil out of the Prosperity Fund for each of the next four years; and to which programmes that investment will be allocated.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292873","292873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147478","2019-10-03","Department for International Trade","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that UK companies investing in Brazil do not contribute to deforestation in the Amazon.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292874","292874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147479","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if she will publish her Department's latest assessment of the effect on the supply of medicines to the UK of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292875","292875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147480","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if his Department will publish their most recent impact assessment of the effects on the UK of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292876","292876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147481","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish her Department's latest assessment of the effect on the supply of food to the UK of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292877","292877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147482","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the previous Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport of 22 July 2019, Official Report, column 1135, on the Telecoms Supply Chain Review, whether her Department has set a timetable for the decision on what involvement Huawei should have in the provision of the UK’s 5G network.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292999","292999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147483","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when Ofcom is expected to report on its investigation of whether CGTN's coverage of Hong Kong protests broke broadcasting rules.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292954","292954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147484","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps her Department is taking to support research into cost-effective alternatives to coal for heavy industry.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292851","292851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147485","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure that medicines to treat cancer in children are available in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292923","292923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147486","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal on access to EU clinical trials for children with rare cancers.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292924","292924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147487","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will set out the performance targets for the determination of complaints to the Independent Case Examiner’s Office in 2019-20.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292819","292819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147488","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what Independent Case Examiner’s Office budget is for 2019-20.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292820","292820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147489","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to help local authorities recruit foster carers.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292918","292918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147490","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to make an assessment of the level of risk of wild fires to (a) Commonwealth nations and (b) British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292973","292973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147491","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has for maintaining access to (a) the European Reference Network on paediatric haemato-oncology and (b) other European reference networks in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292925","292925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147492","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research funding his Department has allocated to the research on the  treatment of vector borne diseases prevalent in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292974","292974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147493","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to reduce the incidences of the use of restraint in children's homes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292919","292919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147494","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of funding allocated by his Department to research on the (a) prevention and (b) cure of vector-borne diseases prevalent in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292975","292975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147495","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Sexual Harassment of UK Doctors: Report 2019 published by Medscape on 1 October 2019, what steps his Department is taking to safeguard junior doctors and medical students against sexual harassment at work.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292852","292852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147496","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to help businesses increase access for disabled people to (a) apprenticeships and (b) jobs.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292853","292853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147497","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the work of local non-governmental organisations, journalists and lawyers operating in occupied Crimea, Donetsk and Luhansk.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292854","292854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147498","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to expand the safeguarding system used to investigate the deaths of vulnerable adults to include everyone who has died while street homeless.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292855","292855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147499","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding was allocated to (a) the Money Advice Service, (b) the Pensions Advisory Service and (c) Pension Wise in each of the five years up to and including 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292822","292822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147500","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding the Money and Pensions Service will receive in 2019.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292823","292823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147501","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of pensioners who rented a home from a private landlord in each year since 2010; and how many and what proportion of pensioners renting from private landlords were in rent arrears in that time period.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292824","292824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147502","2019-10-03","Department for International Development","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to work alongside the One Last Push campaign to ensure that (a) funding and (b) other support is available for polio vaccination programmes in countries at risk from that disease.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292825","292825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147503","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has assessed potential links between the European Institute for Human Sciences and proscribed organisations.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292860","292860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147504","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to protect students at Islamic education centres in the UK from being exposed to potentially radicalising ideology; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292861","292861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147505","2019-10-07","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the next Spending Review will be (a) launched and (b) completed.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292916","292916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147506","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people of pensionable age receiving personal independence payments have been sent a notification requiring them to reapply for that benefit.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292906","292906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147507","2019-10-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims of child sexual abuse have had an award by the Criminal Injuries and Compensation Scheme withheld because (a) of an unspent conviction, (b) the time limit for application was exceeded, (c) the victim was deemed to have consented and (d) the abuse did not involve physical contact.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292917","292917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147508","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when forces will be told of the allocation of funding in order to recruit 6,000 additional officers.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292955","292955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147509","2019-10-07","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the benefit freeze will be lifted in 2020.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293002","293002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147510","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Leadec cleaning staffing provision will be maintained on the First Trenitalia West Coast franchise.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292901","292901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147511","2019-10-07","Scotland Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on HELMS Green Deal mis-selling; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292950","292950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147512","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what specification has been provided for the (a) new and (b) renovated fleet on the First Trenitalia West Coast Franchise.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292902","292902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147513","2019-10-07","Scotland Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on VAT refunds for Police Scotland and Fire Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292951","292951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147514","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding from the public purse was provided to Wigan University Technical College in each year from 2013 to  2019.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292903","292903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147515","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department took steps to try to prevent the closure of Wigan University Training College.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292904","292904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147516","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support his Department has provided to students and their families since the decision to close Wigan University Training College.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292905","292905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147517","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for the publication of the White Paper on energy policy.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292952","292952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147518","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the capacity of (a) anti-corruption intelligence units, (b) counter-corruption units, (c), counter corruption investigation units and (d), the counter-corruption intelligence unit to undertake vetting for new recruits.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292956","292956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147519","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons RDEL in the Supplementary Estimates 2018-19 and the Main Estimates for 2019-20 are different for (a) infrastructure costs, (b) equipment support costs, (c) other costs and services and (d) administration costs.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292879","292879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147520","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his officials had with the Insolvency Service on the draft Finance Bill 2019-20 prior to its publication on 11 July 2019; and whether views were sought on the policy to make HMRC a secondary preferential creditor in insolvencies.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292832","292832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147521","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of establishing HMRC as a secondary preferential creditor in insolvencies on the sustainability of the Pension Protection Fund.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292833","292833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147522","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the policy to make HMRC a secondary preferential creditor in insolvencies on the number of corporate insolvencies from Q1 2020 onwards.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292834","292834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147523","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department will take to ensure the timely publication of (a) GCSE and (b) other test results by multi-academy-trust run schools.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293003","293003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147524","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of establishing HMRC as a secondary preferential creditor in insolvencies on the ability of SMEs to access finance.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292835","292835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147525","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how times the National Policing Board has met in the last year.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292957","292957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147526","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the Resource AME in the Main Estimates 19-20 and the Supplementary Estimates 18-19 are different.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292880","292880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147527","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to teachers at 6th-form colleges on gaining timely access to pupils' previous school's test results in order to set meaningful targets for pupil improvement.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293004","293004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147528","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of (a) the per patient cost to the NHS of treating C-difficile infection (b) the cost the NHS of treating bed-bound patients in hospitals as a result of that infection in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292908","292908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147529","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of treating patients with (a) severe or life-threatening and (b) acute or mild C-difficile infection.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292909","292909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147530","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the Ring-fenced budgets in Main Estimates 19-20 and Supplementary Estimates 18-19 are different.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292881","292881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147531","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the criteria was for deciding that Bristol Port needed £100,000 to prepare for the UK exiting the EU.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292840","292840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147532","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of treating patients with recurrent C-difficile infection in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292910","292910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147533","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money the NHS spent on (a) probiotics and (b) prebiotics in the last (a) 12 months and (b) five years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292911","292911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147534","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Burglary Taskforce has met since its first meeting on 29 April 2019.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292958","292958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147535","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which outcomes from the meeting of the Burglary Taskforce on 29 April 2019 have been implemented.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292959","292959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147536","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, on what date she plans to start the roll-out of 5G in Brecon and Radnorshire constituency.","Biography information for Jane Dodds","Jane Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293005","293005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147537","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police staff and officers are working on the Government funded social media hub to tackle violent content online; and what the volume is of gang-related content that has been (a) disrupted and (b) removed from social media platforms.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292960","292960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147538","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which social media companies have signed up to the Government code of conduct for social media platforms.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292961","292961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147539","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to support (a) claimants with cancer and (b) other vulnerable claimants applying for universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292792","292792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147540","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that home visits for universal credit applications are offered to (a) claimants with cancer and (b) other vulnerable claimants.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292793","292793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147541","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans for further trials of Ecosub platforms in the next two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292857","292857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147542","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government taking to reduce the number of homeless people that die while living on the street.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292827","292827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147543","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the trend in the level of deaths of homeless people is investigated.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292828","292828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147544","2019-10-07","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timeframe is for the next Governor of the Bank of England to take up their post.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292849","292849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147545","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the sexual harassment of NHS staff by (a) members of the public and (b) other NHS staff members.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292829","292829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147546","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure that junior doctors can make complaints about senior and consultant doctors (a) anonymously and (b) without repercussions to their career prospects.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292830","292830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147547","2019-10-07","Northern Ireland Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, by what date would legislation have to be introduced to prevent Welfare Reform mitigations in Northern Ireland expiring on 31 March 2020.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292850","292850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147548","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of vaccinating all cattle against the TB virus.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292889","292889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147549","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the sexual harassment of NHS staff on (a) patient safety and (b) quality of patient care.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292831","292831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147550","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people with cancer that live within a mile of (a) an electricity pylon and (b) a mobile telecommunications mast.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292890","292890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147551","2019-10-07","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of rough sleepers who have died in each of the last seven years who previously served in the armed forces.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292841","292841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147552","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to prevent mobile telecommunications companies from financially exploiting consumers with roaming charges in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292891","292891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147553","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the accuracy of (a) homelessness and (b) rough sleeping statistics.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292842","292842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147554","2019-10-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a committee of inquiry into the causes and effects of the Afghanistan operation between 2003 and 2014.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292892","292892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147555","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on just-in-time manufacturers of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292843","292843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147556","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of drivers of private hire vehicles using a microphone whilst in transit.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292893","292893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147557","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the new homes ombudsman will be appointed.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292953","292953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147558","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress her Department has made on creating a single assessment service for benefits claimants who are disabled or have long-term health conditions.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292898","292898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147559","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Governement, whether he is consulting on permitting a further two per cent increase to local authority precepts in order to fund social care.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292946","292946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147560","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure local surgeries in Southampton are not understaffed.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292962","292962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147561","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how the safety performance of train operating companies at train stations is reported.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292894","292894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147562","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on school suppliers listed as part of Operation Kingfisher.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292986","292986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147563","2019-10-07","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of Operation Kingfisher's (a) bailout fund and (b) administration.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292987","292987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147564","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to make new migraine treatments available through the NHS.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292964","292964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147565","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effects of Operation Snow Bunting planning on the A34 in (a) Oxfordshire and (b) other counties.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292988","292988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147566","2019-10-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 6 and 9 September to Questions 282507, 282510, 282514, 282515, 282516, 282517, 282518, 282519, 282520, 282521, 282522, 282523, 282524, 282525, 282527, 282528 and 282529, what programmes were included in the Natural environment and atmosphere improvement programmes under the heading Improve the Environment; and if she will publish the (a) the Resource Departmental Expenditure Limit, (b) Capital Departmental Expenditure Limit and (c) Annually Managed Expenditure funding allocated to each of those programmes for 2019-20.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292921","292921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147567","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 6 and 9 September to Questions 282507, 282510, 282514, 282515, 282516, 282517, 282518, 282519, 282520, 282521, 282522, 282523, 282524, 282525, 282527, 282528 and 282529, what programmes were included in the Wildlife, international, climate and forestry programme under the heading Improve the Environment; and if she will publish the (a) Resource Departmental Expenditure Limit, (b) Capital Departmental Expenditure Limit and (c) Annually Managed Expenditure funding allocated to each of those programmes for 2019-20.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292922","292922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147568","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the roll-out of the off-payroll rules on levels of UK contracting roles.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292929","292929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147569","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Post Office annual report 2018-19 will be published.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292972","292972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147570","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what indicators his Department uses to measure the effectiveness of the children's care system.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292920","292920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147571","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to permit implied consent for benefit advisers, as well as Members of Parliament, as recommended by the Social Security Advisory Committee.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292794","292794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147572","2019-10-07","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of to Question 291263, what steps (a) his Department and (b) the FCA have taken to ensure that insurers are aware of their responsibility to inform consumers of changes to the way their policies are serviced in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292844","292844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147573","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the reasons for differing rates of home visits to universal credit applicants in different geographical areas; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292795","292795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147574","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 290584, whether his Department was aware of the Saudi Press Agency release of 14 September 2018 that stated that an RSLF helicopter crashed on operations in Al-Mahra province in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292796","292796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147575","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question 291262, if he will place in the Library a copy of the provisions of the referenced fuel supply contingency programme which would be deployed in the event of disruption to fuel supplies in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292845","292845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147576","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 290584, whether his Department was aware of the Saudi Press Agency release of 14 September 2018 that stated that an RSLF helicopter crashed on operations in in Al-Mahra province in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292797","292797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147577","2019-10-07","Department for International Trade","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what progress her Department has made in securing a UK specialised quota within the EU Steel safeguard in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292882","292882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147578","2019-10-07","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many grants to persons ceasing to hold Ministerial and other offices under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 have been paid out in each year since 2010; and what was the total amount paid out in each year.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292932","292932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147579","2019-10-07","Department for International Trade","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether any licences have been granted for military equipment where the Saudi National Guard is certified as the end user since the Court of Appeal’s judgment of 20 June 2019 on arms sales at risk of being used in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292798","292798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147580","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) spousal visas were issued and (b) individual family members were granted entry to the UK from Afghanistan to be reunited with a family member that served as an interpreter with the British Armed Forces (i) from 2012 to April 2019 and (ii) since April 2019.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292883","292883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147581","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of IT specialists entering employment with UK shipyards.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292858","292858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147582","2019-10-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of staff who applied for promotion within her Department from 1 September 2018 to 1 September 2019 and who identified as (a) BAME and (b) White were successful by each grade in her Department.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292940","292940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147583","2019-10-07","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of staff who applied for promotion within her Department from 1 September 2018 to 1 September 2019 and who identified as (a) BAME and (b) White were successful by each grade in her Department.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292941","292941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147584","2019-10-07","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of staff who applied for promotion within his Department from 1 September 2018 to 1 September 2019 and who identified as (a) BAME and (b) White were successful by each grade in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292942","292942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147585","2019-10-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of staff who applied for promotion within his Department from 1 September 2018 to 1 September 2019 and who identified as (a) BAME and (b) White, were successful by each grade in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292943","292943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147586","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of staff who applied for promotion within his Department from 1 September 2018 to 1 September 2019 and who identified as (a) BAME and (b) white were successful by each grade in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292944","292944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147587","2019-10-07","Prime Minister","2019-10-01","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he discussed the conflict in Yemen in his meeting with Iran’s President Hassan Rouhani on 24 September 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292799","292799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147588","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the transfer of taxpayer funds, necessary for the IMS Ltd 2002 payment into court, was authorised by Parliament as per the requirements of the Ordnance Factories and Military Services Act 1984 .","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292965","292965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147589","2019-10-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons IMS Ltd changed its auditors in 2016 after 30 years alongside the implementation date of the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292966","292966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147590","2019-10-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons IMS Ltd paid a dividend of £5 million in 2010 to the Secretary of State for Defence; and for what purposes that money was used.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292967","292967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147591","2019-10-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel reside in (a) Wakefield District and (b) Wakefield constituency.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292884","292884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147592","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department recognises Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe as a hostage of Iran as per the terms of the UN Hostages Convention.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292968","292968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147593","2019-10-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps she is taking to ensure that the green technology and decarbonisation work forces have the skills necessary to respond to the climate emergency.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292907","292907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147594","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria the Government uses to recognise someone as a state-held hostage.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292969","292969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147595","2019-10-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the methodology of the award process for the Future High Streets Fund; and what score bids within Leigh constituency received.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293000","293000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147596","2019-10-03","Department for International Trade","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if she will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292800","292800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147597","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292801","292801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147598","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292802","292802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147599","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292803","292803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147600","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292804","292804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147601","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292805","292805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147602","2019-10-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292806","292806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147603","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292807","292807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147604","2019-10-03","Attorney General","2019-10-01","To ask the Attorney General, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292808","292808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147605","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292809","292809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147606","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292810","292810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147607","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292811","292811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147608","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292812","292812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147609","2019-10-07","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that young people are being appropriately educated on (a) safe use of the highway and (b) the contents of the highway code.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292846","292846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147610","2019-10-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the level of risk to human health by multiple wi-fi systems in flats and houses of multiple occupation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292847","292847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147611","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292813","292813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147612","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292814","292814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147613","2019-10-03","Department for International Development","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will invite representatives of the Jain community to national events organised by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292815","292815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147614","2019-10-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings (a) she and (b) Ministers in her Department have had with the British Board of Film Classification to discuss the implementation of a new age certification regime since 24 July 2019.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292886","292886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147749","2019-10-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 290584, whether the Saudi Government reported the RSLF helicopter crash of 14 September 2018 in Al-Mahra province in Yemen to his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293423","293423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146468","2019-10-01","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to ensure a level playing field in local economies by making local authorities subject to corporation tax on commercial activity.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291404","291404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146857","2019-10-01","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912456","912456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146970","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been spent advertising and promoting the Windrush Compensation Scheme in (a) Romsey and Southampton North and (b) nationally.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292201","292201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146971","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish research undertaken to identify target audiences prior to launching the #knifefree campaign on fast food containers.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292202","292202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146972","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what type of costs are incurred by the public purse when dealing with assets seized by the NCA.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292203","292203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146973","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what financial controls are in place to ensure the effective use of public funds when properties are seized by the National Crime Agency.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292204","292204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146974","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how events are assessed for level of risk for the purposes of inclusion on the National Risk Register.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292205","292205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146975","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on votes for life for British citizens living abroad.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292206","292206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146976","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the decision by the House of Lords on 18 June 2019, whether his Department plans to reinstate and extend the contract with the Thomas Coram Foundation for the administration of a statutory Adoption Register.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292281","292281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146977","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to introduce a statutory register of children who have not found adoptive parents within three months.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292282","292282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146978","2019-10-02","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to develop a strategy for the introduction of low-carbon heavy goods vehicles.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292283","292283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146979","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Keadby Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292284","292284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146980","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Damhead Creek Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292285","292285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146981","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Castleford Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292286","292286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146982","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Barkantine Heat and Power Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292287","292287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146983","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of West Burton CCGT Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292288","292288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146984","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of South Humber Bank Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292289","292289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146985","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Corby Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292290","292290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146986","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Didcot B Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292291","292291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146987","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Great Yarmouth Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292292","292292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146988","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Pembroke Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292293","292293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146989","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Seabank Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292294","292294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146990","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Burghfield Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292295","292295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146991","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Medway Natural Gas Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292296","292296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146992","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of people in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency who have (a) opted out after being auto-enrolled into a workplace pension and (b) saved more than the auto-enrolment minimum contribution.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292297","292297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146993","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on access to cash of NoteMachine's plans to convert approximately 3,000 of its 7,000 free-to-use machines to pay-to-use; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292223","292223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146994","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to apply restrictions on access to (a) social security and (b) health services to non-UK EU citizens (i) without evidence of settled status and (ii) with other legal immigration status after 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292271","292271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146995","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the good comparative attainment of Welsh A-level students in 2019, what plans he has to commission a lessons learned review of education in England.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292272","292272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146996","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her timescale is for the completion of managed migration to universal credit.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292273","292273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146997","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of instances of UK citizens using a non-UK EU consulate in 2018.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292274","292274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146998","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2019 to Question 285165 on Children: Maintenance, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of devolving the calculation of child maintenance liabilities to Scotland.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292298","292298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146999","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure young people are being appropriately educated on safe use of social media to prevent violent language and violent acts becoming the norm in society.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292260","292260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147000","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to (a) ensure that young people are only able to access age appropriate internet and social media sites and (b) hold sites to account when they expose children to inappropriate content.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292261","292261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147001","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that (a) Facebook, (b) Snapchat and (c) other internet sites remove inappropriate posts that bully and cause harm to individuals and groups.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292262","292262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147002","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether UK ports will be required to undertake sanitary and phytosanitary controls on high risk food and feed from the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement; and how long such controls are expected to be in place.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292132","292132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147003","2019-10-02","House of Commons Commission","2019-09-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, when responsibility for Bridge Street subway was transferred to the Parliamentary Estate; and what steps the Commission took to inform Members.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292136","292136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147004","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, who should bear the cost of remedial fire safety work such as fireproofing in a block of flats owned by a Housing Association with half social tenants and half leasehold tenants.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292248","292248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147005","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to issue new guidance on shared spaces.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292085","292085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147006","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a national buildings register of all high-risk buildings over 11m in height in England to store information such as construction materials used fire safety certification.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292249","292249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147007","2019-10-03","House of Commons Commission","2019-09-30","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate the Commission has made of the number of violent threats made against hon. members in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292086","292086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147008","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has for Access to Work to fund communication support for disabled people who are required to undertake work-related activity as a condition for receiving employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292299","292299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147009","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what standards are in place to ensure that disabled people are effectively supported when making a claim to the Access to Work scheme.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292300","292300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147010","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the Government’s policy is for NHS England receiving patients from Wales for healthcare.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292117","292117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147011","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received on the decision of Liverpool Royal Hospital to reduce treatment for patients located in Wales for urinary tract care; and what steps the Government has taken to mitigate the effect of that decision on patients' health.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292118","292118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147012","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients from (a) English and (b) Welsh postcode areas have been treated at Liverpool Royal Hospital for urinary tract care in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292119","292119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147013","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps she is taking to increase consumer confidence in high street retail.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292087","292087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147014","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of empty shops on high streets in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292088","292088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147015","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that every person whose health makes them more vulnerable to flu is able to receive the winter flu vaccine without delay.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292089","292089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147016","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many flash glucose monitors and sensors were prescribed from 1 April 2019 to 30 September 2019 in each CCG area.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292093","292093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147017","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of establishing a national gluten-free prescribing scheme for England to avoid variation in prescribing policies across different Clinical Commissioning Groups.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292301","292301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147018","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of preparations for the roll-out of the aTIV flu vaccine.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292200","292200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147019","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the environment of the increase in VAT on materials used for solar installations to 20 per cent.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292302","292302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147020","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect on the environment of an increase in VAT on fossil fuels.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292303","292303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147021","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department assessed the environmental impact of increasing VAT on materials used for solar installations prior to making that decision.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292304","292304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147022","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to respond to the invitation of 17 June 2019 from the all-party Parliamentary group on deliberative democracy to meet them to discuss progress on the innovation in democracy project; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292305","292305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147023","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will instruct the Payment Systems Regulator to take the necessary steps to prevent further reductions in access to free-to-use cash machines.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292108","292108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147024","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the criteria was for the selection of the 100 places to benefit from the recently announced new Towns Fund.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292094","292094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147025","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if Her Majesty's Courts & Tribunals Service will publish (a) weekly data on the number of probate grants issued in England and Wales and (b) up to date data on the average time between application for and grant of probate.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292207","292207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147026","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when waiting times for probate grants issued in England and Wales will return to below the historical average of three weeks.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292208","292208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147027","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, under what authority Special Adviser Dominic Cummings has the ability to (a) hire and (b) dismiss staff from government departments.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292306","292306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147028","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has any plans to update the special advisers' code of conduct.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292307","292307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147029","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to announce her Department's policy on support for survivors of modern trafficking who have received a positive conclusive grounds decision.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292095","292095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147030","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce a new immigration status of survivor of modern slavery for people who have received a positive conclusive grounds decision through the National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292096","292096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147031","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent on promotion on Twitter in each month since January 2019; and which Twitter accounts had tweets promoted.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292308","292308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147032","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) formal and (b) informal referrals to food banks have been made by Jobcentre Plus in each of the most recent 12 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292109","292109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147033","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when her Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals to tackle unfair practices in the hospitality sector in relation to (a) tips, (b) gratuities, (c) cover charges and (d) service charges.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292105","292105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147034","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much compensation Northern Rail has paid to passengers for delays and cancellations since the start of the current franchise.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292106","292106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147035","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Northern Rail has been fined for cancellations and partial cancellations since the start of the current franchise.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292107","292107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147036","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether each local authority in (a) England and (b) Wales (i) exceeds, (ii) meets or (iii) fails to meet their identified housing need, as outlined by his Department's most recent indicative assessment of housing need, using the National Planning Policy Framework's criteria.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292309","292309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147037","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the Port of Tyne has not received grants from the Brexit Readiness Fund.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292232","292232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147038","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many submissions were received in response to the call for evidence on environmental funding for the British Overseas Territories; and when her Department plans to publish its response to that consultation.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292275","292275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147039","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department’s response to the call for evidence on environmental funding for the British Overseas Territories will include plans to replace the EU environmental funds of BEST and LIFE.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292276","292276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147040","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether each local authority in (a) England and (b) Wales (i) exceeds, (ii) meets or (iii) fails to meet their objectively assessed need, using the National Planning Policy Framework's criteria.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292310","292310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147041","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the oral contribution of 25 September 2019 from the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, and Minister for the Cabinet Office, Official Report Column 739, how much money is available through business representative organisations to help North East manufacturers prepare for the UK leaving the EU; and which organisations are involved in this process.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292233","292233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147042","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of 25 September 2019 from the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, Official Report Column 739, if he will publish the criteria for which a business will be judged fundamentally viable in order to receive assistance from the Government in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292234","292234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147043","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of 25 September 2019 from the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, and Minister for the Cabinet Office, Official Report Column 739, what support has been planned for fundamentally viable businesses in the North East in the event of supply chain and trade issues as a result of the UK leaving the EU on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292235","292235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147044","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Operation Yellowhammer document, what plans are in place for the adequate supply and distribution of food to the North East in the event of disruptions to supply resulting from the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and to what extent those plans account for the potential effect of food price increases on low income groups.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292236","292236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147045","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what measures are in place to support the import of insulin from Denmark (Nova Nordisk) and Germany (Sanofi) in the event of the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292184","292184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147046","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has undertaken of the public health threats posed to the UK by climate change driven changes to vector-borne disease.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292209","292209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147047","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of climate change on the adequacy of the level of national surveillance of disease-spreading vectors in the UK.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292210","292210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147048","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the number of invasive insect species in the UK as a result of the removal of compulsory tick treatment for pets at UK border; and whether there are any plans to reintroduce the tick treatment policy.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292211","292211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147049","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what (a) the cost would be and (b) assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of extending the surveillance of invasive mosquitoes to cover the whole UK.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292212","292212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147050","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to (a) understand and (b) mitigate the risks to the food security of the UK population due to global climate change.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292213","292213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147051","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the biggest risk is to the UK's food security in the (a) short, (b) medium and (c) long-term.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292214","292214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147052","2019-10-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Sudanese counterpart on the removal of their troops from Yemen.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292077","292077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147053","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many statutory instruments her Department needs Parliament to pass before the UK leaves the EU on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292078","292078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147054","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how the Government plans to meet the projected shortfall in electricity supply by 2050 while achieving net zero-emissions targets;  what changes to Government policy will be required; what energy mix will provide the best value for money for the taxpayer to meet that shortfall; and how much of that growth in electricity output will come from onshore wind power.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292215","292215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147055","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether there have been any changes to the Ministerial Code of Conduct since July 2019.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292216","292216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147056","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to increase wildfire resilience in the UK.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292217","292217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147057","2019-10-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 25 July 2019, Official Report, column 1497, on priorities for Government, what the timescale is for the allocation of the £160 million to the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292311","292311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147058","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish an updated List of Ministerial Responsibilities online.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292218","292218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147059","2019-10-02","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department will take to ensure the implementation of the political declaration of the UN High-Level Meeting on Universal Health Coverage across its investments in health and human development.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292312","292312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147060","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affiars, what assessment he has made of the level of compliance of signatories with Article VI of the Treaty on the Non-Proliferation of Nuclear Weapons; and what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in states with nuclear weapons on reducing their stockpile of nuclear weapons.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292219","292219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147061","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what targeted action his Department is taking to increase the take up of the MMR vaccine in London.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292313","292313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147062","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people who for medical reasons cannot be vaccinated against certain infectious diseases remain protected in society and able to lead a normal life.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292220","292220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147063","2019-10-02","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reduction of carbon dioxide emissions if mandatory E10 fuels were introduced.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292314","292314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147064","2019-10-02","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to introduce mandatory E10 fuels; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292315","292315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147065","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the poultry meat sector has access to the labour it needs in any future scenario.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292222","292222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147066","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many individual Healthy Start vouchers have been used in each of the last 10 years for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292110","292110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147067","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of backdating universal credit payments to reduce the five week wait for a first payment.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292316","292316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147068","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of establishing an independent commission to review the value of benefits to ensure they consistently match the cost of living.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292317","292317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147069","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit payments were subject to a deduction for child maintenance arrears.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292318","292318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147070","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the working age benefit freeze on the household incomes of people with (a) disabilities and (b) long term health conditions.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292319","292319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147071","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the application from Hacker House for funding from the Cyber Security Immediate Impact Fund mentioned a trade mission to Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories in November 2015.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292162","292162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147072","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that women receive the same standard of care as men during diagnosis, treatment and aftercare of heart disease or a heart attack.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292090","292090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147073","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the misconception that heart attacks do not happen to women among (a) doctors and (b) the public.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292091","292091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147074","2019-10-02","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support research into the effects of gambling-like mechanics in video games on (a) young and (b) vulnerable players of those games.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292186","292186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147075","2019-10-02","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure the impartiality of the leader of the inquiry into loan charge schemes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292092","292092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147076","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the full NHS People Plan will tackle shortages in the imaging and diagnostic workforce in order to achieve the ambition in the NHS Long Term Plan to increase cancer screening uptake.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292198","292198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147077","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons his Department's plans to publish Progress 8 data do not include key data on BTEC Level 2 qualifications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292111","292111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147078","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what means of redress is available to disabled young people who haven’t received independent careers advice.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292167","292167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147079","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training on the Access to Work scheme is provided to work coaches or advisors who support disabled young people receiving employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292168","292168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147080","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of the Ministerial Code.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292097","292097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147081","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 May 2018 to Question 141857, approach on sign language, what lessons have been learned from the Scottish Government’s to British Sign Language to inform the Government’s thinking in England and Wales.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292237","292237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147082","2019-10-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to secure the release of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292320","292320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147083","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to (a) improve standards and (b) ensure patient safety in privately-run mental health units.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292321","292321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147084","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the Government's level of preparedness within the automotive industry in September 2019 compared to March 2019; and what plans the Government has put in place to protect the automotive industry's just-in-time supply chain.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292169","292169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147085","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department received oral or written representations from the hon. Member for Plymouth Moor View on the awarding of grant money to Crucial Academy Ltd.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292098","292098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147087","2019-10-03","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department first received a communication from the hon. Member for Plymouth Moor View on the (a) continuation and (b) termination of his role at Crucial Academy Ltd.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292100","292100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147088","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the oral contribution of 25 September 2019 from the Prime Minister, Official Report column 791, when he plans to publish the details of the cross-party talks on the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292185","292185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147089","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish a list of the courts and tribunals, including the postcode locations, that have closed between 2010-11 and the most recent financial year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292101","292101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147090","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish a list including the postcode locations of the public libraries that have closed between 2010 and the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292102","292102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147091","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish a list including the postcode locations of the Sure Start children’s centres that have closed between 2010 and the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292103","292103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147092","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many job centres have closed in each constituency in each year between 2010 and the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292104","292104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147093","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason Ministers of his Department are unable to comment on specific buildings with cladding issues raised in correspondence dated 25 September 2019 with the hon. Member for Croydon North.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292250","292250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147094","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that people who are in receipt of Section 4 support are able to pay (a) travel fares which can only be purchased with cash and (b) other upfront travel costs in order to report at Home Office reporting centres.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292322","292322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147095","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to ensure reporting frequencies are not excessively (a) burdensome and (b) expensive for people who live in places where the journey to a Home Office reporting centre is significant.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292323","292323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147096","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the TfL Oyster fare zones scheme will be extended to cover Berkshire stations beyond West Drayton following the commencement of (a) the TfL Rail western section and (b) the full Elizabeth Line service.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292324","292324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147097","2019-10-03","Department for International Trade","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government pursues any export credit guarantees in relation to IMS Ltd’s operations in Iran as sovereign debt.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292325","292325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147098","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what licences have been granted by the Office of Financial Sanctions Implementation with regard to transactions between (a) the UK Government and (b) UK companies and the Iranian Ministry of Defence (MODSAF); and what criteria are used by the Office of Financial Sanctions Implementation when granting such an application.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292326","292326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147099","2019-10-02","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish his Department's cost-benefit analysis of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292327","292327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147100","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of homes in England that have been valued at £0 because surveyors could not be sure that the cladding and insulation on the buildings were not flammable.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292251","292251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147101","2019-10-02","Cabinet Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the results of the Government's stress testing of the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292328","292328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147102","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department has spent on the proposed Abacus Free School project in Hampstead and Kilburn constituency.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292329","292329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147103","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much West Hertfordshire Hospitals NHS Trust has requested from his Department for capital building projects.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292170","292170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147104","2019-10-02","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will review the child benefit rules to include support to all parents of adopted children.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292330","292330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147105","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he approved the practice of sharing patients’ identities with credit check firms to find overseas visitors who can be charged; if he will take steps to put an end to that practice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292187","292187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147106","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2019 to Question 284860 on A34: Oxfordshire, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) deaths and (b) injuries on the A34 in 2018.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292331","292331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147107","2019-10-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when he plans to answer Question 287929, on Public Expenditure: Northern Ireland, tabled on 6 September 2019 by the hon. Member for the City of Chester.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292266","292266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147108","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to answer Question 287927 tabled on 6 September 2019 by the hon. Member for the City of Chester.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292267","292267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147109","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will set out the details of the UK’s negotiation request to the EU on the terms of the UK's departure from the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justine Greening","Justine Greening","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292176","292176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147110","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to answer Question 287926 tabled on 6 September 2019 by the hon. Member for the City of Chester.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292268","292268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147111","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made in the preparation of a Code of Practice under the Parking (Code of Practice) Act 2019; if he will ensure that the Code (a) requires private parking service providers comply with the Equality Act 2010 and (b) gives specific consideration to car park users who have a (i) dementia diagnosis, (ii) development disorder and (c) learning disability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292332","292332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147112","2019-10-02","Department for Education","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has for future funding of the Adoption Support Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292067","292067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147113","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to review the eligibility criteria for NHS patient transport.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292068","292068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147114","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what are the (a) titles and (b) dates of transmission to the EU of all documents prepared for submission to the European Union on current negotiations on the UK's departure from the EU.","Biography information for Justine Greening","Justine Greening","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292177","292177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147115","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were treated for hepatitis C in England in the financial year 2018-19.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292278","292278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147116","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure people who are in contact with drug treatment services are tested for hepatitis C.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292279","292279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147117","2019-10-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has for a White Paper setting out what the Government is seeking to achieve in negotiation of the UK's (a) exit from and (b) new partnership with the EU.","Biography information for Justine Greening","Justine Greening","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292178","292178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147118","2019-10-03","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations the Government has made to the Government of Nigeria on the closure of humanitarian international NGOs in North-East Nigeria.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292071","292071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147119","2019-10-03","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations the Government has made to the Nigerian High Commissioner to the United Kingdom on the closure of humanitarian international NGOs in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292072","292072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147120","2019-10-03","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations the Government has made to the United Nations on the expulsion of humanitarian international NGOs operating in in North-East Nigeria.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292073","292073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147121","2019-10-03","Department for International Development","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on the humanitarian situation in North-East Nigeria of the closure of international NGO operations in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292074","292074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147122","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government has taken to reduce carbon emissions in the housing sector.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292133","292133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147123","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to reduce carbon emissions in the housing sector.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292134","292134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147124","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 291138, on Stronger Towns Fund: Leigh, if he will publish (a) the full methodology and (b) the score of each town within Leigh constituency.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292333","292333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147125","2019-10-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to reduce carbon emissions in the construction sector.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292135","292135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147126","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his announcement of 28 September 2019 of £16.6 billion to guarantee funding for organisations in receipt of EU programme funding in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal, whether charities and non-Governmental organisations that receive funding from the Asylum, Migration and Integration Fund will be eligible for that funding.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292183","292183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147127","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to tackle ash dieback.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292238","292238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147128","2019-10-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of phasing out six month custodial sentences in England and Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292120","292120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147129","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of high street bank branches that have closed in (a) the North West, (b) Merseyside and (c) Wallasey in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292112","292112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147130","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to increase the provision of (a) affordable and (b) social housing in (i) the North West, (ii) Merseyside and (iii) Wallasey.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292113","292113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147131","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2019 to Question 290754, whether the Government met, held discussions or corresponded with the management of the Royal Bank of Scotland to discuss Thomas Cook UK between 14 September 2019 and the collapse of that company.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292221","292221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147132","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve rail connectivity between Wallasey and Liverpool.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292114","292114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147133","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the (a) number of illegal migrants who have entered the UK by crossing the English Channel and (b) proportion of such migrants that have been returned to France in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292277","292277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147134","2019-10-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been purchased through the Help to Buy scheme in (a) the North West, (b) Merseyside and (c) Wallasey in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292115","292115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147135","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that all adult social care workers caring for dementia patients are trained to level Tier 2 of the Dementia Training Standards Framework.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292137","292137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147136","2019-10-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to increase tourism in the North West.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292116","292116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147137","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will compensate (a) victims of and (b) family members affected by the contaminated blood scandal.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292334","292334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147138","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many clinical staff were employed by Ipswich Hospital in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292194","292194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147139","2019-10-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the annual commissioning budget for East Suffolk and Ipswich CCG was in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292195","292195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147140","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the environment of an Ipswich Northern Bypass; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292196","292196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147141","2019-10-02","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2018 to Question 167831 and with reference to paragraph 87 of the Public Administration and Constitutional Affairs Committee’s report of 6 August 2019 entitled The Role of Parliament in the UK Constitution: Authorising the Use of Military Force, how his Department determines whether an international deployment of the armed forces falls (a) above and (b) below the conflict threshold.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292070","292070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147142","2019-10-03","Department for Transport","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has for a Felixstowe to Nuneaton freight rail link; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292197","292197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147143","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will re-establish dedicated funding programmes for local authorities and housing providers to create affordable housing from long-term empty homes throughout England.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292188","292188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147144","2019-10-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many meetings she had with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292142","292142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147145","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will undertake a review of how the legal powers available to local authorities to tackle empty homes and poor standards of management in the private rented sector could be improved.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292189","292189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147146","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will provide support for empty home prevention schemes by offering financial support to owners for sustainability measures and home improvements such as insulation measures designed to increase the longevity and environmental efficiency of existing homes.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292190","292190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147147","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to bring forward secondary legislation to implement mandatory electrical safety checks for the private rented sector.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292075","292075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147148","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how his Department identifies long-term empty homes; and how many long-term empty homes there were in England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292191","292191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147149","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to introduce mandatory electrical safety checks in the social rented sector in England.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292076","292076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147150","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will open funding programmes to tackle empty homes to community-led organisations who are not registered providers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292192","292192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147151","2019-10-02","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292143","292143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147152","2019-10-02","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings she had with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292144","292144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147153","2019-10-02","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will extend the Community Housing Fund to beyond March 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292193","292193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147154","2019-10-02","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292145","292145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147155","2019-10-03","Home Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure equal protection for all domestic abuse survivors by upholding the non-discrimination principle in accordance with Article 4(3) of the Istanbul Convention.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292138","292138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147156","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many meetings she had with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292146","292146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147157","2019-10-02","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has included the drug Dornase Alfa in the priority stockpiling list in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292069","292069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147158","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps her Department has taken to tackle invasive crayfish species in UK rivers.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292239","292239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147159","2019-10-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to require employers to provide domestic abuse survivors with (a) flexible working arrangements and (b) a period of paid leave.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292139","292139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147160","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to (a) protect red squirrels in Northumberland and (b) tackle the damaging effect of the invasive grey squirrel species.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292240","292240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147161","2019-10-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the strategy to deal with invasive Japanese knotweed in (a) Wansbeck constituency, (b) Northumberland and (c) the North East.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292241","292241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147162","2019-10-02","Scotland Office","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser from 1 June to 31 August 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292147","292147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147163","2019-10-03","Treasury","2019-09-30","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the funding for preparations for the UK leaving the EU have been allocated to preparations for leaving (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292269","292269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1147164","2019-10-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of Job Centre Plus offices that have (a) British Sign Language and (b) language interpreters.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292140","292140"
