"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642385","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what measures are being considered to reduce congestion at Dartford (a) before and (b) after the construction of a Lower Thames Crossing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54115","54115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642386","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether contingency measures have been considered to reduce congestion at Dartford if the construction of a Lower Thames Crossing does not reduce congestion at Dartford; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54116","54116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642387","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate how many vehicles per day using all or part of the M25 between junctions 29 and 3 in a clockwise direction joined the M25 (a) before junction 30, (b) at junction 30, (c) at junction 31, (d) at junction 1a, (e) at junction 1b and (f) at junction 2; and in each such case how many of those vehicles left (i) at junction 30, (ii) at junction 1a, (iii) at junction 1b, (iv) at junction 2 and (v) after junction 2.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54117","54117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642388","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the DVLA takes to notify the public that poppy seed consumption could lead to a positive result in a drugs test.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54105","54105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642389","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of people refused a driving licence after testing positive for poppy seeds during a drugs screening.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54106","54106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642390","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) facilities and (b) other support his Department provides for (i) visitors and (ii) staff for (A) lactating mothers and (B) the expressing of breast milk.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54384","54384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642391","2016-11-25","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new ultra-low emission vehicles have been registered in Greater Manchester in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54338","54338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642392","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect that the planned expansion of Heathrow Airport will have on Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54306","54306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642393","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that connectivity between Northern Ireland and London is improved as a result of the planned expansion of Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54304","54304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642394","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations the Government has received from the aviation sector on priorities for its negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54290","54290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642395","2016-11-25","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will consider to remove Govia from the shortlist for the West Midlands franchise.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54262","54262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642396","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess the potential benefits of allowing road users to turn left on red traffic signals at junctions.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54272","54272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642397","2016-11-25","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on issuing a new statutory body acting as an independent aviation air quality authority.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54259","54259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642398","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for road safety of drivers wearing spectacles purchased online.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54386","54386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642399","2016-11-25","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what evidence he has received and assessed in to claims that trade union leaders are encouraging Govia Thameslink Rail employees to take unofficial industrial action.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54347","54347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642400","2016-11-25","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department have received from (a) individual shipping companies, (b) the UK Chamber of Shipping, (c) maritime trades unions and (d) the TUC on National Minimum Wage enforcement for seafarers since July 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54328","54328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642401","2016-11-24","Wales Office","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the contribution of the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs to the Environmental Audit Committee on 25 October 2016, Question 332, what proportion of existing EU legislation within the policy remit of his Department cannot immediately be brought into UK law upon the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54206","54206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642402","2016-11-24","Women and Equalities","2016-11-22","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on steps to increase opportunities for work for older women in the light of the recent raising of the state pension age.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54245","54245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642403","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the level of equality of treatment of different business types under the Pension Protection Fund Levy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54286","54286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642404","2016-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made by the Child Poverty Unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54256","54256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642405","2016-11-25","Department for Education","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of people claiming free childcare for two-year olds are working.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54270","54270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642406","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions his Department has held with (a) Experian and (b) the Pension Protection Fund (PPF) on the equitable treatment of businesses under the PPF levy.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54305","54305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642407","2016-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much (a) basic and (b) additional state pension per week that woman born on 5 April 1953 would receive with 35 years' worth of both National Insurance Contributions and contracting-in to the state second pension; and how much in the new state pension a woman born on 6 April 1953 would receive with 35 years' worth of both National Insurance Contributions and contracting-in to the state second pension.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54268","54268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642408","2016-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and which public telephone lines operated by his Department are higher rate lines; how many calls have been made to those lines in the last 12 months for which data is available; what average duration of calls was to each such line; and what amount of money was charged to all callers using each such line.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54181","54181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642409","2016-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps have been taken to make contact with people who had previously been enrolled automatically into a workplace pension scheme since 2012 but have since withdrawn from it.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54149","54149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642410","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what minimum written notice was given to women affected by state pension age increases under the Pensions Act 1995 and Pensions Act 2011.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54135","54135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642411","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the contribution of the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs to the Environmental Audit Committee on 25 October 2016 to Question 332, what proportion of existing EU legislation within the policy remit of  his  department cannot immediately be brought into UK law upon the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54158","54158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642412","2016-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much he plans to spend on employment support for claimants of employment and support allowance in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54335","54335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642413","2016-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which terminal illnesses he plans to make exempt from benefits assessments.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54343","54343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642414","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants affected by the recent reduction in the benefit cap in (a) the constituency of Tottenham, (b) the London Borough of Haringey and (c) in total are in receipt of (i) jobseeker's allowance, (ii) employment support allowance, (iii) income support, (iv) housing benefit and (v) another benefit.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54393","54393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642415","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to identify those responsible for the Medical Research Council's policies towards ME research over the last decade; and if he will seek those people's removal from positions of influence over future of ME research.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54353","54353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642416","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will review the policy of the Medical Research Council (MRC) in so far as it relates to addressing the dissatisfaction of ME patients with MRC's approach in this area.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54354","54354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642417","2016-11-25","Department for Transport","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many charge points for electric vehicles have been installed in Greater Manchester in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54341","54341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642418","2016-11-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the potential cost to the UK economy of a changing climate over the next 20 years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54331","54331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642419","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department has made to date on meeting the Renewable Energy Directive obligation of 20 per cent renewable sourced energy by 2020; and what estimate he has made of likely progress towards that goal by 2020.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54132","54132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642420","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish advice for employers on how to support parents of premature or sick babies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54129","54129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642421","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy on jobs of the recent takeover of the licence to manufacture Cadbury's biscuits in the UK from Burton's to Mondalez/Kraft.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54122","54122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642422","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what  assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) food industry and (b) price for consumers of recent foreign takeovers in the food industry.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54123","54123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642423","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will develop a cross-government strategy to reduce the incidence of pregnancy discrimination.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54119","54119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642424","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department monitors the public funding used to refurbish Crown post offices to ensure those funds achieve the expected outcomes; and how much was spent from the public purse on refurbishing post office branches that subsequently lost Crown status in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54160","54160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642425","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much the Post Office has paid in compensation to sub post masters as part of the Initial Complaint Review and Mediation scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54161","54161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642426","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the contribution of the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs to the Environmental Audit Committee on 25 October 2016, Question 332, what proportion of existing EU legislation within the policy remit of his Department cannot immediately be brought into UK law upon the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54187","54187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642427","2016-11-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will request that the Medical Research Council conducts an inquiry into the management of the PACE trial to ascertain whether any fraudulent activity has occurred.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54269","54269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642428","2016-11-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will prevent the PACE trial researchers from being given further public research funding until an inquiry into possible fraudulent activity into the PACE trial has been conducted.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54266","54266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642429","2016-11-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for the construction of Sizewell C; and who will be responsible for the construction of that site.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54316","54316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642430","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what (a) facilities and (b) other support his Department provides for (i) visitors and (ii) staff for (A) lactating mothers and (B) the expressing of breast milk.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54366","54366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642431","2016-11-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings he has had to discuss productivity with employers in low-paid sectors in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54255","54255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642432","2016-11-24","Department for International Trade","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what (a) facilities and (b) other support his Department provides for (i) visitors and (ii) staff for (A) lactating mothers and (B) the expressing of breast milk.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54379","54379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642433","2016-11-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he intends to formally enter discussions on a future trade deal with the EU before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54303","54303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642434","2016-11-24","Department for International Trade","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the contribution of the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs to the Environmental Audit Committee on 25 October 2016, Question 332, what proportion of existing EU legislation within the policy remit of his Department cannot immediately be brought into UK law upon the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54200","54200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642435","2016-11-24","Department for International Trade","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many applications from people with a manufacturing background have been received for non-executive positions in his  Department.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54159","54159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642436","2016-11-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to consult representatives of the (a) NHS and (b) care sector as part of his Department's preparations for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54136","54136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642437","2016-11-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on the status of the UK's membership of the EU Customs Union.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54137","54137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642438","2016-11-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to consult representatives of the higher education sector as part of his Department's preparations for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54138","54138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642439","2016-11-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on plans for Government funding to replace EU regional funding after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54139","54139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642440","2016-11-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the contribution of the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs to the Environmental Audit Committee on 25 October 2016, Question 332, what proportion of existing EU legislation within the policy remit of his Department cannot immediately be brought into UK law upon the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54195","54195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642441","2016-11-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what (a) facilities and (b) other support his Department provides for (i) visitors and (ii) staff for (A) lactating mothers and (B) the expressing of breast milk.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54374","54374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642442","2016-11-25","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what time period his Department has set aside to draft EU legislation into UK law.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54261","54261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644294","2016-11-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the potential effect of the removal of Part 2A contaminated land funding on the budgets of local councils.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907518","907518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644295","2016-11-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support the Midlands Engine.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907513","907513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/646317","2016-11-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent steps his Department has taken to encourage community cohesion.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907510","907510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/646318","2016-11-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time, cost and complexity of processes to bring redundant publicly owned land back into use.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907511","907511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/646319","2016-11-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to extend devolution deals across England.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907512","907512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/646320","2016-11-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support the role of local communities in the design of new housing developments.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907516","907516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/646321","2016-11-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the adequacy of the level of dementia training for homecare workers.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907515","907515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/648337","2016-11-30","Wales Office","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on the potential effect on Wales of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907493","907493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/648338","2016-11-30","Wales Office","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on the potential effect on Wales of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907489","907489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/648339","2016-11-30","Wales Office","2016-11-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with (a) his Ministerial colleagues and (b) the Chancellor of the Exchequer on future infrastructure development in Wales.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907490","907490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641161","2016-11-23","Attorney General","2016-11-21","To ask the Attorney General, how many projects in operation in his Department are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53889","53889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641162","2016-11-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many trials were (a) effective, (b) cracked, (c) ineffective and (d) vacated in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53913","53913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641163","2016-11-23","Cabinet Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many projects in operation in his Department are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53886","53886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641164","2016-11-23","Cabinet Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the minimum competency criteria are for evaluating applications for civil service job opportunities for applicants with a sensory disability.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54076","54076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641165","2016-11-23","Cabinet Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps are being taken to ensure that there is consistency in the evaluation criteria for civil service positions.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54077","54077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641166","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many civil or criminal cases against people related to tax evasion have been made as a result of information supplied by the (a) Child Maintenance Group and (b) parents whose child maintenance awards have been directly affected by such evasion.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53985","53985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641167","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of proposed changes to work allowance on the incomes of working households in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54008","54008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641168","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the potential revenue to be obtained from the proposed sale of Green Investment Bank shares.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54041","54041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641169","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what stake the Government plans to retain in the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54042","54042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641170","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, on what date he expects the sale of shares in the Green Investment Bank to be completed.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54046","54046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641171","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment criteria are being applied to potential buyers of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54047","54047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641172","2016-11-24","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to assist those mortgage holders who are seeking to switch to mortgage providers which offer better repayment terms.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53916","53916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641173","2016-11-24","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the effect of its regulations on mortgage affordability assessments on the ability of mortgage holders to switch mortgage providers.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53917","53917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641174","2016-11-24","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of Financial Conduct Authority requirements on mortgage affordability assessments on the (a) ability of mortgage holders to switch mortgage providers, (b) competitiveness of the sector for existing mortgage holders and (c) favourability of post-introductory mortgage terms for existing mortgage holders.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53918","53918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641175","2016-11-24","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will issue a response to Early Day Motion 689, Sale of Public Assets.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53912","53912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641176","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2016 to Question 52165, whether his Department plans to publish its report on Equitable Life in December 2016.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53932","53932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641177","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received from the Northern Ireland Executive on reducing air passenger duty in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53935","53935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641178","2016-11-24","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when HM Revenue and Customs plans to publish its post-implementation review of Real Time Information.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53970","53970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641179","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to integrate a state pension summary into the pensions dashboard.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53996","53996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641180","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the pensions dashboard has functionality built in to prevent people from overspending their lump sums.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53997","53997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641181","2016-11-24","Church Commissioners","2016-11-21","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2016 to Question 52646, for what reason no timetable is in place to expedite the sale of Phase 2 at Paston Reserve, Peterborough; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53954","53954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641182","2016-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new homes for social rent were started in each year since 2010 in (a) East Ham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Newham.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53968","53968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641183","2016-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of affordable homes to rent in (a) East Ham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Newham since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53966","53966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641184","2016-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of statutory homeless households since 2010 in (a) East Ham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Newham.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53967","53967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641185","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 6.6 of the Autumn Statement 2015, if he will publish the application process for applying for extra funding for local authorities in areas affected by high levels of second home ownership.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53987","53987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641186","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 6.6 of the Autumn Statement 2015, when his Department plans to make available the proposed extra funding for communities affected by high levels of second home ownership.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53988","53988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641187","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of benefit sanctions on levels of homelessness.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53979","53979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641188","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has for the future support of voluntary night shelters.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53980","53980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641189","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the level of homeless need in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53981","53981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641190","2016-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to ensure that local authorities in London promote diversity and equality in their procurement strategies.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53906","53906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641191","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the guidance on implementation of the pay to stay scheme will be made available to local authorities; and if he will ensure this is before the introduction of that scheme in April 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53880","53880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641192","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it will be the responsibility of local authorities to collect information on household income in relation to the introduction of the pay to stay scheme.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53877","53877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641193","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many housing associations have indicated that they intend to introduce the pay to stay provisions of the Housing and Planning Act 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53878","53878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641194","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish his Department's estimate of the administrative costs to local authorities of the introduction of the pay to stay scheme.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53879","53879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641195","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will increase the pay to stay income threshold for South East England to that of Greater London.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53875","53875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641196","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many projects in operation in his Department are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53887","53887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641197","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of affordable homes built in each parliamentary constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54024","54024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641198","2016-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his decision to reopen the planning inquiry into the highways safety aspects of Cuadrilla Resources' appeal against Lancashire County Council's decision to refuse planning permission to build shale gas wells at its Roseacre Wood site, whether the analysis supporting his decision differs from that of the inspector concerned on any matter of fact mentioned in or otherwise material to a conclusion reached by that inspector in that case; and what new evidence or new matter of fact he has taken into consideration on the highways safety aspects of that case that has informed his decision to reopen the planning inquiry.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54032","54032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641199","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2016 to Question 52835, how many full-time equivalent civil servants employed within the Cities and Local Growth Unit are based in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54022","54022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641200","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimates he has made of the number of people who were homeless in (a) Salford and (b) Greater Manchester in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53982","53982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641201","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of homeless people in (a) Salford and (b) Greater Manchester with a (i) disability and (ii) mental health condition.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53983","53983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641202","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the cost of the Cities and Local Growth Unit has been in each year of its operation.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53940","53940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641203","2016-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many times the power he has under section 17(7) of the Town and Country Planning (Inquiries Procedure) (England) Rules 2000/1624 to reopen a planning inquiry has been exercised by him and his predecessors to allow an appellant to adduce further evidence in their favour since the introduction of those rules.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54078","54078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641204","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with local authorities in Yorkshire on creating a Mayor of Yorkshire role.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54096","54096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641205","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what procedures are in place for consumer compensation if the 90 per cent geographic voice coverage target set by Ofcom across the UK mobile network is not achieved by the end of 2017.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54045","54045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641206","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with her Chinese counterpart on illegal sale of religious, cultural and historical artefacts.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54087","54087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641207","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the finding of the website stammeringlaw.org.uk on voice recognition systems and duties on companies to make reasonable adjustments, published on 25 September 2012, what statutory requirements there are for companies that use computer answering systems to ensure that those with stammering and other communication needs are able to speak to a real person.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53944","53944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641208","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to enable the BBC to introduce subscription charges for viewing content on its iPlayer outside the UK.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54019","54019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641209","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make it her policy to enable Ofcom to fine mobile operators who do not provide the promised level of service.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54043","54043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641210","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential use of macro hot spot roaming in areas that suffer from poor mobile coverage.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54044","54044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641211","2016-11-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to repay, with interest, funds diverted from the Big Lottery Fund to National Lottery distributors in 2007 to finance the Olympic Games in London in 2012.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53902","53902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641212","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of trends in the level of dissemination of fake news by social media; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53857","53857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641213","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to encourage the operators of the London Eye to increase the affordability of that attraction's prices for lower income families.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53930","53930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641214","2016-11-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the average amount of public funding provided per property under the Broadband Delivery UK scheme.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53950","53950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641215","2016-11-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of premises which will be eligible for the broadband Universal Service Obligation in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53948","53948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641216","2016-11-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of premises in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Wales, (d) Scotland and (e) Northern Ireland (i) will have access to superfast broadband and (ii) are forecast to have signed up to receive superfast broadband by the end of 2017.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53949","53949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641217","2016-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on employment in the UK of awarding the AH-64E Apache programme contract to Boeing.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53919","53919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641218","2016-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with the US Department of Defense on the System Development and Demonstration phase of the F-35 Lightning II programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53920","53920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641219","2016-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of the time taken for Block 3F testing of the F-35 Lighting II programme on the UK's planning Initial Operating Capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53921","53921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641220","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions his Department has had with GKN on the future of the workforce at that company's Yeovil helicopter plant.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53868","53868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641221","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to maximise the UK workshare in the AH-64E Apache programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53859","53859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641222","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the workshare of the AH-64E Apache programme is fulfilled by UK-based companies.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53860","53860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641223","2016-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on whether the legal and contractual issues between International Military Services Ltd and the Republic of Iran have been resolved.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53893","53893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641224","2016-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy of the Memorandum from the US Director of Operational Test and Evaluation to the US Under Secretary of Defense for Acquisition, Technology and Logistics, on the Director's concerns regarding progress and readiness of the F-35 Joint Strike Fighter Programme for initial operational test and evaluation.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54027","54027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641225","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding the Capita-led consortium receives from the public purse  to manage the defence estate annually.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54025","54025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641226","2016-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will (a) name the company providing payroll services to his Department and (b) publish details of that company's charge to his Department of payroll deductions for members of the armed forces who join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54081","54081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641227","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much service personnel in Northern Ireland have paid as a contribution in lieu of council tax in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54053","54053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641228","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how contribution in lieu of council tax is calculated for service personnel stationed in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54054","54054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641229","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government provides to Syria civil defence in (a) Syria and (b) Aleppo.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54090","54090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641230","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that nurseries in County Durham recruit well qualified staff including early years teachers.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54039","54039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641231","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils are registered with (a) high and complex needs and (b) special educational needs in (i) Liverpool and (ii) Liverpool Walton.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53870","53870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641232","2016-11-24","Department for Education","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the change in the early years funding formula on the number of places in maintained nursery schools and nursery classes in the London Borough of Southwark.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53907","53907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641233","2016-11-24","Department for Education","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who is responsible for carrying out the end point assessment for an apprenticeship standard when there is no approved organisation in place to do so.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53956","53956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641234","2016-11-24","Department for Education","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Trailblazer groups which develop new apprenticeship standards will continue to be known as Trailblazer groups once the Institute for Apprenticeships has begun operating in April 2017.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53955","53955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641235","2016-11-24","Department for Education","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will place a copy of the 2015 report on Bright Tribe Multi Academy Trust prepared by the Risk Analysis Division of the Education Funding Agency in the Library.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53969","53969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641236","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on a temporary ban on the commercial netting of sea bass.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53937","53937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641237","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to introduce the bottle deposit return system proposed by Surfers Against Sewage.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53933","53933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641238","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2016 to Question 53157, what steps she is taking to reduce the level of application of (a) nitrogen, (b) phosphate, (c) potash and (d) sulphur on UK farmland while maintaining levels of output; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53991","53991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641239","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department plans to take to maintain protection for coastal towns from the sea dumping of waste after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53931","53931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641240","2016-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has for members of the public to contribute to the consultation on its 25 year plan for the natural environment.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53904","53904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641241","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the level of antibiotic use in meat-producing animals in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54040","54040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641242","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to retain the effect of EU environmental directives in UK law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54006","54006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641243","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to ensure that the UK meets the EU target to reuse and recycle 50 per cent of household waste by 2020.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54005","54005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641244","2016-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with the Environment Agency on removal of the mound of rubbish at the site operated by Rowan Oak Waste on Shaw Road, Dudley.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54012","54012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641245","2016-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on whether the Environment Agency plans to impose penalties on the operators of the Rowan Oak Waste site on Shaw Road, Dudley, for failing to dispose of waste.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54013","54013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641246","2016-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the steps taken by the Environment Agency to remove the mound of rubbish at the site operated by Rowan Oak Waste on Shaw Road, Dudley.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54014","54014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641247","2016-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to  the Answer of 17 November 2016 to Question 52825, what estimate she has made of the level of funding support received from HM Treasury for response and recovery activities relating to emergency events in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54010","54010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641248","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has to increase its overseas diplomatic representation after the vote to leave the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53941","53941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641249","2016-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish on a weekly basis information on Russian and Syrian air assets engaged in attacking civilian targets in Syria; if he will publish the identity of the officer in the chain of command under which those air assets operate; and if he will make such information available to his EU counterparts with responsibility for sanctions policy.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54038","54038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641250","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in South Sudan on stopping armed forces destroying food reserves and restricting access to food for civilians in that country.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54048","54048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641251","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in South Sudan on that country's restriction of employment of non-South Sudanese nationals by non-governmental organisations and other organisations.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54060","54060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641252","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he or the UK representative to the UN have made to other UN Security Council member states on the extension of the UN mission in South Sudan.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54062","54062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641253","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had on the situation in South Sudan with member states of the African Union and representatives from the African Union.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54061","54061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641254","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on that country's relationship with Taiwan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54088","54088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641255","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on steps to improve relations between North Korea and the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54089","54089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641256","2016-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise the case of the seizure of the retreat centre in Mohammadshahr in Karaj belonging to the Council of Assemblies of God Churches with his Iranian counterparts.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54091","54091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641257","2016-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received representations on the banning of the publication of bibles and Christian literature in Farsi.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54092","54092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641258","2016-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on the closure of (a) church-owned theological schools and (b) leadership development programmes in Iran.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54093","54093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641259","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Faiz Mahmoud Ahmed Sherari was provided with consular assistance from the British Government during his recent detention in Israel.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53884","53884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641260","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli government on the recent detention of British citizen Faiz Mahmoud Ahmed Sherari.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53885","53885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641261","2016-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the banning of Yau Wai-ching and Baggio Sixtus Leung from taking office in the Hong Kong Legislative Council by the Chinese government on the Sino-British Joint Declaration; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59324","59324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641262","2016-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the health of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53901","53901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641263","2016-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to (a) write to and (b) meet his Iranian counterpart to discuss the case of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe following reports of her deteriorating health.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53899","53899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641264","2016-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on the case of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53900","53900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641265","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support people in the United Arab Emirates who are threatened, harassed or face arrest for exercising their right of freedom of expression.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53871","53871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641266","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to support the release of Dr Mohamed al-Roken and other human right activists imprisoned in the United Arab Emirates in 2013.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53872","53872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641267","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his United Arab Emirates counterpart on the respect for freedom of expression in that country.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53873","53873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641268","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the 40 million compensation for Chagossian people will be effectively distributed.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53936","53936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641269","2016-11-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Government has to ratify the UNESCO Convention on the Protection of Underwater Cultural Heritage; what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on that ratification; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53922","53922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641270","2016-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to the Dominican Republic to assist with the flooding in that country.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53909","53909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641271","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the annual average payment was to the Government from the US Administration for its use of the Chagos Islands.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53986","53986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641272","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will extend the deadline to apply for 10,000 lump sum payments for the widows and widowers of people who died at least partially as a result of HIV and hepatitis C infection from contaminated blood, beyond 1 March 2017.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53971","53971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641273","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on what date (a) the subcontract for Docklands Medical Services Ltd was sent to High Wealds Lewes Havens Clinical Commissioning Group by Coperforma and (b) Docklands Medical Services Ltd began transporting patients as a subcontractor for Coperforma.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53989","53989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641274","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote and facilitate the diagnosis of autism in children between the ages of two and four years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53960","53960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641275","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department makes available to support NHS providers in renovating, maintaining and developing properties that form part of the NHS estate.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53961","53961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641276","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to reduce access to high-lethality means of suicide; and what such steps have been taken to reduce the availability of helium gas.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53957","53957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641277","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the documentation his Department has received from hepatologists and other medical professionals on the potential proportion of applications to the special category mechanism from people who contracted hepatitis C from contaminated blood which will be successful.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53972","53972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641278","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to improve access to mental health services for black and ethnic minority people in the London Borough of Southwark.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53908","53908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641279","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will guarantee stage 2 payments to people with stage 1 hepatitis C who are co-infected with HIV from 2017-18 rather than requiring those people to apply through the special category mechanism.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53951","53951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641280","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the reformed English support scheme for those affected by contaminated blood, whether allocated funds not spent on beneficiaries (a) in each fiscal year to and (b) at the end of the Spending Review period in 2020-21 will be given back to HM Treasury.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53952","53952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641281","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an estimate of the number of properties that form part of the NHS estate that are not used for clinical purposes.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53962","53962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641282","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff are employed by NHS Property Services in (a) the UK and (b) each region and constituent nation.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53963","53963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641283","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many qualified surveyors are employed by NHS Property Services in (a) the UK and (b) each region and constituent nation.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53964","53964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641284","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many properties owned by NHS Property Services in (a) the UK and (b) each region and constituent nation are (i) vacant, (ii) partially occupied and (iii) fully occupied.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53965","53965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641285","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will respond to the recommendations of the World Breastfeeding Trends Initiative UK Report 2016, published in November 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53959","53959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641286","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had requests for (a) surgery on varicose veins and (b) other treatments refused under the Exceptionality Operational Policy in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53874","53874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641287","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has proposed that some congenital heart disease cases can be re-directed from the Royal Brompton Hospital to Barts Heart Centre; and how many permanent congenital cardiac surgeons Barts Heart Centre employs.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53892","53892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641288","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides to women who are (a) expecting and (b) have given birth to a baby with Down's syndrome.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54094","54094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641289","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce genetic testing for inherited heart conditions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54086","54086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641290","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on providing physiotherapy to patients who have had hip replacement operations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54095","54095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641291","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to hold NHS England to account on the delivery of the diabetes metrics outlined in the Clinical Commissioning Group Improvement and Assessment Framework 2016-17.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54082","54082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641292","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people detained under section 13 of the Mental Health Act 1983 were held in police cells in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) the Liverpool City Region and (d) England in each in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54084","54084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641293","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health community outreach programmes focussed on traditional male environments have been set up to engage with men in each local authority area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54085","54085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641294","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the Regulatory Policy Committee has made of the regulatory impact assessment published by his Department in relation to recently announced plans for community pharmacy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54056","54056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641295","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Director of Public Health for Lancashire's report, published on 6 November 2014, into the Potential Public Health Impacts of the Proposed Shale Gas Exploration Sites in Lancashire, how many of the 61 recommendations in that report his Department has acted on; and which of those recommendations have not been acted on by his Department and why.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54074","54074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641296","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to ensure that NHS England's annual prioritisation process for determining investment in specialised services is subject to transparency requirements at the same level as those placed on NICE's health technology appraisal programme.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54069","54069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641297","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice is offered to expectant mothers on post-natal support for disabled children.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54071","54071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641298","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what help and advice on charitable post-natal support is available to expectant mothers who are due to give birth to a severely disabled child.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54070","54070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641299","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Public Health England report entitled Review of the Potential Public Health Impacts of Exposures to Chemical and Radioactive Pollutants as a Result of the Shale Gas Extraction Process, published in January 2014, how many of the recommendations made in that report his Department has acted on; and which recommendations have not been acted on by his Department and why.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54073","54073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641300","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the 10th Report of the Public Accounts Committee, Session 2016-17, HC397, what progress has been made on the recommendation that NHS England must improve the transparency of its decision making with respect to specialised services.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54065","54065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641301","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on NHS winter planning for 2016-17 of changes in pharmacy funding in the period from December 2016 to April 2017.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54057","54057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641302","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to require NHS England to conduct its annual specialised commissioning prioritisation process in line with guidance issued in January 2016 by the Cabinet Office on consultation principles.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54066","54066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641303","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the publication of final decisions on commissioning policies under NHS England's annual prioritisation process for determining investment in specialised services have been delayed.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54068","54068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641304","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England will announce final funding decisions for the treatments considered through its specialised commissioning prioritisation process.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54067","54067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641305","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recommendations the Regulatory Policy Committee has made  on recently announced plans for (a) community pharmacy and (b) the Pharmacy Access Scheme.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54058","54058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641306","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are for the difference in the number of sessions required for different geographical areas for doctors to remain on the National Performers List.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54083","54083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641307","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's assessment is of the potential implications of drilling for shale gas for the health of residents living in close proximity to shale gas well sites.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54017","54017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641308","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2016 to Question 50498 on the Care Quality Commission, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the safeguards in place in the standard NHS contract to ensure rapid transfer of patient data to the relevant clinical commissioning group in the event of a sudden and unplanned cessation of operation of a contracted provider; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54015","54015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641309","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to estimate the number of residents living in close proximity to Cuadrilla Resources' shale gas well at Preston New Road who have pre-existing health conditions potentially susceptible to aggravation by drilling for shale gas.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54021","54021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641310","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support clinical commissioning groups that need improvement or have the greatest need for improvement for diabetes care under the Clinical Commissioning Group Improvement and Assessment Framework.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53992","53992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641311","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what timetable he has set for publishing the next diabetes-specific ratings as part of the Clinical Commissioning Group Improvement and Assessment Framework; and if he will publish that data on a quarterly basis.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53993","53993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641312","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people with muscle-wasting conditions living in Kent, Surrey or Sussex have access to a local neuromuscular care adviser.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53945","53945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641313","2016-11-24","Department of Health","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the change in the level of NHS England's administration costs since the introduction of the Health and Social Care Act 2012.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54009","54009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641314","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will ensure that EEA citizens who (a) have resided in the UK for a period exceeding five years and (b) are married to a UK citizen are able to obtain permanent residency in the UK without the need for them to have comprehensive sickness insurance.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54028","54028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641315","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what processes were followed by her Department when granting Maxim Bakiyev asylum; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54011","54011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641316","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse has made to the police in each month since it was established.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54031","54031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641317","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to review the requirement for EEA citizens to have comprehensive sickness insurance when applying for permanent resident status in the UK as a result of the vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54029","54029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641318","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for permanent resident status from EEA citizens have been rejected since June 2015 on the grounds of the applicant not having comprehensive sickness insurance.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54030","54030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641319","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to build another short-term detention facility in Scotland as a result of the decision by Renfrewshire Council to refuse planning permission for a short-term immigration detention facility.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 59323","59323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641320","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the status is of the report of the inquiry into overseas funding of extremism in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53895","53895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641321","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the planned publication date is of the report of the inquiry into funding of extremism in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53896","53896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641322","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the terms of reference are for the inquiry into funding of extremism in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53897","53897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641323","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of the misuse of bots for the harvesting of event tickets through primary ticketing platforms have been reported to the police under the Computer Misuse Act 1990.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53898","53898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641324","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to appeal Renfrewshire Council's decision to refuse planning permission for a short-term immigration detention facility.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53914","53914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641325","2016-11-24","Home Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Renfrewshire Council's refusal of planning permission for a short-term immigration detention facility, whether the Government still plans to close Dungavel Detention Centre.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53915","53915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641326","2016-11-24","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to the Dominican Republic to assist with the flooding in that country.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53910","53910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641327","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Sierra Leone.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53883","53883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641328","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will attend the sixty-first session of the UN Commission on the Status of Women in New York in March 2017.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53867","53867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641329","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on promoting a cross-government approach to implementing the UN's Step it Up for Gender Equality initiative.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53869","53869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641330","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to meet the Executive Director of UN Women.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53858","53858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641331","2016-11-24","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to paragraph 10 of the explanatory memorandum to the Commonwealth Development Corporation Bill, what estimate she has made of market demand over Commonwealth Development Corporation's next strategy cycle.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54037","54037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641332","2016-11-24","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the net receipts were from the Commonwealth Development Corporation in each of the last seven financial years; and what proportion of these receipts counted as overseas development aid.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54033","54033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641333","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to help to support food-insecure people in South Sudan.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54050","54050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641334","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to help support internally displaced South Sudanese refugees.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54051","54051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641335","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to help combat cholera outbreaks in South Sudan.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54049","54049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641336","2016-11-24","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) total remuneration package, (b) amount of expenses claimed and (c) number of first and business class flights taken was by each member of the Commonwealth Development Corporation board in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54034","54034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641337","2016-11-24","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in which countries the Commonwealth Development Corporation has invested in the last seven years; and what the total value of investments was in each country.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54035","54035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641338","2016-11-24","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) number and (b) value of re-capitalisations carried out by the Commonwealth Development Corporation was since the establishment of that Corporation.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54036","54036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641339","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the needs of older people with AIDS in sub-Saharan Africa.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54097","54097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641340","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to Uganda, Sudan, Ethiopia and Kenya to support South Sudanese refugees.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54052","54052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641341","2016-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to Answer Question 49066, tabled on 18 October 2016 by the right hon. Member for Camberwell and Peckham, on the use of compainants' previous sexual history in rape cases.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54072","54072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641342","2016-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions during the last four years a serious further offence investigation involving probation services in England and Wales concluded that an offender had missed more than two appointments with those services without reasonable excuse; and on how many occasions the offender was not taken back to court as a result.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54003","54003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641343","2016-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether data on numbers of offenders breached by a community rehabilitation company is given on request to the local police force.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54002","54002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641344","2016-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate her Department has made of the (a) average cost of a fit for work appeal and (b) total cost to the public purse of such appeals from July 2013 to June 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53881","53881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641345","2016-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of First-Tier tribunal (Social Security and Child Support) users represented themselves as litigants in person; and what proportion of those tribunals found in favour of the appellant.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53876","53876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641346","2016-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total amount of unpaid (a) court and (b) tribunal fees was in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53939","53939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641347","2016-11-23","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions he has had with the National Crime Agency on its investigations into allegations of political influence on the operations of the National Assets Management Agency in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53934","53934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641348","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to use revenues from clean air zones to promote cycling and walking and other healthy sustainable transport alternatives.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53938","53938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641349","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the date at which physical work to construct the extensions of Heathrow Airport will commence.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53973","53973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641350","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the likelihood of judicial review delaying the Heathrow Airport construction timetable.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53974","53974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641351","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the likelihood of the planning inquiries phase of Heathrow Airport expansion being (a) extended and (b) delayed.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53975","53975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641352","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Privacy Notice on data collection on the HS2 website was removed; and what the reasons for that removal were.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53911","53911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641353","2016-11-29","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the potential number of vehicles using (a) the Dartford River Crossing and (b) a Lower Thames Crossing in each direction following the opening of a Lower Thames Crossing broken down by each option under consideration for that crossing in (i) the month before opening, (ii) the month after opening, (iii) each month in the fifth year after opening, (iv) each month of the tenth year after opening, (v) each month in the fifteenth year after opening and (v) each month in the twentieth year after opening.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53929","53929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641354","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate how many vehicles per day using all or part of the M25 between junctions 3 and 29 in an anticlockwise direction joined the M25/A282 (a) before junction 2, (b) at junction 2, (c) at junction 1b, (d) at junction 1a and (e) at junction 30; and in each such case how many such vehicles left the M25/A282 (i) at junction 2, (ii) at junction 1a, (iii) at junction 31, (iv) at junction 30 and (v) after junction 30.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53928","53928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641355","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of crossings at (a) the Dartford River Crossing and (b) a Lower Thames Crossing (i) before and (ii) after the construction of a Lower Thames Crossing to be categorised as (A) local, (B) region, (C) long-distance, (D) national and (E) international for each option under consideration for the Lower Thames Crossing.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53927","53927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641356","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will negotiate to fast-track the public national policy statement consultation on Heathrow Airport expansion in order to deliver that project more quickly.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53953","53953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641357","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Government's policy is on bus service provision in rural areas.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53891","53891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641358","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward an accessibility action plan to improve access to taxis and private hire vehicles for guide dogs and their owners.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53903","53903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641359","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the monthly volume of vehicles using the Dartford River Crossing is in each direction for the last 12 months for which information is available by toll-tariff categories.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53925","53925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641360","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the predicted effect on congestion and uninterrupted free-flowing traffic on the M25/A282 at Dartford of (a) Option C and (b) A14 proposals for a Lower Thames Crossing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53926","53926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641361","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to promote best practice amongst licensing authorities on the use of taxis and private hire vehicles by guide dog owners.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54007","54007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641362","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress there has been on the electrification works to the TransPennine rail line through Stalybridge; and what his most recent estimate is of the potential completion date of those works.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54026","54026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641363","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2016 to Question 53161, what steps he is taking to ensure that the electrical vehicle chargepoint network has the capacity to meet future demand; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54023","54023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641364","2016-11-24","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Government will take steps to ensure that the expansion of Heathrow Airport supports job creation and economic growth in the Tees Valley.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54079","54079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641365","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of foreign-registered vehicles using the Dartford Crossing in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54098","54098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641366","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many complaints were made to his Department or Highways England on congestion at the Dartford Crossing in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54099","54099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641367","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicle accidents on the A282 were registered by Highways England in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54100","54100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641368","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed tolling of the Blackwall Tunnel on traffic levels using the Dartford Crossing.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54101","54101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641369","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the review, entitled What works to enhance inter-parental relationships and improve outcomes for children, published in March 2016, what steps his Department is taking to support the training of the future workforce to deliver the expert couple interventions.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54080","54080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641370","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether UK state pensioners who reside in the Irish Republic will receive annual updating of their UK state pension after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54055","54055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641371","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason provisions on the long service cap within the Pensions Act 2014 have not yet come into force.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54016","54016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641372","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that people affected by the increase in the basic state pension age are contacted and made aware of that increase.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54001","54001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641373","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure (a) low, fair and transparent charges and (b) robust standards in auto-enrolment schemes; and if he will ensure the good governance and fair conversion of pension provision in such schemes into income.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54000","54000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641374","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has put in place to support self-employed people to save into a pension; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53995","53995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641375","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made on the effect of his Department's reforms to pensions on different age groups.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53999","53999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641376","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the planned new procedures to tackle child maintenance evasion by non-resident parents who fail to declare their full income for tax purposes to be rolled out across the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53984","53984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641377","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of all fit-for-work decisions made in initial assessments for employment and support allowance which were subsequently overturned at appeal for each (a) month and (b) year from July 2013 to date.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53882","53882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641378","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of employment support staff employed by his Department have undergone training to help them identify and support people who may be at risk of suicide or self-harm.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53958","53958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641379","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of the potential cost to providers of requiring all private pension payments, including to those pensioners whose contributions were paid prior to 1997, to increase in line with the retail price index.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53947","53947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641380","2016-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of pensioners whose contributions were paid prior to 1997 who are not receiving annual increases to their private pension payments which are in line with the retail price index.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53946","53946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641381","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will carry out an impact assessment on the freedom and choice pension reforms.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53998","53998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641382","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants transferring from disability living allowance to personal independence payments have had their claim disallowed due to non-attendance at an assessment appointment.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53978","53978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641383","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appointments for claimants transferring from disability living allowance to personal independence payments have been rearranged or cancelled at the request of a person other than the claimant in (a) Plymouth and (b) the South West in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53977","53977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641384","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, in what areas under which spending headings the 2 billion post office transformation and modernisation fund has been spent; and how much of that funding has been spent on redundancies.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53990","53990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641385","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2016 to Question 52983, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of people using pre-payment meters.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53976","53976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641386","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will hold discussions with his (a) Colombian and (b) US counterpart on ending the use of child labour in the mining of coal in Colombia.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53890","53890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641387","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many projects in operation in his Department are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53888","53888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641388","2016-11-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with GKN on the future of the workforce at that company's Yeovil helicopter plant.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53894","53894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641389","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support the UK civil and military helicopter sector.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53861","53861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641390","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for its policies of the finding of the 2016 Lloyds Business Digital Index report, published in October 2016, that (a) 35 per cent of small businesses in the East Midlands have no basic digital skills and (b) 69 per cent of small businesses still need to invest in cyber security.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53864","53864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641391","2016-11-23","Department for International Trade","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department has taken to improve awareness among businesses in the East Midlands of (a) exporting opportunities and (b) government support for exporting.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53865","53865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641392","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies were in receipt of EU research and innovation funding in (a) the UK and (b) Wales in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53866","53866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641393","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department monitors the accessibility of franchised post offices for people with (a) mobility impairments, (b) learning disabilities and (c) other disabilities.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53994","53994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641394","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his most recent estimate is of the number of civil servants working in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53942","53942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641395","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff of the former Department for Energy and Climate Change have not had their contracts renewed since the creation of his Department.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53943","53943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641396","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to meet any of the companies involved in the takeover of the Cadbury's biscuit licence by Mondalez/Craft.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54004","54004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641397","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to undertake baseline monitoring of the health of residents living in close proximity to Cuadrilla Resources' shale gas well site at Preston New Road.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54018","54018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641398","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to institute baseline monitoring sites for air quality in residential areas in close proximity to Cuadrilla Resources' shale gas well site at Preston New Road.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54020","54020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641399","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the population of (a) deprived urban and (b) other urban areas in Hull has lived within one mile of the nearest post office outlet in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54059","54059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641400","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to run a communications campaign aimed at employers to emphasise the economic benefits of retaining women employees.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54064","54064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641401","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, (a) when he last met and (b) what future meetings he has planned with representatives of Maternity Action .","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54063","54063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641402","2016-11-23","Department for International Trade","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the salary will be for non-executive board members in his Department.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53862","53862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641403","2016-11-23","Department for International Trade","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his plans are for the number of hours worked per week by non-executive board members in his Department.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53863","53863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641404","2016-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has for inclusion within negotiations on the UK leaving the EU the continuing participation by the UK in Operation Sophia; and if he will take steps to ensure continuing UK participation in that operation after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53905","53905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/641405","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on maintaining euro-denominated clearing in the UK after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54075","54075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642169","2016-11-24","Church Commissioners","2016-11-21","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to tackle anti-semitism.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907445","907445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643117","2016-11-24","House of Commons Commission","2016-11-21","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will take steps to provide crche services for the children of hon. Members, staff and visitors.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907449","907449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643703","2016-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will introduce an air quality national framework for low emission zones.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907463","907463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643704","2016-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the sheep dip sufferers support group on organophosphate poisoning.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907462","907462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643705","2016-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure timely payments from the Rural Payments Agency.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907461","907461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638612","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has spent from the public purse on advertising the marriage tax allowance in each year since it was introduced.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53728","53728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638613","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if the Government will intervene in the business rates appeal by Bilfinger GVA on behalf of NHS trusts to prevent public funds being spent on Bilfinger GVA,","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53735","53735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638614","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many P800 adjustments were issued to individual taxpayers to correct for an over or under payment of income tax in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53751","53751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638615","2016-11-22","HM Treasury","2016-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has undertaken or commissioned research on introducing an internet sales tax.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53703","53703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638616","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications for the Rent a Room tax relief scheme have been received by HM Revenue and Customs by region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53777","53777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638617","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been claimed in tax relief under the Rent a Room scheme in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53778","53778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638618","2016-11-23","HM Treasury","2016-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52148, if he will make an assessment of the potential implications for his Department's policies of a transfer of jobs related to Euro-dominated clearing from London to Europe.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53855","53855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638619","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations he has made to the European Commission on the progress of the Government's application to the EU solidarity fund for flood damage.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53823","53823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638620","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding to date his Department has made available to each local authority area affected by flood damage from Storms Desmond, Eva and Frank; and how much of that funding was allocated from (a) the Communities and Business Recovery scheme, (b) the Bellwin scheme and (c) other funding sources.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53824","53824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638621","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) people renting rooms and (b) rooms available to rent in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53779","53779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638622","2016-11-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with local authorities about their future access to European Structural Funding.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53788","53788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638623","2016-11-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the change in the number of affordable homes to (a) rent and (b) buy since 2010.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53801","53801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638624","2016-11-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of statutory homeless households between 2009-10 and 2015-16.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53802","53802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638625","2016-11-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new homes for social rent were started in (a) 2009-10 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53803","53803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638626","2016-11-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to allocate funding to parish councils for flood damage resulting from floods in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53805","53805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638627","2016-11-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to bring forward a framework for devolution within England.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53706","53706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638628","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of winter maintenance readiness on the road network.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53707","53707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638629","2016-11-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities and combined authorities are in discussion with his Department for devolution deals due to be announced in the next round.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53708","53708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638630","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government plans to take (a) through guidance to property developers and local authorities and (b) otherwise to protect the capacity for nightclubs and live music venues to continue to trade when planning permission is being considered for converting existing offices nearby to residential properties.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53755","53755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638631","2016-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2016 to Question 51986, what guidance the Government plans to issue to (a) local authorities, (b) nightclubs, (c) residents of existing properties and (d) property developers applying for planning permission to convert offices to residential properties on their respective rights and responsibilities in relation to noise.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53756","53756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638632","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department's cyber security department investigated the recent hacking of Yahoo in order to inform its policies; and whether the Government plans to introduce a mandatory reporting requirement for breaches of that type.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53704","53704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638633","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to allow football fans to have a greater say on the running of the football clubs they support.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53714","53714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638634","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with Facebook on regulation of fake news on social media.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53698","53698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638635","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she has made an assessment of the relationship between the proportion of National Lottery funding on projects in each English region compared to the proportion of ticket sale income generated in those regions.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53699","53699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638636","2016-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on what dates she has been invited to participate in meetings of the EU Exit and Trade Cabinet Committee.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53718","53718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638637","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2016 to Question 50339, what the (a) name, (b) job title and (c) responsibility is of each of the unpaid advisers currently based in her Department.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53795","53795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638638","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to make major tourist attractions affordable for children from lower income families.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53799","53799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638639","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has for further investment in local facility infrastructure to increase activity levels.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53791","53791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638640","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department will begin accepting bids for Hyde Park Barracks towards the end of 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53782","53782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638641","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether an Intended Reprovision Plan is being assessed for (a) Hyde Park Barracks and (b) the Household Cavalry as part of his Department's Footprint Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53783","53783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638642","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings Ministers or officials of his Department have had with representatives from Bilfinger GVA to discuss the relocation of (a) Hyde Park Barracks and (b) the Household Cavalry in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53784","53784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638643","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the expected income derived from the sale of Hyde Park Barracks has already been budgeted for in current defence planning.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53785","53785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638644","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made an assessment of the current and forecast market value of Hyde Park Barracks.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53775","53775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638645","2016-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Protector programme for unmanned aerial systems is planned to be funded from his Department's core budget or as an Urgent Operational Requirement.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53692","53692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638646","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 8 November 2016, Armed Forces Pension Scheme - Advance from the Contingencies Fund, HCWS249, when he was first made aware of the shortfall in the net cash requirement amount for the Armed Forces Pension and Compensation Schemes.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53724","53724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638647","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 8 November 2016, Armed Forces Pension Scheme - Advance from the Contingencies Fund, HCWS249, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer to ensure that shortfalls in the net cash requirement amounts do not arise in the future.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53725","53725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638648","2016-11-23","Department for International Trade","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the value of arms sales from the UK to the Saudi government was in 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53727","53727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638649","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the National Grid's North West Coast Connections project on flight training in and around Cumbria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53747","53747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638650","2016-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's input will be to the public consultation on the National Grid's North West Coast Connections project.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53748","53748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638651","2016-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will issue guidance on how local small and medium-sized enterprise businesses can benefit from defence supply chain procurement.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53701","53701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638652","2016-11-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to allow and support British companies to bid for contracts in the procurement process for the Trident successor programme.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53716","53716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638653","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many employers in the (a) public and (b) private sector offered apprenticeships in (i) East Ham constituency, (ii) the London Borough of Newham and (iii) England in (A) 2010, (B) 2011, (C) 2012 and (D) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53750","53750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638654","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding was provided from the public purse for early years (a) childcare, (b) children's centres, (c) nurseries and (d) other provisions in Bristol West constituency in 2015-16; how much such funding is allocated for (i) 2016-17 and (ii) 2017-18; and what estimate her Department has made of how many full-time equivalent places such funding supports.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53754","53754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638655","2016-11-22","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the relationship between employees' working hours and the cost associated with childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53745","53745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638656","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department takes to ensure that funds allocated to local authorities to fund support for early years is spent (a) in the year for which it is allocated and (b) on early years activities.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53734","53734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638657","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of reductions in local authority funding to children's centres in Greater Manchester on educational attainment of children since 2010.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53736","53736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638658","2016-11-22","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the efficacy of the English Baccalaureate in achieving its objectives.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53762","53762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638659","2016-11-22","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to reduce the difference in attainment for children under five between the North West and the national average.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53792","53792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638660","2016-11-22","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to make funding for the Primary PE and Sport Premium available to provide activity opportunities for children during school holidays.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53790","53790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638661","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how (a) her Department's plans for post-16 education, (b) the Post-16 Skills Plan and (c) the apprenticeship levy will provide improved support for women to (i) take up and (ii) continue participating in STEM subjects.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53833","53833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638662","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to reverse the decline in the number of 31 to 60 year olds studying in part-time higher education in England since 2006-07.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53834","53834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638663","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the Higher Education and Funding Council's progress in delivering the support for part-time and flexible higher education as set out in the Government's Higher Education Funding for 2016-17 letter of March 2016.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53835","53835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638664","2016-11-23","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential contribution which loans for students studying second degrees will make towards closing the higher level skills gap in England.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53836","53836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638665","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of flood damage as a result of Storms Desmond, Eva and Frank to (a) national park authorities, (b) county councils, (c) borough councils, (d) fire and rescue authorities, (e) police and crime authorities and (f) parish councils.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53825","53825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638666","2016-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how she plans that members of the public will be able to contribute to the upcoming consultation on the 25 Year Natural Environment Plan.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53770","53770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638667","2016-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to publish the details of the public consultation on the 25 Year Natural Environment Plan.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53771","53771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638668","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any part of the Rural Payments Agency's senior management payment package is performance related.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53821","53821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638669","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cases are outstanding for commons payments from the Rural Payments Agency under the 2015 Basic Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53822","53822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638670","2016-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much in payments due to have been made in 2015 by the Rural Payments Agency have not yet been paid to commons farmers.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53729","53729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638671","2016-11-22","Department for Education","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much milk is consumed in (a) nursery and (b) primary schools.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53742","53742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638672","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the press release issued by the Minister for the Middle East of 3 November 2016, what further steps he plans to take in respect of the approval by the Israeli government of permits for constructing new homes in the illegal settlement of Gilo, East Jerusalem.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53730","53730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638673","2016-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he and his Department have had with the (a) Indian and (b) Pakistani governments on the situation in Kashmir.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53737","53737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638674","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the implications for the viability of successful peace talks between the government of Israel and the Palestinian Authority of the Palestinian Authority naming schools after terrorists who have killed Israelis.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53694","53694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638675","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the implications are for his Department's assessment of the Palestinian Authority's level of adherence to the principle of non-violence set out in the memorandum of understanding between the Palestinian Authority and the UK of the Palestinian Authority naming a new school after a terrorist who planned the Munich Olympics massacre.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53695","53695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638676","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will seek compensation for the demolition of UK or EU-funded buildings by Israel in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53815","53815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638677","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times the UK Ambassador to Ethiopia has raised with the Ethiopian government the case of Andargachew Tsege; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53800","53800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638678","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to parties involved in the conflict in Yemen on the safety and kidnapping of journalists.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53758","53758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638679","2016-11-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what UK representation was involved in John Kerry's negotiations on the conflict in Yemen during his visit to Oman on 14 November 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53760","53760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638680","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Bristol West constituency (a) he estimates have undiagnosed and (b) have diagnosed hepatitis C; and how many people who have been so diagnosed have access to the latest treatments for hepatitis C.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53766","53766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638681","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November 2016 to Question 51807, for what reasons access to the new treatments for hepatitis C that have been approved as cost-effective by NICE has been limited to 10,011 people in 2016-17.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53772","53772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638682","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England on its decision to limit the number of people able to access new hepatitis C treatments to 10,011; and on what basis that number was chosen.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53767","53767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638683","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle physical inactivity in areas with high levels of economic deprivation.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53789","53789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638684","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the average number of people with diabetes in England who received a foot risk assessment within 24 hours of admission to hospital in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53780","53780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638685","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the World Health Organisation's Global Health Sector Strategy on Viral Hepatitis, whether he plans to produce a national strategy for the elimination of hepatitis C by 2030.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53796","53796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638686","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that GP surgeries are reimbursed for the training of GPs.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53806","53806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638687","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP surgeries are in deficit.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53807","53807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638688","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on GP surgeries of waiting times to process electronic patient registrations.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53808","53808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638689","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what reports his Department has received from the seven experts embedded in Capita on the level of performance of the contract between his Department and that company.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53809","53809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638690","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff are employed to process medical record envelopes in GP surgeries.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53826","53826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638691","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) names and (b) backgrounds are of the seven experts his Department is embedding within Capita to work on ratification plans to resolve the issues with the movement and processing of medical records.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53810","53810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638692","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many instances have been recorded of Medical Record Envelopes arriving at GP surgeries damaged or with files missing.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53811","53811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638693","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patient medical records are held electronically on the GP2GP system.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53812","53812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638694","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure compensation is paid to GPs who are affected by payment delays related to the Capita contract.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53829","53829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638695","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patient medical records are held on paper.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53830","53830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638696","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many medical record envelopes have been received by GP surgeries during April to September 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53827","53827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638697","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of attendances at accident and emergency departments resulted in primary diagnosis of a mental health condition in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53719","53719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638698","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of local suicide prevention plans.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53720","53720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638699","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with clinical commissioning groups on the reorganisation of acute stroke services.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53721","53721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638700","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with sustainable transformation plan leaders on the reorganisation of acute stroke services.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53722","53722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638701","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more effective acute stroke services through their reorganisation.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53723","53723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638702","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reusing prescribed medication in blister packs which has been dispensed but not used.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53697","53697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638703","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) women and (b) babies have been transferred from Liverpool Women's Hospital to intensive care units in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53732","53732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638704","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the value in recruiting and retaining staff of salary sacrifice company cars to employers in the NHS.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53726","53726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638705","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from local government leaders on sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53717","53717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638706","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes to community pharmacy funding on the delivery of pharmaceutical services in Greater Manchester; and whether it is his intention to devolve (a) responsibility for and (b) funding of pharmacies to the Greater Manchester Combined Authority or its component local authorities.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53712","53712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638707","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the sufficiency of transitional/transformational funding for Greater Manchester health and social care devolution.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53709","53709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638708","2016-11-23","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department's contract with Capita for moving medical records has cost to date.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53828","53828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638709","2016-11-23","Home Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to publish her Department's Immigration and Enforcement Business Plan 2016-17.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53856","53856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638710","2016-11-23","Home Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from the alleged Klyuev organised crime group her Department has subjected to an (a) asset freeze and (b) asset recovery in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53854","53854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638711","2016-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will provide a breakdown of the proposed additional 2,500 prison officers by prison.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53713","53713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638712","2016-11-22","Home Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2016 to Question 52462, on which dates the Inter-Ministerial Group on Violence against Women and Girls met in 2016.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53769","53769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638713","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2016 to Question 50607, what assessment her Department has made of HIV drug resistance in the countries that her Department operates in; and what steps her Department is taking to tackle HIV drug resistance in those countries.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53776","53776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638714","2016-11-23","Department for International Development","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2016 to Question 907183, what support the Government plans to give to improve investment in renewable energy to benefit people in developing countries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53738","53738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638715","2016-11-25","Department for International Development","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has for the inclusion of HIV and AIDS within its Leaving No-One Behind framework.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53739","53739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638716","2016-11-22","Department for International Development","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has a methodology for ranking countries and regions on the adequacy of care and treatment that is available to fight HIV and AIDS in those countries and regions.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53841","53841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638717","2016-11-22","Department for International Development","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which international summits and conferences on tackling HIV and AIDS Ministers of her Department plan to attend in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53842","53842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638718","2016-11-22","Department for International Development","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her international counterparts on changes in the level of international donor funding for tackling HIV and AIDS between 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53850","53850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638719","2016-11-22","Department of Health","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make a statement on the adequacy of mental health assessments in HM Prison Strangeways, Manchester.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53715","53715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638720","2016-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many fines have been issued by courts to children for criminal offences in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53743","53743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638721","2016-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times children under the age of 18 have been re-categorised and transferred to adult prisons in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53744","53744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638722","2016-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what her Department's current assessment of the level of safety is for staff at (a) Medway, (b) Oakhill and (c) Rainsbrook secure training centres.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53741","53741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638723","2016-11-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the ratio of prisoners to prison officers was in each prison in England in each year from 2006.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53702","53702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638724","2016-11-22","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2016 to Question 52620, on County Londonderry, what the legal basis is for the Government's position given in that Answer.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53768","53768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638725","2016-11-23","Prime Minister","2016-11-18","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she has had with the (a) Scottish Government, (b) Welsh Government and (c) Northern Ireland Executive on the (i) European Social Funds, (ii) European Regional Development Fund and (iii) access and membership of the single market.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53831","53831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638726","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of construction jobs that are likely to be created through each construction contract as part of High Speed 2 Phase One in each year.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53798","53798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638727","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to promote the recruitment of local workers for the construction and operation of High Speed 2 (HS2) in (a) London, (b) Birmingham and (c) the rest of the HS2 Phase One route; and what reporting requirements he is placing on HS2 contractors with regard to (i) local labour recruitment, (ii) spending with local suppliers and (iii) recruitment from disadvantaged and under-represented groups.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53814","53814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638728","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the change in the number of (a) cars and (b) HGVs using the Dartford Crossing in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53838","53838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638729","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average speed was on vehicles travelling between junction 2 and junction 31 of the M25 on weekday evenings between 4pm and 7pm in August (a) 2008, (b) 2012 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53837","53837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638730","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what definition will be used for the term local workers in relation to recruitment policies introduced for the construction phase of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53813","53813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638731","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions in the last 12 months the Dartford Crossing has been closed; and what the cause was of each such closure.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53804","53804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638732","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the chart entitled HS2 Review Phase 1 Target Schedule on page 10 of the High Speed 2 Plus supporting slides, published by HS2 Limited on 17 March 2014, if he will update that chart so that it provides the latest contribution schedule for High Speed 2 Phase One.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53773","53773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638733","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33141, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of the removal of the tollbooths at the Dartford Crossing on air quality in Dartford.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53774","53774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638734","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with local authorities to encourage coordination between local transport plans and High Speed 2.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53793","53793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638735","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs that will be created in (a) Cheshire and (b) the North West as a result of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53794","53794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638736","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has received reports of any train operating companies that are not compliant with the Rail Vehicle Accessibility (Non-Interoperable Rail System) Regulations 2010.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53786","53786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638737","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which body is responsible for ensuring that train operating companies are compliant with the that Rail Vehicle Accessibility (Non-Interoperable Rail System) Regulations 2010.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53787","53787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638738","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, at what level tolls at the Severn Bridge will be set from January 2017.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53757","53757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638739","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will detail all policies or guidance which his Department has developed or issued which have been subject to an equality impact assessment since 2010; and what the outcome of those assessments was.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53753","53753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638740","2016-11-23","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of which train operating companies are fully compliant with the Rail Vehicle Accessibility (Non-Interoperable Rail System) Regulations 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53752","53752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638741","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is undertaking market research to improve its estimates on the number of incidents relating to truck and bus wheel loss.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53691","53691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638742","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the level of progress of the work to upgrade the M3 motorway.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53696","53696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638743","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average speed of vehicles travelling between junctions 3 and 2 on the M25 on weekdays between 4pm to 7pm in August (a) 2008, (b) 2012 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53845","53845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638744","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average speed of vehicles travelling between junctions 4 and 3 on the M25 on weekdays between 4pm to 7pm in August (a) 2008, (b) 2012 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53846","53846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638745","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average speed of vehicles travelling between junctions 2 and 3 on the M25 on weekdays between 8am to 9am in August (a) 2008, (b) 2012 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53847","53847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638746","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average speed of vehicles travelling between junctions 3 and 2 on the M25 on weekdays between the hours of 8am to 9am in August (a) 2008, (b) 2012 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53848","53848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638747","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) cars and (b) HGVs that will use the Dartford Crossing in the next (i) year, (ii) five years and (iii) 10 years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53843","53843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638748","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average speed of vehicles travelling between junctions 4 and 3 on the M25 on weekdays between the hours of 8am to 9am in August (a) 2008, (b) 2012 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53849","53849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638749","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the level of the toll that is levied on HGVs using the Dartford Crossing during peak hours.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53844","53844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638750","2016-11-22","Department for Transport","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2016 to Question 52862, if he will make representations to (a) the Home Secretary and (b) Chief Officers of Police to put in place measures to enforce the ban on coloured decorative lights on HGV vehicles.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53840","53840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638751","2016-11-23","Wales Office","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what work his Department is undertaking with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the process for the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53816","53816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638752","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support Magnox workers affected by the redundancy cap.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53817","53817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638753","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential savings to the public purse of Magnox and other nuclear workers' pension schemes being included in the public sector redundancy cap.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53818","53818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638754","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on Magnox workers' pensions of those pensions being included in the redundancy cap.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53819","53819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638755","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has met employers in the nuclear industry in relation to their pensions being included as part of the redundancy caps in the public sector.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53820","53820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638756","2016-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent from the public purse through the Work Choice programme on employment support for claimants of employment and support allowance in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53749","53749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638757","2016-11-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many UK pensioners live in (a) other EU countries, (b) Commonwealth countries and (c) the rest of the world; and how many of those people have an address in Bristol West constituency as their most recent UK residence.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53851","53851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638758","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the estimated completion date is for appointing Deputy Chairs and Members of the Central Arbitration Committee which commenced in July 2014; and what progress has been made on that appointment process.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53853","53853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638759","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what (a) correspondence and (b) representations he has received from the (i) Chairman of the Central Arbitration Committee, (ii) hon. Members and (iii) members of the House of Lords on appointments to that Committee.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53852","53852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638760","2016-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what access to finance support is available to businesses in Oldham.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53711","53711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638761","2016-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department takes to ensure that government funding to cavity wall insulation providers is spent as intended.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53746","53746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638762","2016-11-22","Department for International Trade","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what support is available to engineering companies in Oldham wishing to export to new markets.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53710","53710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638763","2016-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what change there has been in the number of households using pre-payment meters in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53705","53705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638764","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on when officials from the Office of Nuclear Regulation last met Sellafield trades union leaders from (a) Unite, (b) Prospect and (c) the GMB.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53763","53763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638765","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many franchised former Crown post offices have closed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53764","53764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638766","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the average number of financial service specialist jobs there are at those (a) Crown post offices and (b) post offices which have been franchised to WHSmith.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53765","53765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638767","2016-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department has published on the (a) number and (b) names of cavity wall insulation providers who have received government funding.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53690","53690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638768","2016-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how and by what criteria he evaluates the effectiveness of the spending of government grants to cavity wall insulation providers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53740","53740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638769","2016-11-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the UK car manufacturing sector of proposals in the HM Revenue and Customs consultation on salary sacrifice for the provision of benefits-in-kind.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53733","53733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638770","2016-11-22","HM Treasury","2016-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to make representations to the British Bankers Association on reviewing the industry protocol on access to banking.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53797","53797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638771","2016-11-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on British businesses that are part of the EU Emissions Trading Scheme.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53781","53781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638772","2016-11-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has plans for the Precautionary Principle set out in Article 191 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union to be transposed into UK law when the UK leaves the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53759","53759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638773","2016-11-22","Department for International Trade","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent steps he has taken to advise businesses with respect to trading with illegal Israeli settlements; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53761","53761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638774","2016-11-25","Department for International Trade","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2016 to Question 52404, what discussions he has had with officials of his Department to prepare a framework for bilateral investment treaties when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53832","53832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638775","2016-11-23","Department for International Trade","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Government's press release of 14 October 2016 on the visit to the Occupied Palestinian Territories of the UK trade envoy for that region, what further steps he plans to take in order to facilitate trade by (a) people in the Palestinian Business Women's Forum and (b) other Palestinian women.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53731","53731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638776","2016-11-22","Department for International Trade","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which countries his Department plans to prioritise for future international free trade agreements in the event of the UK leaving the EU customs union.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53693","53693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638777","2016-11-22","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of exiting the EU on higher education research and development in the North West.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53700","53700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638778","2016-11-22","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 11 November 2016 to Question 51791, if he will define what is considered to be a network industry.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53839","53839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638276","2016-11-21","Attorney General","2016-11-17","To ask the Attorney General, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in the Law Officers' Departments in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53511","53511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638277","2016-11-21","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the potential cost to the public purse of the Government's appeal to the Supreme Court on triggering Article 50.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53514","53514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638278","2016-11-21","Attorney General","2016-11-17","To ask the Attorney General, how many agency staff the Government Legal Department employed at what cost in 2015-16.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53587","53587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638279","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what value for money assessment the Government made of the first payment to Kids Company of 2015-16 made in accordance with Section 70 of the Charities Act 2001.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53664","53664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638280","2016-11-21","Cabinet Office","2016-11-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many working days were lost due to mental illness in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53510","53510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638281","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much of the first grant the Government paid to Kids Company in 2015-16 is her Department seeking to recover for the public purse.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53523","53523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638282","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the amount of money paid to Kids Company in 2015-16 that went towards fulfilling that charity's objectives.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53524","53524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638283","2016-11-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government made any provisions for the purposes for which the first assistance funds paid to Kids Company in 2015-16 could be used.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53525","53525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638284","2016-11-22","Cabinet Office","2016-11-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government has made an assessment of the level of potential risk of cyber interference by foreign governments in elections in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53501","53501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638285","2016-11-21","HM Treasury","2016-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the revenue accrued by HM Treasury through tax on ivory artworks and objets d'art in each of the last five years; and if his Department will make an estimate of the potential cost to the public purse of a ban on the ivory trade in the UK in the next five years.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53507","53507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638286","2016-11-21","HM Treasury","2016-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of increasing Small Business Rate Relief for businesses in London.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53490","53490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638287","2016-11-21","HM Treasury","2016-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information (a) his Department and (b) HM Revenue and Customs holds on the number of UK pensioners who receive state pensions from other EU member states.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53492","53492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638288","2016-11-22","HM Treasury","2016-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to participate in EU proposals to introduce a form of public country-by-country reporting after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53534","53534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638289","2016-11-22","HM Treasury","2016-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings he, his predecessor or Ministers of his Department have had during 2016 to date with representatives of multinational enterprises which have a UK turnover exceeding 600 million annually.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53532","53532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/638290","2016-11-22","HM Treasury","2016-11-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2016 to Question 44206, what his policy is on which countries would need to introduce public country-by-country reporting before the UK would introduce such reporting.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 53597","53597"
