"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082642","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the BBC on improving their subtitling service.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229124","229124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082643","2019-03-11","Cabinet Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has reviewed its policy on awarding grants as a result of the cancellation of the Garden Bridge project.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229173","229173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082644","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2019 to Question 227143 on Africa: EU aid and with reference to a Channel 4 news report on migrant deaths of 25 February 2019, what information her Department holds on the number of migrant deaths in facilities run by (a) the Directorate for Combating Illegal Migration and (b) other facilities funded by the EU Emergency Trust Fund for Africa.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229232","229232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082645","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the decision-making process which resulted in the £30 million investment in the Garden Bridge Trust through an increase in block grant to Transport for London.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229174","229174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082646","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans the Government has to develop a national languages strategy.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229078","229078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082647","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the £30 million grant to the Garden Bridge Trust has been spent to date; and whether any funding allocated to that project has been returned to his Department.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229175","229175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082648","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to undertake an inquiry into the Garden Bridge Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229176","229176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082649","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how often (a) resettlement day release and (b) overnight release has been used in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229233","229233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082650","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many home consultations were (a) requested, (b) granted and (c) refused for work capability assessments for universal credit claimants in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229234","229234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082651","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Post Office branches have closed in (a) North West Durham constituency, (b)the North East and (c) the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229235","229235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082652","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the ability of medium-sized companies to pay the proposed charges for continuing to submit technology appraisals and highly specialised technology recommendations.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229236","229236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082653","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) resettlement day release and (b) overnight release on resettlement outcomes.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229237","229237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082654","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support his Department plans to provide to medium-sized companies who will not be eligible for the 75 per cent discount in relation to the proposed charges for making a technology appraisal and a highly specialised technology appraisal.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229238","229238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082655","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Biosimilars Medicines Programme Board is effectively overseeing hospital trusts in relation to following shared decision-making principles and patient consent guidance when implementing biosimilar switching programmes; and what steps his Department has taken when that guidance has not been followed.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229239","229239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082656","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post office branches have been relocated into retail premises in (a) North West Durham, (b) North East England and (c) the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229240","229240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082657","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of NHS Improvement's metrics to support biosimilar uptake within the Model Hospital dashboard on adherence to best practice guidance on shared-decision making and patient consent, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229241","229241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082658","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the accessibility of online visa applications.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229242","229242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082659","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how Regional Medicines Optimisation Committees are monitoring and measuring the uptake of best value biological medicines; and what steps those committees are taking to ensure that patient consent and involvement is consistently observed.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229243","229243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082660","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the contributions made to the apprenticeship levy by different sectors in each year since the introduction of that levy.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229244","229244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082661","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many spouse visas were granted on the basis of exceptional circumstances where the sponsor did not meet the minimum income requirement in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229177","229177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082662","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of how much of the money from the apprenticeship levy has been used by employers from each sector in each year since the introduction of that levy.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229245","229245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082663","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the minimum income requirement on the integration of non-EEA partners of British citizens.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229178","229178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082664","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the public purse of women leaving the labour force due to the minimum income requirement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229179","229179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082665","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether tenants will be fully consulted as part of the review into the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229246","229246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082666","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the findings of his Department’s most recent review into the effects of the minimum income requirement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229180","229180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082667","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has been of the potential effect of the devolution of the adult education budget on the diversity of adult education provision.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229181","229181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082668","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to make an announcement on progress relating to the national retraining scheme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229182","229182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082669","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of dangerous journeys being taken by unaccompanied child refugees with family in the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229183","229183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082670","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish its response to the school exclusions review call for evidence; and what steps his Department plans to take in response to that call for evidence.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229184","229184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082671","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied minors have been resettled in the UK under section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229185","229185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082672","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he will publish his Department’s plans on how to implement EU Equine Passport Regulation – (EU) No. 2015/262; and whether his Department has developed alternative proposals for when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229186","229186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082673","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department plans to announce the final results of the Windrush lessons learned review.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229187","229187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082674","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department plans to announce the final details of the Windrush compensation scheme.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229188","229188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082675","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the length of time it will take to fully compensate everyone eligible under the Windrush compensation scheme.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229189","229189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082676","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to provide earmarked funding for The West Midlands Combined Authority to help it implement its local cycling and walking infrastructure plan.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229190","229190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082677","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much money Plymouth is planned to receive from the Stronger Towns Fund in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229247","229247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082678","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what criteria was used to assess deprivation in communities as part of allocating funding via the Stronger Towns Fund.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229248","229248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082679","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of people benefit from the free TV licence for over-75s in (a) North West Durham, (b) North East of England and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229249","229249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082680","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to address the claims by African veterans of the Second World War who received the gratuity payment at the end of that war that the payment was made at different rates based on ethnicity.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229191","229191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082681","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials of his Department have had with Royal Commonwealth Ex-Service League on the gratuity payments made to African soldiers made at the end of the Second World War; and whether his Department has information on the number of veterans who were subject to the differential pay.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229192","229192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082682","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what powers the Child Maintenance Group has to recover funds from a parent reluctant to support their child or children; and how many times each power has been used in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229125","229125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082683","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list all the crematoria in England operating within the 50-yard requirement of Section 5 of the Cremation Act 1902.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229086","229086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082684","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 2 (General) Certificate of Sponsorship have been submitted in each month since November 2018; how many of those applications were granted; and how many of those applications were refused as a result of the annual cap having been reached.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229193","229193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082685","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many dangerous driving cases by (a) police officer rank and (b) police force area the Independent Office for Police Conduct has considered in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229126","229126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082686","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many dangerous driving cases the Independent Office for Police Conduct has considered which have resulted in (a) misconduct not found, (b) no further action, (c) management advice, (d) a written warning, (e) a final written warning, (f) an extension of a final written warning, (g) a dismissal with notice and (h) a dismissal without notice in each of the last five  years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229127","229127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082687","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases the Independent Office for Police Conduct considered which lasted (a) less than six months, (b) six to 12 months, (c) 12 to 24 months, (d) 24 months or longer before a conclusion was reached in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229128","229128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082688","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line B School Infrastructure and Funding of Education (Department) of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229194","229194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082689","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to HM Treasury, Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates 2018-19, Department for Education, Spending in DE, Line C School Infrastructure and Funding of Education (ALB) (Net), what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in that line of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229250","229250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082690","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line D Education Standards, Curriculum and Qualifications (Department) of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229251","229251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082691","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line E Social Care, Mobility and Equalities (Department) of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229252","229252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082692","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line F Social Care, Mobility and Equalities (ALB) (Net), of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229253","229253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082693","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the future of the Erasmus programme for UK students after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229195","229195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082694","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line G Standards and Testing Agency of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229254","229254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082695","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2019 to Question 226741 on Exports: Advertising, how much of the £1.90 million spent on advertising on online digital formats was spent on (a) Twitter, (b) Facebook, (c) Instagram, (d) Google, (e) LinkedIn and (f) other sites.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229255","229255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082696","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line H Teaching Regulation Agency of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229256","229256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082697","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received on ensuring that UK students can participate in the Erasmus programme after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229196","229196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082698","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line I Education and Skills Funding Agency (ESFA) of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229257","229257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082699","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line J Grants to LA Schools via ESFA of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229258","229258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082700","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line K Grants to Academies via ESFA of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229259","229259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082701","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line L Higher Education of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229260","229260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082702","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 202 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding outlined in Line M Further Education of the estimate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229261","229261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082703","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions his Department has had with his EU counterparts on the UK seeking association to the next Erasmus programme regardless of whether the UK leaves the EU with a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229197","229197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082704","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the Government's funding mechanism for Erasmus+ underwrites will work in practice; and which body or bodies will be responsible for allocating that money to students.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229198","229198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082705","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to HM Treasury Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates 2018-19 Department for Education Spending in DEL, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital allocations set out at line N Higher Education (ALB) (net).","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229262","229262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082706","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to HM Treasury Central Government Supply Estimates 2018-19: Supplementary Estimates 2018-19 Department for Education Spending in DEL, what programmes are funded by the (a) resource and (b) capital funding set out at line O Further Education (ALB) (net).","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229263","229263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082707","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on staffing levels of the changes to the Health and Care Professions Council registration fees from October 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229129","229129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082708","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 213222 on Immigration: EU Nationals, what the differences are between the rights retained by Irish citizens under the (a) EU Settlement Scheme and (b) Common Travel Area.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229264","229264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082709","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 19 June 2018 to Question 153188, whether reciprocal rights to study will include (a) third level education and (b) schooling; and whether those rights will cover cross-border provision across the Irish land border.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229265","229265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082710","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2018 to Question 153188, Common Travel Area, whether the Government's commitment to reciprocal Common Travel Area rights to social welfare entitlements and benefits for Irish nationals will encompass all social security provision currently accessible to Irish nationals in the UK under EU free movement rights.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229266","229266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082711","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2018 to question 153188, whether the commitment to reciprocal Common Travel Area rights to health care includes cross-border provision across the Irish land border.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229267","229267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082712","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much money has been spent from the public purse on the National Holocaust Memorial.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229098","229098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082713","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the cost to the public purse of the National Holocaust Memorial was as a result of civil servant resources.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229099","229099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082714","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much and what proportion of the cost to the public purse of the National Holocaust Memorial was as a result of payments to (a) members of staff of and (b) advisers to the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229100","229100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082715","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2019 to Question 226741 on Exports: Advertising, how much of the £0.72 million spent on advertising in physical formats was spent on (a) billboards, (b) leaflets and (c) other forms of physical advertising.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229268","229268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082716","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2019 to Question 226741 on Exports: Advertising, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of exports as a result of the Exporting is Great publicity campaign.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229269","229269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082717","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what initiatives, in addition to the Local to Global podcast, his Department has introduced for the Exporting is Great campaign.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229270","229270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082718","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on (a) Gazan patients allegedly using medical permits to smuggle weapons or explosives into Israel at the behest of Hamas and (b) the extent of fraudulent applications for medical permits by Gazans.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229271","229271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082719","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussion he has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) his Irish counterpart on establishing a bi-lateral arrangement on the recognition of driving licences between the to countries in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229130","229130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082720","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how may road policing officers there have been in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229272","229272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082721","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much money his Department has spent on road safety each year since 2009.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229273","229273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082722","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of individuals subject to the  2019 Loan Charge in (a) Lewisham, Deptford constituency, (b) London Borough of Lewisham and (c) London.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229274","229274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082723","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what provision has been made to ensure that disguised remuneration scheme providers are liable for the tax on fees taken from each individual’s income during that scheme's operation.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229275","229275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082724","2019-03-11","Wales Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on trends in violent crime in Wales; and what the outcomes were of those discussions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229131","229131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082725","2019-03-11","Wales Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will list the (a) visits he has made to Welsh Parliamentary constituencies and (b) the purpose for each of those visits in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229132","229132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082726","2019-03-11","Wales Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on the potential effect of the Stronger Towns fund on Welsh communities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229133","229133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082727","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time is for routine NHS appointments across all departments in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229101","229101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082728","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time is for a GP appointment in (a) Yorkshire and (b) England in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229102","229102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082729","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to review the immigration rules in relation to the medical research sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229276","229276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082730","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department plans to make available for constructing schemes in local cycling and walking infrastructure plans.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229134","229134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082731","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2019 to Question 210707 on electromagnetic fields: health hazards, whether the independent Advisory Group on Non-ionising Radiation plans to make an assessment of the effect on health of (a) developments and advances in the use and coverage of wireless signals across the UK since 2012 and (b) the roll out 5G networks.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229277","229277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082093","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to amend the rules on vehicle licensing as a result of the judgment of the Court of Justice of the European Union in Fundo de Garantia Automovel v Juliana and another, Case C-80/17.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228560","228560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082094","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the criteria for the distribution of the (a) Housing Infrastructure Fund Forward Fund, (b) Estates Regeneration Fund, (c) Home Building Fund, (d) Small Sites Fund and (e) Land Assembly Fund on the number of houses built in different local authority areas.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228561","228561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082096","2019-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals, similar to provisions in the Land Reform (Scotland) Act 2003, to improve access to inland waterways.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228656","228656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082097","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department takes to ensure that all procurements satisfy qualifying criteria.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228657","228657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082098","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on awarding contracts to contractors whose tender is more expensive than the lowest quote.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228658","228658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082099","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has ever awarded a contract to an insolvent company.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228659","228659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082101","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Egyptian counterpart on the detention of Egyptian human rights activist Azza Soliman; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228660","228660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082102","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will take steps to ensure that all people providing care can be subject to regulation and an enhanced DBS check.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228661","228661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082103","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to help ensure the safety of people procuring services of self-employed carers.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228662","228662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082105","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to tackle issues arising from a potential convergence between gaming and gambling.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228663","228663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082106","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) of the increased use  loot boxes in and (b) other aspects of video games on levels of gambling.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228664","228664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082108","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish his White Paper on online harms.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228665","228665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082109","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to include policies to protect children from video game features that encourage gambling behaviour in his White Paper on online harms.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228666","228666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082110","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to increase awareness among parents of the potential for some video games to encourage gambling behaviour in children.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228667","228667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082111","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Gambling Commission on (a) the use of loot boxes in video games and (b) concerns that those features encourage gambling behaviour.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228668","228668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082112","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the video games sector on concerns about the convergence of gaming and gambling.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228669","228669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082113","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to publish its Green Paper on family justice matters.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228670","228670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082115","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taken to (a) reform and (b) tackle widespread corruption in the debt collection industry.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228671","228671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082116","2019-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps he has taken to ensure the transparency of all publicly funded medical research.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228672","228672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082117","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps has he taken to ensure that medicines developed from public research are (a) accessible and (b) affordable.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228673","228673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082118","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the Innovation in Democracy Programme; and what the timescale is for announcing the successful local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228562","228562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082119","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to encourage businesses to offer meaningful employment to people with dyslexia.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228674","228674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082120","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward proposals obliging housing developers as a condition of planning consent to provide defibrillators (a) on site during the construction and (b) for use by residents following the completion of developments.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228675","228675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082122","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will allocate additional funding for resources to protect young victims of crime.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228676","228676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082123","2019-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the timescale for the review of the British Horseracing Authority's review whip sanctions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228544","228544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082124","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2018 to Question 174614  on Horses: Slaughterhouses, how many soliped and equidae were slaughtered in 2018; and how many of those soliped and equidae carried passports issued by Weatherbys.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228545","228545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082125","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what analysis his Department has conducted on the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on procedural changes in flagging eligibility for the pupil premium.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228677","228677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082126","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what analysis his Department has conducted with the Department for Housing, Communities and Local Government on the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on procedural changes in flagging eligibility for pupil premium by local authority area.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228678","228678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082128","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on the number of pupils eligible for the pupil premium; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228679","228679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082129","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the evidential basis is for the Government's conclusion that the UK will automatically fall out of the European Universities Institute Convention upon the UK’s exit from the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228680","228680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082130","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that the UK aligns with the package of regulations set out under the EU's smarter rules for safer food proposals after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228681","228681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082131","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason HMRC is not enabling the removal by supply ship of scrap metal from Mare harbour in the Falkland Islands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228546","228546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082133","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Tackling Antimicrobial Resistance Action Plan 2019-2024, how delinking the price paid for antimicrobials from the volume sold will ensure that products produced by industry are affordable to the NHS.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228682","228682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082134","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using models that de-link the cost of research and development from the price of the final product and the volume of sales, as set out in the 2016 UN Political Declaration of the High-Level Meeting of the General Assembly on antimicrobial resistance, to ensure that new diagnostics, medicines and tools created are accessible and affordable.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228683","228683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082136","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Scottish Limited Partnerships have not registered a Person of Significant Control.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228684","228684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082137","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the value was of fines levied against Scottish Limited Partnerships for failing to register a Person of Significant Control in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228685","228685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082138","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Scottish Limited Partnerships are qualifying partnerships under the terms of the Scottish Partnerships (Register of People with Significant Control) Regulations 2017 and the Companies and Partnerships (Accounts and Audit) Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228686","228686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082140","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the proportion of brownfield sites that have been contaminated by asbestos.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228687","228687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082141","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS login is fully tested and fit for launch.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228688","228688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082142","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many dwellings built or created through Permitted Development Rights in England have been found to be in breach of Building Regulations since 2015.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228689","228689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082143","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the per annum cost is of the additional staff his Department has recruited since June 2016 to work on projects relating to the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228690","228690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082145","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the Barnett consequentials of the Stronger Towns Fund will be for (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228691","228691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082146","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the Barnett consequentials of the Stronger Towns Fund will be made available to the Scottish Government, Welsh Government and to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228692","228692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082147","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 226005, High Speed 2 Railway Line, how much has been disbursed from the public purse on fees and disbursements to the barristers chambers referred to in relation to HS2 matters.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228532","228532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082149","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to change the military Brigade structure throughout the UK; and what effect changes to the military Brigade structure would have on the 38 (Irish) Brigade in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228563","228563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082150","2019-03-11","Women and Equalities","2019-03-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that workers receive equal pay regardless of age.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228693","228693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082152","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken since 1 July 2016 to assess the effect of the UK’s departure from the EU on Eurotunnel’s handling of freight volumes from the continent.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228592","228592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082153","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the taxpayer of upgrading Eurotunnel’s terminals in the UK and France ahead of the UK’s departure from the EU.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228593","228593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082154","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total costs to date are from the procurement exercise for additional roll-on roll-off ferry freight capacity in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228594","228594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082156","2019-03-11","Cabinet Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the estimated cost to Government has been of cyber incidents affecting the public sector in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228784","228784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082157","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 February 2019 to Question 221775 on UK Shared Prosperity Fund, when he plans to publish the outcomes of the consultation on the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228694","228694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082158","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when Delay Repay 15 will be introduced on the Great Eastern Mainline.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228695","228695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082159","2019-03-11","Prime Minister","2019-03-05","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to her comments of 4 March 2019 that there is no direct correlation between certain crimes and police numbers, whether she has made an assessment of which crimes do have a direct correlation with police numbers.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228696","228696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082160","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans does his Department has for improving health outcomes for people with long-term cognitive and behavioural difficulties caused by carbon monoxide poisoning.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228595","228595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082161","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will meet with campaigners and the Rt Hon. Member for Rhondda to discuss reviewing provision of neurorehabilitation services throughout the country, particularly in cases of brain injury caused by carbon monoxide poisoning.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228596","228596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082163","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it is Government policy for energy companies to make it compulsory for customers to have smart meters installed if they wish to remain on a fixed tariff.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228547","228547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082164","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary for Family support, housing and child maintenance to the Work and Pensions Select Committee on 21 November 2018, what progress has been made on introducing implicit consent in universal credit for organisations offering support to claimants.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228697","228697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082165","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2018 to Question 190938, whether (a) for a closed universal credit claim there is read-only access to the payment statements as well as the journal and (b) there is read-only access to all closed previous universal credit claims even after a new claim has been opened.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228698","228698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082166","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many medical assessments for personal independence payment have been held in private gyms and spas in (a) County Durham, (b) North East of England and (c) the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228699","228699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082167","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the length of time claimants are waiting for a decision to be made on their mandatory reconsideration of carer’s allowance claims in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228700","228700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082169","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what consultation his Department has undertaken on the level and appropriateness of parking fines on issued in NHS hospital car parks.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228785","228785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082170","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 209284 on Palestinians: Schools, whether her Department has commissioned the study into the new Palestinian textbooks.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228536","228536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082171","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the salaries of Palestinian Authority (PA) employees paid by her Department will be reduced as a result of the the announcement by the PA Minister of Finance that the salaries of public employees will be partial following the ending of US support to the PA.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228548","228548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082172","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has in addition to the levy transfer, to review the (a) barriers and (b) incentives to non-levy participation in degree apprenticeships.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228564","228564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082173","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to ensure disadvantaged young people are able to access degree apprenticeships.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228565","228565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082175","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to establish performance criteria for degree apprenticeships and social mobility.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228566","228566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082176","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps he plans to take to support the denuclearisation of the Korean peninsula after the recent US-North Korean talks in Hanoi.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228597","228597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082177","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many requests for research funding into Lyme Disease have been submitted to National Institute for Health Research health protection research units; how many of those applications have been approved; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228549","228549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082178","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Administration on the possibility of military intervention in Venezuela by outside forces.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228598","228598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082179","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it remains his Department’s policy to convene a summit of European and Arab foreign ministers to discuss the US Administration's proposed peace plan for that region.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228599","228599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082180","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the US Administration has provided his Department with the Administration's draft proposals for a Middle East peace plan.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228600","228600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082181","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he considers it (a) accurate and (b) acceptable that the United States administration has still not shared the draft proposals in its Middle East Peace Plan with the governments of (a) France and (b) Germany.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228601","228601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082183","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to issue a formal apology to the Government of Slovenia for describing that country as a former Soviet vassal state.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228602","228602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082184","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Iranian counterparts on their recent testing of submarine-based cruise missile technology.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228603","228603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082185","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of advances in the abilities of medical practitioners to diagnose Lyme Disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228550","228550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082187","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps he is taking to prevent Iran from producing nuclear-armed warheads that can be carried by that country's submarine-based cruise missiles.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228604","228604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082188","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the processing of asylum claims from people fleeing the persecution of Christians overseas.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228605","228605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082190","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the reported deaths of 3,731 Christians in Nigeria in 2018, what representations he has made to the Home Secretary on the assessment of asylum claims from Nigerian Christians.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228606","228606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082191","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what training is given to medical practitioners to enable them to (a) recognise the symptoms of and (b) treat Lyme Disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228551","228551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082192","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government in Myanmar on the destruction of churches in Kachin state and their replacement with Buddhist pagodas.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228607","228607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082194","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he has made an assessment of the effectiveness of his Department's programme to involve religious minorities in reconciliation programmes in Iraq; and whether he has plans to extend those reconciliation programmes to religious minorities in other countries.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228608","228608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082195","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the arrest of Pastor Wang Yi and his wife Jiang Rong of the Early Rain Covenant Church in Chingdu province in December 2018 on charges of incitement to subvert state power.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228609","228609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082196","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the (a) persecution of Christians, (b) suppression of the Christian faith in that country and (c)that country's  plans to issue a new, state-approved translation of the Bible.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228610","228610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082197","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Zimbabwean counterpart on the violent suppression of civilian protests in that country in January 2019.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228611","228611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082199","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Russian government to end impunity and conduct prompt and effective investigations into all threats and incidents of violence against human rights defenders and journalists.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228612","228612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082200","2019-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to bring forward legislation on increased sentencing for animal cruelty in this session of Parliament.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228701","228701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082201","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he will expedite visa applications for Russian human rights defenders, journalists and civil society activists wishing to visit the UK to discuss the human rights situation in Russia; and whether the Government will provide temporary visas for sanctuary, or full asylum, for Russian human rights defenders and journalists who need to leave Russia due to concerns for their safety.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228613","228613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082203","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise press freedom in all bilateral discussions with Russia and call for the (a) immediate and unconditional release of all journalists and bloggers jailed and (b) an end to violence against journalists in Russia.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228614","228614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082204","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2018 to the Question 199278 on Driving and Diabetes, when the DVLA plans to publish its guidance on the use of continuous or flash glucose monitoring devices for drivers with diabetes.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228552","228552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082205","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of widening the scope of the Women in Finance Charter to other sectors of the economy.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228702","228702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082206","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the conclusions of the AAT MP Survey Results, published on 21 January 2019, which found that 54 per cent of hon. Members would support changing the Women in Finance Charter to incorporate all sectors of the economy.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228703","228703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082207","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the widening of the Women in Finance Charter to cover other sectors of the economy.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228704","228704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082208","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will rename the Women in Finance Charter to reflect the contribution of women across the whole of the economy.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228705","228705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082210","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons his Department missed the deadline or refiled its gender pay gap data for 2017-18.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228615","228615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082211","2019-03-11","Women and Equalities","2019-03-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will make an estimate of the number of companies that have not yet filed accurate gender pay gap data for 2017-18.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228616","228616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082212","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the undertakings in the Armed Forces Covenant, what steps he is taking to ensure that veterans are identified when they enter the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228567","228567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082213","2019-03-11","Women and Equalities","2019-03-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Guardian article of 28 February 2019 entitled Lack of sanctions makes a mockery of gender pay gap reports, if she will make an estimate of the number of companies that have provided mathematically impossible figures for gender pay gap data for (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228617","228617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082214","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of mentoring support for armed forces veterans in prisons on re-offending rates.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228568","228568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082215","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the number of grammar schools on levels of social mobility.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228569","228569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082217","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has allocated to local authorities for the development of new (a) garden cities and (b) villages.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228570","228570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082218","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the annual cost was of medical education per student in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228571","228571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082219","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the annual cost was of engineering education per student in higher education institutions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228572","228572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082220","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the annual cost was of social media studies education per student in higher education in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228573","228573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082222","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the annual cost was of dental education per student in higher education in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228574","228574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082223","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the amount of HRT that was (a) prescribed and (b) dispensed in England and Wales in 2017-18.","Biography information for Rachel Maclean","Rachel Maclean","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228786","228786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082224","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the annual cost was of veterinary education per student in higher education in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228575","228575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082226","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of expanding mentoring services for veterans leaving prison nationwide.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228576","228576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082227","2019-03-11","Women and Equalities","2019-03-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many companies were asked to refile their gender pay gap data for 2017-18 due to inaccurate or missing data.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228618","228618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082228","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps his Department has taken to raise standards in schools.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228577","228577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082229","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to increase the take-up of STEM subjects.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228578","228578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082230","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the oral contribution of 4 March 2019 by the hon. Member for South Shields, Official Report, column 749, when he plans to make a statement on the Government's response to the Food Insecurity Bill.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228706","228706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082231","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many active motorway speeding cameras are situated on the (a) M1, (b) M2, (c) M3, (d) M4, (e) M5 and (f) M6.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228553","228553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082233","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been issued speeding fines on the (a) M1, (b) M2, (c) M3, (d) M4, (e) M5 and (f) M6 in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228554","228554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082234","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the average cost to schools of a pupil on an Education, Health and Care Plan .","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228579","228579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082235","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequacy of high needs funding for schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228580","228580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082236","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been spent by each local authority in the North West on education appeals tribunals; and what the value was of costs awarded to applicants in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228581","228581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082237","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether Warrington Borough Council will be eligible to bid for funding from the Stronger Towns Fund.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228582","228582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082239","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an estimate of the value of funding from the Stronger Towns Fund that will be allocated to Cheshire and Warrington.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228583","228583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082240","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking with the Department for Education to provide free sanitary products in (a) secondary schools, (b) colleges and (c) universities.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228707","228707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082241","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to provide free sanitary products to (a) girls and(b) women in (i) secondary schools, (ii) colleges and (iii) universities.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228708","228708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082243","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference his oral contribution on 5 March 2019, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on an industrial strategy for small modular nuclear reactors.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228709","228709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082244","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his oral contribution of 5 March 2018, Official Report, column 788, how much money has been spent from the public purse on preparing for a potential industrial strategy for small modular reactors.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228710","228710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082246","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his oral contribution of 5 March 2018, Official Report, how much the Government plans to spend on a potential industrial strategy for small modular reactors.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228711","228711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082247","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his oral contribution of 5 March 2018, Official Report, column 788 whether it his policy to provide as much fiscal support to a north sea oil and gas sector deal as is given to any potential industrial strategy for small modular reactors.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228712","228712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082248","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his oral contribution of 5 March 2018, Official Report, column 788 whether it his policy to provide as much fiscal support for renewable energy as is given to any potential industrial strategy for small modular reactors.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228713","228713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082250","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department met representatives of the fossil fuel industry to discuss EcoDrive, a gadget to help preserve fuel usage.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228619","228619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082251","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department met representatives of the fossil fuel industry to discuss EcoDrive, a gadget to help preserve fuel usage.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228620","228620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082252","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's consultation entitled Taxi and private hire vehicle licensing: protecting users, published on 12 February 2019, whether he has plans for statutory guidance to prohibit vehicles from undertaking journeys which do not take place or end in the area which they are licensed.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228584","228584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082253","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the consultation on statutory guidance for the licensing of private hire vehicles, whether the Government will provide financial assistance to help vehicle owners make the changes necessary to meet the new regulations.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228585","228585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082254","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 140109 on Healthy Start and Nursery Milk schemes, how much funding his Department allocated to the (a) Healthy Start scheme and (b) Nursery Milk Scheme in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2017-18 and (iv) 2018-19.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228714","228714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082255","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to allocate to Wales money for community rejuvenation similar to other towns in England.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228715","228715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082257","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking with local taxi licensing authorities to ensure that drivers continue to meet standards after the initial granting of their licence.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228621","228621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082258","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Immigration White Paper, published in December 2018, if he will publish his Department's engagement proposals as described in that White Paper.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228716","228716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082259","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to prevent taxi or private hire vehicle drivers from operating exclusively outside of the locality in which they are licensed.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228622","228622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082261","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Stronger Towns Fund will be replicated in Wales.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228717","228717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082262","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much interest has been paid by NHS trusts and Foundation Trusts on bailout loans from his Department in (a) the last 12 months and (b) each of the last five years; where such interest is paid to; and for what purposes such interest payments were subsequently used.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228718","228718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082264","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Immigration White Paper, published in December 2018, what type of engagement he plans to undertake in relation to the proposals described in that White Paper.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228719","228719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082265","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the eligibility criteria for the Stronger Towns Fund will be; and whether local authorities can apply to that fund for (a) specific projects or (b) grants for general use.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228555","228555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082266","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Immigration White Paper, published in December 2018, when the engagement set out in that White Paper will take place.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228720","228720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082267","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Immigration White Paper, published in December 2018, if he will hold discussions with (a) the Royal College of Nursing and (b) other organisations representing the health and social care workforce on the proposals in that White Paper.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228721","228721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082268","2019-03-11","Cabinet Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2019 to Question 227162 on Brexit, when his Department will disclose full recent costs of TV advertising related to the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228722","228722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082270","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will publish the full analysis his Department undertook that concluded that the NHS spends £470 on average per person per year on treating people required to pay the immigration health surcharge.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228723","228723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082271","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the competitiveness of the UK peer-to-peer lending sector compared to (a) the US, (b) China and (c) the rest of the world.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228623","228623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082272","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have invested in an Innovative Finance ISA; and what assessment he has made of the level of uptake of that ISA.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228624","228624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082273","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the comparative merits of flat rate Interchange Fees as opposed to fees proportional to the value of the transaction; and whether his Department plans to exercise section 7 of the Interchange Fee (Amendment) (EU Exit) Regulations 2018 to decrease the per transaction interchange fee.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228625","228625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082274","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his oral contribution of 25 February 2019, Official Report column 36, what his timescale is for the (a) piloting and (b) introduction of teaching on lifesaving and first aid skills; and what support his Department is providing to schools for that teaching.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228724","228724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082276","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his oral contribution of 25 February 2019, Official Report column 36, how he plans to distribute the £6 milllion support package for schools.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228725","228725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082277","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the publication of final guidance and regulations on teaching Relationship and Sex Education and Health Education in schools, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of including lessons on combating loneliness and social isolation.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228726","228726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082278","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question 225546 on Biofuels: Import Duties, when she plans to make a public announcement on biofuel tariffs ahead of the UK leaving the EU on the 29 March 2019; (a) when and (b) how she plans to inform representatives of the UK bioethanol industry of the decision on those tariffs; and if she will make it her policy that there will be at least 15 working days between informing representatives of the UK bioethanol industry and making that public announcement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228727","228727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082279","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he expects a decision will be made on the commissioning of a prostate surgery robotic unit at the Alexandra Hospital in Redditch.","Biography information for Rachel Maclean","Rachel Maclean","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228787","228787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082280","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nurses left the NHS in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228728","228728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082281","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what provisions are in place to ensure a sustainable future for children’s services in West Lancashire.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228626","228626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082282","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what purposes jobcentre staff will visit claimants in hospital.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228729","228729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082283","2019-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support he plans to provide to businesses to help with the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228730","228730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082284","2019-03-11","Cabinet Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the change has been in the ratio per thousand of population of (a) male and (b) female children diagnosed with cancer in the UK between (a) 2008 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228627","228627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082285","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold discussions with his US counterpart on future sanctions on North Korea following the recent discussions between the US and North Korea.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228628","228628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082286","2019-03-11","Church Commissioners","2019-03-05","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, when she expects the internal investigation into complaints against the Dean of Christ Church college Oxford to conclude.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228586","228586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082287","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the (a) performance of the procurement process in the NHS and (b) susceptibility of that process to procurement fraud.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228731","228731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082288","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking with the NHS to tackle the cost of fraud to the NHS.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228732","228732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082289","2019-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2019 to Question 226666 on Air Pollution: Scunthorpe, if he will provide that same information for Scunthorpe in the North Lincolnshire local authority area.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228629","228629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082291","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that the review of the loan charge is undertaken (a) independently and (b) rigorously.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228630","228630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082292","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that the review of the loan charge will report by the end of March 2019.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228631","228631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082293","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that HMRC treats people affected by the loan charge in a sensitive and supportive but appropriate way.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228632","228632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082294","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to introduce access and waiting time standards for adults with an eating disorder.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228733","228733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082295","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to increase funding for community eating disorder services for children and young people.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228734","228734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082296","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase public awareness of the symptoms of eating disorders.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228735","228735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082297","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on ensuring that business rate relief is not used for second homes to avoid council tax in (a) rural and (b) coastal communities.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228736","228736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082298","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many incomplete patient treatments there have been where the waiting time was over 52 weeks in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228737","228737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082299","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has plans to require employers to contract occupational health services; and what assessment she has made of the potential costs to business of implementing such a requirement.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228633","228633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082300","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the quality of (a) occupational health services and (b) SEQOHS accreditation scheme in measuring the effectiveness of those services in delivering successful returns to work.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228634","228634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082301","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the average cost to an employer of contracting a physician-led occupational health service.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228635","228635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082302","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential growth of the occupational health market in the event that all employers contracted occupational health services.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228636","228636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082303","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to EIM21774 of the Employment Income Manual, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the tax exemption for employer-funded medical treatment; and what estimate he has made of the (a) cost to the public purse of implementing that exemption, (b) savings accrued to the public purse of the use of that exemption and (c) amount that has been claimed by employers under that exemption since its introduction.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228637","228637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082304","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussion he has had with the Secretary of State for (a) Work and Pensions and (b) Health and Social Care on reform of the tax exemption for employer-funded medical treatment.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228638","228638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082305","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has any plans to amend the Income Tax (Recommended Medical Treatment) Regulations 2014 to incentivise employers to support staff returning to work after a period of sickness absence; and what assessment he has made of the effect of the 28 consecutive day qualifying period on the number of staff returning to work.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228639","228639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082306","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent financial incentives she has introduced to encourage employers to invest in the health and well being of their workforce through the contracting of services designed to facilitate more rapid returns to work by employees at risk of health-related job loss.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228640","228640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082307","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeframe is for the public consultation on the healthy start welfare food scheme, announced in the paper entitled, Childhood Obesity: A plan for action, published in June 2018.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228641","228641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082308","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question 225521 on Specialist Schools: Complaints, how many complaints he has received from parents in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228738","228738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082309","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children aged (a) four to five and (b) 10 to 11 years were recorded as obese in (i) England, (ii) each English region and (iii) each London borough in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228739","228739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082310","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated to healthy start welfare foods payments in each year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228740","228740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082311","2019-03-11","Women and Equalities","2019-03-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether there are companies that have not filed their gender pay gap data for 2017-18.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228642","228642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082312","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many full-time equivalent school nurses there were in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228741","228741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082313","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many falls among people aged 65 and over led to a hospital admission in each year since 2009-10; and what the five most frequent types of those falls were.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228742","228742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082314","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the review of post-18 education and funding.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228643","228643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082315","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Disabled People of 22 January 2019, Official Report, column 106WH on the satisfaction ratings of disability benefit claimants, if she will commission independent research on the satisfaction rates of claimants who have recently undergone a work capability assessment.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228788","228788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082316","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 30 May 2018 to Question 146988 on the revised wording of the ESA65B letters sent to employment support allowance claimants’ GPs, on what date the meeting took place at which the British Medical Association and the Royal College of General Practitioners agreed to that revised wording.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228789","228789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082317","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much each NHS trust spent on legal fees defending employment tribunal cases relating to (a) discrimination, (b) unfair dismissal and (c) public interest disclosure in each year since 2016.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228644","228644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082318","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will consult the welfare benefits advice sector and disability charities on the wording of the ESA65B letter to claimants’ GPs after a Work Capability Assessment that finds them fit for work.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228790","228790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082319","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with E. coli in each financial year for which data are available since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228743","228743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082320","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many immigration appeals are pending in ETS-linked cases.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228537","228537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082321","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether A1 forms for artists and musicians will be accepted after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228645","228645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082322","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons applicants for universal credit are subject to a five week assessment period before being entitled to claim that benefit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228538","228538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082323","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions his Department has had with Educational Testing Service (ETS) on ETS's allegations of cheating by overseas students taking the test of English for international communication in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228539","228539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082324","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the contribution of the occupational health market to the economy.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228646","228646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082325","2019-03-07","Department for International Trade","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to increase the level of foreign direct investment into (a) Belfast and (b) the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228744","228744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082326","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing exemptions from the requirement to apply for the settled status scheme for non-UK EU citizens who are of pensionable age and have lived in the UK for more than five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228745","228745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082327","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what circumstances deductions are made from a claimant's universal credit payment in order to contribute to her Department's administration costs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228540","228540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082328","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing exemptions to the requirement to apply for the settled status scheme for non-UK EU citizens who are spouses of UK citizens.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228746","228746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082329","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what circumstances a universal credit claimant will be advised by a work coach to close his or her current application and make a new application; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228541","228541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082330","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he expects NHS England's response to the consultation on contracting arrangements for Integrated Care Providers to be published; if he will make it his policy that no such contracts will be entered into until (a) that response has been published and (b) the House of Commons has had an opportunity to annul or approve any regulations relating to those contracting arrangements; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228647","228647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082331","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, by what date he has planned for the first Integrated Care Providers contracts to be entered into.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228648","228648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082332","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of pension sharing orders relating to police pensions; and if he will review his policy to ensure that people in receipt of police pensions are not disadvantaged by such orders in the event that they become divorced.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228791","228791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082333","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to continue the Troubled Families programme beyond 2020.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228747","228747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082334","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools which were classified at their previous inspection as (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate were subsequently classified in an inspection in 2018 or 2019 as (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires improvement and (d) inadequate.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228748","228748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082335","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how long the guidance that drivers with autism must notify the DVLA regardless of whether the condition affects their driving was on the DVLA website before it was amended; and how many drivers contacted the DVLA to inform them of their condition during that time period.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228749","228749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082336","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the value of employment tribunal fees that have yet to be reimbursed through the fee refund scheme.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228750","228750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082337","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to contact those people eligible for the employment tribunal fee refund scheme who have not yet applied.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228751","228751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082338","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken is for the completion of claims made under the employment tribunal fee refund scheme in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228752","228752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082339","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the funding per pupil at (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (i) Brentwood and Ongar constituency and (ii) Essex in (A) 2016-17, (B) 2017-18, (C) 2018-19, (D) 2019-20 and (E) 2020-21.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228753","228753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082340","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to address the issue of taxi drivers and local service owners denying access to guide and hearing dog owners; and whether his Department will bring forward legislative proposals to make disability equality training mandatory to ensure the Equality Act 2010 is followed by taxi drivers and local service owners.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228649","228649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082341","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of applications to UK Visas and Immigration under the new super priority service were not decided within the twenty-four hour service standard; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228556","228556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082342","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects RAF Northolt to close for its runway refurbishment and other works; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228557","228557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082343","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which schemes or Departmental budgets will be affected by the reallocation of funds to the Stronger Towns Fund.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228558","228558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082344","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Turkish counterpart on the detention of Abdullah Ocalan.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228650","228650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082345","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to issue good practice guidance to support local authorities’ use of powers to deal with unauthorised encampments; what his timetable is for issuing that guidance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228542","228542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082346","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many promoters of loan schemes relating to the loan charge 2019 have been prosecuted.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228754","228754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082347","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have been convicted of offences relating to arrangements which have been promoted and marketed as tax avoidance schemes and sentenced to over 95 years custodial in relation to the promotion of loan schemes.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228755","228755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082348","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, in how many companies involved in loan charges has the (a) employer and employee been a single individual and (b) scheme promoter been the employer.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228756","228756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082349","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much Big Lottery funding (a) per capita and (b) in total was allocated to (i) Barnsley East constituency, (ii) Barnsley, (iii) South Yorkshire, (iv) Yorkshire and the Humber, (v) the South East, (vi) the South West, (vii) London and (viii) England in each of the last five years for which data are available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228757","228757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082350","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help resolve tensions in Kashmir; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228758","228758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082351","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in (a) India and (b) Pakistan on the situation in Kashmir; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228759","228759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082352","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the maintenance of the human rights of people in Kashmir.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228760","228760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082353","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals were deported by another country to the UK in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228651","228651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082354","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the public consultation on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund has been delayed.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228587","228587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082355","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to written statement HCWS1376, what steps she is taking to ensure that the benefits of a single digital platform are extended to claimants who do not have access to computers or the internet.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228588","228588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082356","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of empowering local authorities to penalise landlords of commercial properties that are left vacant for lengthy periods of time.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228589","228589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082357","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any RAF personnel on secondment to BAE Systems in Saudi Arabia have (a) maintained Royal Saudi Air Force planes engaged in military operations in Yemen and (b) trained Royal Saudi Air Force personnel engaged in military operations in Yemen.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228761","228761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082358","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff were employed in HMRC's Office of the General Counsel and Solicitor in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228762","228762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082359","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of Government intervention in the retail and hospitality sectors to minimise the number of businesses that pay above-market rents.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228590","228590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082360","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the ability of UK police to deal with child abduction cases.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228591","228591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082361","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to announce the successful applicants for Wave 13 of the Free School programme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228763","228763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082362","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether all graduates of the National College for High Speed Rail will be required to work on the High Speed 2 project for a length of time after they graduate.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228533","228533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082363","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of personal independence payment who are known to have lifelong conditions which are unlikely to improve have been awarded an ongoing award (a) in Brighton and Hove and (b) nationally.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228652","228652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082364","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make it her policy to end regular reviews of personal independence payment for claimants of working age with (a) motor neurone disease, (b) other degenerative conditions and (c) lifelong conditions which are unlikely to improve; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228653","228653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082365","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many GPs are registered in the Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228654","228654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082366","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to help halt the decline in people studying modern languages at university.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228655","228655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082367","2019-03-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many members of staff in his Department are working full-time on preparation for an adequacy assessment by the European Commission following the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228764","228764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082368","2019-03-07","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff of his Department are working on programmes relating to UK-EU law enforcement information-sharing following the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228765","228765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082369","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to reduce or eliminate hospital car parking charges for nurses, doctors and essential healthcare workers.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228543","228543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082370","2019-03-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Prime Minister has entered into correspondence with the European Council on changing the mandate of the European Commission to allow for the adoption of part two of the Withdrawal Agreement on citizens’ rights under Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228559","228559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082371","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many sustainability and transformation plans that have been produced included a workforce plan within them.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228766","228766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082372","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department closed in 2010; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228767","228767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082373","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the value has been of UK arms export licences to Turkey issued in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228768","228768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082374","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department closed in 2011; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of each of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228769","228769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082376","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department closed in 2012; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of each of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228771","228771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082377","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department closed in 2013; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of each of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228772","228772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082378","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department closed in 2014; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of each of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228773","228773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082379","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department closed in 2015; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of each of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228774","228774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082380","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received from his counterparts in (a) the European Commission and (b) EU member states on human rights abuses against the (i) Syrian and (ii) Kurdish people.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228775","228775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082381","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department closed in 2016; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of each of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228776","228776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082382","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department closed in 2017; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of each of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228777","228777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082383","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts his Department closed in 2018; on what dates those court buildings were sold; and what the value was of each of those sales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228778","228778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082384","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken to process DBS checks for potential care workers.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228779","228779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082385","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government has any plans to promote human rights in the UK and abroad through the creation of a dedicated UK Minister or commissioner for human rights.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228780","228780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082386","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average annual cost to a GP's surgery is of providing NHS GP funding formula funded primary care to someone between the ages of 20 to 49 years old.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228781","228781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082387","2019-03-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what Bills need to be passed by Parliament by 29 March 2019 in order for the UK to leave the EU.","Biography information for Mr Dominic Grieve","Mr Dominic Grieve","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228530","228530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082388","2019-03-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate the Government has made of the length of time required for the full implementation of all EU-exit related Acts of Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Dominic Grieve","Mr Dominic Grieve","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228531","228531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082389","2019-03-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many EU-exit related statutory instruments have been approved.","Biography information for Mr Dominic Grieve","Mr Dominic Grieve","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228534","228534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082390","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when a review of the operation of section 5C (Children's centres: advisory boards) Childcare Act 2006 was last undertaken; and if he will publish good practice on the operation of Advisory Boards.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228782","228782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082391","2019-03-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate the Government has made of the number of EU-exit related statutory instruments that are required to be approved by 29 March.","Biography information for Mr Dominic Grieve","Mr Dominic Grieve","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228535","228535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082392","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to ensure that children in their first 1001 days have access to Sure Start services.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228783","228783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082588","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assist the Government of the Solomon Islands in their response to the recent oil spill near Rennell Island.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229080","229080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081154","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","What steps his Department is taking to ensure that safety standards are maintained when residences are created under permitted development.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909533","909533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081155","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","What his policy is on house building on the green belt.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909534","909534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081156","2019-03-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","What plans his Department has to support local authorities in the delivery of services.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909536","909536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081701","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of Saudi Arabia's record on the maintenance of human rights in determining his policy on future trade with Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227994","227994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081702","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of NICE guidance on timelines for hyperglycaemia before the provision of additional treatment in order to reduce clinical inertia among type 1 diabetes patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227995","227995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081703","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to (a) improve insulin initiation in primary care throughout Northern Ireland and (b) reduce clinical inertia among type 1 diabetes patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227996","227996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081704","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of people with Type 1 diabetes who meet NICE-recommended blood glucose targets in order to reduce the (a) incidence and (b) cost of complications among people with that type of diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227997","227997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081705","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to (a) help people with diabetes recognise the symptoms of hypoglycaemia and (b) reduce the incidence of hypoglycaemia among those people.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227998","227998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081706","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of diabetes patients achieving time in range glucose readings of between 70mg/dl to 180mg/dl.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227999","227999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081707","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) improve service quality and (b) remove variation in that service for people with type 1 diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228000","228000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081708","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Diabetes Transformation Fund on the (a) treatment and (b) care of people with (i) type 1 and (ii) type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228001","228001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081710","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that healthcare professionals adopt the principles set out in the 2018 NHS England guidance entitled Language Matters: Language and diabetes to enable positive interactions between people living with diabetes and physicians.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228002","228002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081711","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government is on course to meet its annual immunisation targets for at-risk groups in 2019.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228003","228003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081712","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to improve vaccination coverage rates throughout the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228004","228004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081713","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the reasons why uptake rates among groups eligible for the free influenza vaccine are low.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228005","228005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081714","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase vaccination uptake rates among healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228006","228006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081715","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking increase vaccination uptake rates among carers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228007","228007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081716","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with car companies on preventing the theft of keyless cars.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228008","228008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081717","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Government of Botswana on ensuring the protection of endangered species in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228057","228057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081718","2019-03-06","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many standards checks have been conducted for (a) Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency driving examiners and (b) Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency delegated examiners in the last financial year.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228009","228009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081719","2019-03-06","Women and Equalities","2019-03-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will make it her policy to update the Government’s guidance on positive action; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228058","228058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081720","2019-03-06","Women and Equalities","2019-03-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228059","228059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081721","2019-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has undertaken any recent assessment on trends in the level of economic inactivity in socio-economic groups.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228060","228060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081722","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant of the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government of 28 January 2019, Official Report, column 465, on Leaseholders: Removal of Dangerous Materials, if he will publish the names of the 80 buildings where owners and developers have made a commitment to fund the cost of remediation, or have had a warrantee claim accepted.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228010","228010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081723","2019-03-07","Department for International Development","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether it remains her policy to allocate 0.7 per cent Gross National Income to poverty reduction programmes overseas.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228061","228061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081724","2019-03-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reverse the decline of pollinators.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228062","228062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081725","2019-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to hold a meeting with some of the youth climate strikers.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228063","228063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081726","2019-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish the draft animal sentience bill.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228064","228064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081727","2019-03-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report entitled Plastic packaging plan: Achieving zero 'waste' exports, published by Policy Connect in January 2019, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a target of net zero UK exports of recyclable plastic packaging by 2030.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228065","228065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081728","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason her Department does not pay bereavement support to widows and widowers where tacit consent to marriage with their former partner was not given but where the material circumstances of their relationship were the same as those of a married couple.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228066","228066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081729","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date his (a) Ministers and (b) officials were informed of the circumstances of the September 2017 M5 van crash in which five people died; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227962","227962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081730","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the recent conclusion of the inquest into the September 2017 M5 van crash in which five people died informed his decision to consult on banning dangerous old tyres.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227963","227963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081731","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many instances of a Serious Further Offence review of murder has resulted in the perpetrator being (a) charged and (b) convicted where the supervisory agency has been (i) the National Probation Service and (b) a Community Rehabilitation Company in each year since 2014 in England and Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228067","228067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081732","2019-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of whether universal credit claimants paid weekly, fortnightly or on a four-weekly basis for part-time work may receive a lower annual benefit than those who are paid on a last day of the month-basis for the same number of hours worked.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228068","228068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081733","2019-03-12","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason EORI numbers cannot be automatically allocated to intra-EU only traders with registered VAT numbers.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227938","227938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081734","2019-03-12","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many of the 40,000 businesses who have registered for an EORI number (a) were and (b) were not already VAT registered.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227939","227939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081735","2019-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spends annually on health and welfare services for veterans of World War Two.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228011","228011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081736","2019-03-12","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of intra-EU traders who need to register for an EORI number that (a) are and (b) are not already VAT registered.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227940","227940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081737","2019-03-12","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the £2 million allocated to helping traders to make customs declarations has been drawn down by traders upskilling their capacity to make customs declarations; how many grant funding applications have been made to that fund; and many traders have been successful in such applications.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227941","227941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081738","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the £2 million allocated to helping traders to make customs declarations has been spent on (a) administering the scheme and (b) helping traders.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227946","227946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081739","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what (a) reasons and (b) circumstances armed military personnel can be deployed on UK soil.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228069","228069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081740","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK Parliament has any role on the deployment of armed military personnel on UK soil.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228070","228070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081741","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many scam artists were arrested on Westminster Bridge in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227947","227947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081743","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many crimes involving scam artists on Westminster Bridge were reported in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227948","227948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081744","2019-03-06","Home Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many scam artists on Westminster Bridge were cautioned in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227949","227949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081745","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) civilian staff and (b) military personnel based in (i) the UK and (ii) Saudi Arabia were employed on the (A) Saudi Arabian National Guard Communications Project and (B) Ministry of Defence Saudi Armed Forces Project on 1 April 2018.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228071","228071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081746","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) expenditure was in the financial year 2017-18 and (b) budget is for 2018-19 for the (i) Saudi Arabian National Guard Communications Project and (ii) Ministry of Defence Saudi Armed Forces Project.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228072","228072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081747","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many leasehold properties were (a) built and (b) approved in (i) England and (ii) Lancashire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227950","227950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081748","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the strengthening of human rights in South Sudan.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228012","228012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081749","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on mental illness and suicide among ex-servicemen and women.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228013","228013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081750","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department collects data on the (a) number of armed forces veterans who have died by suicide each year and (b) that same information by local authority area.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228014","228014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081751","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what her Department’s priorities are for the upcoming African Union Summit in Niger; and whether representatives from the Government plan to attend.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227934","227934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081752","2019-03-07","Department for International Development","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department’s priorities are for the upcoming international conference on tackling gender-based violence in humanitarian crises in Oslo; and who will be representing the Government at that conference.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227942","227942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081753","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Zambian counterpart on (a) trophy hunting and (b) culling of hippopotamuses in that country.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228169","228169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081754","2019-03-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has a fixed-length absence limit for staff on sick leave.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228073","228073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081755","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HMRC has taken against the promoters of disguised remuneration schemes.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227951","227951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081756","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are subject to the 2019 Loan Charge.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227952","227952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081757","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are subject to the 2019 Loan Charge in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227953","227953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081758","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are subject to the 2019 Loan Charge in Haltemprice and Howden constituency.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227954","227954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081759","2019-03-06","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing mentoring services for all veterans who leave prison.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227955","227955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081760","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to ensure secure military communications hardware procurement maintains sovereign capability.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228015","228015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081761","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of nurses in England in training compared with other countries on which information is available in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228074","228074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081762","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of recruitment by the Royal Military Police.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228016","228016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081763","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress he has made on training 10,000 more healthcare students by 2020, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228075","228075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081764","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to patrol UK territorial waters, particularly the North Sea, in advance of the deployment of P-8 aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228017","228017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081765","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of (a) the annual in service cost of the P-8 patrol aircraft and (b) the number of years those aircraft can be expected to remain in service.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228018","228018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081766","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress the Government has made towards meeting its target of recruiting 5,000 more GPs by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228076","228076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081767","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) Chief Information Officers and (b) Chief Clinical Information Officers there have been in the NHS Digital Academy in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228077","228077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081768","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the level of funding for wellbeing services for the NHS workforce.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228078","228078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081769","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the (a) costs and (b) expenses attributed to the HS2 Design Panel since the Panel's formation.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227932","227932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081770","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to secure the supply of (a) methotrexate and (b) hydroxychloroquine in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228079","228079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081771","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any MOD contractor has loaded weapons on to aircraft since March 2015 in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228080","228080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081772","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of NHS England’s £130 million funding for the Linear Accelerator programme was spent in (a) 2016-17 (b) 2017-18  (c) 2018-19; what funding his Department plans to allocate to that programme in (i) 2019-20 and (ii) 2020 - 21; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228019","228019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081773","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with his Emirati counterpart the case of Alia Abdel Nour.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228081","228081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081774","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of cancer patients should have received radiotherapy as part of their cancer treatment in 2018.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228020","228020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081775","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to prevent Saudi Arabia from employing child soldiers in Yemen.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228082","228082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081776","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will issue a formal statement in support of the uprising against Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228083","228083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081777","2019-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has plans to extend (a) maternity and (b) paternity leave and pay for parents of (i) very sick and (ii) premature children.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228084","228084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081778","2019-03-07","Department for Transport","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the DVLA  plans to update its guidance for drivers with diabetes who take insulin on using Flash GM and Continuous Glucose Monitoring technologies to monitor their blood glucose levels.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228085","228085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081779","2019-03-07","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many public sector workers were directly affected by the recent HMRC exercise to reconcile pensions which resulted in overpayments due to changes in the guaranteed minimum pension.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228086","228086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081780","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to bring forward regulations on who is permitted to administer (a) botox injections and (b) dermal fillers.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228087","228087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081781","2019-03-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of personal independence payment were sent home from their assessment appointments at Independence Assessment Services in 2018 due to staffing issues.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228088","228088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081782","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what funding his Department allocates to organisation that provide advice to people that self-build on planning applications.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228021","228021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081783","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that social housing in equipped with adequate (a) heating and (b) insulation.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228022","228022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081784","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to repair play facilities in parks.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228023","228023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081785","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many Help to Buy equity loans were agreed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228024","228024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081786","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what support his Department provides to rehouse victims of domestic abuse.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228025","228025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081787","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle loneliness.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228026","228026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081788","2019-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to combat bulimia among young people.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228027","228027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081789","2019-03-11","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the provision in the Northern Ireland (Sentences) Act 1998 capping time spent in prison for Troubles-related offences at two years applies to members of the (a) armed forces, (b) police and (c) security services and (b) paramilitaries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227933","227933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081790","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to bring the performance of screening programmes in London in line with the rest of England and Wales.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228089","228089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081791","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to ensure that databases and IT systems for health screenings are fit for service.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228090","228090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081792","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of care leavers aged 19-21 years old had contact with a personal adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228091","228091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081793","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers aged 19-21 years there are by local authority area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228092","228092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081794","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers aged 19-21 years there are who have had contact with a personal adviser in the last 12 months by local authority area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228093","228093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081795","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of care leavers aged 19-21 years have each local authority been in contact with in the year ending 31 March 2018.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228094","228094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081796","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers there are aged 19-21 years in the Dorset County Council area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228095","228095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081797","2019-03-06","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers there are aged 19-21 years in the Poole Council area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228096","228096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081798","2019-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to increase the number of labour market inspectors in line with the International Labour Organisation benchmark of one for every 10,000 workers.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228097","228097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081799","2019-03-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to increase prosecution and conviction rates for non-payment of the minimum wage.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228098","228098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081800","2019-03-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) average waiting time and (b) longest wait between the Employment Tribunal receiving an employment tribunal application and the date of the first hearing has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227964","227964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081801","2019-03-06","Treasury","2019-03-04","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of pausing the introduction of the loan charge.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228099","228099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081802","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of (a) intermediate care beds and (b) long-term nursing home beds in North Staffordshire hospitals.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227965","227965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081803","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference the Northern Staffordshire Community Hospitals Consultation, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the quality of care in local nursing homes is maintained.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227966","227966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081804","2019-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the GIS data used to construct the boundaries of the (a) 18 Low Flying Areas and (b) boundaries for the three Tactical Training Areas in the UK.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228100","228100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081805","2019-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) number and (b) value of compensation payments made in the last five years to people living below Tactical Training Areas was.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228101","228101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081806","2019-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) number and (b) value of compensation payments made in the last five years to people living below the Tactical Training Area in central Wales was.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228102","228102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081807","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Northern Staffordshire community hospitals consultation, whether any existing care homes in Northern Staffordshire could be used to accommodate intermediate care beds.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227967","227967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081808","2019-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the reasons were for the compensation payments made in the last five years to people living below the Tactical Training Area in central Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228103","228103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081809","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Stronger Towns Fund will be administered as part of the forthcoming UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228028","228028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081810","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the methodology used was to calculate English regional shares of Stronger Towns Funds.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228029","228029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081811","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much money from the Stronger Towns Fund will be allocated to Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228030","228030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081812","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of funding from the Stronger Towns Fund will be allocated to Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228031","228031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081813","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Barnett Formula be applied to calculate the share of the Stronger Towns Funding to be allocated to Wales, Scotland and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228032","228032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081814","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the allocation of funding from the Stronger Towns Fund to towns in Wales will be administered by the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228033","228033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081815","2019-03-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients were discharged from University Hospitals of North Midlands into (a) community hospital and (b) care home beds in each week from 2013 to 2018.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227968","227968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081816","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department has provided to the community of Marikana following the loss of life at the Lonmin mine in August 2012.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228034","228034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081817","2019-03-07","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) British military liaison officers and (b) advisers are (i) currently embedded and (ii) have been embedded in organisations in Saudi Arabia in each year since 2015; with which organisations they have been embedded; and how many, at what rank and role, have worked in Saudi Air Operations Centres.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228104","228104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081818","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to seek the release of the miners imprisoned as a result of the strike at Lonmin’s mine in Marikana.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228035","228035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081819","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to take steps to ensure that the British company Lonmin is held accountable for the loss of life at its mine in Marikana in August 2012.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228036","228036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081820","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the comparative value of sport to British soft power and international influence compared to other soft power assets.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228037","228037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081821","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on (a) sports organisations' and (b) National Governing Bodies’ international work and events in the next year.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228038","228038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081822","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what studies his Department has commissioned or conducted on the worldwide reach of British soft power assets.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228039","228039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081823","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what statistics his Department uses to measure the value of British soft power assets.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228040","228040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081824","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has taken steps to ensure that overseas trade missions contain representation from sporting National Governing Bodies or sport more widely.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228041","228041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081825","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the ability of sporting events to underpin his work in furthering the UK’s trading relationships.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228042","228042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081826","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the proportion of foreign direct investment into the UK which is accounted for by investment in sports.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228043","228043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081827","2019-03-06","Department for International Trade","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has taken steps to ensure that trade missions associate with and run alongside UK sporting events.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228044","228044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081828","2019-03-06","Department for International Development","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effect of sporting charities and development work on the UK's international reputation.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228045","228045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081829","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much the Government plans to allocate from its Stronger Towns Fund to Barnsley.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228105","228105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081830","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much the Government plans to allocate from its Stronger Towns Fund to towns in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228106","228106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081831","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what form the Government's needs-based formula to determine the allocation of the Stronger Towns Fund will take.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228107","228107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081832","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Stronger Towns Fund, when the bidding process to determine allocation of the £600 million of Government funding through a bidding process to communities in any part of the country will commence; and who will be eligible to bid for that funding.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228108","228108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081833","2019-03-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Stronger Towns Fund, what criteria his Department plans to use when determining the allocation of the £600 million of Government funding through a bidding process to communities in any part of the country.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228109","228109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081834","2019-03-07","Department for International Development","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to reports in the Indian Ocean Newsletter on 22 February 2019, that the UK Government is seeking to expand the role of British companies providing education services in Uganda, what plans her Department has to provide new funding to UK companies to deliver education services in Uganda; and which organisations and individuals the Minister of State for Africa has met with since January 2019 on this issue.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228110","228110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081835","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for the Government to publish a response to the consultation on Planning reform: supporting the high street and increasing the delivery of new homes, with particular respect to the sections relating to the expansion of permitted development rights.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228111","228111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081836","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the Government response to the consultation entitled Planning reform: supporting the high street and increasing the delivery of new homes.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228112","228112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081837","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the financial effect on local authorities of providing services to support new development taken forward under the office to residential permitted development rights process.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228113","228113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081838","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on local authority finances of providing services to support residential development on commercial sites under permitted development.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228114","228114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081839","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of effect on local authority finances of conversion of office space to residential units under permitted development.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228115","228115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081840","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of former office blocks that have been converted to residential units under permitted development rights for use as temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228116","228116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081841","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential cost to the public purse of housing homeless individuals and families in former office blocks converted to residential units through permitted development rights.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228117","228117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081842","2019-03-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) steps his Department has taken, (b) guidance his Department has issued and (c) discussions his Department has had in the last 12 months on the rules and regulations surrounding the award of honours by British overseas territories.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227969","227969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081843","2019-03-06","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what regulations there are to enforce rules on the wearing of non-British approved orders with military uniform when representing Her Majesty the Queen and the Government on official business; and what sanctions exist when those rules and regulations are violated.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227970","227970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081844","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Administration on the recent summit between the leaders of the US and North Korea in Vietnam.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228046","228046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081845","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Saudi Arabian counterparts on the use of Sudanese child soldiers within the Yemeni civil war during his recent visit to the Gulf.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228118","228118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081846","2019-03-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Departments holds on the number of child soldiers of Sudanese origin who have been involved in the Yemeni civil war.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228119","228119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081847","2019-03-07","Department for Education","2019-03-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2019 to Question 203906 on Educational Psychology: Staff, when the results of the evaluation of the Educational Psychology Workforce in England his Department commissioned will be published.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228120","228120"
