"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731261","2017-06-26","Women and Equalities","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland and (b) Members of Northern Ireland Executive on the protection and promotion of LGBT rights in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136","136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731262","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to require local councils to rehouse social tenants displaced due to disaster within their local area.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132","132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731263","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether tackling climate change was discussed at recent meetings with the DUP leadership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137","137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731264","2017-06-26","Women and Equalities","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the Government's policy is on protecting the right of (a) Christians and (b) people of other religious beliefs to wear or carry religious symbols in public.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 168","168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731265","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to encourage sixth form and technical colleges to contact electoral offices to provide registration days and ID provision before any future elections.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 169","169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731266","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with Ruth Davidson MSP on (a) promoting LGBT rights across all countries within the UK and (b) the priorities for the Government's deal with the DUP.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 141","141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731267","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many workless households there are in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 182","182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731268","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of (a) the cost to the public purse of administering the 2017 General Election and (b) the amount that accrued to the public purse as a result of candidates losing their deposits at that election.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 183","183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731269","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support people with arthritis and musculoskeletal conditions to return to and to stay in work.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 184","184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731270","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on the UK's participation in Creative Europe.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211","211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731271","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to refund fast track payments made by applicants for partner visas where the processing of those applications has been suspended as a result of the legal challenge to the Government's minimum income requirement.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216","216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731272","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) women and (b) men working in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency earn less than £10 per hour.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7","7"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731273","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are registered as self-employed in (a) Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8","8"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731274","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of household debt in (a) Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 9","9"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731275","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he plans to publish his Department's Annual Report and Accounts for 2016-17.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 31","31"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731276","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 64393, when he plans to publish the transparency data on contracts over £10,000.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 32","32"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731277","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 28 March 2017 to Answer 69549, what strategic and tactical changes have been made to coalition operations against Daesh since the (a) Ministerial Plenary for the Global Coalition Working to Defeat ISIS on 22 March 2017 and (b) inauguration of President Trump.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 33","33"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731278","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will respond to the recommendations contained within the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Hunger report, Hungry Holidays, published in April 2017.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 37","37"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731279","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to introduce legislation on property ownership and public contracting by overseas companies and legal entities.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 38","38"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731280","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the outcome of the Government's consultation on property ownership and public contracting by overseas companies and legal entities.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 39","39"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731281","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish the Gibb report into the Southern Rail franchise.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 46","46"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731282","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to improve corporate and tax transparency in the Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 47","47"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731283","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) his Department or (b) Network Rail have carried out a risk assessment on the ability to evacuate the concourse at London Victoria Station platforms 15 to 19 at peak time in an emergency.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 44","44"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731284","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reasons are for the time taken to publish the Gibb report into the Southern Rail franchise.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 45","45"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731285","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are registered to work through umbrella companies.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 58","58"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731286","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance and (c) universal credit were processed within five days during the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 59","59"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731287","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of nurses from the EU working in the NHS.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 61","61"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731288","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency in employment who are aged between (a) 50 to 59, (b) 60 to 69 and (c) over 70 years old.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 68","68"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731289","2017-06-26","Department for International Development","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to increase funding to support grassroots groups working to end violence against women and girls across the world.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 62","62"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731290","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in employment which primarily requires working at night in (a) Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 69","69"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731291","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people with learning difficulties and seeking work were unemployed in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 70","70"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731292","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that more surplus food is redistributed by retailers to charities supporting those experiencing hunger and food poverty.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 63","63"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731293","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many non-UK EU nationals are resident in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 71","71"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731294","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to establish a regulatory body for fuel pricing.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 64","64"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731295","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of ending the triple lock on pensions on pensioner poverty.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 65","65"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731296","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to recruit a specialist, highly-trained early years workforce.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 75","75"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731297","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the effect of the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014 on the work of charities.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 76","76"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731298","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many organisations have been fined for failing to comply with regulations on third party campaigning set out in the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 77","77"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731299","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to decide on the extension of the yellow card early warning system for benefit sanctions across the UK","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 85","85"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731300","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the potential effect on the level of UK GDP of the UK leaving the EU prior to the conclusion of any deal with the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 153","153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731301","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate his Department has made of the number of officials it has yet to recruit which it requires for the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 154","154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731302","2017-06-26","Department for International Trade","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the timetable is for trade negotiations formally to commence with non-EU countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 155","155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731303","2017-06-26","Department for International Trade","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the number of trade agreements it will plan to commence with non-EU countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 156","156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731304","2017-06-26","Department for International Trade","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the timetable is for concluding trade negotiations with non-EU countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 157","157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731305","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of his senior negotiating team are women.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 160","160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731306","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in Iran on the decision of the Supreme Court in Iran not to free British-Iranian Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe; what steps he has taken to make sure Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe can see her lawyer; and what steps plans to take to ensure she is free.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 161","161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731307","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect of withdrawing from the single market on the land border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 162","162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731308","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure continued UK participation in EU research programmes into musculoskeletal conditions after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185","185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731309","2017-06-26","Prime Minister","2017-06-21","To ask the Prime Minister, on how many occasions the EU Exit and Trade Cabinet Committee has met; and who chaired each such meeting.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186","186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731310","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the report by Chris Gibb on the Southern rail franchise and the Government's response to that report.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217","217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731311","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the amount of revenue lost to the Exchequer as a result of professional football players and managers concealing income from image rights; and what steps he is taking to prevent that practice.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187","187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731312","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library a copy of her Department's report on foreign funding of extremism and radicalisation in the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 219","219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731313","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he had made of the effect of the growth of umbrella companies on tax revenues.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188","188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731314","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to review the use of umbrella companies by employers and employment agencies.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189","189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731315","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many interventions under section 437(1) of the Education Act 1996, for home schooling, have been made by local authorities in the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 213","213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731316","2017-06-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will review the rules governing permitted development for change of use from commercial and industrial to residential; and what estimate he has made of changes in use by borough in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 242","242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731317","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with officials of the Northern Ireland Executive and other key stakeholders in Northern Ireland on the implications of the UK leaving the EU for agri-food (a) producers and (b) labelling sectors.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170","170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731318","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the National and Ulster Farmers Unions and other key stakeholders are involved in discussions on negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 171","171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731319","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to ensure that subsidy payments to farmers are maintained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 172","172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731320","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timetable is for the EU to agree a ban on microbeads.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 173","173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731321","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department gives to wildlife and conservation bodies to help purchase land for conservation and shooting purposes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 174","174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731322","2017-06-26","Prime Minister","2017-06-21","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions she has had with the former Taoiseach Enda Kenny on the land border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland as the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142","142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731323","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 71377, on Southern: standards, on what date the Government plans to publish the report by Chris Gibb on performance of the Southern rail franchise; for what reasons the Government did not publish that report before the General Election; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 194","194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731324","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training the Government is providing for teachers on the new GCSE grades system.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 176","176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731325","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much Government investment has been made in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 177","177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731326","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether work on the Access for All lift provision at Teddington Station will be completed by the end of 2017-18.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 307","307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731327","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what timetable the Government has for completion of Crossrail 2.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 308","308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731328","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the planned 20 per cent increase in planning fees will be implemented.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 309","309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731329","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in Creative Europe when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 237","237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731330","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to review the relationship between the Education and Skills Funding Agency and local education authorities regarding the provision of sites for new schools; and if she will make a statement on the effectiveness of current arrangements for such provision.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 310","310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731331","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Answer of 30 March 2017 to Question 69306, for what reason he believes the information requested would undermine the ability to negotiate the best possible deal for Britain.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 239","239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731332","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the increase in the number of people diagnosed with arthritis and other musculoskeletal disorders in relation to (a) funding and (b) public health strategy.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254","254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731333","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average salary for (a) men, (b) women, (c) non-UK EU nationals in the Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 255","255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731334","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to Together For Syria's Election 2017 manifesto, what steps he plans to take to work with the international community to protect civilians in Syria.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 256","256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731335","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Government's policy is on changing the law on abortion in (a) England and Wales and (b) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281","281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731336","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many interventions have been made by social services relating to home schooling in the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 282","282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731337","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Pre-Exposure Prophylaxis impact trial will begin; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 283","283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731338","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce smoking amongst pregnant women.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 284","284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731339","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the timescales on the new nutrient profile model will be published; and for what reasons the publications of those timescales has been delayed.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 285","285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731340","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will take steps to ensure agricultural subsidies for farmers and landowners are used to enhance access to places the public can walk in.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 265","265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731341","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to bring Scottish Limited Partnerships within the scope of the register of persons of significant control.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 257","257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731342","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will make it a requirement that all schools are fitted with sprinkler systems for fire safety; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 258","258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731343","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent in prescribing paracetamol in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 325","325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731344","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow GP surgeries to directly provide patients with paracetamol, and other low cost readily available drugs, rather than issuing such medication via a prescription.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 326","326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731345","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse is for a prescription of paracetamol.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 327","327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731346","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on benefits for disabled people over the course of this Parliament.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 356","356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731347","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will enter into negotiations with the Mineworkers Pension Scheme Trustees to discuss the current surplus sharing arrangements.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 357","357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731348","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to (a) improve mental health provision and (b) support the needs of children and young people.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 328","328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731349","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to lower the voting age to 16.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 358","358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731350","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of potential changes to NHS expenditure resulting from the new capped expenditure process arising from (a) limiting the number of operations carried out by non-NHS providers, (b) drawing out waiting times for planned care, (c) stopping NHS funding for some treatments, (d) closing wards and theatres and reducing staffing, (e) closing or downgrading services, including emergency or maternity units, (f) selling estate and other property-related transactions and (g) stopping prescriptions for some items.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 449","449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731351","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visas to work in the UK have been issued for people taking up nursing positions in the NHS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 329","329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731352","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many foreign nationals are working in the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 330","330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731353","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from Cabinet colleagues about reintroducing the student nursing bursary.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 331","331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731354","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish minutes of the meetings between Ministers and the Democratic Unionist Party on supporting the Queen's Speech 2017.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 359","359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731355","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will establish an independent body to set rules for and formalise general election leaders debates.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 360","360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731356","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when final plans for savings in each local area affected by the new capped expenditure process in the NHS will be agreed; who has final responsibility for agreeing those plans; and when and by whom those final plans will be made public.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 450","450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731357","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of staff shortages in the NHS by number and position.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 332","332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731358","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will repeal the Fixed-terms Parliaments Act 2011.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 361","361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731359","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much per person the NHS has spent on treating people with mental health conditions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 334","334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731360","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals on the reform of the House of Lords to make that House accountable to the electorate.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 362","362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731361","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will consider alternative voting systems for general elections and introduce a proportional system.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 363","363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731362","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is between a patient being diagnosed with a mental health issue and receiving access to counselling and talking therapies.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 333","333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731363","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will lift the one per cent pay cap.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 364","364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731364","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many days have been lost in the NHS due to staff absence and sickness in  each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 335","335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731365","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make available funding for the renewal and redevelopment of high streets.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 365","365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731366","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase patrols and speeding enforcement at accident blackspots on the A19.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 336","336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731367","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to give local authorities the power to (a) take over or (b) mandate owners to develop, sell or clear blight and derelict sites suitable for commercial or residential development.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 366","366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731368","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many dedicated officers there are in each police force that specialise in fraud.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 337","337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731369","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to provide police forces with additional resources when handling complex fraud cases.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 338","338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731370","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will grant local authorities the power to insist that landlords or home owners maintain their properties to an acceptable standard where that condition is having a negative impact upon the local community.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 367","367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731371","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce legislative proposals to abolish or reduce the fees local authorities charge to mediate high-hedge disputes under the Anti-social Behaviour Act 2003 and the High Hedges Regulations 2005.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 368","368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731372","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what criteria were used to select the location of letting agents' fees ban workshops.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 369","369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731373","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit the use of polystyrene ceiling tiles in rented accommodation.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 370","370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731374","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what fire risk assessments have been carried out on the use of polystyrene ceiling tiles; and whether this product should be removed from the market.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 371","371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731375","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with representatives of community broadband schemes in England about the roll-out of superfast broadband services.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 412","412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731376","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to publish its response to the consultation that closed on 1 February 2017 on driving offences and penalties relating to causing death or serious injury.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 413","413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731377","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with the Government of Pakistan on the death sentence for blasphemy placed on Taimoor Raza.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 414","414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731378","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will allocate resources to ensure that van hire firms and the police are able to share intelligence and information in order to prevent terrorist attacks using hired vans as weapons.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 415","415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731379","2017-06-26","Northern Ireland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will set out a timetable to introduce legislation ending the practice allowing anonymity for donations to political parties operating in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 1","1"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731380","2017-06-26","Northern Ireland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions the Government has had with the Government of the Republic of Ireland on the (a) seizure of substantial amounts of Semtex in Dublin on 3 June 2017, (b) capacity of dissident republican groups to obtaining Semtex and (c) response of An Garda Síochiná to those incidents.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2","2"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731381","2017-06-26","Northern Ireland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the Government's policy is on the jurisdictional status of (a) Lough Foyle and (b) Carlingford Lough; and what recent discussions have been held with the Government of the Republic of Ireland on those disputed jurisdictions.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3","3"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731382","2017-06-26","Northern Ireland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information he has received on instances of voter fraud in the 2017 General Election; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4","4"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731383","2017-06-26","Northern Ireland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will initiate consultation on aligning libel law in Northern Ireland with that in England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 5","5"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731384","2017-06-26","Leader of the House","2017-06-21","To ask the Leader of the House, if she will introduce proposals to rescind standing orders relating to English votes for English laws; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6","6"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731385","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what evidence a claimant will have to provide to secure an exemption in relation to support for a child conceived without your consent.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 10","10"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731386","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which (a) public and (b) other agencies under which circumstances will have access to information recorded in relation to support for a child conceived without your consent.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 11","11"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731387","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on the number of terminations in families which already have at least two children of the introduction of Support for a child conceived without your consent.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 21","21"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731388","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the appeals process is for applications for Support for a child conceived without your consent which have been declined by his Department.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 22","22"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731389","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what budget has been allocated from the public purse for training third party professional referrers in relation to the process for application for Support for a child conceived without your consent.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 23","23"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731390","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether data recorded on the form NCC1, Support for a child conceived without your consent, will be made available to defence solicitors acting in rape, sexual assault and domestic abuse cases.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 12","12"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731391","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training his Department has provided to third party professionals in relation to assisting people with applications for Support for a child conceived without your consent.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 24","24"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731392","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many third party professionals in Scotland have been approved to complete the form NCC1, Support for a child conceived without your consent.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 13","13"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731393","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training his Department has provided to third party professionals in respect of disclosures made in connection with applications for Support for a child conceived without your consent.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 25","25"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731394","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will carry out an equality impact assessment in relation to the restriction of child tax credits to the first two children in a family.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 26","26"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731395","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the non-consensual sex exemption in relation to child tax credits on the safety of women and children in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 14","14"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731396","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department plans to record information that a child has been conceived as a result of rape for the purposes of Support for a child conceived without your consent.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 15","15"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731397","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's policy is on the disposal of data relating to Support for a child conceived without your consent when the claimant is no longer in receipt of child tax credits.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 16","16"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731398","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department plans to assess whether a claimant of Support for a child conceived without your consent is living with the person by whom the child was conceived.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 17","17"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731399","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training has been given to his Department's staff for the assessment of applications for Support for a child conceived without your consent.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 18","18"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731400","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the differential effect of the non-consensual sex exemption on women and men.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 19","19"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731401","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how child tax credits awarded under the non-consensual conception exemption will be (a) classified and (b) coded in official documents.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 27","27"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731402","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of pregnancies that will occur as a result of rape in families that already have at least two children in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 20","20"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731403","2017-06-26","Northern Ireland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the duty to inform the police of a relevant offence contained in the provisions of NCC1, support for a child conceived without consent, on the safety of women and children in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 28","28"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731404","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 64994, on procurement, what estimate he has made of the amount spent on procurement management by his Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 36","36"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731405","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the provisions relating to applications for Support for a child conceived without your consent, what his Department's policy is on the implications for third party professionals who verify that a claimant qualifies for that support in the event that the claimant's case is subsequently assessed as weak.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 29","29"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731406","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse has been of holding the 2017 General Election.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 30","30"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731407","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much revenue was generated from visa applications that were denied in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 40","40"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731408","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much revenue was generated by the premium visa service in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 41","41"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731409","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many survivors of the Grenfell Tower fire have reported to Kensington and Chelsea Council as homeless; and how many of those people are now in temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 66","66"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731410","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his predecessor's letter of 20 May 2013 to the Coroner investigating the Lakanal House fire incident, what steps were taken to simplify the language in Approved Document B.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 67","67"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731411","2017-06-26","Scotland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what Government investment and projects supporting regeneration there are in Barrhead, East Renfrewshire.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 73","73"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731412","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of UK businesses operating in Qatar; and what assessment he has made of the effect on such businesses of sanctions imposed by other countries on Qatar since 5 June 2017.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 394","394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731413","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts in (a) Saudi Arabia, (b) UAE, (c) Bahrain, (d) Egypt and (e) Yemen on the imposition of sanctions by those countries on Qatar since 5 June 2017; what steps he is taking to facilitate a negotiated solution to the dispute between those countries; and what assessment he has made of the prospects for restoration of full diplomatic ties between those countries.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 395","395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731414","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the terms of the Riyadh Agreement reached between members of the Gulf Cooperation Council in November 2014; and what assessment he has made of compliance by the Government of Qatar with the terms of that agreement (a) before and (b) after 5 June 2017.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 396","396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731415","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of UK nationals living in Qatar; and what assessment he has made of the effect on such UK nationals of sanctions imposed by other countries on Qatar since 5 June 2017.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 397","397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731416","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many requests for consular assistance his Department has received from UK nationals in Qatar since 5 June 2017; and what support his Department is providing in response to such requests.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 398","398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731417","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of illegal cigarettes sold in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 513","513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731418","2017-06-26","Wales Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2017 to Question 70760, what (a) discussions and (b) other communications his Department has had with (i) the Ministry of Defence (MOD) and (ii) the Welsh Assembly Government on the relocation of MOD St Athan 4 School of Technical Training since February 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 399","399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731419","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many incidents of water pollution through the excess use of fertilisers were recorded in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 514","514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731420","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 70761, what estimate his Department has made of the costs of (a) staff relocation, (b) movement of equipment and (c) upgrading of buildings associated with transferring No. 4 School of Technical Training to Cosford; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 400","400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731421","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many successful prosecutions there have been for the polluting of watercourses in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 515","515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731422","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the commitment in the Queen's Speech 2017 to introduce an independent public advocate to act for bereaved families after a public disaster, whether there will be a time limit on the advocate taking up cases; whether the advocate will be able to initiate inquiries on behalf of bereaved families; whether the advocate will be able to compel witnesses in an inquiry; and whether the advocate will be able to make formal recommendations to the Government to support people affected by such disasters.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 401","401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731423","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of sentence for a conviction for the illegal sale of tobacco was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 516","516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731424","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many farmers in England and Wales have received their full 2016 CAP Pillar 1 payments; and how many such farmers are yet to receive their full balance.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 403","403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731425","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of reported pollution incidents of watercourses were officially investigated in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 524","524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731426","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what strategy his Department has to support a growth pipeline to help small businesses in Scotland expand.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 404","404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731427","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made on roll-out of Universal Credit in Scotland to date; and what lessons have been learned from that process.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 405","405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731428","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66737, what progress has been made on plans to give single parents with children born through surrogacy the same rights as couples.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 510","510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731429","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with representatives of mobile telephone operators on 3G and 4G coverage in rural areas in Scotland.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 406","406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731430","2017-06-26","Attorney General","2017-06-21","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions for the sale of illegal tobacco have taken place in each police authority area in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 511","511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731431","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plan and timetable his Department has for the sale of the Forthside Barracks site.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 407","407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731432","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps are being taken to strengthen sentences for people convicted of the sale of illegal tobacco.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 512","512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731433","2017-06-26","Scotland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions his Department has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding for the Stirling and Clackmannanshire City Deal.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 408","408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731434","2017-06-26","Scotland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of local authorities on the Stirling and Clackmannanshire City Deal.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 410","410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731435","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Scottish Government on his Department's Industrial Strategy green paper.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 411","411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731436","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of sanctions imposed by other countries on Qatar since 5 June 2017 on UK imports of liquefied natural gas from Qatar.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 261","261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731437","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on Qatar's food imports of the closure of the Abu Samra border between that country and Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 262","262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731438","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to relocate regional assets held in national galleries and libraries to their areas of origin to promote regional tourism.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 339","339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731439","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding the Government provides to public bodies to promote and develop tourism to the Durham Heritage coast.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 340","340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731440","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if the Government will make funding available for the construction and maintenance of a swimming pool and other leisure facilities in Easington constituency to promote health and wellbeing.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 341","341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731441","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make representations to the Treasury to (a) lift the public pay sector cap and (b) allow the Armed Forces Pay Review Body to make recommendations on pay rises without that pay gap restriction.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 342","342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731442","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make it a specific offence to discriminate against and abuse members of the armed forces.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 343","343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731443","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will create a veterans register to help identify and support the needs of veterans (a) generally and (b) during the transition back into civilian life.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 344","344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731444","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's priorities are for the 35th session of the UN Human Rights Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 297","297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731445","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on reform of the UN Human Rights Council; what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on potential reforms at the 35th session of the UN Human Rights Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 298","298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731446","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent on supporting veterans injured on active service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 345","345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731447","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to publish a draft International Sanctions Bill.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 301","301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731448","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support he plans to make available to homeless veterans in the next five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 346","346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731449","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the suicide rate of veterans; and what mental health support is available to ex-service personnel after they leave the armed forces.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 347","347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731450","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the Government's policy is on supporting children from low income families to meet their developmental milestones prior to starting primary school.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 348","348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731451","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make additional funding available in areas of high deprivation to improve early years provision so that children from low income families do not fall behind their peers prior to starting primary education.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 349","349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731452","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have gone into care in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 350","350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731453","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been provided in each of the last five years to fund children's care services.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 351","351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731454","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the number of people willing to foster children in care.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 352","352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731455","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's policy is on fox hunting.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 353","353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731456","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure the Hunting Act 2004 is fully enforced.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 354","354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731457","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward proposals to strengthen penalties for those in breach of the Hunting Act 2004.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 355","355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731458","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce funding for the Peninsular Rail Task Force's immediate tasks from November 2016.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 248","248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731459","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much will be spent on railway upgrade work in the South West in (a) Control Period 5 and (b) Control Period 6.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 249","249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731460","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to dispose of (a) Stonehouse Barracks and (b) the Royal Citadel in Plymouth.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 202","202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731461","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes in the level of funding for police forces on those forces' ability to counter terrorism.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 424","424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731462","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to review the indicative allocation of the revenue support grant for 2018-19 and 2019-20.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 425","425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731463","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to improve nursery care to ensure that all children are ready for school age at five.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 525","525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731464","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the National Shipbuilding Strategy has been written; and when his Department plans to publish that strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 435","435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731465","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to publish new strategic equality objectives.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 438","438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731466","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the reduction in SSN submarines from seven to six will have on the Navy's capabilities.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 439","439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731467","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reducing the number of Sentinel aircraft on the RAF's ISTAR capabilities.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 440","440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731468","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions in each year since 2009-10 local building control authorities used their powers under section (a) 35, (b) 36, (c) 36 (6), (d) 77 and (e) 78 of the Building Act 1984 to alter, or cease building works because of concerns about fire safety.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 383","383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731469","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when and by whom the decision was taken to introduce the new capped expenditure process in the NHS; and how that decision was communicated to (a) NHS provider bodies and (b) patients and the public.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 446","446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731470","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance has been issued by (a) his Department, (b) NHS England and (c) NHS Improvement on the new capped expenditure process in the NHS; and if he will publish that guidance.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 447","447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731471","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which local health economies will be subject to the NHS capped expenditure process; and how the decision was reached as to which local health economies will be included in that process.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 448","448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731472","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who in his Department has lead responsibility for the new capped expenditure process in the NHS.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 385","385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731473","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to protect and promote patient's rights under the NHS constitution in those areas affected by the new NHS capped expenditure process.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 386","386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731474","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing a requirement that air rifles should be kept in a locked cabinet; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 74","74"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731475","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish all assessments carried out into the costs of retrofitting sprinklers in high-rise, multi-occupied residential buildings since 2013.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 78","78"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731476","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many inspection and enforcement staff have been employed to audit premises under the Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005 in each Fire Safety Authority in England in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 79","79"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731477","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether Reynobond PE aluminium panels are banned for use as cladding on high-rise residential tower blocks in the UK.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 80","80"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731478","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to support the growth of the co-operative and social enterprise sector.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116","116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731479","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on measures aimed at supporting the growth of the co-operative sector.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117","117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731480","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to support community-owned renewable energy.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 118","118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731481","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the first Royal Navy submarine to have been fully recycled under the Submarine Dismantling Project.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 119","119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731482","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects to decide on base porting arrangements between Devonport and Portsmouth for the new (a) Type 26 and (b) Type 31 frigates.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120","120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731483","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 27 April 2017 to Question 71682, what plans the Government has to review its policy on insurance premiums.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 166","166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731484","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to trigger the UK's exit from the London Convention.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146","146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731485","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many survivors of the Grenfell Tower fire who have been recorded as made statutory homeless have been re-housed by the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea Council (a) in London boroughs neighbouring Kensington and Chelsea, (b) in London boroughs not neighbouring Kensington and Chelsea and (c) outside London.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 148","148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731486","2017-06-26","Prime Minister","2017-06-21","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to her statement of 17 June 2017 on the Grenfell Tower disaster, how many local authorities have been approached about enforcement of fire orders in high-rise buildings; how many such buildings have been found to be non-compliant with orders; and on what date she expects to have completed checks with all local authorities.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 138","138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731487","2017-06-26","Prime Minister","2017-06-21","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to her statement of 17 June 2017 on the Grenfell Tower disaster, how many fire safety reviews are to be conducted into housing association and local authority high-rise buildings similar to Grenfell Tower; and on what date all such reviews are expected to conclude.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 139","139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731488","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions each fire safety authority brought prosecutions against persons under the Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005 in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 178","178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731489","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the benefits of exempting registered community benefit societies from (a) corporation tax and (b) business and non-domestic rates.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 179","179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731490","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent on the A38 in Devon in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180","180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731491","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) the co-operative sector and (b) representatives from employee-owned businesses on increasing national productivity by incentivising and encouraging employees.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181","181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731492","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US on that country's membership of the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 215","215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731493","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the planned date is for the Hinkley Point C reactor to start transmitting electricity to the National Grid; and whether the proposed contract for that reactor includes punitive measures for delay beyond that date.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 221","221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731494","2017-06-26","Department for International Trade","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to increase trade between Scotland and Israel; and what potential opportunities there will be for that trading relationship after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 175","175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731495","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding has been allocated to the A38 in Devon in (a) 2018, (b) 2019, (c) 2020, (d) 2021 and (e) 2022.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 195","195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731496","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will create a shared Prosperity Fund to replace EU economic aid.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 238","238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731497","2017-06-26","Wales Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2017 to Question 70837, what plans are in place for officials or Ministers in his Department to visit the 4 School of Technical Training at MOD St Athan in 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 274","274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731498","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) cautions, (b) Alteration Notices, (c) Enforcement Notices and (d) Prohibition Notices under Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005 were issued by each Fire Safety Authority in England in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 240","240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731499","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 70832, whether he has carried out an impact assessment of effect of relocation on (a) 614 RAF Auxiliary Squadron, (b) University of Wales Air Squadron, (c) 2300 Air Cadets Squadron, (d) Regional Rehabilitation Unit for Wales and the Midlands and (e) the Band of the Prince of Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 275","275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731500","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many inspections of premises under the Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005 were carried out by each Fire Safety Authority in England in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 241","241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731501","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 70759, what plans are in place to expand existing sport and recreation facilities on his Department's St Athan site; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 276","276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731502","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 70831, if he will place in the Library copies of discussion papers on the proposed relocation of his Department's St Athan No. 4 School of Technical Training to RAF Cosford; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277","277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731503","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterparts in (a) Jordan and (b) Saudi Arabia on the revocation of licences for the Al Jazeera Media Network to broadcast in those countries.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 263","263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731504","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 70755, if he will place the 2017 Initial Gate Business Case for Project CUBIT in the Library; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278","278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731505","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the UAE on the recent announcement of that country's intention to punish expressions of sympathy towards Qatar with imprisonment for up to 15 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 264","264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731506","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of sanctions imposed by other countries on Qatar since 5 June 2017 on (a) commercial flights and (b) commercial shipping between the UK and Qatar.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 260","260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731507","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the merits of the proposal by the hon. Member for Bassetlaw on the removal of landfill taxes to assist the removal of waste from the abandoned waste site at Sandy Lane, Worksop.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 259","259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731508","2017-06-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-06-21","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many instances of voters being wrongly excluded from the electoral list were identified at the 2015 General Election; and in which constituencies such exclusions took place.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 302","302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731509","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent progress his Department has made on investment in flood defences.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 198","198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731510","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if the Government will review fire safety regulations to ensure that highrise accommodation is required to have more than one fire exit.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 244","244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731511","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if the Government will review fire safety regulations to ensure that cladding on highrise accommodation is fireproof.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 245","245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731512","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that people who lose benefits under personal independence payments reassessments are allowed to keep their mobility vehicle until the appeals process has been completed.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 246","246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731513","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if the Government will review the fire safety regulations to ensure that highrise accommodation is required to have sprinklers.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 247","247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731514","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average call response time was to calls made to the Tax-Free Childcare helpline in (a) May and (b) June 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 225","225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731515","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether it is planned that the Youth Full-Time Social Action review will publish its findings and recommendations by October 2017.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 203","203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731516","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many community rehabilitation companies are in dispute with his Department on the payment mechanism.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 377","377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731517","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to provide certainty of energy policy in order to attract green technology companies to the UK.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 226","226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731518","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure that reductions in energy bills do not affect commitments to emissions reductions.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 227","227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731519","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many financial penalties have been incurred by (a) number and (b) financial value by community rehabilitation companies in (i) England, (ii) Wales and (iii) each county in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 378","378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731520","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many parents have signed up for the Tax-Free Childcare scheme to date.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228","228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731521","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department expects the review of community rehabilitation company performance measures to be completed.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 379","379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731522","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many end-state performance targets have been met by each community rehabilitation company providers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 380","380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731523","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appointments have been (a) offered and (b) undertaken by service users of community rehabilitation companies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 376","376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731524","2017-06-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-06-21","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many postal votes were discounted because the signature or date of birth was not accepted by returning officers in each constituency in the (a) 2015 and (b) 2017 General Election.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 433","433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731525","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total external costs of advisers and other bought-in items was to his Department for franchise specification and procurement for each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 234","234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731526","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons she did not appoint one of the above the line candidates for the role of representing Wales on the BBC Board.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 527","527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731527","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proactive steps (a) his Department and (b) NHS England are taking to ensure adequate provision of mental health support for people affected by the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 444","444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731528","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the number of (a) adults and (b) children who are (i) experiencing or (ii) likely to experience post-traumatic stress disorder, depression or other mental health problems as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 445","445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731529","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the number of free schools to be built each year.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 453","453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731530","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will allocate additional funding to the local mental health trust to strengthen provision of mental health support for people affected by the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 441","441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731531","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on preventing new places in schools that have been rated inadequate or requiring improvement by Ofsted.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 454","454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731532","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will allocate additional funding to the relevant local authority to support the mental health of people affected by the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 442","442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731533","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what specific steps his Department is taking to support the mental health of people who have experienced bereavement as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 443","443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731534","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the involvement of universities in academy sponsorship, the founding of free schools and charging maximum tuition fees.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 455","455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731535","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with representatives of the relevant EU funding bodies on applications for EU funding by UK creative organisations for multi-annual projects running until 2020.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 387","387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731536","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with industry representatives on the effect of the UK exiting the EU on cross-border co-production agreements.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 388","388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731537","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the trends in income from artists resale rights.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 389","389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731538","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of the UK exiting the customs union on the procedures for transporting cultural objects between museums across international borders.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 390","390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731539","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the opening of specialist maths schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 456","456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731540","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether an assessment has been made of the merits of continuing to pay into and receive funding from Creative Europe after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 391","391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731541","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on inclusivity rules and faith school admissions.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 457","457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731542","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the number of independent schools involved in academy sponsorship or the founding of free schools","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 458","458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731543","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the tax status of independent schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 459","459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731544","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the ban on the establishment of new selective schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 460","460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731545","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to carry out a review of school admissions policy.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 461","461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731546","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the teaching of literacy and numeracy in the early years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 462","462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731547","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on phonics screening testing.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 463","463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731548","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the knowledge of times tables by 11 year olds.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 464","464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731549","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the creation of a new national programme to attract experienced industry professionals to work in further education colleges.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 486","486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731550","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on accountability of schools at key stage 3.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 465","465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731551","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the introduction of new institutes of technology.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 487","487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731552","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on reviewing funding across tertiary education.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 488","488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731553","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the number of apprenticeships for young people to be delivered by 2020.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 489","489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731554","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the proportion of pupils to be entered for the EBacc combination of GCSEs by the end of this Parliament.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 466","466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731555","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on allowing large firms to place apprentices within their supply chains.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 490","490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731556","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on teaching apprenticeships.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 491","491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731557","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the proportion of schools to be entered for the Ebacc combination of GCSEs by 2025.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 467","467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731558","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on introducing a UCAS-style portal for technical education.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 492","492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731559","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on bus and train travel for apprentices.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 493","493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731560","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on access to an academic, knowledge-rich curriculum.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 468","468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731561","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on leave for training for all employees.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 494","494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731562","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the introduction of a national retraining scheme.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 495","495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731563","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on teaching assistants becoming qualified teachers through a degree apprenticeship.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 496","496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731564","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on lifelong learning in digital skills.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 497","497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731565","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Creative Europe in facilitating international professional networks for the creative industries over the last five years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 392","392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731566","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on funding the creation of nurseries in primary schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 498","498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731567","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on all new primary schools including a nursery.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 499","499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731568","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to collect data on the (a) amount and (b) proportion of the UK's allocation of the European Structural Investment Fund that have benefited the arts and culture sector.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 393","393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731569","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on mental health first aid training for teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 500","500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731570","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on ensuring that every school has a single point of contact for mental health services.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 501","501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731571","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the placement of responsibilities for family support and child protection services.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 502","502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731572","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has held discussions with the Secretary of State for Transport and the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government Secretary on the potential risk and costs of a fire at the abandoned waste site at Sandy Lane, Worksop.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 419","419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731573","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on introducing a curriculum fund to encourage cultural and scientific institutions to help develop knowledge-rich materials for schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 469","469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731574","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on assessments at the end of primary school.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 470","470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731575","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on how Ofsted can give parents more information on what their children are being taught.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 471","471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731576","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the proportion of offenders is who were recorded as having successfully completed their period of licence or post-sentence supervision in (a) England, (b) Wales and (c) each community rehabilitation company following a release from custody in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 517","517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731577","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what date his Department plans to deliver the strategic (IT) gateway; and what the reasons are for delay.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 518","518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731578","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many service users main contact with the community rehabilitation company is by telephone, in each community rehabilitation company in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 519","519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731579","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the repayment of student loans by teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 472","472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731580","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment the Government has made of staff moral in community rehabilitation companies in England and Wales.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 520","520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731581","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many multi-agency public protection arrangements eligible offenders are managed by the National Probation Service in (a) England, (b) Wales and (c) each county in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 521","521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731582","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on providing career support for teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 473","473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731583","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on unnecessary paper work.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 474","474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731584","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered care homes in Bassetlaw constituency do not have a fire sprinkler system.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 402","402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731585","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will list the number of police officers, by rank, employed in each of the four geographic forces in Wales in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 51","51"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731586","2017-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will set out the number of Army personnel, by rank, who were listed as (a) regulars and (b) reservists in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 52","52"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731587","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to make a further statement on tidal power and tidal lagoons.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 53","53"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731588","2017-06-27","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on reviewing the proposals for (a) additional capacity improvements at Cardiff Central Station and (b) a new station at St Mellons Parkway.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 54","54"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731589","2017-06-27","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether funding for Wales currently provided through all EU programmes will be matched by the Government after 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 55","55"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731590","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish the National Shipbuilding Strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 86","86"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731591","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the outcome of his Department's review of the DWP estate, including jobcentres; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 87","87"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731592","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Answer of 13 April 2017 to Question 70785, what plans he has to fill the vacancies in HMRC Minimum Wage Compliance Unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 88","88"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731593","2017-07-03","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate has been made of the number of transplant operations failing due to patients not being able to afford to pay for prescriptions; and if he will bring forward free prescriptions for people who have had transplants.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 81","81"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731594","2017-07-03","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research has been conducted into the number of school days missed by female pupils who live in households unable to afford female sanitary products; and what guidance her Department has issued on the provision of such products.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 82","82"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731595","2017-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much assistance his Department (a) has and (b) plans to provide to charities and other non-governmental organisations assisting refugees from African countries residing in Israel following the implementation of the so-called deposit law amendment to the Prevention of Infiltration (Offences and Jurisdiction) Law, 5714-1954 on 1 May 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 83","83"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731596","2017-07-03","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions Vodafone and other mobile phone networks have failed to provide mobile phone coverage for police during disaster recovery situations in the last 12 months; and what steps she plans to take to remedy this.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 84","84"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731597","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which 16 to 19 year old sports academies were established in 2015 and 2016; and which of these remain open.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208","208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731598","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on which dates between September 2015 and March 2016 spot inspections took place at the Worksop Town football academy; and at which location these inspections were carried out.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209","209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731599","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students in Worksop Town football academy in 2015-16 were assessed for student support; and how many received financial support during their studies.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210","210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731600","2017-06-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2017-06-21","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if she will conduct a national audit to determine how many (a) students and (b) other registered voters voted in more than one parliamentary constituency in the General Election 2017.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 140","140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731601","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many new nurses have been employed in each NHS hospital trust in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218","218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731602","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in Bassetlaw constituency have (a) asbestos and (b) no fire sprinkler system.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 220","220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731603","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was paid to West Anglia College for the 2015-16 Worksop Town football academy; how many students from that academy received passes in maths and English; and how many students from that academy progressed to further or higher education.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 212","212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731604","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 8 March 2017 to Question 66308, what progress her Department has made on the Youth Full-Time Social Action review.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190","190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731605","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to facilitate and encourage self-organisation and cooperatives for self-employed people.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 191","191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731606","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of parents who will sign up for Tax-Free Childcare in 2017-18.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 222","222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731607","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on supporting businesses who are unable to get flood insurance as part of their commercial insurance.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 214","214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731608","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many childcare providers have signed up to provide Tax-Free Childcare to date.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 223","223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731609","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many phonecalls HM Revenue and Customs has received from parents and childcare providers on Tax-Free Childcare to date.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 224","224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731610","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to reduce low pay among self-employed people.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 192","192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731611","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what adjustments his Department makes to ensure that people with (a) a history of suicide or self-harm and (b) other mental health conditions are treated with appropriate care and caution during benefits assessments.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 193","193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731612","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department plans to take to prevent school pupils and staff being exposed to asbestos in schools.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 196","196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731613","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will provide funding to local authorities for the installation of sprinklers and other fire safety measures in high-rise flats.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 197","197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731614","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's internal staffing and administration costs were for franchise specification and procurement in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 235","235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731615","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the full report and recommendations of Chris Gibb's project board into rapid improvements of Southern Rail will be published.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 236","236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731616","2017-06-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish a list of organisations and individuals who submitted evidence to the Commercial Radio Deregulation Consultation.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 311","311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731617","2017-06-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the independent review of S4C will be completed before 1 January 2018.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 312","312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731618","2017-06-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the independent review of S4C will be launched before 1 September 2018.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 313","313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731619","2017-06-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to respond to the Commercial Radio Deregulation Consultation.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 314","314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731620","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received a response on the latest investigation into the death of Stephen O'Malley; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279","279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731621","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to cease work capability reassessments for employment and support allowance claimants with the most severe health conditions and disabilities where the condition is unlikely to improve; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280","280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731622","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to improve National Probation Service effectiveness for cases (a) of domestic abuse and (b) involving the safeguarding of children.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 522","522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731623","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on reducing the burden of Ofsted inspections.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 475","475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731624","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government has produced or is planning to produce a report on the effectiveness of the new Integrated Offender Management arrangements.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 523","523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731625","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on introducing a single jobs portal for schools to advertise vacancies.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 476","476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731626","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to address the fact that self-employed workers are less likely to get onto apprenticeships as they are not on the payroll for PAYE and therefore not part of the levy calculation.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 509","509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731627","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on introducing a new national funding formula for schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 477","477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731628","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on budget cuts and the new funding formula.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 478","478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731629","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on increasing the schools budget in the next five years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 479","479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731630","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the Pupil Premium.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 480","480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731631","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on universal infant free-school meals.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 481","481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731632","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on school breakfasts in primary schools in England.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 482","482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731633","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on replacing  existing technical qualifications with new qualifications.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 483","483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731634","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the number of teaching hours per year.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 484","484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731635","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on future investments in further education colleges.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 485","485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731636","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students attending (a) comprehensive and (b) grammar schools in England are within each decile of the Income Deprivation Affecting Children Index.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 528","528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731637","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to invest in further education colleges involve additional (a) revenue and (b) capital funding.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 529","529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731638","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in each region and local authority in (A) cash terms and (B) 2014 prices in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 530","530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731639","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what methodology her Department plans to use to measure the effectiveness of the phonics screening test.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 531","531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731640","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to protect the pupil premium proposed per pupil in (a) cash and (b) real terms.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 532","532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731641","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship starts there were by 18 to 24 year olds in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 533","533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731642","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers there were in state primary schools in England in each year from 2010-11 to the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 534","534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731643","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers there were in state secondary schools in England in each year from 2010-11 to the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 535","535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731644","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the retention figures are for (a) primary and (b) secondary school teachers who began their employment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 536","536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731645","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to protect funding under the pupil premium scheme.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 537","537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731646","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government consultation, Analysing family circumstances and education, published on 12 April 2017, what the proportion is of pupils attending (a) selective schools (b) non-selective schools in highly selective areas, and (c) other non-selective schools from families in each income decile according to equivalised household income.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 544","544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731647","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on consulting on allowing people with Early Years Teacher Status and Early Years Professional Status to lead nursery and reception classes in maintained schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 539","539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731648","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of young people starting apprenticeships in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16 and (g) 2016-17 went on to complete them.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 538","538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731649","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Early Years Workforce Strategy, what funding the Government plans to make available to the early years sector to support that sector in developing quality improvement support in partnership with schools and local authorities.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 540","540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731650","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils her Department estimates will be studying T-Levels in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 541","541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731651","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government consultation, Analysing family circumstances and education, published on 12 April 2017, what the proportion is of pupils attending (a) faith primary schools and (b) all other primary schools from families in each decile according to equivalised household earnings.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 545","545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731652","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government consultation, Analysing family circumstances and education, published on 12 April 2017, what the proportion is of pupils attending (a) faith secondary schools and (b) all other secondary schools from families in each decile according to equivalised household earnings.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 546","546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731653","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the extent of the use of flammable cladding in school buildings.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 547","547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731654","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the provision of sprinkler systems in school buildings.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 548","548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731655","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students beginning their first undergraduate degree in England in the (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16 and (g) 2016-17 academic years were within each decile of the Income Deprivation Affecting Children Index.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 542","542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731656","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the potential cost of ensuring that all (a) new school buildings and (b) existing school buildings undergoing substantial refurbishment are fitted with sprinkler systems.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 549","549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731657","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to guarantee apprenticeship funding for non-levy paying employers in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20, (c) 2020-21 and (d) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 543","543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731658","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse of fires in school buildings has been in each year from 2010-11 to the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 550","550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732616","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to tackle the skills gap.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900020","900020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732763","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the sector-based approach in delivering the aims of the Government's industrial strategy.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900040","900040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732764","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the merits of introducing statutory paid leave for parents who suffer the loss of a child.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900038","900038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732765","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support the growth of small businesses.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900034","900034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732766","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department has made on implementing the recommendations of the Hendry Review on Tidal Lagoons.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900033","900033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732767","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of precarious work on the workforce.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900032","900032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/735979","2017-06-28","Northern Ireland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans the Government has for the representation of Northern Ireland at the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU in the absence of the Northern Ireland Executive.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900012","900012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/735980","2017-06-28","Northern Ireland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress has been made on power-sharing arrangements in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900014","900014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724551","2017-05-02","HM Treasury","2017-04-26","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 69989, on whisky: excise duties, for what reasons his Answer does not refer to representations received from the Scottish whisky industry on excise duties on spirits.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71998","71998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724552","2017-05-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2017 to Question 68586, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the opportunities to increase off-road cycling as part of that Department's environment strategy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72000","72000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724553","2017-05-02","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the total savings to the public purse of reductions in the number of Army personnel since the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71999","71999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724554","2017-05-02","Department for Education","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided per pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in Bolsover constituency in the last seven years.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72006","72006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724555","2017-05-02","Department for Education","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of families in Bolsover constituency are in receipt of 15-hours a week of free childcare for three and four-year olds.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72011","72011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724556","2017-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2017 to Question 69988, whether her Department plans to make an assessment of the effect of microplastics on the welfare of land animals.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72012","72012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724557","2017-05-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2017 to Question 69979, for what reason that Answer does not refer to any assessment of the effectiveness of the ban on the sale of antique ivory objects made after 1947.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72014","72014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724558","2017-05-02","Department of Health","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Liverpool Community Health NHS Trust's announcement of 30 March 2017 on the new arrangement to manage community services in Liverpool, what future bidding process NHS Improvement plans to use relating to the Liverpool Community Health Contract.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72015","72015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724559","2017-05-02","Department of Health","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 April 2017 to Question 70905, on Department of Health, for what reasons NHS Improvement placed (a) Bernie Cuthell at Manchester Mental Health Trust and (b) Karen Jackson at Southport and Ormskirk NHS Trust.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72016","72016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724560","2017-05-02","Department of Health","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2017 to Question 70013, for what reason that Answer does not refer to any plans by his Department to conduct an assessment of the effect of microplastics entering the marine environment on human health.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72013","72013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724561","2017-05-02","Department for Transport","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase patrols on known accident black spots on the A1.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72001","72001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724562","2017-05-02","Department for Transport","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to have a High Speed 2 station in Sheffield city as well as Meadowhall.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72002","72002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724563","2017-05-02","Department for Transport","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to Answer representations to him by representatives from Newton made on 13 March 2017.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72008","72008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724564","2017-05-02","Department for Transport","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the effect on the number of jobs in Derbyshire of the High Speed 2 spur line being developed.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72009","72009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724565","2017-05-02","Department for Transport","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many houses will be potentially affected by the High Speed 2 spur; and how many of those houses will be demolished.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72010","72010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724566","2017-04-27","Department for Transport","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from the Mayor of London on capping the number of private hire licences in London.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72004","72004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724567","2017-05-02","Department for Transport","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess the potential merits of alternatives to the siting of a High Speed 2 Station in Sheffield city centre in view of the number of dwellings in the area of the High Speed 2 spur that will have to be demolished.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72005","72005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724568","2017-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many representations he has received from whom on improving benefit assessments for pupils with severe disabilities.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72007","72007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724569","2017-05-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-04-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total amount of housing benefit claimed was in Bolsover constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Dennis Skinner","Mr Dennis Skinner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 72003","72003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724084","2017-04-27","Cabinet Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2017 to Question 68738, when he plans to supply the answer referred to in the Answer.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71842","71842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724085","2017-04-27","Cabinet Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much financial support Southampton has received from publicly funded projects and infrastructure investment over the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71849","71849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724086","2017-04-27","Cabinet Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of trends in the extent of the gender pay gap in the public sector in Scotland in the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71884","71884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724087","2017-04-27","Cabinet Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much Government investment has been made in Ochil and South Perthshire constituency since 2015.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71885","71885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724088","2017-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he has made an estimate of the cost to the public purse of business rate relief for fee-paying schools in England for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71929","71929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724089","2017-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount of business rates paid by state schools in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71930","71930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724090","2017-04-27","HM Treasury","2017-04-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been raised from the soft drinks industry levy in the last 12 months; and what estimate he has made of likely revenue from that levy in the next three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71853","71853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724091","2017-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total payroll cost of his Department's Extended Ministerial Office was; and how many civil servants worked in that office during its existence.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71846","71846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724092","2017-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether South Gloucestershire Council has made any funding applications to his Department for new developments, spatial plans or strategic development sites in Thornbury and Yate constituency.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71867","71867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724093","2017-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the outcome of South Gloucestershire Council's application to the large sites and housing zones capacity fund for a new Buckover Garden Village is.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71866","71866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724094","2017-04-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many housing association tenants have bought their home through the right to buy scheme to date.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71876","71876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724095","2017-04-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many stadiums in the UK had disabled access in (a) 2010 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71835","71835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724096","2017-04-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many complaints concerning nuisance calls have been reported to the Information Commissioner's Office in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71989","71989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724097","2017-04-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps her Department has taken to reduce the number of nuisance calls.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71994","71994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724098","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's Better Defence Estate strategy, what the status of Duncombe Barracks in York is.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71861","71861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724099","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reserve personnel are registered in the City of York Local Authority area.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71858","71858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724100","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people are employed in the City of York at Defence Business Services National Security Vetting.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71859","71859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724101","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the merits of re-deploying military units from Strensall to Gamecock Barracks, Nuneaton.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71850","71850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724102","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants are employed by his Department in the City of York; and what proportion those staff represent of all civil servants employed in the City of York.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71860","71860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724103","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military, (b) civilian and (c) contracted staff were employed at 34 Field Hospital on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71862","71862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724104","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military, (b) civilian and (c) contracted staff will be required at Gamecock Barracks as a result of implementation of suggestions made in his Department's Better Defence Estate document.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71863","71863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724105","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding from the public purse was for charities which support veterans in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71883","71883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724106","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many children of service personnel are currently receiving education in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in the City of York local authority area.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71951","71951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724107","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's Better Defence Estate strategy, what plans he has for the Defence Business Services National Security Vetting in York.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71952","71952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724108","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what safety assessment his Department has carried out on the military sites in the City of York to determine whether the land is suitable for house building.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71953","71953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724109","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to close the Queen's Own Yorkshire Yeomanry Museum as a result of the proposals in his Department's Better Defence Estate report, published in November 2016.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71954","71954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724110","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service houses there are in the City of York local authority area.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71968","71968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724111","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to close the Kohima Museum at Imphal Barracks as a result of the proposals in his Department's Better Defence Estate report, published in November 2016.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71955","71955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724112","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's report, A Better Defence Estate, published in November 2016, whether a full asbestos risk assessment has been carried out at military sites in the City of York local authority area.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71956","71956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724113","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many additional military units are planned to be located at Gamecock Barracks as a result of the proposals in his Department's Better Defence Estate report, published in November 2016; and if he will name those units.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71957","71957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724114","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) City of York Council and (ii) representatives of military and civilian units based in York to discuss the Better Defence Estate programme.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71958","71958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724116","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what analysis the military sites in the City of York were subject to prior to the publishing of his Department's Better Defence Estates strategy.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71959","71959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724117","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the same grade of training facilities are available at (a) Gamecock Barracks, Nuneaton and (b) Strensall Station, York.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71960","71960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724118","2017-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many additional (a) family houses and (b) single living accommodation will be required for (i) officers and (ii) non-commissioned staff at Gamecock Barracks, Nuneaton as a result of the proposals in his Department's Better Defence Estate report, published in November 2016.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71961","71961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724119","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of proposed reductions to school budgets set out in the new Schools National Funding Formula on children's attainment relating to reading ages.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71962","71962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724120","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of proposed reductions to school budgets set out in the new Schools National Funding Formula on children's attainment in national curriculum tests and assessments.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71963","71963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724121","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps the Government has taken to tackle extremism in schools.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71944","71944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724122","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what groups or working parties which her Department hosts or provides secretarial support to are routinely attended by representatives of education trade unions.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71890","71890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724123","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools her Department consulted on the planned changes to school budgets set out in the new National Funding Formula.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71873","71873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724124","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 71090, on Department for Education, how much spending was forecast on 16 to 19 education following the autumn statement 2016; and how much was subsequently allocated to institutions.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71894","71894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724125","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total payroll cost of her Department's Extended Ministerial Office was; and how many civil servants worked in that office during its existence.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71847","71847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724126","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on Johnson Kane.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71841","71841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724127","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of planned changes to school budgets set out in the new National Funding Formula on the level of attainment in internal and external assessments of children who qualify for free school meals.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71874","71874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724128","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils are in receipt of free school meals in (a) England, (b) the South East and (c) Southampton.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71852","71852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724129","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many representations her Department has had from head teachers (a) in favour of and (b) against the changes in funding for school budgets in the new National Funding Formula.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71872","71872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724130","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of her Department's budget for 16 to 19 education was underspent in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71843","71843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724131","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of the Resource Departmental Expenditure Limit budget for 16 to 19 education, excluding apprenticeships, was reallocated to other budgets in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71844","71844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724132","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the Resource Departmental Expenditure Limit budget was for 16 to 19 education, excluding apprenticeships, in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71845","71845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724133","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much the Government has spent on the National College of Digital Skills, Ada; and how much it plans to spend on Ada in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71834","71834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724134","2017-04-27","Department for Education","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many unauthorised absences from schools were recorded in (a) Woking constituency, (b) Surrey, (c) the South East and (d) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71990","71990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724135","2017-04-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what financial assistance the Government provides for land owners to clear their land after they have been the victims of fly tipping.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71836","71836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724136","2017-04-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2017 to Question 70108, on fly-tipping, who receives the proceeds of fines for small-scale fly-tipping incidents.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71840","71840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724137","2017-04-27","Department for Transport","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to review the Certificates of Equivalent Competency system.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71902","71902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724138","2017-04-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her priority to extend the maximum sentence which the courts can impose for offences involving animal cruelty.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71877","71877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724139","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the security situation in Sudan and South Sudan.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71892","71892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724140","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to protect Sub-Saharan migrants trying to reach Europe against the risk of their being sold as slaves or hostages in Libya.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71900","71900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724141","2017-04-27","Home Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to prevent female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71889","71889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724142","2017-04-27","Home Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to support asylum seekers fleeing Middle Eastern countries due to being persecuted because of their religious belief.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71887","71887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724143","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on securing a peace settlement in Yemen.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71946","71946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724144","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the implications for his Department's policy on Turkey's bid to become a member of the EU are of the result of the recent Turkish referendum.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71901","71901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724145","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Government of Paraguay on recent gang violence in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71871","71871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724146","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on South Korea's impeached President Park Geun-hye.","Biography information for Alex Salmond","Alex Salmond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71903","71903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724147","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any areas of sea between the UK and the Republic of Ireland have changed jurisdiction in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71856","71856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724148","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the jurisdiction of any seas in the northern and southern maritime borders of the UK and the Republic of Ireland have been exchanged in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71857","71857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724149","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Government of China on the use of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71969","71969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724150","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to comply with UN Security Council Resolution 2334 (2016).","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71983","71983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724151","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Government of Iran on the use of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71970","71970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724152","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Government of Saudi Arabia on the use of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71971","71971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724153","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support Christians at risk of religious persecution in countries with a high level of such persecution.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71992","71992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724154","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government will retain its commitment to the UN Security Council Resolution 2334 (2016) (a) during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU and (b) after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71982","71982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724155","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Pakistan on the protection of religious minorities and the charge of blasphemy.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71993","71993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724156","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Government of Pakistan on the use of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71972","71972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724157","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the US Administration on the use of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71973","71973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724158","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Government of Belarus on the use of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71974","71974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/724159","2017-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the planned demolition of the village of Khan Al-Ahmar in the East 1 planning zone.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 71981","71981"
