"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091088","2019-03-21","Home Office","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to the letters of the Hon. Member for East Worthing and Shoreham of 13 August 2018, 17 September 2018 and 4 March 2019 on the visa application of constituent Mr H.W.P of Lancing, West Sussex.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233431","233431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091089","2019-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fixed penalty notices for littering were issued in Havering in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233487","233487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091090","2019-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle anti-vaccine misinformation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233488","233488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091091","2019-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the incidence of contaminated chicken being sold at supermarkets.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233489","233489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091092","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the take-up of STEM subjects for pupils from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233490","233490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091093","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in which London boroughs his Department plans to build new special free schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233491","233491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091094","2019-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to tailor food standards to (a) serve UK trade interests and (b) keep standards high.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233543","233543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091095","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage schools to install automated external defibrillators on their premises.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233544","233544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091096","2019-03-20","Home Office","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that street preachers do not disseminate extremist material from proscribed terror groups.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233545","233545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091097","2019-03-20","Department for International Trade","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to tackle the reduction in the UK exports of goods and services to Switzerland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233546","233546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091098","2019-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measures are in place to help universal credit claimants with the repayment of debt.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233547","233547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091099","2019-03-20","Department for International Trade","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase the level of UK exports of goods and services to China.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233548","233548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091100","2019-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children in households affected by the two-child limit on welfare payments are in (a) Romford and (b) the borough of Havering.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233549","233549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091101","2019-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timeframe is for the completion of the integration of the F-35 fleet's MBDA Meteor beyond visual range air-to-air missile and SPEAR precision surface attack missile.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233550","233550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091102","2019-03-20","Department for International Development","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of linking the 0.7 per cent spending target to the financial year instead of the calendar year to help make the budget easier to manage.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233551","233551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091103","2019-03-20","Department for International Development","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of her having sign-off and accountability for aid spending by other Government Departments.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233552","233552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091104","2019-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the announcement, Royal Marines hone skills in Norway, published on 8 February 2019, what plans his Department has to increase defence cooperation with Norway.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233553","233553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091105","2019-03-20","Treasury","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of a tourist tax by local authorities on trends in the level of tourism.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233554","233554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1091106","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of secondary school places that will be required in Romford in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233555","233555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089431","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Action for Children press release entitled Children's funding slashed by a third per child leaving thousands at risk of falling into crisis, dated 26 February 2019.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232981","232981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089432","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the economic merits of the level of funding for early intervention services provided by local authority children’s services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232982","232982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089433","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Action for Children press release entitled Children's funding slashed by a third per child, leaving thousands at risk of falling into crisis, dated 26 February 2019, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of funding for children’s services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232983","232983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089434","2019-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to increase tourism in (a) coastal areas and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233033","233033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089435","2019-03-20","Department for Transport","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether restrictions are placed on departmental trade unions in respect of recruiting staff to join a trade union.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233002","233002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089436","2019-03-20","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department is responsible for recruiting detention gatekeepers; and whether his Department retains oversight and management of detention gatekeepers once they are in post.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233003","233003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089437","2019-03-20","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training detention gatekeepers receive on indicators of trafficking or modern slavery.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233004","233004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089438","2019-03-20","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to maintain public safety and security at mosques in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232975","232975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089439","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with Ofqual on preparations for the new functional skills qualifications for September 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232976","232976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089440","2019-03-20","Department for Transport","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support the introduction and expansion of very light railway systems in towns and cities across the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232977","232977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089441","2019-03-20","Department for International Development","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with representatives of the Government of Mozambique on potential UK aid in the aftermath of cyclone Idai.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232978","232978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089442","2019-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2019 to Question 230624, if his Department will make an assessment of the number of UK citizens living in refugee camps in (a) Iraq, (b) Jordan, (c) Lebanon, (d) Syria and (e) Turkey.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232979","232979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089443","2019-03-20","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support his Department is providing to the security services of (a) New Zealand and (b) Australia in connection with the terror attack on two Christchurch mosques on 15 March 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232995","232995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089444","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many websites or internet-based platforms (a) accessible from the UK and (b) published within the UK have been shut down as a result of intelligence services investigations into islamophobic extremist activities, including radicalisation operations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232996","232996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089445","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home department, if he will make an estimate of the number of (a) print and broadcast media and (b) social media publications accessible from the UK which promote beliefs and rhetorics similar to those used by the perpetrator or perpetrators of the terror attack on two Christchurch mosques on 15 March 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232997","232997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089446","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an estimate of the number of (a) print and broadcast media and (b) social media publications published within the UK which promote beliefs and rhetorics similar to those used by the perpetrator or perpetrators of the terror attack on two Christchurch mosques on 15 March 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232998","232998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089447","2019-03-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to prevent proliferation of videos and documents published by the perpetrator or perpetrators of the terror attack on two Christchurch mosques on 15 March 2019 on (a) print and broadcast media, (b) social media and (c) other internet sites and platforms accessible from the UK.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232999","232999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089448","2019-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much of the £1 billion for the courts reform programme (a) has been spent on consultancies and, (b) is projected to be spent on consultancies (i) in total and (ii) as a proportion of overall spending.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233000","233000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089449","2019-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent by the HM Courts and Tribunals Service on the courts reform programme to date.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233001","233001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089450","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release of 15 March 2019 on Support on wellbeing for teachers in schools and colleges, who the members are of the advisory group on teachers' wellbeing; when that group plans to meet; and what the timescale is for reporting its recommendations to his Department.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233008","233008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089451","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department's teacher workload advisory group is next plans to meet.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233009","233009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089452","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings are scheduled of his Department's advisory panel on early years, language, literacy and communication apps.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233010","233010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089453","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings are scheduled for his Department's independent panel of experts on the model music curriculum.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233011","233011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089454","2019-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report entitled the Disability Price Tag 2019, published by Scope in February 2019, what assessment she has made of the extra costs incurred by disabled people; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232967","232967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089455","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to promote awareness of Asda’s Tickled Pink campaign in order to encourage people to check their breasts.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232984","232984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089456","2019-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report entitled the Disability Price Tag 2019, published by Scope, what steps she is taking to ensure that personal independence payment assessments accurately capture the extra costs incurred by disabled people.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232968","232968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089457","2019-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timeframe is for the universal credit managed migration trial that is planned to start in July 2019; and if she will publish an assessment of the effectiveness of that trial after it has concluded.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232969","232969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089458","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to (a) promote Asda’s Tickled Pink campaign and (b) encourage women to be their breast friend to increase early diagnosis rates.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232985","232985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089459","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to enable deaf people to use 999 to contact the ambulance service using video relay services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232986","232986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089460","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to enable deaf people to make a 999 call to contact the police using video relay services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232987","232987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089461","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the financial sustainability of the children’s services department in the local authority of St Helens.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233015","233015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089462","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the reduction in funding available for children’s services in St Helens borough on the number of (a) referrals to children’s services, (b) re-referrals within 12 months, (c) children in need, (d) child protection enquiries, (e) child protection plans, (f) looked after children.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233016","233016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089463","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment has been made of the effect of the funding allocated to children’s services between 2010-11 and 2017-18 on the number of (a) referrals to children’s services; (b) re-referrals within 12 months, (c) children in need, (d) child protection enquiries, (e) child protection plans and (f) looked after children.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233017","233017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089464","2019-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2019 to Question 230807 on Ilois Finance, how many visits £312,899.37 has financed, and how many Chagossians have to date (a) expressed interest but not yet participated and (b) participated in those visits from (i) Seychelles, (ii) Mauritius, (iii) the UK and (iv) other countries.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233007","233007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089465","2019-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps has his Department has taken to enable deaf people to use 999 to contact the fire brigade using video relay services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232988","232988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089466","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations his Department has made to the 999 Liaison Committee on the availability for video relay services to facilitate deaf people contacting the emergency services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232989","232989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089467","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of the provision of a Video Relay Service for deaf people who need to contact the emergency services using 999.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232990","232990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089468","2019-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much charcoal for domestic barbecues the UK (a) produces and (b) burns in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232994","232994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089469","2019-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of potential merits of the NHS offering micro suction treatments to improve hearing (a) in addition to and (b) instead of syringing; what information his Department holds on the number of people whose impaired hearing is not improved by syringing; whether the NHS has plans to introduce micro suction as part of NHS Long-Term Plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232980","232980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089470","2019-03-20","Department for Transport","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the report entitled, Identifying the Multimodal Strategic Freight Network and the Value of Improving its Operation, published by the UK Major Ports Group, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the cost of bottleneck junctions in (a) Bramley, Hampshire and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233019","233019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089471","2019-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to comply with Article 109, Recital 5 of the European Electronic Communications Code in relation to people whose first language is British Sign Language.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232991","232991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089472","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of calls to the (a) NHS 111 service and (b) NHS 111 BSL service resulted in the dispatch of an ambulance in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232992","232992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089473","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents were handled by the Emergency SMS service in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232993","232993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089474","2019-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many properties that are the responsibility of Defence Infrastructure Organisation have (a) mould and (b) asbestos.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233031","233031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089475","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of effect of sex and relationships education on rates of (a) pregnancy and (b) abortion in those under the age of (i) 16 and (ii) 18 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232970","232970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089476","2019-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2019 to Question 230918, what plans the Government has to conclude the mandate of UN Human Rights Council resolutions 30/1 and 34/1 on promoting reconciliation, accountability and human rights in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233020","233020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089477","2019-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that journalists' trade unions internationally are (a) consulted on the UK's media freedom campaign, and (b) invited to participate in his Department's London conference on media freedom in July 2019.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233021","233021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089478","2019-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average cost of a (a) CT scanner (b) MRI scanner and (c) LINAC scanner is, and what his Department's policy is on replacing out of date equipment.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233005","233005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089479","2019-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what value for money criteria were used to make the decision to close Welbeck College; whether that criteria will be used to assess the sustainability of the Army Foundation College Harrogate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233022","233022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089480","2019-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 February 2019 to Question 221840 on Army: Recruitment, when he plans to place in the Library a copy of the media buying brief produced for the Crown Commercial Service for the Your Army Needs You advertising campaign launched in January 2019.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233023","233023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089481","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what is the cost per minute is of telephoning UK Immigration Services from a (a) landline and (b) mobile phone.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233024","233024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089482","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average number of calls received by UK Immigration Services was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233025","233025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089483","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time was for a telephone call to UK Immigration Services in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233026","233026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089484","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average cost of a telephone call to UK Immigration Services was, from a (a) landline, and (b) mobile phone.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233027","233027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089485","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the UK Immigration Services telephone line is not a free phone service.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233028","233028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089486","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason his Department charges callers to the UK Immigration Services phoneline in advance of being connected to an operator.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233029","233029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089487","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has plans to make the UK Immigration Services telephone service a freephone service.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233030","233030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089488","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the public appointments he has authorised since he took office.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233012","233012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089489","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2019 to Question 230746 on Schools: Finance, on what dates (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department met representatives of the campaign group WorthLess.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233013","233013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089490","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the (a) individuals and (b) organisations consulted prior to the publication of the Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education, and Health Education in England Government consultation response; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232971","232971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089491","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who his Department consulted before drawing up the draft statutory guidance on Relationship's Education and Relationships and Sex Education for governing bodies, proprietors, head teachers, principals, senior leadership teams, teachers; what research was evaluated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232972","232972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089492","2019-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families were in receipt of the lower child disability addition of a legacy benefit for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233018","233018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089493","2019-03-20","Treasury","2019-03-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the commemorative 50 pence coin issued to mark the UK's departure from the EU has been minted.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233006","233006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089494","2019-03-20","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of apprenticeships that will have been started between 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233014","233014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089495","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what legal cases on a parent's right to withdraw their child from sex education lessons were considered by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232973","232973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089496","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Section 34(2)(d) of the Children and Social Work Act 2017, under what circumstances a (a) pupil may be excused and (b) a pupil below a specified age, from receiving relationships and sex education or specified elements of that education; if he will make it his policy to allow a parental opt out for (i) all and (ii) or part of  (A) relationships and (B) sex education; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232974","232974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1089497","2019-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish the legal position on Article 62 of the Vienna Convention on the Law of Treaties.","Biography information for Rachel Maclean","Rachel Maclean","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233032","233032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087714","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what sectors he has identified as most at risk in the event that the UK does not replicate existing EU trade agreements before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909807","909807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087764","2019-03-14","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer , what support his Department provides to UK businesses preparing and completing (a) import and (b) export declarations.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909800","909800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088339","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government,  what the change was in central government funding for local authority children’s services between 1 April 2015 and 1 April 2018.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231961","231961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088604","2019-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to promote the creation of skilled green jobs.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909869","909869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088608","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-14","What plans he has to mark the centenary of UK Export Finance.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909804","909804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088609","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-14","What recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of inward foreign direct investment.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909808","909808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088610","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-14","What progress his Department has made on proposals for the scrutiny of future free trade agreements.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909811","909811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088611","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-14","What recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of inward foreign direct investment.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909812","909812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088613","2019-03-14","Women and Equalities","2019-03-14","What steps she is taking to help ensure that companies report accurate gender pay gap figures before the 4 April 2019 deadline.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909791","909791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088614","2019-03-14","Women and Equalities","2019-03-14","What steps she is taking to maintain equalities protections in law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909792","909792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088680","2019-03-19","Women and Equalities","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the opening statement to the seventy-second session of the Committee on the Elimination of Discrimination against Women by Elysia McCaffrey on 26 February 2019 on women in Northern Ireland, what political structures are required to (a) authorise and (b) approve the UK's response; and what the timescale is for that response to be published.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232565","232565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088681","2019-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on implementing the recommendations in relation to health from Lord Ashcroft's Veterans' Transition Review published in February 2014.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232564","232564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088682","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure and monitor that women have full information about the screening available in the public and private sectors and the conditions being screened for, before they embark on the screening pathway.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232550","232550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088683","2019-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the effect of pre-construction agreements between offshore wind farm owners and contractors on employment (a) conditions, (b) practices and (c) levels.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232557","232557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088684","2019-03-18","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what measures she is taking to ensure that the most marginalised children receive an education.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232551","232551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088685","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, further to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question HL13127, whether his Department relies on the assurances provided by the Bahraini Government in assessing the case of Sayed Ahmed Alwadaei’s family members; and what assessment the Government has made of information provided by independent bodies such as the UN, Amnesty International and Human Rights Watch on this matter.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232533","232533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088686","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether officials from his Department attended the proceedings in Bahrain on 25 February 2019 in which the three-year prison sentences against family members of Sayed Alwadaei were upheld.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232534","232534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088687","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Bahrain on the case of the family members Sayed Ahmed Alwadaei.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232535","232535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088688","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps they will take to escalate engagement with the Libyan authorities on securing justice for the descendents of Major Farouk Hamadalla who was forced off the British Overseas Airways Corporation VC10 en route from London to Khartoum on the 22nd July 1971.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232536","232536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088689","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the River Class 2 patrol vessel, HMS Forth (a) at inception and (b) when it was accepted by the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232590","232590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088690","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to deliver the low carbon commitment in the NHS England Long Term Plan; and what discussions he has had with pharmacy organisations on the role of pharmacists in helping patients decide whether to opt for low carbon inhalers.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232504","232504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088691","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimated build time was for HMS Forth at inception; and whether that ship was delivered on time.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232591","232591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088692","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the build of HMS Forth was affected by (a) design problems, (b) technical issues or (c) relationship issues between the Royal Navy, Ministry of Defence and the contractor.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232592","232592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088693","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, at inception what the estimated hand over date of HMS Forth was; and when sea trials were expected to commence.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232593","232593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088694","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Royal Navy officially accepted HMS Forth; when her sea trials commenced; and what the date is when sea trails are expected to be completed.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232594","232594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088695","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase (a) patient and (b) clinician awareness of the (i) effect on carbon emissions of inhalers and (ii) range of low carbon inhalers available; and how he plans to measure progress on the increased use of low carbon inhalers in the NHS.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232644","232644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088696","2019-03-18","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Government subsidy the Northern railway franchise will receive in the next financial year.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232653","232653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088697","2019-03-19","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent steps his Department has taken to prepare for the possibility of holding elections to the European Parliament in May 2019.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232513","232513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088698","2019-03-19","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of electric vehicle charging points in towns and cities throughout the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232514","232514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088699","2019-03-19","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her Zimbabwean Government on (a) health services and (b) UK aid to that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232515","232515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088700","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times the Financial Conduct Authority has taken enforcement action against lenders who have breached the rules on affordability checks for loans in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232597","232597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088701","2019-03-18","Department for International Trade","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will take steps to ensure that contracts for the delivery of (a) NHS and (b) other public services will be excluded from future trade deals.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232631","232631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088702","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the average waiting time at (a) e-passport gates and (b) manual passport checks at the UK border in airports throughout the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232516","232516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088703","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of Ofsted's rating on the ability of a school to recruit teaching staff.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232517","232517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088704","2019-03-18","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what further steps his Department plans to take to educate people on the dangers of using a mobile phone while driving.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232609","232609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088705","2019-03-18","Department for Education","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Spring Statement 2019, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing every secondary school age female with a reusable menstrual cup.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232544","232544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088706","2019-03-19","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to reform taxi and private hire licensing laws.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232503","232503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088707","2019-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Oldham East and Saddleworth, of 6 March 2019, Official Report, column 969, what the terms of reference will be for the review into the adequacy of social security support for disabled people; and who will be involved in that review.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232571","232571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088708","2019-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Oldham East and Saddleworth, of 6 March 2019, Official Report, column 969, what plans she has to change the culture of her Department.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232572","232572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088709","2019-03-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that High Speed Two will not affect the protection of woodlands.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232522","232522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088710","2019-03-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that High Speed Two will not affect the bird nesting season.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232523","232523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088711","2019-03-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent loss of ancient woodland as a result of High Speed Two.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232524","232524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088712","2019-03-18","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to adopt the finding of Natural England on the planting ratio of 30:1 to ensure conservation of the ancient woodlands that will potentially be damaged by High Speed Two.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232525","232525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088713","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March to Question 229807, how HMRC communicated with people affected by disguised remuneration debt to ensure that they were aware that it was HMRC’s policy not to force the sale of a main residence in relation to a DR debt.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232642","232642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088714","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long-Term Plan, what steps he plans to take to deliver a ten-fold increase in the proportion of patients who receive thrombectomy procedure after stroke so that all eligible patients have access to that treatment by 2022.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232501","232501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088715","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how Health Education England plans to increase the number of stroke specialists trained to deliver thrombectomy.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232502","232502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088716","2019-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the universal credit system has access to information provided to the Government’s Tell Us Once system for registering births and deaths; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232505","232505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088717","2019-03-19","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure a transparent selection process for the next President of the World Bank Group.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232626","232626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088718","2019-03-19","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to World Bank Group shareholders for a merit-based selection process for the selection of the next President of the World Bank Group.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232627","232627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088719","2019-03-18","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent representations she has received on the selection process for the position of President of the World Bank.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232628","232628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088720","2019-03-18","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with World Bank Group shareholders on the practice of choosing the President of the World Bank based on nationality.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232629","232629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088721","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England’s document, Investment and evolution: A five-year framework for GP contract reform to implement the NHS Long Term Plan, published on 31 January 2019, what plans his Department has to ensure the integration of local authority-commissioned public health services within the new Primary Care Networks.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232537","232537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088722","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England’s document, Investment and evolution: A five-year framework for GP contract reform to implement the NHS Long Term Plan, published on 31 January 2019, what plans his Department has to ensure the integration of (a) sexual and reproductive health services and (b) contraception provision within the new Primary Care Networks.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232538","232538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088723","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England’s document, Investment and evolution: A five-year framework for GP contract reform to implement the NHS Long Term Plan, published on 31 January 2019, whether the new Network Contract DES will require Primary Care Networks to collaborate with local authorities in delivering integrated care to local populations.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232539","232539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088724","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England’s document, Investment and evolution: A five-year framework for GP contract reform to implement the NHS Long Term Plan, published 31 January 2019,  whether his Department has plans to introduce a national service specification for women’s health including a focus on (a) sexual and reproductive health and (b) contraception.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232540","232540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088725","2019-03-19","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether it is Government policy to seek a transparent vote by World Bank Group shareholders for the selection of the next World Bank President.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232630","232630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088726","2019-03-18","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new pieces of rolling stock have been ordered by Train Operating Companies or their suppliers in each year between 1997 and 2019.","Biography information for James Morris","James Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232556","232556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088727","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he had with (a) the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, (b) the boiler manufacturing industry and (c) trade unions prior to his announcement on 13 March 2019 of a ban on gas boilers in new dwellings from 2025.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232519","232519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088728","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of unrestricted funding grants delivered to charities by charity lotteries.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232632","232632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088729","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the complementary benefits of funding from both charity lotteries and the National Lottery to charities.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232633","232633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088730","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the benefits delivered to local charities by charity lotteries.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232634","232634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088731","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of potential merits for his policies of the Gambling Commission’s recent findings that 55 per cent of charity lottery players do so in order to support good causes in contrast to only 15 per cent of National Lottery players and 5 per cent of scratchcard players.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232635","232635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088732","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the Government’s rationale is for having a limit on the annual sales of charity lotteries.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232636","232636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088733","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons the charity lottery sector is the only type of charity fundraising which has limits imposed on its fundraising.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232637","232637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088734","2019-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he will publish the full list of CSSF projects his Department is involved in.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232541","232541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088735","2019-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of new homes were built by (a) local authorities, and (b) social landlords and housing associations in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232530","232530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088736","2019-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many square kilometres of marine protected areas there were in (a) the UK and (b) UK overseas territories in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232531","232531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088737","2019-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Spring Statement of 13 March 2019, HCWS1407, what the delivery timescale is for Wave 3 allocations for Local Full Fibre Networks in north Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232532","232532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088738","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what language support NHS services should provide for refugees who lack the English language skills required to communicate with those services in (a) the UK and (b) in Liverpool.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232640","232640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088739","2019-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229147 on Buildings: Insulation, whether Department has consulted the (a) Fire Protection Association and (b) Association of British Insurers on the build-up of the test.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232573","232573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088740","2019-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229147 on Buildings: Insulation, how many fire barriers will be used in that test.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232574","232574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088741","2019-03-19","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he expects the Honours Forfeiture Committee will respond to the letter from the rt hon. Member for Birkenhead of 14 February 2019 on Sir Philip Green's knighthood.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232529","232529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088742","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the forthcoming NHS workforce implementation plan will model future patient demands as part of determining NHS future workforce needs.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232596","232596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088743","2019-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the time period is for his target to build 250,000 affordable homes through the Affordable Homes Programme.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232520","232520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088744","2019-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the total grant investment for affordable housing was by Homes England and its predecessor organisations in each financial year for which data is available.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232521","232521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088745","2019-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many mandatory reconsiderations of employment and support allowance appeals have been successful in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232645","232645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088746","2019-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many reconsiderations of employment and support allowance decisions occurred after her Department had been notified that an appeal had been lodged in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232646","232646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088747","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to begin a review of the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232543","232543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088748","2019-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent conversations he has had with his French counterpart on that country's visa plans for UK business travellers.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232506","232506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088749","2019-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his French counterpart on plans that country has for a centralised biometric database when processing UK business travellers.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232507","232507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088750","2019-03-19","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the stakeholders that his Honorary Medical Advisory Panel on driving and diabetes mellitus consults with to inform its reviews of the current guidance.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232647","232647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088751","2019-03-19","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what processes are in place to ensure that the Medical Advisory Panel on driving and diabetes mellitus consults regularly with a broad and representative range of stakeholders.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232648","232648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088752","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 223521 on Waiting Lists: North East, whether any changes to the pledges of (a) a maximum four-hour wait in A&E from arrival to admission, transfer or discharge and (b) other waiting times set out on pages 32 and 33 of the Handbook to the NHS Constitution will be subject to public consultation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232545","232545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088753","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Scope report entitled Disability Price Tag 2019, what steps she is taking to reduce the extra costs faced by disabled people.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232508","232508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088754","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that personal independence payment assessments address the full range of extra costs faced by disabled people.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232509","232509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088755","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will extend protections to ensure no disabled person receiving a disability premium within employment support allowance has to transition to universal credit via natural migration.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232510","232510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088756","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will create a new disability element within the universal credit system to replace the disability premiums available within employment support allowance.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232511","232511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088757","2019-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current waiting time is from the submission of a complaint to the office of the Independent Case Examiner to the allocation of the case to an Investigation Case Manager; and what steps she is taking to reduce that time.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232654","232654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088758","2019-03-18","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the proposed Passenger Charter set out in his Aviation 2050 document will incorporate services provided by Border Force and NATS in addition to other parts of industry including airlines and airports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232655","232655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088759","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the ending of new HIV transmissions in England by 2030.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232566","232566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088760","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2019 to Question 229820 on tax collection, what the total amount was that the Affluent teams working in HMRC raised in additional taxation from high net worth individuals from 2010 to April 2017.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232585","232585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088761","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2019 to Question 227387 on smuggling, how many HMRC staff work with Border Force to assist with anti-smuggling activity.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232586","232586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088762","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer on 4 March 2019 to Question 226685 on tax avoidance, how many users of tax avoidance schemes did HMRC have under review in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015, (d) 2016, (e) 2017 and (f) 2018.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232587","232587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088763","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to question 229219 on taxation tribunals, how much HMRC spent last year on tribunal costs.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232588","232588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088764","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer on 7th January 2019 given to Question 203919 on tax avoidance, how many promoters of tax avoidance schemes have paid HMRC a penalty in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232589","232589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088765","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the gross weekly income thresholds for each child maintenance rate of pay were last updated.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232605","232605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088766","2019-03-19","Wales Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on (a) Holyhead and (b) Pembroke Docks of the plan to have lower tariffs on goods entering the UK via Northern Ireland rather than via other UK ports.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232598","232598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088767","2019-03-19","Wales Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps his Department (a) has taken and (b) to make an assessment of the effect of the Government’s temporary tariff regime for the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on Welsh businesses.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232599","232599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088768","2019-03-19","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been directly employed by local authorities in England since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232600","232600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088769","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the total value of council property in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232601","232601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088770","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2019 to Question 229223 on Rough Sleeping and Homelessness Reduction Taskforce, how many meetings the Taskforce has had; and what the date was of its most recent meeting.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232582","232582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088771","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will respond to the review entitled Bercow: Ten Years On, on provision for children and young people with speech, language and communication needs in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232624","232624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088772","2019-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children are living with autism in (a) Sheffield, Brightside and Hillsborough constituency, (b) Sheffield and (c) England.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232625","232625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088773","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many tents were given to prisoners on discharge from jails in England and Wales in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232612","232612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088774","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many tents were issued to people under the supervision of Community Rehabilitation Companies in England and Wales in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232613","232613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088775","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) CZ long phones and (b) smart phones were confiscated from prisoners in England and Wales during each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232614","232614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088776","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drug seizures were made in prisons in England and Wales in each of the last three years; and what drugs were seized.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232615","232615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088777","2019-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison staff have received additional training to enable them to provide mentoring support to new prison officers in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232616","232616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088778","2019-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent initiatives he has introduced to reduce the attrition rate of prison officers.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232617","232617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088779","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what lessons have been learned from recent prison officer recruitment campaigns.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232618","232618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088780","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what additional resources he has provided to prison governors in the last 12 months to help them foster a good working environment for their staff.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232619","232619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088781","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken in the last 12 months to improve physical conditions in prisons.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232620","232620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088782","2019-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders were engaged in learning and skills in prisons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232621","232621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088783","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the prison population was engaged in offender learning and skills in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232622","232622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088784","2019-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders were engaged in learning that now falls outside of core prison education provision in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232623","232623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088785","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new personal independence payment claimants with epilepsy have had their claim (a) accepted and (b) rejected since April 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232547","232547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088786","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new personal independence payment (PIP) claimants with epilepsy have had their PIP decisions overturned in their favour as a result of a mandatory reconsideration since April 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232548","232548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088787","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new personal independence payment (PIP) claimants with epilepsy have had their PIP decisions overturned in their favour as a result of an appeal hearing since April 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232549","232549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088788","2019-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Bangladeshi counterpart on the plight of Rohingya refugees; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232526","232526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088789","2019-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason the Government decided to host a Myanmar Trade and Investment Conference in London; and what account was taken of human rights violations by the Government of Myanmar before the decision was made to host that conference.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232527","232527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088790","2019-03-18","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department was consulted on the decision to host a Myanmar Trade and Investment Conference in London; and what advice she gave on human rights violations in that country.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232528","232528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088791","2019-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2019 to Question 230845 on Housing: Students, how many of the 62 high rise student accommodation buildings which have Aluminium Composite Material (ACM) are (a) university-owned and (b) privately owned; in which local authority areas they are located; and if he will list the three buildings for which no remediation plan is currently underway or being developed.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232575","232575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088792","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is his target to create three million new high-quality apprenticeships by 2020.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232576","232576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088793","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons money wrongly paid to HMRC in January 2000 was not returned to the Roadchef Employee Benefits Trust until September 2018.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232577","232577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088794","2019-03-19","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the £18.25 million that HMRC will invest in Overseas Development Assistance funding over the next six years will come from its existing budget or new funding allocated to that department.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232643","232643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088795","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the reduction in the maximum rate at which deductions can be made from universal credit to repay an advance payment is not being implemented until October 2019.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232578","232578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088796","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the extension of the period over which universal credit advance payments have to be repaid from 12 months to 16 months is not being implemented until October 2021.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232579","232579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088797","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to develop a strong market for age and identity verification products to (a) protect young people against internet harms and (b) to reduce online fraud.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232638","232638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088798","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that digital ID has carries the same age proofing weight as a passport or other physical ID document.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232639","232639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088799","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect the Competition and Market Authority’s proposed extension of the scope of its funeral market investigation to consider the delivery of funeral plans will have on the timing of HM Treasury’s response to its consultation on funeral plan regulation.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232580","232580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088800","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department plans to publish its response to its consultation on funeral plan regulation, launched in June 2018.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232581","232581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088801","2019-03-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a maximum five-year sentence for animal cruelty as a deterrent to animal cruelty offenders who use such acts of cruelty to manipulate human victims.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232542","232542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088802","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support Trading Standards.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232583","232583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088803","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Home Office plans to respond to the enquiry of 30 January 2019 to UKVI from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central, on behalf of her constituent Mr James Doherty.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232602","232602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088804","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2019 to Question 230859 on Schools: Finance, how many head teachers he has had discussions with in each month from February 2018 to date.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232641","232641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088805","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to support the UK automotive industry in the ambition set out in the that strategy to secure the UK’s position as a world leader in shaping the future of mobility.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Dame Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232518","232518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088806","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Home Office plans to respond to the enquiry of 23 January 2019 from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central on behalf of her constituent Ms Valerie Hayes.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232603","232603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088807","2019-03-19","Home Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Home Office plans to respond to the enquiry of 23 January 2019 to UKVI from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central on behalf of her constituent, Mr Maloth.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232604","232604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088808","2019-03-18","Department for Education","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the degree to which standards are adequately and continuously assessed by OFSTED at schools where the most recent inspection was outstanding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232611","232611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088809","2019-03-18","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to meet the specified deadline to develop the Local Cycling and Walking Infrastructure Plan.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232649","232649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088810","2019-03-18","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has for regulating bus services throughout the Liverpool city region.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232650","232650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088811","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made over the effect of denied spousal visas on families across the UK.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232651","232651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088812","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what housing support his Department provides to people who are of pensionable age.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232652","232652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088813","2019-03-18","Department for Education","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he's taken to support access to schooling for children with Chronic Fatigue Syndrome.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232584","232584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088814","2019-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on the vote at the United Nations Human Rights Council on the report and recommendations of the Independent International Commission of Inquiry on the 2018 Protests in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232512","232512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088815","2019-03-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural affairs, what guidance he has provided to agri-food exporters on food labelling in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and what assessment he has made of the capacity of those exporters to put in place that labelling by the end of March 2019.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232567","232567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088816","2019-03-19","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to start discussions with trades unions on its equal pay review.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232552","232552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088817","2019-03-19","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department allows Departmental trade unions to host presentations on induction courses in his Department's central offices.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232553","232553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088818","2019-03-18","Department for International Trade","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will outline the support services available for export businesses seeking to expand in global markets.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232568","232568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088819","2019-03-19","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department adheres to the findings of the employment appeal tribunal ruling in the case of Dudley Metropolitan Borough Council v. Mr G Willetts to ensure that voluntary overtime is included in holiday pay.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232554","232554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088820","2019-03-19","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the performance management reports marks for driving examiners in (a) Quarter 1 and (b) Quarter 2 of 2018.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232555","232555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088821","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on additional paid leave for (a) parents of premature babies and (b) multiple birth parents.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232569","232569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088823","2019-03-18","Women and Equalities","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on providing sanitary products free of charge in community health centres.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232570","232570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088824","2019-03-19","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to her counterpart in the US administration on its decision to maintain its reduction to UNRWA funds.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232607","232607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088825","2019-03-19","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department plans to allocate to UNRWA in response to its emergency appeal for 2019.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232608","232608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088826","2019-03-19","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many alleged breaches of the Civil Service Code by Special Advisers have been acted upon by his Department in the last 12 months; and if he will list those alleged breaches by Department.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232610","232610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088827","2019-03-19","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the extent to which alternative providers will assume existing Interserve contracts in the event that Interserve enters administration.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232559","232559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088828","2019-03-19","Department for International Development","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of UNRWA funding as a result of the decision by the US Government to reduce its funding to that agency.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232595","232595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088829","2019-03-18","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much money from the UK’s Prosperity Fund was used to support the fossil fuel industry in 2018.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232546","232546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088830","2019-03-19","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of Interserve going into administration.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232560","232560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088831","2019-03-19","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the capacity of alternative providers to take over public sector contracts held by Interserve, in the event that Interserve enters administration.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232561","232561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088832","2019-03-19","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on schools of Interserve entering administration.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232562","232562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088833","2019-03-19","Cabinet Office","2019-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with alternative providers on taking over Interserve contracts in schools, in the event that Interserve enters administration.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232563","232563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088834","2019-03-19","Department for Transport","2019-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2019 to Question 230103 on Southern, how many Southern services ran without an on-board supervisor in (a) 2017, (b) 2018 and (c) 2019 for the (i) whole and (ii) part of their journey.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232558","232558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087716","2019-03-13","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","What steps his Department is taking to move civil service jobs out of London in line with the Government's Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909770","909770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087717","2019-03-13","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","Whether the Government plans to conduct further voter ID pilots; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909771","909771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087718","2019-03-13","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","What plans the Government has to use the centenary of Nancy Astor’s election to Parliament to encourage more women to stand for public office.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909772","909772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087719","2019-03-13","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","What steps he is taking to ensure that Government (a) suppliers and (b) subcontractors are paid on time.","Biography information for Andrew Lewer","Andrew Lewer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909773","909773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087720","2019-03-13","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","What plans he has to use social impact bonds in Government procurement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909774","909774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088221","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the cost to the public purse of extending full fibre relief from five years to (a) 10 years, (b) 15 years and (c) 20 years by financial year.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231921","231921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088224","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish proposals for modernising the eCommerce Directive.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231922","231922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088225","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the ability of local authorities to re-house refugees in respect of the notice period refugees are given to vacate premises.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232009","232009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088227","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of changes to permitted development rights on the long-term viability of high streets and town centres.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231916","231916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088228","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) English and (b) Welsh police services did claim from the apprenticeship levy in 2018.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232077","232077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088230","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to strengthen UK co-operation with international partners to ensure the (a) prosecution and (b) extradition of people who commit international crimes.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231923","231923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088231","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many herds were tested for bovine tuberculosis in the badger cull areas of (a) Gloucestershire area 01, (b) Somerset area 02 and (c) Dorset area 03 in each of the calendar years from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231888","231888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088233","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the proportion of specialised social care provided by community hospitals.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231928","231928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088234","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224304 on Health Services: Reciprocal Arrangements, how many European Health Insurance Cards have been issued to people over the age of 70 in each of the nations and regions of the UK.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231936","231936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088236","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how non-UK EU nationals will be able to inform his Department online about changes to passports or national identity cards after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231889","231889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088237","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his Department's policy is on the mutual recognition approach to airport staff screening as discussed at the Transatlantic Aviation Security Industry Roundtable in 2018.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232005","232005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088239","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to advocate a unilateral approach to airport staff screening at the International Civil Aviation Organization in 2019 as opposed to the mutual recognition approach discussed at the Transatlantic Aviation Security Industry Roundtable in 2018.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232006","232006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088240","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that university students receive value for money from student fees.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232112","232112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088242","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to ensure that on medicine courses the effect of eating disorders on mental health is given parity of esteem with their effect on physical health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231929","231929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088243","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of safer schools officers in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232025","232025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088245","2019-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many pubs closed in the 12 months (a) before the business rates revaluation came into force in 2017 and (b) after that revaluation.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231972","231972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088246","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Conservative Party Human Rights Commission's report of 18 February 2019, what assessment he has made of the validity of concerns that China’s Confucius Institutes may represent a threat to academic freedoms and freedom of expression.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231982","231982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088247","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will bring forward legislative proposals to require transparency from and ensure that Confucius Institutes and other foreign institutions are not able to hold undue influence, whether political, ideological or religious, on the curriculum and teaching practices of British institutions.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231983","231983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088250","2019-03-15","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many reported offences of each crime type there were in (a) Havering and (b) England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231935","231935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088251","2019-03-18","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the UK's tenth place rating in the Worldwide Educating for the Future Index 2018 produced by the Economist Intelligence Unit.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232099","232099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088253","2019-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department is making in its assessment of the merits and development of small modular nuclear reactors.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231904","231904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088254","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to prevent VAT evasion by overseas companies using internet platforms with fake VAT numbers.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231905","231905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088257","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to bring unoccupied properties back into use.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231954","231954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088259","2019-03-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the risk to those coastal areas likely to be worst affected by rising sea levels.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231927","231927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088260","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will hold a public consultation on changes to the (a) guidance and (b) principles related to the regulation of pesticides in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231974","231974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088262","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will increase the (a) capacity and (b) operating budget of the Expert Committee on Pesticides in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231975","231975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088264","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to include independent scientific advice within the authorisation process for active substances used in plant protection products in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231976","231976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088265","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the UK's future pesticide regime will provide equal levels of accountability and scrutiny to the EU pesticide regime in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231977","231977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088267","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that renewals for approvals of (a) active substances used in plant protection products and (b) plant protection products cannot be extended indefinitely by the relevant public bodies in the event that UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231978","231978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088268","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question 223982 on Cervical Cancer: Screening, if he will make it his policy to (a) require CCGs to monitor and report to him on the availability of cervical screening appointments at GP surgeries and (b) request the information necessary to allow him to monitor regularly the rates of attendance for cervical screening appointments.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231979","231979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088270","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much Her Majesty's Courts and Tribunal Service spent on consultancies (a) in total, (b) per consultancy in each of the financial years (i) 2016-17 and (ii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231973","231973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088271","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Gaza on the treatment of animals in Rafah Zoo.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232054","232054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088273","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government can take to (a) provide support to and (b) if necessary re-house the animals in Rafah Zoo, Gaza.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232055","232055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088274","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the provisions of section 8(1) of the London County Council (Improvements) Act 1900 had an effect on the (a) Government’s decision to locate the proposed Holocaust Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens and (b) development of plans for the Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231906","231906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088275","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he made of Zimbabwe's human rights record prior to sharing sensitive personal information with the Government of Zimbabwe on potential deportees to that country.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232075","232075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088277","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are taken to ensure that people in immigration removal centres have uninterrupted access to prescribed medication.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232076","232076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088278","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential economic effect on businesses in the West Midlands of the proposals set out in the Tax Information and Impact Note for the UK Tariff 2019.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232080","232080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088280","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential economic effect on businesses in the West Midlands of the provisions in the Tax Information and Impact Note for the UK Tariff 2019.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232081","232081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088281","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the (a) number and (b) effectiveness of nets used by developers to prevent birds nesting in trees.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231924","231924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088283","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance he has given to planning authorities on the use of nets by developers to prevent birds nesting in trees.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231925","231925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088284","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with the RSPB and other wildlife charities on the use of nets by developers to prevent birds nesting in trees.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231926","231926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088286","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Care Leaver Covenant announced by his Department in October 2018, how many organisations have signed up to offer placement opportunities to young care leavers.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232062","232062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088287","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Care Leaver Covenant announced by his Department in October 2018, how many placements for (a) work experience, (b) internships and (c) apprenticeships have been made available to young care leavers under that strategy to date.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232063","232063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088289","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many separate health and safety incident reporting processes are in use by staff working in each prison in England and Wales.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232067","232067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088291","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of monitoring systems for psychoactive substances in prisons.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232068","232068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088293","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with trade unions on the effectiveness of monitoring systems for psychoactive substances in prisons.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232069","232069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088295","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of staff working in prisons are (a) directly employed by HM Prison Service, (b) employed by an external contractor to deliver medical services and (c) employed by an external contractor to deliver education services.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232070","232070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088297","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of his Department’s spending on consultancy fees relating to the introduction of the new Prison Education Framework.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232071","232071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088298","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of spending by each prison in England and Wales on consultancy fees relating to the introduction of the new Prison Education Framework.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232072","232072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088300","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department last surveyed the characteristics of children and young people involved in crime.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232050","232050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088301","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department last made an assessment of the effect of poverty on youth crime.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232051","232051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088302","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 5 March 2019, Health and Disability Announcement, HCWS1376 and the extension of the contract for the Health and Disability Assessment Service, (a) what the value of that contract extension is, (b) what the terms of that contract extension are and (c) what performance targets have been set out in that contract extension.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232105","232105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088304","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, reference to the Written Statement of 5 March 2019, Health and Disability Announcement, HCWS1376, whether there will be a pilot of the integration of assessment services due to be implemented from 2021.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232106","232106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088306","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, reference to the Written Statement of 5 March 2019, Health and Disability Announcement, HCWS1376, what estimate she has made of the cost by budget headline of the integration of assessment services due to be implemented from 2021.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232107","232107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088308","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, reference to the Written Statement of 5 March 2019, Health and Disability Announcement, HCWS1376, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its new single digital platform is accessible to ill and disabled people.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232108","232108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088309","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement, of 5 March 2019, HLWS1343, how many ill and disabled people will be involved in her Department’s test on sanctions and conditionality; and what steps her Department plans to take in response to the conclusions of that test.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232109","232109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088311","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that sixth form colleges have adequate funding to offer courses in modern foreign languages.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231958","231958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088312","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that sixth form colleges have adequate funding to offer courses in all STEM subjects.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231959","231959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088314","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking ensure that sixth form colleges receive adequate funding to offer (a) student support and (b) extra-curricular activities.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231960","231960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088315","2019-03-18","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to engage with head teachers who have expressed concerns with respect to reductions in school funding.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232064","232064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088316","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of people who are currently awaiting the outcome of a mandatory reconsideration of a work capability assessment.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232056","232056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088318","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people awaiting the outcome of a mandatory reconsideration of an award after a personal independence payment assessment.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232057","232057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088319","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the average waiting time for people for a mandatory reconsideration of their award after a work capability assessment in each of the last five months.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232058","232058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088320","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the average amount of time people waited for a mandatory reconsideration of their award after a personal independence payment assessment in each of the last five months.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232059","232059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088321","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of EU citizens with a criminal record eligible to apply for (a) pre-settled status and (b) settled status.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232082","232082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088323","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the average waiting time at assessment centres in the most recent period for which figures are available; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232052","232052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088324","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether an applicant for (a) pre-settled and (b) settled status whose application has been refused on criminal records grounds is entitled to appeal that decision in the event that the UK leaves the EU (i) with and (ii) without a deal.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232083","232083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088326","2019-03-15","Department for International Development","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the process for charities to bid for funding from her Department on (a) the ability of specialist organisations to successfully bid for such funding and (b) women that are potential benefactors of that funding.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232049","232049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088327","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, at what stage an applicant for (a) pre-settled and (b) settled status whose application is denied on criminal records grounds would become an unlawful resident.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232084","232084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088329","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the prevelance of (a) stress, (b) loneliness, (c) anxiety, and (d) substance misuse among undergraduate students.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231917","231917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088330","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2019 to Question 228159 on Saudi Arabia: Military Aid, whether UK military personnel alerted the chain of command of any suspected violations of international humanitarian law by the Royal Saudi Airforce since the March 2015 intervention in the civil war in Yemen.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232088","232088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088332","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the refusal rate has been for applications for visitor visas from Pakistan in (a) each of the last (a) three years and (b) three months.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232042","232042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088333","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the steps the Government is taking to ensure that victims of serious crimes receive more frequent updates on the progress of their cases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232017","232017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088335","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of private sector probation companies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232018","232018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088336","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish statistics by (a) age and (b) gender of prison officers recruited in each of the last three years; and what the retention rate has been of prison officers in that same time period.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232019","232019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088338","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of violent crimes that involved the use of a (a) firearm and (b) knife in (i) Coventry, (ii) the West Midlands and (iii) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231899","231899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088341","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the financial sustainability of local authority children’s services departments.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231962","231962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088342","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes in the level of funding for children’s services on (a) schools, (b) the police and (c) the NHS.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231963","231963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088344","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the change in the level of funding per child for children’s services on the number of (a) children in need (b) child protection plans and (c) looked after children since 2010.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231964","231964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088345","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of NHS trusts in England that have outsourced cancer treatment services, in part or in whole, to private sector providers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231900","231900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088347","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the the effect of the change in the level of funding for children’s services in West Lancashire on the number of (a) referrals to children’s services; (b) re-referrals within 12 months, (c) children in need, (d) child protection enquiries, (e) child protection plans and (f) looked after children since 2010.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231965","231965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088349","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the sustainability of local authority children’s services budgets.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231966","231966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088351","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the correlation between funding for children’s services between 2010-11 and 2017-18 and the number of (a) referrals to children’s services, (b) re-referrals within 12 months, (c) children in need, (d) child protection enquiries, (e) child protection plans and (f) looked after children.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231967","231967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088352","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the overspend by local authorities on children’s services spending in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18; and how much additional funding was allocated to children’s services in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17 and (iii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231968","231968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088354","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have made representations to his Department on the sustainability of the provision of children’s services.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231969","231969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088355","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's budget was for its Dynamic Purchasing System for employment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231938","231938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088357","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent by her Department through its Dynamic Purchasing System for employment by each constituency in north Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231939","231939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088358","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which organisations were allocated funding through her Department's Dynamic Purchasing System for employment in each of the last five years; and what the value was of that funding so received for each of those organisations.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231940","231940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088359","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been referred onto the Work and Health programme by her Department's work coaches.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231941","231941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088361","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people have been referred to Remploy through her Department's Work and Health programme.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231942","231942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088362","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of her Department's work coaches have referred people to the Work and Health programme.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231943","231943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088364","2019-03-18","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to reduce levels of stress in the civil service.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231901","231901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088365","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for his Department to announce plans for future refugee resettlement programmes ahead of the conclusion of the Vulnerable Person’s Resettlement Scheme in 2020.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232093","232093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088367","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities to maintain their current capacity to resettle refugees.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232094","232094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088368","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment has been made of the ability of refugees arriving through the resettlement programmes to access universal credit on the day of their arrival.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232095","232095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088370","2019-03-18","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the White Paper entitled The UK’s future skills-based immigration system, published in December 2018, what additional funding his Department plans to make available to support their English language strategy beyond the current English Language Co-ordination Fund; and on what basis those funds will be allocated.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232096","232096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088372","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with his Saudi Arabian counterpart on conditions in Saudi Arabian prisons for women's rights activists.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231902","231902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088374","2019-03-18","Department for International Trade","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will publish the (a) white list of countries to which UK companies can ship Category C military goods under OGTC licences, (b) number of licences granted each year since 2010 and (c) names of the countries in which the end user for those licences is based.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232089","232089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088375","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Government's objectives are in participating in the NATO Allied Command Transformation programme.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231877","231877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088377","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British Army officers at the rank of colonel and above are currently attached to NATO Transformation Command; what ranks they are; and what roles they are performing at NATO Transformation Command.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231878","231878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088378","2019-03-18","Department for International Trade","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the automotive sector on the potential economic effect of the imposition of tariffs in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231903","231903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088380","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the practice of schools closing before the end of the school day on Fridays.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232026","232026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088381","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229147 on Buildings: Insulation, whether his Department plans to test the higher-risk scenario of high-pressure laminate panels with combustible insulation behind them.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232020","232020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088383","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229147 on Buildings: Insulation, whether in the event that that test results in failure his Department will advise that all buildings with that combination of materials be stripped of combustible cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232021","232021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088384","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229147 on Buildings: Insulation, whether in the event that that combination of materials passes that test his Department will conduct further large-scale tests with high-pressure laminate panels and combustible insulation materials as took place with aluminum composite material cladding in summer 2017.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232022","232022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088385","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229147 on Buildings: Insulation, whether his Department has estimated the number of buildings with high-pressure laminate cladding and stone wool insulation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232023","232023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088387","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229147 on Buildings: Insulation if he will inform the House before that test is conducted.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232024","232024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088388","2019-03-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report entitled Families and Food in Hard Times: rising food poverty and the importance of children's experience, published by SPERI in 2018, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that wages and social benefits are in combination adequate to provide socially acceptable levels of eating and living.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231930","231930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088391","2019-03-18","Department for Transport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2019 to Question 221797 on Roads: Accidents, if his Department will make an assessment of the merits of recording the number of road accidents attributed to glare from (a) LED and (b) halogen bulbs in car headlights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232053","232053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088392","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Algerian counterparts on the postponed presidential elections in that country.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231912","231912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088394","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential for civil unrest as a result of the postponed Algerian presidential elections.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231913","231913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088395","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to raise the national funding rate for 16 to 18 year old students (a) to £4,760 a year or (b) in line with inflation.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231914","231914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088397","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times stop and search was used by Lancashire Constabulary in 2018; and (a) how many convictions there were for crimes involving the use of knives and (b) how many of those convictions resulted from arrests following stop and search in Lancashire in 2018.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231915","231915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088398","2019-03-18","Department for International Trade","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the needs of the NHS in negotiating future trade deals.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231970","231970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088400","2019-03-18","Department for International Development","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent since 2017 on landmine clearance; how many landmines have been cleared with that funding; and what proportion of those landmines were (a) manufactured landmines and (b) improved explosive devices.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232097","232097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088401","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the valproate pregnancy prevention programme in reducing the number of children born with birth defects and persistent developmental disorders.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232043","232043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088402","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made on the number of healthcare professionals that are not complying with the requirements of the valproate pregnancy prevention programme.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232044","232044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088403","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of link between birth defects and persistent developmental disorders and fathers taking valproate at the time of conception.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232045","232045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088405","2019-03-15","Department for International Development","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to ensure that its work on landmines will be updated to include appropriate responses to the rise in the global use of improvised explosive devices.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232098","232098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088406","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that student accomodation is fit for habitation.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232086","232086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088408","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the economy of plastic pollution.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231992","231992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088409","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Equality and Human Rights Commission's findings following its investigation into the fire at Grenfell Tower.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232087","232087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088411","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money his Department has allocated for the reduction of single use plastics.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231993","231993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088412","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money has been made available to increase recycling from (a) residential waste and (b) trade waste.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231994","231994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088414","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been allocated from the Borderlands Growth Deal to (a) Carlisle City Council, (b) Cumbria County Council, (c) Dumfries and Galloway Council, (d) Northumberland County Council and (e) Scottish Borders Council.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232041","232041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088415","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the accelerated planning Green Paper.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231908","231908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088417","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018 on Spring Statement, HCWS540, what the timescale is for the Response to consultation on Planning Reform.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231909","231909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088418","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2019 to Question 207185 on Cannabis: Medical Treatments, whether data on prescriptions of cannabis-based medicinal products will (a) be published in the public domain, (b) include UK-wide data and (c) include the numbers of people obtaining a such a prescription.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232047","232047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088419","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the Independent Report on Build Out Rates.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231910","231910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088420","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2019 to Question 207185 on Cannabis: Medical Treatments, whether data on prescriptions of cannabis-based medicinal products will include (a) the type of product prescribed, (b) the indication that product was prescribed for and (c) the number of those such prescriptions by NHS clinical commissioning group area.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232048","232048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088422","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish further detail on the proposed Future Homes Standard.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231911","231911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088423","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much capital expenditure has been incurred by his Department for removing asbestos from school buildings in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232027","232027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088425","2019-03-18","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Spring Statement 2019, when he plans to publish details of the funding announced for the provision of free sanitary products in schools and colleges.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232028","232028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088426","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to implement the Government’s Tackling Antimicrobial Resistance Action Plan 2019-2024; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231971","231971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088428","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools built in phase one of the Priority Schools Building Programme had sprinkler systems fitted for fire safety.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232029","232029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088429","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the level of annual Dart Charge (a) road user charge and (b) enforcement write-offs in respect of the Dartford-Thurrock river crossing since the introduction of the Dart Charge in November 2014.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231988","231988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088431","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of annual write-offs have related to penalty charges not issued on a timely basis since the introduction of the Dart Charge in November 2014.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231989","231989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088432","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what penalty clauses are in place in the Dart Charge operator’s contract in relation to penalty charges not issued on a timely basis.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231990","231990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088434","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the protocol is for the annual write-off of irrecoverable Dart Charge debts; and whether there is ministerial sign-off of those debts.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231991","231991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088435","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2019 to Question 229815 on Tomography: Procurement, what estimate he has made of the change in cost to the NHS of scanning services as a result of the procurement of PET-CT scanning provision.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232100","232100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088437","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Spring Statement, how much additional funding he has allocated for the provision of free sanitary products in secondary schools and colleges in the 2019-20 academic year.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232030","232030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088438","2019-03-18","Department for International Trade","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the publication entitled UK Trade in Numbers, published on 26 February 2019.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232101","232101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088440","2019-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of ring-fencing Medical Research Council funds for biomedical research into ME in order to ensure that overall research funding for ME is proportional to that spent on research into similarly prevalent health conditions.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231931","231931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088441","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the number of jobs that will be created for UK-resident (a) seafarers and (b) divers at the (i) transportation, (ii) installation, (iii) construction and (iv) maintenance phases of the Inch Cape Offshore Wind Farm; and what recent assurances he has sought from Red Rock Power regarding the contractors engaged to carry out each phase of work.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231985","231985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088443","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of employment practices of shipping companies contracted to work in the offshore wind sector on employment levels for UK-resident seafarer (a) Ratings and (b) Officers.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231986","231986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088444","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of medical training bodies on ensuring that training programs for doctors, nurses and other health professionals include the most up to date guidance on diagnosis and appropriate treatment of myalgic encephalomyelitis.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231932","231932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088446","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that UK employment law applies to shipping companies contracted to (a) transport, (b) install, (c) construct and (d) maintain offshore wind farms on the UK Continental Shelf.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231987","231987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088447","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 4.25 of the Office for Budget Responsibility's Economic and Fiscal Outlook, published in March 2019, if he will publish the most recent data by (a) percentile and (b) decile relating to mean total pay.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232085","232085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088449","2019-03-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timescale is for the conclusion and response to the Telcoms Supply Chain Review.","Biography information for Mr Bob Seely","Mr Bob Seely","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232110","232110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088450","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with NICE on bringing forward the release of the revised NICE guidelines on ME, due to be published in October 2020.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231933","231933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088452","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with NICE on issuing an interim warning on the potential dangers of graded exercise therapy (GET) as a treatment for ME, prior to issuing its revised guideline in October 2020.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231934","231934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088454","2019-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the financial benefit of the EU's Creative Europe programme to the UK creative arts industries.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232060","232060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088456","2019-03-18","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many incidents of knife crime there were in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland, and (d) Northern Ireland in each of the last nine years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231918","231918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088457","2019-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an estimate of the cost to the public purse of continuing to participate in the European Union's Creative Europe programme after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232061","232061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088459","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy,  what estimate he has made of the amount of funding as a percentage of GDP that was allocated to research and development by (a) Government, (b) public sector organisations excluding local authorities and (c)the  private sector in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231919","231919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088460","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding the Government has allocated to research into (a) photonics and (b) optoelectronics in each (a) nation and (b) region of the UK in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231920","231920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088463","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2019 to Question 229815 on Tomography: Procurement, through what methods NHS England drew attention to the public engagement process to test the phase II procurement approach for PET-CT scanning services.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232102","232102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088465","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's Void Reduction Plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231882","231882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088466","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2019 to Question 229815 on Tomography: Procurement, whether NHS England has sought any further public engagement on the procurement of PET-CT scanning services since 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232103","232103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088467","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of (a) the sentience of decapod crustaceans and (b) their capability to feel pain; whether decapod crustaceans are included in the definition of animal in the draft sentience Bill; and when he plans to publish the Farm Animal Welfare Council investigation into decapod crustacean sentience.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231995","231995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088468","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the change has been in the total number of full time equivalent police officers in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231890","231890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088469","2019-03-18","Attorney General","2019-03-13","To ask the Attorney General, what the change has been in the level of funding allocated to the Crown Prosecution Service in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231891","231891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088470","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of those released under investigation by the police in the last 12 months for which figures are available had no case brought against them.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231944","231944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088471","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were released under investigation by the police in the most recent 12-month period for which figures are available by each police authority.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231945","231945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088472","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures are in place to monitor compliance with bail conditions.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231946","231946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088473","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time is for a person who has been released under investigation to be contacted by an investigating officer.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231947","231947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088474","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total value has been of government spending on subsidies for the manufacture and purchase of low emission and electric vehicles in (a) 2010-11 and (b) 2018-19.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232031","232031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088475","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether interviews are recorded when a person is interviewed by the police without legal representation.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231948","231948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088476","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions for motoring offences were pursued by the police (a) overall and (b) in each police force area in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231892","231892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088477","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with gestational diabetes in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231937","231937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088478","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) patients and (b) members of the public took part in the two webinars related to the procurement process of PET-CT scanning services.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232104","232104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088479","2019-03-18","Department for International Development","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many members of staff of her Department have been seconded to other government departments or agencies to work on preparations for the UK’s withdrawal from the EU in each month since those secondments first commenced by (a) civil service grade and (b) destination department.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231879","231879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088480","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, (a) on how many occasions and (b) on what dates the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Children and Families has visited (i) a maintained nursery school, (ii) a private, voluntary and independent nursery, (iii) a children's centre and (iv) any other childcare setting since his appointment to that role.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232065","232065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088481","2019-03-18","Department for International Development","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with (a) trade unions and (b) other associations representing staff of her Department on secondments of her Department's staff to work on matters relating to the UK's withdrawal from the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231880","231880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088482","2019-03-18","Department for International Development","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on her Department's performance against its aims and objectives of the secondment of staff of her Department to other government departments to work on matters relating to the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231881","231881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088483","2019-03-18","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer 18 February 2019 to Question 220061, if he will publish the figures based on the Crime Survey for England and Wales for the number of reported offences for each crime type in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231893","231893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088484","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has visited an immigration removal centre since his appointment as Home Secretary.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232066","232066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088485","2019-03-18","Department for International Trade","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, for what reason (a) article 4 of the Trade and Partnership Agreement between the UK Government and the Government of Israel describes the territoriality of only the UK and (b) the territoriality of Israel is referred to only in the explanatory memorandum; what legal force the explanatory memorandum has; and what assurances the Government has given to the state of Israel on accepting the territorial limitation of that UK-Israel agreement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231955","231955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088486","2019-03-18","Department for International Trade","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Trade and Partnership Agreement between UK Government and the Government of the State of Israel presented to Parliament in February 2019, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the provisions of the UK-Israel Agreement are not applied to Israeli settlements in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231956","231956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088487","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March to Question 223963, what progress his Department has made on reducing the level of violence in prisons.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231894","231894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088488","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that maths and English education in prisons is appropriate for individuals with specific learning difficulties.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231895","231895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088489","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she plans to take to grant Trusted Agent Status to Local Authority Welfare Officers in order to help them to assist universal credit claimants.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232074","232074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088490","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of including the category of veterans in the Mental Health Services Data Set.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231996","231996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088491","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what comparative assessment he has made of the effect of learning difficulties on offenders' (a) probability of serving a custodial sentence and (b) rates of recidivism.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231896","231896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088492","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to promote public awareness of the risk to health of using barbeques in enclosed spaces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232007","232007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088493","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many public health funerals there have been since 2010; and what the cost to the public purse has been of those funerals.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232037","232037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088494","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to support festival providers in safeguarding people attending festivals from the risks of carbon monoxide poisoning; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232008","232008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088495","2019-03-18","Department for International Trade","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what provisions there are in the Trade and Partnership Agreement between the UK Government and the Government of Israel for monitoring the adherence by both parties to duties to respect democratic principles and human rights; how respect for democratic principles and human rights is defined; whether those rights are based on (a) international and (b) European law; whether respect for democratic principles and human rights (i) is limited to the territories of each party or (ii) includes territories annexed or under the control of each party; and what the effect on the agreement is of one party not respecting democratic principles and human rights.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231957","231957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088496","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April 2018 to Question 137044 on Undocumented Workers: Construction, how many of the 85 potential victims of trafficking identified during Operation Magnify who were arrested prior to being identified were subsequently detained; and for which offences the detention took place.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231997","231997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088497","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his plans are for the future of NHS England’s Commissioning through Evaluation programme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231897","231897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088498","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the regional variation in the uptake of MedTech products across the NHS.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231898","231898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088499","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether immigration detainees have access to free independent interpreting services during appointments with medical staff in immigration removal centres.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231998","231998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088500","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether immigration removal centre staff receive training on indicators of trafficking and modern slavery; and what information is covered in that training.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231999","231999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088501","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether UK Visas and Immigration staff receive mandatory training on (a) identifying signs of exploitation and (b) what actions to take if exploitation is identified; and what information is covered in this training.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232000","232000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088502","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the additional funds for tackling knife crime announced in the Spring Statement will be allocated to (a) the seven police forces with the highest rise in knife crime, (b) Nottinghamshire Police Force and (c) other police forces.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231907","231907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088503","2019-03-18","Wales Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many times he has met with trade unions in Wales since July 2016.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232038","232038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088504","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the £100m in additional funding for 2019-20 to tackle serious violence announced in the Spring Statement will be allocated to each police force.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232003","232003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088505","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much of the £100m additional funding in 2019-20 to tackle serious violence will be allocated to the Metropolitan Police.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232004","232004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088506","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of problem gambling on mental ill health.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232039","232039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088507","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to stop the far right radicalising young people online.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232040","232040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088508","2019-03-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Justice of 4 March 2019, Official Report, column 698 on the Privatised Probation System, when he plans to meet with the hon. Member for Sefton and the family of Sam Cook.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232002","232002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088509","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when HMRC plans to publish details of the process for retailers to apply for their (a) economic identifier and (b) facilities identifier codes for the Tobacco Track and Trace system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231980","231980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088510","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will extend by 12 months the implementation date of 20 May 2019 for the Tobacco Track and Trace system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231981","231981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088511","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Immigration Removal Centre staff receive training on identifying vulnerable adults based on his Department's adults at risk in immigration detention policy.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232001","232001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088512","2019-03-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) RAF personnel and (b) BAE Systems personnel seconded under Government-to-Government agreements work in direct support of Royal Saudi Air Force operational squadrons engaged in the war in Yemen; what the functions are of those personnel; and what restrictions are placed on their support for active operations.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232090","232090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088513","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report entitled the Disability Price Tag 2019, published by Scope in February 2019, what steps she plans to take to made additional funding available to cover potential extra costs incurred by disabled people; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232032","232032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088514","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report entitled the Disability Price Tag 2019, published by Scope in February 2019, what steps she is taking to ensure that disabled people can afford the same standard of living as non-disabled people.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232033","232033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088515","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report entitled the Disability Price Tag 2019, published by Scope in February 2019, what steps she is taking to ensure that personal independence payments assessments accurately capture the extra costs incurred by disabled people.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232034","232034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088516","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will extend the provisions of the Universal Credit (Transitional Provisions) (SDP Gateway) Amendment Regulations 2019 to claimants in receipt of (a) disability premiums and (b) enhanced disability premiums.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232035","232035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088517","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report entitled the Disability Price Tag 2019, published by Scope in February 2019, what steps she is taking to ensure that families with disabled children moving on to universal credit receive the same financial support that they did under the legacy benefits system.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232036","232036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088518","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 216183 on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Buildings, for what reasons his Department owns two properties with an asset value of over £5 million in Buenos Aires.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231949","231949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088519","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 216183 on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Buildings, for what reasons his Department owns two properties with an asset value of over £5 million in Kampala.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231950","231950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088520","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what deadline is to implement the new online system to submit Access to Work signed claim forms with invoices.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231984","231984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088521","2019-03-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 216183 on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Buildings, for what reasons his Department owns four properties with an asset value of over £5 million in Paris.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231951","231951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088522","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2018 to Question 122336 on Orkambi, whether he has made an estimate of the potential savings accruing to the public purse from reduced hospital admissions in the event that Orkambi is made available on the NHS.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232091","232091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088523","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2018 to Question 122358 on Orkambi: Republic of Ireland, whether he has had further discussions with his Irish counterpart on the cost-effectiveness of Orkambi in treating cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232092","232092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088524","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what equalities assessment his Department has undertaken on access to student finance for individuals of Muslim faith.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231952","231952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088525","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of alternative funding arrangements for student finance that is compatible with sharia law for individuals of Muslim faith.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231953","231953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088526","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what funding he is making available to enforce the Marine Protection Area around Ascension Island announced in the Spring Statement.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232111","232111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088527","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what back-up power generation systems are in place for NHS Digital; and when they were last tested under load.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232078","232078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088528","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether a central register of back-up generators at NHS hospitals is maintained by his Department.","Biography information for Gareth Snell","Gareth Snell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232079","232079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088529","2019-03-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how the Construction Sector Deal funding will be disbursed; and how he plans to assess the effect of that funding on that sector.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232010","232010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088530","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to increase funding for the British Business Bank to match the £2.1 billion invested by the European Investment Bank in the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232011","232011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088531","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2017 to Question 191916 on research: finance, how the Government plans to protect R&D funding after the end of the implementation period.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232012","232012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088532","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Spring Statement 2019, whether NPIF funding to the European Bioinformatics Institute refers to the Northern Powerhouse Investment Fund.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232013","232013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088533","2019-03-18","Treasury","2019-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for how long he plans to fund the JET nuclear fusion reactor.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232014","232014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088534","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department (a) has conducted or (b) plans to conduct an equality impact assessment on the proposal to increase police stop and search powers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232015","232015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088535","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the exemption for PhD-level roles from visa caps announced by the Chancellor of the Exchequer in his Spring Statement includes exemption from the minimum salary requirement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232016","232016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088536","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department’s Interim Assessment of the first year of the Independent Child Trafficking Advocates (ICTA) service, what assessment he has made of the merits of expanding the ICTA scheme to all unaccompanied and separated children.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232046","232046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088537","2019-03-18","Home Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much of the £100 million fund to tackle knife crime announced in the Spring Statement will be allocated to the Metropolitan Police.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232073","232073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088538","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to footnote 7 on page 4 of the Policy Statement: Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education, and Personal, Social Health and Economic Education, published in March 2017, what the evidential basis was for the statement that providing a parent with a blanket right to withdraw their child from sex education is no longer consistent with English case law, or with the ECHR and UNCRC; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231871","231871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088539","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  with reference to footnote 7 on page 4 of the Policy Statement: Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education, and Personal, Social Health and Economic Education, published in March 2017, if he will list those English cases that necessitate the proposed limitation on the right of parental withdrawal from sex education in secondary schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231872","231872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088540","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to footnote 7 on page 4 of the Policy Statement: Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education, and Personal, Social Health and Economic Education, published in March 2017, when the current right of withdrawal ceased to be compatible with the European Convention on Human Rights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231873","231873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088541","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  with reference to footnote 7 on page 4 of the Policy Statement: Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education, and Personal, Social Health and Economic Education, published in March 2017, when the current right of withdrawal ceased to be compatible with the United States Convention on the Rights of the Child; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231874","231874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088542","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 69 on pages 16 to 17 of Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education and Health Education in England Government consultation response, published in February 2019, what the evidential basis was for the statement that the current legislation contains a right to withdrawn which is no longer compatible with English caselaw and the European Convention on Human Rights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231875","231875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088543","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 69 on pages 16 to 17 of Relationships Education, Relationships and Sex Education, and Health Education in England Government consultation response, published in February 2019, whether it is his policy to ensure that all pupils should be given the opportunity to opt out of, as well as into, sex education lessons from three terms before they turn 16, regardless of the wishes of their parents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231876","231876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088544","2019-03-18","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants received exit payments in excess of £95,000 in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231883","231883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088545","2019-03-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local government employees have received exit payments in excess of £95,000 since 1 January 2017.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231884","231884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088546","2019-03-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS employees received exit payments in excess of £95,000 in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231885","231885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088547","2019-03-15","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants received exit payments in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018; and what the (i) average and (ii) highest payment was in each of those years.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231886","231886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088548","2019-03-18","Cabinet Office","2019-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost to the public purse was of exit payments paid to civil servants in excess of £95,000 in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231887","231887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087039","2019-03-14","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many chartered accountants his Department currently employs.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231410","231410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087040","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will made an assessment of trends in the level of (a) bullying and (b) harassment of people with autism in the workplace.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231511","231511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087041","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the PACE trial of therapies on reducing the effects of (a) myalgic encephalomyelitis and (b) chronic fatigue syndrome.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231512","231512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087043","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to allocate funding for the ten-year review of progress on reducing health inequalities since the publication of the report entitled Fair Society, Healthy Lives, published by Michael Marmot.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231513","231513"
