"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76516","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the rolling stock maintenance arrangements will be for the franchise agreement with NXET Trains Ltd for rail passenger services on the Essex Thameside line.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204533","204533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76517","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of assaults on (a) staff and (b) customers on public transport in the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204526","204526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76518","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which rail lines and services broadband improvements will be financed from the £53.1 million fine imposed on Network Rail by the Office of Rail Regulation.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204506","204506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76519","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the new trains due to be introduced during the new franchise agreement with NXET Trains Ltd for rail passenger services on the Essex Thameside line will equipped with accommodation for a train guard.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204583","204583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76520","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many air accidents in the UK in the last five years arose from (a) pilot error and (b) mechanical breakdown.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204556","204556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76521","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many new (a) automatic ticket gates and (b) ticket vending machines will be introduced at stations on the Essex Thameside route under the terms of the new franchise agreement with NXET Trains Ltd for rail passenger services.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204587","204587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76522","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the planned investment in stations on the Essex Thameside line during the new franchise agreement with NXET Trains Ltd will be funded by the (a) franchisee, (b) Network Rail and (c) the public sector in each case.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204532","204532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76523","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what safeguards there are in the new franchise agreement on the Essex Thameside line with NXET Trains Ltd against unsafe reductions in staff over the life of the agreement.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204586","204586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76524","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with NXET Trains Ltd about minimum levels of (a) on-train, (b) station and (c) ticket office staffing levels in each year of the new franchise agreement for rail passenger services on the Essex Thameside line; and what current staffing levels are in each such category on the line.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204584","204584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76525","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the costs of planned investment in (a) Wi-Fi access on trains, (b) provision of customer information and (c) SMART ticketing technology during the new franchise agreement with NXET Trains Ltd for passenger services on the Essex Thameside line; what proportion of each category of funding will fall to (i) the franchisee, (ii) Network Rail and (iii) the public sector.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204530","204530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76526","2014-07-14","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with NXET Trains Ltd over plans to make staff more visible at stations on the Essex Thameside line during the term of the new franchise agreement for rail passenger services.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204585","204585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76527","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total annual public sector payment will be in each year to 2029 under the new franchise agreement for rail passenger services on the Essex Thameside line.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204531","204531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76533","2014-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to speed up the appeals process for people whose benefits have been sanctioned.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204674","204674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76534","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what action his Department is taking to address the exploitation of low-skilled workers.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204527","204527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76535","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) male and (b) female benefit claimants in (i) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency, (ii) Scotland and (iii) the UK have been sanctioned in the last (A) six months and (B) 12 months.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204521","204521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76536","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of wage incentives claimed by employers who have recruited employees aged 16-24 through the Work Programme or Jobcentre Plus in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204633","204633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76537","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of 18 to 24 year olds who have started a work experience placement whilst claiming jobseeker's allowance (JSA) were not claiming JSA within six months of starting the placement.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204628","204628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76538","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the number of people aged between 16 and 24 who are not in employment or training and are not claiming jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204630","204630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76539","2014-07-14","Cabinet Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the proportion of young people who left and subsequently returned to claiming jobseeker's allowance within six months in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204631","204631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76540","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what processes his Department has agreed to enable housing associations to be informed when tenants migrate to universal credit.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204415","204415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76541","2014-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the independent review of jobseeker's allowance sanctions being conducted by Matthew Oakley to be laid before Parliament.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204479","204479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76542","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) males and (b) females in Kilmarnock and Loudoun are enrolled in the National Employment Savings Trust.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204520","204520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77063","2014-07-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve the service complaints system.","Biography information for Duncan Hames","Duncan Hames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904805","904805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77504","2014-07-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on prescribing anti-malarial prophylaxis to members of the armed forces serving overseas.","Biography information for Mr David Heath","Mr David Heath","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904820","904820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77505","2014-07-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects to announce a decision on the normal pension age for workers in the Defence Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904806","904806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77506","2014-07-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to meet his Belgian counterpart to discuss the procurement of F-35 Joint Striker Fighters by that country.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904818","904818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77507","2014-07-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent representations he has received regarding reductions in expenditure on the Army.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904819","904819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78279","2014-07-16","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps the Government is taking to tackle youth unemployment in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904828","904828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65960","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote the Open Access academic publishing movement in the UK.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204123","204123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65961","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress he has made in negotiations with private publishers on the confidentiality clauses negotiated by them when supplying university libraries.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204124","204124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65962","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what work the Life Science Investment Organisation is doing to promote the life sciences sector in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204143","204143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65963","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014, Official Report, column 536W, on business: Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the success of the recent roadshow his Department co-hosted to promote the delivery of the British Business Bank in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204144","204144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65964","2014-07-10","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with banks about the consequences for a mortgage application of taking out a payday loan.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204209","204209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65965","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will review existing trade descriptions legislation and its effect on regulating companies that describe themselves or hold themselves to be acting as legal firms.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204154","204154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65966","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to encourage businesses to engage with schools so that students develop a more practical understanding of business.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204193","204193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65967","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether public sector organisations from the devolved administrations have been invited to participate in Healthcare UK's Business Forum for stakeholders on 24 July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204220","204220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65968","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204288","204288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65969","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204269","204269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65970","2014-07-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of apprenticeships commenced in the last 12 months were with (a) small and medium-sized enterprises, (b) larger firms, (c) public sector employers and (d) voluntary sector employers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204315","204315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65971","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204318","204318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65972","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204336","204336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65973","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to make additional provision for adult education in places where centres such as Learn Direct are being closed down.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204360","204360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65974","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204337","204337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65975","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in (a) his Department and (b) the Prime Minister's Office since 2010 were previously (i) political appointees within that Department or Office and (ii) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204362","204362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65976","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 506W, on official visits, what domestic visits each of the Ministers of his Department has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204377","204377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65977","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Prime Minister's Office spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204306","204306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65978","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what occasions (a) each Minister within his Department and (b) the Prime Minister has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204308","204308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65979","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204270","204270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65980","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse was (a) in total, (b) of wine served at, (c) of food served at and (d) of catering staff working at the Best of British Creative Industries reception on 30 June 2014; and which ministers attended that event.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204246","204246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65981","2014-07-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-07","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what guidance the Minister of State for Cities and Constitution has given to local enterprise partnerships on informing (a) district councils and (b) hon. Members about Growth Deal schemes before briefing the media; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204251","204251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65982","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions officials from his Department have held with their counterparts in the Northern Ireland Office about that Department accepting placements from the Civil Service fast stream programme.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204147","204147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65983","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to tackle copycat websites which are charging for free Government services.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204211","204211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65984","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent meetings he has had with internet search engine companies on steps to tackle copycat websites which are charging for free Government services.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204213","204213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65985","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of savings to businesses in (a) the UK, (b) the Thames Valley and (c) Windsor constituency as a result of the Red Tape Challenge.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204115","204115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65986","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will request UK Financial Investments Ltd to investigate the reasons why banks in receipt of financial support from the public purse have used deceptive practices to recover loans through sending of the letters purporting to be from law firms which do not exist.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204120","204120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65987","2014-07-10","Cabinet Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the aggregate household debt was in the final quarter of the 2013-14 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204217","204217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65988","2014-07-10","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce a derelict land tax.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204221","204221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65989","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications have been submitted from Northern Ireland for the Help to Buy mortgage guarantee scheme since January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204227","204227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65990","2014-07-10","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the (a) compliance and (b) performance of Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited following HM Revenue and Custom's last audit of such compliance and performance of Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited in respect of the Annual PM Schedule under 17.1(a) of the Private Finance Initiative contract between HM Revenue and Customs and Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204244","204244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65991","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when HM Revenue and Customs last audited the (a) compliance and (b) performance of Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited in respect of the Annual PM Schedule, under 17.1(a) of the Private Finance Initiative contract between HM Revenue and Customs and Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204245","204245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65992","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204303","204303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65993","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204285","204285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65994","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 675W, on official visits, what domestic visits each of the Ministers of his Department has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204368","204368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65995","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204352","204352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65996","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204333","204333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65997","2014-07-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204319","204319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65998","2014-07-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204338","204338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65999","2014-07-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the introduction of selective licensing in relevant areas and the level of private-sector rates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Richard Ottaway","Sir Richard Ottaway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204242","204242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66000","2014-07-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204271","204271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66001","2014-07-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish the conclusions of its review of property conditions in the private rented sector; and whether his Department plans to restrict borough-wide selective licensing schemes.","Biography information for Sir Richard Ottaway","Sir Richard Ottaway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204243","204243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66002","2014-07-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204289","204289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66003","2014-07-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many onshore wind development planning applications that had been considered by local planning authorities were subsequently called in by his Department in each of the five years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204131","204131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66004","2014-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will discuss with the Football Association the development of safe standing areas in Premiership Club grounds.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204214","204214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66005","2014-07-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether mobile data services will be expanded in Northern Ireland as part of the Mobile Infrastructure Project.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204228","204228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66006","2014-07-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of how many households in Northern Ireland will benefit from each phase of the Mobile Infrastructure Project; and what the current expected date of completion is for each phase of that project in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204229","204229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66007","2014-07-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204290","204290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66008","2014-07-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what level of funding has been allocated by his Department to projects in Northern Ireland under the Mobile Infrastructure Project.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204239","204239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66009","2014-07-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204272","204272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66010","2014-07-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the financial benefit to (a) Essex and (b) the East of England arising from the launch of the Tour de France.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204361","204361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66011","2014-07-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204339","204339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66012","2014-07-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204320","204320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66013","2014-07-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 665W, on official visits, what domestic visits each of the Ministers of his Department has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204376","204376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66014","2014-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Military Aviation Authority recommended that F-35B BK-3 should not transit the Atlantic Ocean in time for the Royal International Air Tattoo.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204371","204371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66015","2014-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost was of the extension of the C-17 Globemaster III sustainment package contract; and for how long that contract will run.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204369","204369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66016","2014-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions the Military Aviation Authority has recommended that the F-35B be (a) grounded and (b) restricted in operations; what the reason was for each such recommendation; and what the duration of the grounding or restriction was in each such case.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204370","204370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66017","2014-07-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204321","204321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66018","2014-07-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204340","204340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66019","2014-07-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204273","204273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66020","2014-07-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204291","204291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66021","2014-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2014, Official Report, column 221W, on Combined Cadet Force, if he will make an assessment of the effect of recruitment to existing community-based cadet forces.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204145","204145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66022","2014-07-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which military units and agencies are currently based at Imphal Barracks; how many square metres of accommodation they each occupy; whether his Department has any plans to close any of those units, or to move them away from Imphal Barracks; and if so which units are involved and what plans are under consideration.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204130","204130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66023","2014-07-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in providing accommodation for HQ1 Division in York what assumption his Department has made about how long the Divisional HQ will remain at Imphal Barracks.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204129","204129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66024","2014-07-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-07","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what representations or applications from Welsh cities to the City Deals Fund he has received.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204122","204122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66025","2014-07-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-07","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which cities in Wales have been allocated money from the City Deals fund.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204119","204119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66026","2014-07-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-07","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when the decision to extend City Deals funding beyond England was taken.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204121","204121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66027","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of an increase in the numbers of young people at school age on funding for provision for 16-18 year olds in each year of the next Parliament.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204208","204208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66028","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to regularly publish any (a) private equity, (b) private school business and (c) other business connections and interests of (i) current and (ii) former (A) senior public sector employees, (B) Ministers and politicans and (C) board members of his Department (1) promoting, (2) taking up board positions on and (3) involved in the running of academies and free schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204189","204189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66029","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what requirement there is to consult where an existing single academy trust wishes to become a multi-academy trust; what steps are taken when those requirements to consult are not met; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204191","204191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66030","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish any names his Department holds of (a) current and (b) former senior public employees and Ministers (i) promoting, (ii) taking up board positions on and (iii) involved in the running of academies and free schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204190","204190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66031","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications were received from academies to expand to meet parental demand as part of Round 1 of the Academies Capital Maintenance Fund 2014-15; and how many such applications were approved.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204264","204264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66032","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to reform school performance measures to include destination data and include the number of school students who enter employment or work-based training.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204197","204197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66033","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of secondary school students in Gloucestershire qualify for the pupil premium.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204206","204206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66034","2014-07-10","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the level of funding for each pupil aged 16 to 18 years old in each academic year until 2020.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204202","204202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66035","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204292","204292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66036","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204274","204274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66037","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204341","204341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66038","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204322","204322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66039","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued in relation to restrictions on types of food that may be served and consumed in publicly-funded faith schools.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204358","204358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66040","2014-07-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204323","204323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66041","2014-07-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204342","204342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66042","2014-07-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204275","204275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66043","2014-07-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204293","204293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66044","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204294","204294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66045","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204276","204276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66046","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204343","204343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66047","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204324","204324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66048","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the potential economic benefits of an ecologically coherent network of marine protected areas in UK waters.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204171","204171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66049","2014-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage farmers to extend the seasonal production of fresh fruit and vegetables.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204219","204219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66050","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the economic cost of the degradation of natural capital in the UK's marine environment.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204173","204173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66051","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the UK's seabed is protected from the fishing practice of bottom trawling.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204165","204165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66052","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the seabed within the UK's Exclusive Economic Zone is designated as marine protected areas; and what proportion of such areas exclude the fishing practice of bottom trawling.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204168","204168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66053","2014-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will introduce legislative proposals to enshrine the concept of a listed landscape.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204222","204222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66054","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his officials consulted their counterparts in the Northern Ireland Executive in preparation for the EU Agriculture and Fisheries Council on 16 and 17 June 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204177","204177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66055","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the decline in the bee population; what steps he is taking to tackle such a decline; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204117","204117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66056","2014-07-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will place in the Library a summary of his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser's latest analysis of the decline in the bee population.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204118","204118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66057","2014-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to deal with Argentine threats to the commercial sustainability of the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204128","204128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66058","2014-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to assist the Nigerian government in combating Al-Shabab and prevent the kidnap of young people.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204125","204125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66059","2014-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had on the prospects for India joining the nuclear non-proliferation treaty during his visit to that country in July 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204112","204112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66060","2014-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Burmese counterpart on ensuring the safety of foreign aid workers delivering essential assistance to displaced Rohingya Muslims in that country.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204169","204169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66061","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise at the UN the Amendment to the Protocol on the Statute of the African Court of Justice and Human Rights adopted at the 23rd Ordinary Session of the African Union.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204218","204218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66062","2014-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204325","204325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66063","2014-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204344","204344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66064","2014-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 639W, on official visits, what domestic visits each of the Ministers of his Department has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204374","204374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66065","2014-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204277","204277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66066","2014-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204295","204295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66067","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204296","204296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66068","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP practices have closed since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204309","204309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66069","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will re-establish the NHS Diabetes website.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204231","204231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66070","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether a compromise agreement has been reached, or is in the process of being reached, with the currently suspended chief executive of the Christie NHS Foundation Trust on the termination of her employment.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204260","204260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66071","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to impose a duty on local authorities to commission follow-up services to the NHS Health Check.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204237","204237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66072","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that whistleblowers willing to give evidence on allegations of wrongdoing at the Christie NHS Foundation Trust will not be victimised or otherwise suffer detriment from the Trust for so giving evidence.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204259","204259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66073","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to provide a separate follow-up service to the NHS Heath Check Programme.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204230","204230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66074","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to include a diabetes-related indicator in the Health Premium Incentive scheme; if he will consult the diabetes community on the design of that scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204232","204232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66075","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 566W, on NHS: inovations, to whom in the Prime Minister's Delivery Unit the Innovation, Health and Wealth programme has been reporting during the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204247","204247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66076","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, columns 566-7W, on NHS: intellectual property, what the name and job title is of the official in NHS England responsible for the intellectual property strategy of the NHS; and what the name and job title is of that official's line-manager.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204248","204248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66077","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 566W, on NHS: innovation, if his Department will publish the sunset review of innovation and improvement bodies before the House rises for the summer recess.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204249","204249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66078","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, columns 566-7W, on NHS: intellectual property, what data has been collected by NHS England on the effectiveness of the existing NHS intellectual property strategy to inform its review.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204250","204250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66079","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204278","204278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66080","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the level of (a) NHS expenditure and (b) other expenditure for which his Department is responsible has been for the (i) treatment and (ii) prevention of obesity in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204313","204313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66081","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were admitted to hospital with a (a) primary and (b) secondary diagnosis of liver disease in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204314","204314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66082","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with Public Health England on progress made by the BeClear Campaign to improve the detection of rare cancers over the last (a) six months and (b) year.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204310","204310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66083","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS trusts offer a screening programme of osteoporosis to reduce falls and fractures.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204311","204311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66084","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients diagnosed with rheumatoid arthritis received an annual review in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204312","204312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66085","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 566W, on NHS: innovation, when the Innovation, Health and Wealth Implementation Board has met during the last 12 months; what assessment he has made of progress on the Innovation, Health and Wealth programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204307","204307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66086","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204345","204345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66087","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204326","204326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66088","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve support for people with aphasia.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204363","204363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66089","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what financial assistance the NHS provides to NHS staff who have to (a) drive and (b) take public transport to work.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204359","204359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66090","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Chief Executive of Healthcare UK has met with officials from the Northern Ireland Executive to promote his organisation's work in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204195","204195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66091","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his Ministerial counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on promoting in Northern Ireland the support and services offered to healthcare providers by Healthcare UK.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204196","204196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66092","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Minister in his Department approved the transfer of commissioning responsibility for NHS Innovations hubs from the NHS Institute for Innovation and Improvement to strategic health authorities in 2009.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204167","204167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66093","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent work Healthcare UK has done to encourage healthcare providers in Northern Ireland to work with their British counterparts on bidding for overseas projects.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204194","204194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66094","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evidence was (a) received and (b) commissioned by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence prior to its recommendation to recommend the commissioning of branded weight loss programmes by NHS agencies.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204140","204140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66095","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of branded weight loss programmes in achieving healthy and sustainable weight loss.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204139","204139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66096","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what fees have been paid to (a) Apposite Capital LLP, (b) The Orchard Down Consultancy Ltd, (c) Mike Farrar Consulting Ltd and (d) the NHS Confederation for their work on the NHS Accelerator Fund project.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204164","204164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66097","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the likely effects of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership on the National Health Service.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204141","204141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66098","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, further to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, columns 566-7W, on NHS: intellectual property, what returns have been made by Commissioners determining which providers have passed or failed the Commissioning for Quality and Innovation pre-qualification thresholds in 2012-13 and 2013-14 since April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204180","204180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66099","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, further to his Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 278W, on haemolytic uraemic syndrome, when the next meeting of the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence's evaluation committee will take place; and how soon after that meeting he expects to place a copy of NHS England's response in the Library.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204175","204175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66100","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria he uses when considering whether to invite his counterparts from the devolved administrations to international health summits hosted by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204176","204176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66101","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, further to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, columns 566-7W, on NHS: intellectual property, whether the Innovation, Health and Wealth board will publish the review of NHS intellectual property before 23 July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204182","204182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66102","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Care Quality Commission has made in its thematic data review of diabetes care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204235","204235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66103","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct Monitor to publish its strategy for engaging with whistleblowers in its fact-finding investigation into alleged wrongdoing at the Christie NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204257","204257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66104","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Care Quality Commission plans to publish its thematic data review of diabetes care.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204236","204236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66105","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that no settlement is reached between the Christie NHS Foundation Trust and its chief executive, Caroline Shaw, on the termination of her employment until Monitor and the Care Quality Commission have concluded their current investigations into allegations of wrongdoing and published the outcome.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204258","204258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66106","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Care Quality Commission plans to use the findings from its thematic data review of diabetes care.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204234","204234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66107","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on allegations that tissue samples were sold by the Christie NHS Foundation Trust to pharmaceutical companies without the knowledge of the patients concerned; whether his attention was drawn to any such allegations; and what investigation his Department has (a) conducted and (b) plans to conduct into such allegations.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204255","204255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66108","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason the NHS Accelerator Fund and the development project were not put out to public tender.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204192","204192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66109","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the National Institute for Health Research has reported to his Department the results of the research commissioned on idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204216","204216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66110","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on bariatric surgery in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204132","204132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66111","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the role bariatric surgery has in achieving healthy and sustainable weight loss.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204133","204133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66112","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department evaluates the efficacy and cost-effectiveness of bariatric surgery.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204134","204134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66113","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on (a) Weight Watchers programmes, (b) Slimming World programmes and (c) any other branded weight loss programme in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204135","204135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66114","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on specialist eating disorder clinics in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204136","204136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66115","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulance calls were responded to by (a) the police and (b) the fire service in (i) England, (ii) Lancashire and (iii) Hyndburn constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204157","204157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66116","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the sufficiency and geographical distribution of NHS specialist eating disorder clinics.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204137","204137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66117","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department evaluates the efficacy and cost-effectiveness of branded weight loss programmes.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204138","204138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66118","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to address regional inequalities in health outcomes for interstitial lung disease in the last year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204151","204151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66119","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of ambulances responding to the most serious calls failed to respond within eight minutes in (a) England, (b) Lancashire and (c) the Hyndburn Constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204212","204212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66120","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the future of intellectual property in the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204188","204188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66121","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 566W, on NHS: innovation, what outputs and outcomes he uses to judge NHS England's compliance with its legal duty to promote innovation.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204186","204186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66122","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and the Secretary of State for Education on guidance to be issued to paediatricians on age assessments of unaccompanied migrant children.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204184","204184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66123","2014-07-14","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of levels of trust held by the British Muslim community in the Prevent strategy.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204223","204223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66124","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her timetable is for the decision on the use of police water cannon in Great Britain.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204127","204127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66125","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria are used in her Department to decide what historic files should be (a) retained and (b) destroyed; when these criteria were established; and what reviews have been undertaken of these criteria since.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204142","204142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66126","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the proposed guidance from the Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health for paediatricians on cases of age assessment of unaccompanied migrant children.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204179","204179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66127","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of her Department's expenditure on the (a) immigration system once associated fee income has been deducted and (b) asylum system in each of the last three financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204254","204254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66128","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many litigation cases around age assessments of unaccompanied migrant children there were in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13; and what the cost of such cases was to (i) local authorities and (ii) her Department.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204183","204183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66129","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the nationality and gender of each suspected victim of trafficking referred to the Trafficking Victim Support Scheme operated by the Salvation Army was in June 2014 in which (a) region and (b) county each of the suspected victims was found; which agency referred each person to the Scheme; in which town the shelter was to which they were placed for the relevant period; and what contact it had with each victim after they exit the shelter to ensure they are not re-trafficked.","Biography information for Sir Richard Ottaway","Sir Richard Ottaway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204181","204181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66130","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ensure that people who visit Scotland to participate in or watch the Commonwealth Games in 2014 are not able to remain in the country illegally after the Games have finished.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204199","204199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66131","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have entered the UK in each of the last five years to participate in the London marathons and who remain in the country illegally; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204205","204205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66132","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who came to the UK to participate in the 2012 Paralympic Games who remain in the country illegally; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204201","204201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66133","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many knife-related crimes were recorded in (a) London, (b) Tower Hamlets and (c) Bethnal Green and Bow constituency in the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204172","204172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66134","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in her Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204327","204327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66135","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what professional development courses are made available to staff of her Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204346","204346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66136","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answers of 9 April 2014, Official Report, column 274WS and 14 January 2014, Official Report, column 481W, on human trafficking: victim support schemes, for what reason information on each individual and on their gender and location was not given in the former Answer; and if she will provide that information in response to future parliamentary questions seeking equivalent information.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204317","204317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66137","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK Border Force has reached any understanding with individual Scottish fishing boats regarding the employment of members of their crew who are not citizens of EEA member states.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204355","204355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66138","2014-07-10","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 9 April 2014, Official Report, column 274W, on human trafficking: victim support schemes, how many of those referred were (a) men and (b) women, by country; what steps are taken to ensure that after the victim exits the shelter into which they have been placed by the Salvation Army they are not retrafficked or enter contact with their former traffickers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204316","204316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66139","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204279","204279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66140","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what occasions each Minister within her Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204297","204297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66141","2014-07-09","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, on what occasions each Minister within her Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204298","204298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66142","2014-07-09","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204280","204280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66143","2014-07-09","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what professional development courses are made available to staff of her Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204347","204347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66144","2014-07-09","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in her Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204328","204328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66145","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 681W, on official visits, what domestic visits each of the Ministers of her Department has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204375","204375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66146","2014-07-09","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that displaced Rohingya Muslims have access to basic medicine and healthcare provision.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204170","204170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66147","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many reports of fraud or corrupt practices her Department has received (a) in writing and (b) through the development tracker website in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204163","204163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66148","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether decisions to award funding under the Global Poverty Action Fund were made by the Civil Society Department, Policy and Research Division of her Department or by Triple Line Consulting Ltd.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204162","204162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66149","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation of displaced Rohingya Muslims in Burma.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204198","204198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66150","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent from the Conflict Pool in each country in each year since its launch.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204161","204161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66151","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what additional support she is providing to authorities in West Africa to help them with the recent ebola outbreak.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204215","204215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66152","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent from the Rapid Response Facility in each country in each year since its launch.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204160","204160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66153","2014-07-10","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much has been paid to Triple Line Consulting Ltd for the management and running of the Global Poverty Action Fund in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204159","204159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66154","2014-07-09","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what work the Commonwealth Scholarship Commission does to promote the availability of its scholarships to students resident in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204178","204178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66155","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Collaborative TB Strategy for England will be jointly published and delivered by Public Health England and NHS England.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204226","204226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66156","2014-07-09","Department for International Development","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much public funding her Department gave directly or indirectly to Oxfam in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204126","204126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66157","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department will impose a cap on the number of contracts any one bidder can be awarded to undertake the work of the 21 community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204265","204265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66158","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for compensation were rejected by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014 to date; and if he will list in each case the injuries sustained by the applicant and the reason for the application being refused.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204261","204261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66159","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Court of Appeal hearings have been televised since cameras were first allowed in court.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204262","204262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66160","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many books there are in HM Prison (a) Leeds and (b) Wakefield.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204166","204166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66161","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether secure colleges will contain segregation units.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204372","204372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66162","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204329","204329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66163","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners committed suicide in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204365","204365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66164","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce mandatory training for lawyers dealing with children.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204364","204364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66165","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204348","204348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66166","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204281","204281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66167","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204299","204299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66168","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many minutes in total of Court of Appeal hearings have been televised since cameras were first allowed in court.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204267","204267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66169","2014-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the maximum share of the total contract value for community rehabilitation companies any one successful bidder will be able to be awarded.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204268","204268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66170","2014-07-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she next plans to meet the (a) CEO and (b) chair of the British Business Bank to discuss how that organisation can more effectively support Northern Ireland businesses.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204241","204241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66171","2014-07-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, on what occasions each Minister within her Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204300","204300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66172","2014-07-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204282","204282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66173","2014-07-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what professional development courses are made available to staff of her Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204349","204349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66174","2014-07-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in her Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204330","204330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66175","2014-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, columns 724-5W, on official visits, what domestic visits each of the Ministers of her Department has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204373","204373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66176","2014-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Chief Executive of Healthcare UK to ensure that business, academia, health and public sector organisations in Northern Ireland are included in Healthcare UK's priorities for 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204204","204204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66177","2014-07-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to her Answer of 3 July 2014, Official Report, column 713W, on work experience, whether her Department follows Cabinet Office guidance on work experience placements.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204174","204174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66178","2014-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she intends to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Bury South  constituency of 12 June 2014 on a youth summit on building a shared future.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204146","204146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66179","2014-07-09","Prime Minister","2014-07-07","To ask the Prime Minister, what representations he has received about establishing a national cemetery; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204225","204225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66180","2014-07-09","Prime Minister","2014-07-07","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to establish a national cemetery; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204238","204238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66181","2014-07-09","Scotland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204301","204301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66182","2014-07-09","Scotland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204283","204283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66183","2014-07-09","Scotland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204331","204331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66184","2014-07-09","Scotland Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204350","204350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66185","2014-07-09","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204351","204351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66186","2014-07-09","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204332","204332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66187","2014-07-09","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Fifth Report of the Transport Committee of Session 2013-14, on Access to Transport for Disabled People, HC 116, what assessment he has made of the progress of bus operators in installing audio-visual announcement systems for people with sight loss as recommended in paragraph 29 of that report.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204357","204357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66188","2014-07-09","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204284","204284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66189","2014-07-09","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the results of the bus driver disability training review.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204356","204356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66190","2014-07-09","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204302","204302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66191","2014-07-09","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of extending the potential economic benefits of extending High Speed 2 to Colchester.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204240","204240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66192","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it a condition of the Bus Service Operators Grant incentive for real time information equipment that the performance data generated should be made available to the traffic commissioners.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204207","204207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66193","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding has been allocated to support rural bus routes in Cornwall in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204153","204153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66194","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Bradford will be included in any future northern high speed rail line across the Pennines.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204158","204158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66195","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many local transport authorities achieve the bus punctuality targets set by the Senior Traffic Commissioners.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204210","204210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66196","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much transport grant was given to Warrington Borough Council in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204149","204149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66197","2014-07-09","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the local transport authorities which form Rail North and are jointly responsible for the (a) TransPennine Express and (b) Northern Rail franchises will have the freedom to specify (i) staffing levels, (ii) ticket office hours and (iii) driver-only specification of new rolling stock in the new franchise bids for each line.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204185","204185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66198","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many public inquiries into bus performance were undertaken by each traffic commissioner in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204152","204152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66199","2014-07-09","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to reduce congestion (a) in Windsor constituency and (b) around Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204116","204116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66200","2014-07-09","Wales Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204304","204304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66201","2014-07-09","Wales Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204286","204286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66202","2014-07-09","Wales Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204334","204334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66203","2014-07-09","Wales Office","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204353","204353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66204","2014-07-09","Women and Equalities","2014-07-07","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 677W, on official visits, what domestic visits each of the Ministers in the Government Equalities Office have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204367","204367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66205","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 721W, on official visits, what domestic visits each of the Ministers in his Department has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204366","204366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66206","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what professional development courses are made available to staff of his Department; and what the cost to the public purse is of each such course.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204354","204354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66207","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many senior civil servants appointed to positions in his Department since 2010 were previously (a) political appointees within that Department and (b) employed by a political party.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204335","204335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66208","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on legal fees in cases relating to the release of information requested under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204287","204287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66209","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what occasions each Minister within his Department has taken domestic flights on official business since May 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204305","204305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66210","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff by grade and full-time equivalence are currently employed by his Department in dealing with policy on benefit sanctioning.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204233","204233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66211","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2014, Official Report, column 640W, on Independent Living Fund, when he expects his Department's plans for evaluating the effect on former users of the closure of the Independent Living Fund will be completed; and when those plans will be published.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204114","204114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66212","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2014, Official Report, column 640W, on Independent Living Fund, what plans he has to publish his Department's assessment of the effect on former users of the closure of the Independent Living Fund.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204113","204113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66213","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency received winter fuel payments in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204150","204150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66214","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2014, Official Report, column 640W, on Independent Living Fund, what support his Department plans to provide users of the Independent Living Fund affected by the closure of the Fund.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204187","204187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66215","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to work with Remploy factory workers since the factory closure programme began; how many former Remploy factory employees are now in mainstream work; and how many former Remploy employees have been supported by the Access to Work scheme since the factory closure programme began.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204148","204148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66216","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with learning disability charities on the closure of the Independent Living Fund.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204156","204156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66217","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on learning disability outcomes of the closure of the Independent Living Fund.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204155","204155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66218","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants from Bethnal Green and Bow constituency had benefit sanctions overturned in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204203","204203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66219","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants from (a) England, (b) London and (c) Bethnal Green and Bow constituency were sanctioned in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204200","204200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66220","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received in support of maintaining the local welfare provision grant to local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204263","204263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66221","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for jobseeker's allowance made by (a) men and (b) women in the first quarter of 2014 were made within six months of a previous claim ending.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204266","204266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66222","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people entered the Access to Work scheme in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204256","204256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66223","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Warrington Borough and (b) Warrington North constituency were in (i) relative and (ii) absolute poverty in 1997-98 and each year since.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204253","204253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66224","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2014, Official Report, column 126W, on personal independence payment, and with reference to the National Audit Office report, Personal Independence Payment: early progress, how his Department plans to recoup the £140 million shortfall in benefit savings estimated in that report while delivering the PIP reassessment programme within its original timescales and budget.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204224","204224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66225","2014-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what methodology is used by his Department to assess the comparative costs and benefits of the Access to Work scheme.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204252","204252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76528","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of recent trends in reported road casualties.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904767","904767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76529","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of recent trends in road safety statistics.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904765","904765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76530","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to relieve congestion on roads in Hampshire.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904753","904753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76531","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans the Government has for further high-speed rail developments.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904766","904766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76532","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress his Department has made on the pilot of a new enforcement process for foreign-registered vehicles that have overstayed.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904754","904754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76908","2014-07-10","Leader of the House","2014-07-07","To ask the Leader of the House, what recent guidance he has given to his ministerial colleagues on making statements to the House before they are made to the media.","Biography information for Pat Glass","Pat Glass","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904796","904796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76909","2014-07-10","Leader of the House","2014-07-07","To ask the Leader of the House, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues about Private Members' Bills.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904789","904789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76924","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on a second railway line to connect Plymouth with London and the Midlands.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904748","904748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76941","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to relieve congestion on roads.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904749","904749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76942","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of Britain's rail track mileage is capable of accommodating full-sized lorry trailers on trains.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904750","904750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/76965","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the economic and social contribution of airports to (a) the Exchequer and (b) the local communities they serve; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904764","904764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65850","2014-07-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeships have been taken up by (a) men and (b) women (i) aged up to 21 years, (ii) aged 22 to 24 years and (iii) aged 25 years and above in the last year.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204107","204107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65851","2014-07-08","Cabinet Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been registered as self-employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204098","204098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65852","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance he gives to Departments on the publication of business cases for major projects.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204103","204103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65853","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will discuss with (a) the Secretary of State for Justice and (b) the Secretary of State for the Home Department the implications for his policies on delivery of public services by private companies of the findings of the Howard League for Penal Reform report, Corporate Crime? A dossier on the failure of privatisation in the criminal justice system, published in May 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204052","204052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65854","2014-07-09","Cabinet Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of GDS technical employees are female.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204068","204068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65855","2014-07-08","Cabinet Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed on a part-time basis in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204081","204081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65856","2014-07-08","Cabinet Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were employed on a full-time basis in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204082","204082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65857","2014-07-08","HM Treasury","2014-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether consumer credit firms and peer-to-peer platforms located outside the UK but within the European Economic Area will (a) need to be authorised or supervised by the Financial Conduct Authority and (b) continue to be able to lend money online to UK consumers under the terms of the EU Electronic Commerce Directive.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204077","204077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65858","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, where each company seeking authorisation as a bank was located when the application was made in each of the last four years; and when each such application was determined.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204070","204070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65859","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a list of each application for the change of control of a bank made in the last four years.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204057","204057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65860","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department last conducted a review of the process of granting authorisation for (a) banks and (b) insurance companies.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204059","204059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65861","2014-07-08","HM Treasury","2014-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many consumer credit firms and peer-to-peer platforms located outside the UK, but within the European Economic Area and which lend money online to UK consumers have been granted interim permission to trade by the Financial Conduct Authority.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204062","204062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65862","2014-07-09","HM Treasury","2014-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the role of private equity in providing capital to the (a) banking sector and (b) insurance sector.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204058","204058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65863","2014-07-08","HM Treasury","2014-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to his Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion of the total workforce of such contractors is made up by apprentices.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204067","204067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65864","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will publish a code of practice for the management of residential property.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204061","204061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65865","2014-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in which month the redress arrangements concerning letting and managing agents will commence.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204060","204060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65866","2014-07-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the register of landlords in Scotland in reducing bad practice.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204056","204056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65867","2014-07-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with West Midlands Fire Authority on staffing patterns in that fire service.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204053","204053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65868","2014-07-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the new Model Tenancy Agreement will be published.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204054","204054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65869","2014-07-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department intends to publish the results of the review of residential property conditions.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204055","204055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65870","2014-07-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the current timetable is for the review of the Treasure Act 1996; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204094","204094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65871","2014-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to incorporate discussion of torture, sexual violence and other war crimes, crimes against humanity and other human rights violations in the military training provided to the Burma Army by the UK.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204090","204090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65872","2014-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what quantity of tritium has been imported from the US for use by his Department in H1616 shipping packages since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204092","204092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65873","2014-07-09","Department for Education","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of young people not in employment, education or training in each of the last five years were women.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204104","204104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65874","2014-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to his Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion of the total workforce of such contractors is made up by apprentices.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204063","204063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65875","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to his Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion of the total workforce of such contractors is made up by apprentices.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204064","204064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65876","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to support an independent, international inquiry, with Burmese participation, into alleged war crimes and crimes against humanity in Burma.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204080","204080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65877","2014-07-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his Department's announcement of 20 February 2014, on funding for the International Organization for Migration Greece Assistance for the Voluntary Return and Reintegration of Returnees project, from which budgets the Government's contribution will be funded; how that funding will be spent; what assistance will be provided to the victims of human trafficking from EU countries being supported through that project; what reintegration assistance will be provided to the 75 returning migrants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204078","204078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65878","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of the widespread use of torture in the conflict zones of Burma and alleged war crimes and crimes against humanity in that country.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204075","204075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65879","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to urge the government of Burma to sign the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights; and what assessment he has made of the policy of the government of Burma on this matter.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204089","204089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65880","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had regarding Burma at the Global Summit to End Sexual Violence in Conflict.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204087","204087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65881","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost of work undertaken by his Department relating to nuclear disarmament was in 2013-14; and if he will make it his policy separately to detail in his Department's Annual Report and Accounts expenditure and activity relating to nuclear disarmament.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204083","204083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65882","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of sexual violence in conflict in Burma.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204084","204084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65883","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to urge the government of Burma to end torture, investigate reports of continuing use of torture, and bring the perpetrators to justice.","Biography information for Robert Buckland","Mr Robert Buckland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204085","204085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65884","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on people with physical impairments and learning disabilities of the proposals by third sector providers to close residential care homes available to them.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204095","204095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65885","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the availability of a range of housing and care options for people with physical disabilities and learning difficulties.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204096","204096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65886","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the future of residential care for people with complex needs including physical impairments and learning difficulties; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204097","204097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65887","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014, Official Report, column 520W, on telemedicine, when NHS England will publish a set of consistent measures for commissioners to demonstrate the effect of telehealth technologies on health outcomes.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204071","204071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65888","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014, Official Report, column 520W, on telemedicine, how many telehealth, telecare and telecoaching connections there were in each region of England in 2011.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204072","204072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65889","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014, Official Report, column 520W, on telemedicine, when NHS England will issue the first in its regular surveys on the number of individuals who benefit from telehealth services; to whom the survey will be issued; when the survey will report and be published; how it will be analysed; and how often it will be repeated.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204073","204073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65890","2014-07-10","Department of Health","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people over the age of 75 years were diagnosed with dementia after being admitted to hospital as an emergency inpatient in England in each year since  2009-10.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204074","204074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65891","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to his Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion of the total workforce of such contractors is made up by apprentices.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204065","204065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65892","2014-07-09","Department of Health","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of how much arthritis has cost the UK economy in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204051","204051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65893","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to her Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion of the total workforce of such contractors is made up by apprentices.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204066","204066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65894","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Option 3 in her Department's consultation on the review of section 24 of the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 would be effected by a statutory instrument under section 75 of the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204076","204076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65895","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the Exchequer has been of the asylum and immigration system once fee income has been deducted in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204069","204069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65896","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many e-gates are now in operation at (a) UK ports and (b) Manchester Airport; what proportion of such passengers are using e-gates; and what the rejection rates is of travellers using e-gates (i) in the UK and (ii) at Manchester airport.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204088","204088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65897","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders aged 18 to 21 years were held in each prison establishment in England and Wales on the latest date for which data is available.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204105","204105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65898","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many officials in his Department in civil service pay bands (a) SCS Pay Band 4/Grade 1, (b) SCS Pay Band 3/Grade 2, (c) SCS Pay Band 2/Grade 3 and (d) SCS Pay Band 1/Grade 5 have left to work for (a) G4S, (b) Serco, (c) Sodexo, (d) GEOAmey, (e) Capita, (f) Atos, (g) Mitie, (h) Working Links, (i) A4E, (j) MTC Amey, (k) GEO Group and (l) Carillion since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204086","204086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65899","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many secondments into his Department there were in each year since 2010; from which organisations each such person was seconded; and into which areas of his Department they were seconded.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204106","204106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65900","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have been seconded into his Department and its executive agencies from (a) G4S, (b) Serco, (c) Capita, (d) Working Links, (e) A4E, (f) Sodexo, (g) GEO Amey, (h) Mitie, (i) MTC Amey, (j) GEO Group, (k) Atos and (l) Carillion in each year since 2010; in which area of his Department such staff were seconded; how long each secondment lasted; and what the reasons were for each secondment.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204110","204110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65901","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have been seconded from his Department and its executive agencies into (a) G4S, (b) Serco, (c) Capita, (d) Working Links, (e) A4E, (f) Sodexo, (g) GEO Amey and (h) Mitie; in which areas of his Department such staff previously worked; how long each secondment lasted; and what the reasons were for each secondment.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204111","204111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65902","2014-07-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison places in each prison in England and Wales are designated as available to hold offenders aged 18 to 21 years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204079","204079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65903","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what occasions in the last four years the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments has been notified under the Business Appointment Rules of former officials of his Department taking up employment after leaving government; what advice the Committee published; what conditions the Committee laid down; whether any such conditions have been breached; and in each case what organisation the official went to work for.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204091","204091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65904","2014-07-08","Department for Transport","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre, Stornoway has permanent radio access to the radio network covering the Clyde, Arran and the Ayrshire coast.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204102","204102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65905","2014-07-08","Department for Transport","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre at Belfast was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in June 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204099","204099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65906","2014-07-08","Department for Transport","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre at Liverpool was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in June 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204101","204101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65907","2014-07-08","Department for Transport","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre at Stornoway was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in June 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204100","204100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65908","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the independent evaluation of the Work Programme to be published.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204108","204108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65909","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to improve the performance of the Work Programme for people over 50 years of age; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204109","204109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65910","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse of all employment and support allowance appeals has been since May 2010; and what the cost of all such appeals which were successful has been.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204093","204093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65624","2014-07-07","Attorney General","2014-07-03","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Crown Prosecution Service is taking to prosecute payday money lenders under the Fraud Act 2006.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203917","203917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65625","2014-07-08","Attorney General","2014-07-03","To ask the Attorney General, if he will place in the Library a copy of each item of correspondence between his Department and (a) the Home Office and (b) Lord Brittan of Spennithorne in relation to child abuse in (a) 1984 and (b) 1985; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203925","203925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65626","2014-07-07","Attorney General","2014-07-03","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of all defendants of charges of (a) rape, (b) sexual offences other than rape and (c) domestic violence have been aged (i) 18 to 24 and (ii) 14 to 17 in each of the last 10 financial years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203934","203934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65627","2014-07-07","Attorney General","2014-07-03","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of all unsuccessful outcomes in rape cases have been because of victim issues in each of the last seven financial years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203935","203935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65628","2014-07-07","Attorney General","2014-07-03","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of unsuccessful Crown Prosecution Service prosecutions have been because of victim issues in each of the last seven financial years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203936","203936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65629","2014-07-08","Attorney General","2014-07-03","To ask the Attorney General, if he will place in the Library copies of papers from Lord Brittan of Spennithorne in relation to child abuse in 1983 and 1984 and which were referred to his Department by the Home Office; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204036","204036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65630","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the value of publishing the average total debt of individuals subject to individual voluntary arrangements.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204045","204045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65631","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) consumers and (b) endorsement of consumer protection law of the hand-over of investigations from the Office of Fair Trading to the Financial Conduct Authority.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204046","204046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65632","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) internal and (b) external complaints have been received by his Department about alleged breaches of the Civil Service Code of Conduct since 2010; and what steps his Department has taken in response to each such complaint.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203953","203953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65633","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many small and medium-sized business in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England and Wales have (i) applied for and (ii) been granted loans by the British Business Bank in the last year.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203964","203964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65634","2014-07-08","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) men and (b) women received support from the Care to Learn scheme in each of the last two academic years; what the total cost of the Care to Learn scheme was in each such year; and what the projected cost of the scheme will be in 2014-15.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204006","204006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65635","2014-07-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in further education or training in the last academic year were (a) parents and (b) single parents.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204008","204008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65636","2014-07-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) men and (b) women have applied for Advanced Learner loans since the start of the scheme.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204007","204007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65637","2014-07-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) men and (b) women in further education received funding for childcare through the Discretionary Learner Support scheme in the last academic year; and what the total amount spent on such support was.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204009","204009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65638","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assistance his Department provides to help small rural businesses to export; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203921","203921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65639","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support and protection the Government provides to UK businesses experiencing cyber attacks.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203893","203893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65640","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to encourage the development of intellectual property in (a) Brighton, Kemptown and (b) Brighton and Hove; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203870","203870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65641","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to increase business formation in (a) Brighton, Kemptown and (b) Lewes District; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203874","203874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65642","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what additional support he is providing to encourage businesses in Brighton, Kemptown to export to overseas markets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203879","203879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65643","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of apprenticeship starts by size of workplace in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203888","203888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65644","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what he estimates the lifetime earning premium of those with (a) L3 apprenticeships and (b) L4+ apprenticeships will be compared to level 2 apprenticeships.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203892","203892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65645","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to improve the protection of intellectual property in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203867","203867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65646","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage technology-based start-ups to develop in towns and cities outside London.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203868","203868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65647","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what evidence he has of attempts by foreign intelligence services to instigate cyber attacks on UK companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203895","203895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65648","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to bar (a) G4S, (b) Serco and (c) any company under investigation for serious fraud from bidding for government contracts to deliver public services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203972","203972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65649","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) internal and (b) external complaints have been received by his Department about alleged breaches of the Civil Service Code of Conduct since 2010; and what actions his Department has taken in response to each such complaint.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203954","203954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65650","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid in corporation tax by businesses registered in Dover and Deal in each of the last five years; and what proportion of such taxation was paid by small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203948","203948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65651","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that sharing of customer information collected by HM Revenue and Customs is subject to appropriate safeguards.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203961","203961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65652","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) internal and (b) external complaints have been received by his Department about alleged breaches of the Civil Service Code of Conduct since 2010; and what actions his Department has taken in response to each such complaint.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203958","203958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65653","2014-07-08","HM Treasury","2014-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the level of bank lending to small and medium-sized businesses since May 2010.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203916","203916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65654","2014-07-08","HM Treasury","2014-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the proportion of households who will be eligible for tax-free childcare who currently spend more than (a) £7,000, (b) £8,000, (c) £9,000 and (d) £10,000 on childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203904","203904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65655","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will consider reducing VAT on hotels to encourage tourism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203878","203878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65656","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued on whether the landlord or tenant is responsible for the payment of council tax on the day that a tenancy ends.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203889","203889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65657","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued on whether the landlord or tenant is responsible for the payment of council tax when a tenant leaves the property but fails to inform the landlord.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203890","203890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65658","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the number and proportion of businesses which have access to high-speed broadband in Brighton, Kemptown constituency.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203866","203866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65659","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate how much money will be raised from society lotteries in (a) Brighton, Kemptown and (b) Brighton and Hove in the next 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203877","203877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65660","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will (a) review and (b) amend or provide an exemption to the five-year housing land availability test for councils who have land on the proposed High Speed 2 rail route.","Biography information for Natascha Engel","Natascha Engel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203897","203897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65661","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage estate agents to notify buyers and sellers of the cost guarantee and other options available to them to prevent the practice of gazumping.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203918","203918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65662","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent steps he has taken to promote community rights under the Localism Act 2011.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203922","203922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65663","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to better protect emergency services from attacks by youths.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203967","203967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65664","2014-07-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reason the Local Government Transparency Code 2014 requires publication of the names of union representatives who spend over 50 per cent of their time on union duties, in addition to the number of such representatives and estimates of their cost as a percentage of the total pay bill; and if he will bring forward proposals to amend the code so that the identity of individuals is not published.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203951","203951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65665","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the total amount of money awarded to good causes by the National Lottery in (a) Brighton, Kemptown constituency and (b) Brighton and Hove.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203983","203983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65666","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it the policy of the Government to prevent nursing homes and residential rest homes charging lower fees for residents funded by local authorities than for residents who are self-funding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204017","204017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65667","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library correspondence between his Department and the London Borough of Tower Hamlets relating to the frequency of publication of East End Life.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203996","203996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65668","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment Ofcom has made of the reasons for disputes between service providers and Openreach over (a) the provision of telephone and broadband services and (b) the service provided to James and Susan Love of Aldington, Worcestershire.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203865","203865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65669","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 598W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, whether any UK personnel other than RAF personnel embedded with the 432nd Wing will remain at Creech following cessation of the NATO ISAF missions in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204034","204034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65670","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2014, Official Report, column 239, on unmanned air vehicles, whether the amendment of Joint Services Publication 398 on UK Rules of Engagement makes any reference to (a) operations conducted remotely or (b) cross-border targeted operations.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204044","204044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65671","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 354W, on Afghanistan, how many evidence-based assessments have been carried out by his Department on the effects of lethal targeting; and if his Department will carry out or commission further assessment on use of remotely piloted air systems in Afghanistan in carrying out a post-campaign strategic review.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204047","204047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65672","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2014, Official Report, column 95W, on the Intelligence Service, if he will take other steps to ensure that fused and shared data is not used for targeted killing by foreign states outside Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204048","204048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65673","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2014, Official Report, column 99W, on unmanned air vehicles, what assessment he has made of the degree to which Reaper redeployment abroad is significant; and if he will make it his policy to receive parliamentary approval before active use of any Reapers based outside Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204049","204049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65674","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2014, Official Report, column 240W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, whether his Department maintains identical munitions records for those sorties of US-owned systems operated by UK personnel.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204030","204030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65675","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) internal and (b) external complaints have been received by his Department about alleged breaches of the Civil Service Code of Conduct since 2010; and what actions his Department has taken in response to each such complaint.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203955","203955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65676","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the Stimson Task Force report on his drone policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204027","204027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65677","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2014, Official Report, column 240W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, whether the US-UK Foreign Military Sales agreement will affect future basing for the Reaper fleet.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204026","204026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65678","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 12 June 2014, Official Report, column 233W, on Africa, what the current (a) rank, (b) squadron and (c) function is of each member of UK personnel deployed in Nigeria and Ethiopia.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204025","204025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65679","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to allow academy trusts to raise capital finance based on the value of school title deeds.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204028","204028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65680","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many proposed transactions relating to land sold by academy trusts he has (a) approved and (b) declined since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204029","204029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65681","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support his Department is providing for school governors during their school's transition to academy status; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203977","203977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65682","2014-07-08","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding each school received per pupil in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204019","204019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65683","2014-07-08","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools offer all-through provision to pupils from reception to year 13.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203937","203937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65684","2014-07-08","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many boys who were (a) eligible and (b) not eligible for free school meals attended a primary school at which there were (i) one, (ii) two and (iii) three male full-time equivalent teachers in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203909","203909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65685","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which overseas counterparts have complained to the Government about matters relating to adoption, care proceedings or other matters relating to child protection in the UK; and what the substance of those complaints was.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203896","203896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65686","2014-07-08","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2014, Official Report, column 538W, on academies, if he will disaggregate the data to identify payments under the Sponsor Capacity Fund detailing (a) when any such grant was awarded, (b) how much was awarded, (c) whether each organisation subsequently sponsored any academies and (d) the date on which any monies were returned to the Department by those who did not.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203913","203913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65687","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of levels of literacy and numeracy in (a) primary school leavers and (b) secondary school leavers in (i) Brighton, Kemptown constituency, (ii) East Sussex and (iii) South East England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203872","203872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65688","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason it is not possible for telephone callers to be put through to the Education Funding Agency.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203886","203886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65689","2014-07-08","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which secondary schools which were not girls' schools had fewer than 10 per cent of their qualified full-time teachers as males in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203907","203907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65690","2014-07-08","Department for Education","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many young people who entered care at each age and who left care at 16 or older and who did not return to their birth parents had been taken into care because of (a) abuse or neglect, (b) child's disability, (c) parents' illness or disability, (d) family in acute stress, (e) family dysfunction, (f) socially unacceptable behaviour, (g) low income, (h) absent parenting and (i) any other reason in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203905","203905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65691","2014-07-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many members of staff have been employed on a full-time basis at the Office of Carbon Capture and Storage in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203882","203882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65692","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the written statement of 3 July 2014, Official Report, column 61WS, on management of overseas owned plutonium in the UK, whether the plutonium from Germany and Sweden respectively allocated to the UK civilian stockpile will be subject to the withdrawal from safeguards option under article 14 of the tripartite UK-Euratom-IAEA Voluntary Safeguards Agreement of 1977.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204041","204041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65693","2014-07-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much public funding is being provided in 2014-15 for research and development projects examining industrial carbon capture and storage.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204016","204016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65694","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make an assessment of the implications for environmental safety in the UK hydraulic fracturing programme of studies published in 2013 by the University of Missouri on the problem of dispersal of endocrine disrupter chemicals from fluids used in the fracking process for natural gas.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203982","203982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65695","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England and Wales are currently using third party deductions to help pay their energy bills; and what steps he is taking to ensure that customer energy prices fall in line with wholesale prices.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203960","203960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65696","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to his Department's solar strategy and initiative with the Department for Education to encourage the deployment of PV on schools, how many schools in England and Wales have installed solar panels to date; when he expects all schools in England and Wales to generate their own power from solar PV or other renewable sources; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203947","203947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65697","2014-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with his French counterpart on the effects of the EU Sulphur Directive on (a) the shipping industry, (b) jobs and (c) the environment; and what the outcomes of those discussions were.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203938","203938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65698","2014-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many veterinary surgeons are qualified to undertake bovine tuberculosis testing in each NUTS-1 region of England.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204003","204003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65699","2014-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the cost of introducing annual testing for bovine tuberculosis.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204013","204013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65700","2014-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 137W, on forests: Christchurch, how many areas of woodland and heathland in Hurn Forest will be affected by the cable route; and what steps have been taken to consult local people about the environmental effect.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204015","204015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65701","2014-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what statistics his Department holds on the use of fixed penalty notices in each local authority area.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203998","203998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65702","2014-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the role of outdoor-reared pigs in transmission of bovine TB; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203887","203887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65703","2014-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on implementing a ban on pesticide neonictinoids; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203903","203903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65704","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Bahrain about the treatment of the democracy movement in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203906","203906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65705","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what commitments the government of Burma has made to implement the declaration on preventing sexual violence in conflict.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203910","203910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65706","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the report of the Stimson Task Force on US drone policy, published on 28 June 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204042","204042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65707","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 641W, on the USA, if his Department will update the 1946 UK-USA agreement to take better account of developments in technology since 1946 and ensure that data shared under the agreement is not used for targeted killing by the US outside Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204050","204050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65708","2014-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss the coverage of the situation in eastern Ukraine by the BBC Russian Service with that Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204020","204020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65709","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 611W, on abortion, what estimate he has made of the number of HSA4 forms returned to the terminating doctor pending completion as of June 2014.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204043","204043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65710","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effects of the use of emergency hormonal contraception on the rate of abortion in women aged under 25; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204001","204001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65711","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children aged (a) under 10 and (b) 10 and over were admitted to hospital with a (i) primary and (ii) secondary diagnosis of viral hepatitis in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204022","204022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65712","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) financial and (b) human resource his Department has made available to develop policies to tackle obesity in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204024","204024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65713","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) people, (b) people under 18, (c) people under 16 and (d) people under 12 (i) attended and (ii) were admitted via accident and emergency departments for excessive consumption of alcohol in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204021","204021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65714","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the housing needs of people who have mental health conditions who are (a) released from prison, (b) discharged from secure hospitals to the community and (c) on community sentences; and what steps he is taking to address those needs.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204023","204023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65715","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department last conducted a review of evidence concerning the long-term health effects of emergency hormonal contraception; what evidence  that review took into account; and if he will commission another such review.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204000","204000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65716","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the causes of trends in the number of abortions which were performed on women who had already had an abortion in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lord McCrea of Magherafelt and Cookstown","Dr William McCrea","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203980","203980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65717","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of the application form for Section 251 support made by the Health and Social Care Information Centre to the Confidentiality Advisory Group following completion of the pilot scheme on the main study of the What About YOUth?","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204011","204011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65718","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to request reports from those signed up to the Responsibility Deal for Public Health who have yet to submit reports.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203969","203969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65719","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of companies who have only signed up to pledges set out in the Responsibility Deal as they refer to the health of their own workforce rather than those regarding the content of their products.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203970","203970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65720","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England and Wales have been treated for a mental health problem in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203965","203965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65721","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) adults and (b) children in (i) the North West, (ii) Lancashire and (iii) East Lancashire contacted their GP because of a skin condition in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203940","203940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65722","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 504W, on tobacco packaging, whether he plans to publish draft regulations to outlaw smoking in cars with children present in time for them to be made law before the end of March 2015.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203950","203950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65723","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to enable surgeries to end contracts to use 0844 numbers early.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203952","203952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65724","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS trusts offer a screening programme for osteoporosis.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204002","204002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65725","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of plans by the General Dental Council to increase the Annual Retention Fee by 64 per cent on the ability of the NHS to attract new dentists from all sectors of society.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203883","203883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65726","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of living in damp homes on the health of (a) children in general and (b) asthmatic children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203871","203871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65727","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate how many autistic children there were in the most recent five year period for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203875","203875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65728","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for all (a) NHS patients classified as urgent and (b) NHS cancer patients classified as urgent.","Biography information for Natascha Engel","Natascha Engel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203876","203876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65730","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the extent to which chief officers of territorial police forces have used the Marine Navigation Act 2013 to permit port constables to act outside their port area for policing purposes connected with the port constable's police area.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203891","203891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65731","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish (a) all submissions and memos to Ministers and (b) correspondence with other government departments relating to the review by officials of the Geoffrey Dickens dossiers.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203924","203924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65732","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of (a) the number of immigrants in the UK without legitimate immigration status and (b) the three most common countries from which such people originate.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203931","203931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65733","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total cost to the public purse was of overtime worked in HM Passport Office in each month between May 2011 and December 2012.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203941","203941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65734","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total cost to the public purse was of overtime worked in HM Passport Office in June 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203942","203942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65735","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to bring forward proposals for reform of the firearms licensing fees system.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203943","203943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65736","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 27 May 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regards to Mr M Nissar.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203920","203920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65737","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) internal and (b) external complaints have been received by her Department about alleged breaches of the Civil Service Code of Conduct since 2010; and what actions her Department has taken in response to each such complaint.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203956","203956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65738","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in Ashfield constituency have been on probation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203963","203963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65739","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 4 March 2014, Official Report, column 730W, on British nationality, how many orders stripping people of citizenship have been made since 4 March 2014; what the nationality of each person so affected was; and what the grounds of the decision were in each additional case.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204031","204031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65740","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cannabis factories have been discovered and abolished in the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203968","203968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65741","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to answer Question 199498, tabled by the hon. Member for Leeds Central on 6 June 2014.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203976","203976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65742","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the request by Rupert Ogwuezor dated 13 June 2011 for reconsideration of his case (HO reference: 01085860/2) will be determined; and what the reasons are for the time taken to process this case.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204014","204014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65743","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what statistics her Department holds on the use of fixed penalty notices in each local authority area.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203999","203999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65744","2014-07-08","Home Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 128W, on Didier Pierre Paulet, for what reasons her Department commented on the case of Abu Qatada.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204018","204018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65745","2014-07-08","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-03","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to his Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 134W, on computer software, what feedback has been received on the mechanics of the implementation of Microsoft 365 from (a) members of the Administration Committee and (b) other hon. Members.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203932","203932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65746","2014-07-08","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-03","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to his Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 134W, on computer software, how many calls the PICT Service Desk has received from hon. Members and their staff relating to problems resulting from the migration of their mailboxes to Microsoft 365.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203933","203933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65747","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 183W, on Yemen, if she will make an assessment of the effects on security in Yemen of remotely piloted air systems.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204032","204032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65748","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2014, Official Report, columns 181-2W, on Afghanistan, if she will place in the Library all official agreements reached between her Department and USAID on the transfer of the Bost Agripark in 2009.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203971","203971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65749","2014-07-08","Department for International Development","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with the Israeli government on its plans to liaise with the new Palestinian government to bring about improvements in the humanitarian situation in the border areas; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203949","203949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65750","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of child witnesses who had given evidence in court by video recording rather than by live video link in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203945","203945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65751","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the proportion of (a) judges, (b) magistrates and (c) prosecutors currently working in courts who have undergone specialist training on working with children in a court environment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203944","203944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65752","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to prevent people from publishing explicit photos online sent to them in trust by their former partners.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204005","204005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65753","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire have been arrested for possession of (i) Class A drugs, (ii) Class B drugs and (iii) Class C drugs in the last year; and what steps his Department is taking to rehabilitate people convicted of drug-related crimes.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203962","203962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65754","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2014, Official Report, column 671W, on courts: video conference, if he will publish a list of the remote sites for giving evidence in England and Wales.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204004","204004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65755","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-03","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many successful prosecutions for (a) postal, not proxy, vote fraud and (b) electoral registration fraud there have been in each of the last 15 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203974","203974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65756","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice, for failure to produce waste documents in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203984","203984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65757","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases remained unprocessed by the Parole Board on 1 (a) January, (b) April, (c) July and (d) October in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203975","203975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65758","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice, for depositing litter in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203985","203985"
