"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693393","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff of his Department are employed in media relations and communications roles; and how much was spent on the salaries of such staff members in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65114","65114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693394","2017-02-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress the Government has made in reducing long-term unemployment in areas of high unemployment in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65085","65085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693395","2017-02-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time is for an appeal against a mandatory reconsideration of a decision on personal independence payments in (a) Warrington, (b) the North West and (c) England.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65086","65086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693396","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons people who are in receipt of employment and support allowance and who live with a relative are unable to claim a disability premium if they meet all other relevant assessment criteria.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65042","65042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693397","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that recipients of universal credit do not fall into rent arrears while waiting to receive payments.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65157","65157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693398","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of universal credit have a managed payment to landlord in Great Grimsby.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65158","65158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693399","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the length of time it takes for working families to receive universal credit payments.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65160","65160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693400","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit sanctions have been applied to recipients of universal credit in Great Grimsby constituency in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65159","65159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693401","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department plans to monitor the effect of changes in the level of financial support for new claimants in the employment and support allowance work-related activity group on disabled people.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65064","65064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693403","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January to Question 61042, what estimate his Department has made of how long it will take to halve the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65189","65189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693404","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 December 2016 to Question 57882, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decrease in the number of energy efficiency measures installed in homes since January 2014 on the Government's commitment to reduce carbon emissions.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65125","65125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693405","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed Heineken takeover of Punch Taverns on jobs in the microbrewing industry.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65129","65129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693406","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to Each Home Counts: an independent review of consumer advice, protection, standards and enforcement for energy efficiency and renewable energy, published in December 2016, whether he plans to implement any of the recommendations of that review.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65128","65128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693407","2017-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will discuss guidance and assistance to support high street retailers competing with large out of town developments with the devolved legislations.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65078","65078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693408","2017-02-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to protect Magnox workers affected by reforms to final salary pension schemes across the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority Estate.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65061","65061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693409","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding the Green Investment Bank has provided to projects in Humberside in each fiscal year since its inception.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65062","65062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693410","2017-02-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Post Office branches were classed as (a) temporarily closed and (b) permanently closed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65096","65096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693411","2017-02-27","Department for Education","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure apprenticeship starts offer opportunities for employment across the UK and not just in the region where the apprenticeships are served.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65081","65081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693412","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many civil servants of his Department oversee contracts which have been awarded to external providers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64991","64991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693413","2017-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her Department's policy to ensure that maintaining high standards of animal welfare is a priority in future trade negotiations on food and agriculture.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64983","64983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693415","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many civil servants of his Department oversee contracts which have been awarded to external providers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65002","65002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693416","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Government will continue to apply the standards forming the basis of the EU's Everything But Arms programme in UK trade with the world's least-developed countries after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64948","64948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693417","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to promote trade and investment in green technology into the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65135","65135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693418","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62357, how many times Rolls Royce received cover from UK Export Finance in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65071","65071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693419","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62357, what the value of cover provided to Rolls Royce was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65072","65072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693420","2017-02-27","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2017 to Question 59272, whether a date has been set for Parliament to vote on the ratification of the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65089","65089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693421","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether liberalisation of the UK's agricultural markets has been raised (a) in his discussions with his Australian counterpart and (b) within the Australia-UK trade working group dialogue.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65178","65178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693422","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether liberalisation of the UK's agricultural markets has been raised (a) in his discussions with his counterpart in New Zealand and (b) within the UK-New Zealand trade policy dialogue.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65179","65179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693423","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his counterparts in Australia, New Zealand and South Africa have raised the issued of abolition of farming subsidies during discussions on future trade agreements.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65177","65177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693424","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his policy is on maintaining the simplified rules of origin on Jordanian exports agreed by the EU in 2016 for the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65180","65180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693425","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effect on UK environmental legislation of the investment protection provisions in the EU-Canada free trade agreement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65181","65181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693426","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take in negotiations for a US-UK trade deal to protect the British automotive industry.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65182","65182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693427","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff of his Department are employed in media relations and communications roles; and how much has been spent on the salaries of such staff members.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65103","65103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693428","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February to Question 63568, if he will take steps to include a clause on compliance with Article 18 of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights in future bilateral trade and investment agreements; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65190","65190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693429","2017-02-27","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make it his policy to prioritise (a) UK higher education and (b) higher education distance learning in the Government's future trade export strategy.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65216","65216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693430","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to ensure that UK environmental standards are maintained in any deal with the US.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65184","65184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693431","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to ensure that UK social and labour standards are maintained in any negotiations for a trade deal with the US.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65183","65183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693432","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the NHS is specifically protected from privatisation in any international trade deals.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65226","65226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693433","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effect on UK fisheries legislation of the investment protection provisions of the EU-Canada free trade agreement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65173","65173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693434","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the need to protect the NHS when considering any future trade deal.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65227","65227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693435","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions his Department has had on protections for the UK agricultural and fishing sectors with (a) trade partners that are members of the Friends of Fish or the Cairns Group blocs and (b) other trade partners.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65174","65174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693436","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Brazil on whether UK export finance provided to Petrobras in the last five years has been used for the purpose intended.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65175","65175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693437","2017-02-24","Department for International Trade","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership is the UK's preferred model for a future UK-US trade agreement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65176","65176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693438","2017-02-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff in his Department are employed in media relations and communications roles; and how much has been spent on the salaries of such staff members.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65108","65108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693439","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has for membership of the European Committee for Standardisation and the enforcement of that Committee's standards after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65131","65131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693441","2017-02-27","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with representatives of the European Medicines Agency on cooperation on the licensing of homeopathic products after the UK exits the European Union.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65093","65093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693442","2017-02-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the future of the UK steel industry.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64955","64955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693443","2017-02-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if the Government will publish its letter to trigger Article 50 for public scrutiny after it has been issued to the European Commission.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64975","64975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693444","2017-02-24","Cabinet Office","2017-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants of his Department oversee contracts which have been awarded to external providers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 65056","65056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/705496","2017-02-28","HM Treasury","2017-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to support economic growth outside London and the South East.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908965","908965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/705878","2017-02-28","HM Treasury","2017-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he is taking to encourage investment in innovative UK science and technology projects.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908969","908969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/705879","2017-02-28","HM Treasury","2017-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he is taking steps to support wage growth.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908967","908967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/705880","2017-02-28","HM Treasury","2017-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people his Department employs in Wales.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908966","908966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/705881","2017-02-28","HM Treasury","2017-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he is taking to encourage business investment in the UK.","Biography information for David Rutley","David Rutley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908970","908970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692425","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much income has been accrued to his Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64736","64736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692426","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of government procurement is from UK companies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64748","64748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692427","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with companies with which the Government has contracts on corporate social responsibility and the payment of corporation tax.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64753","64753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692428","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment the Government has made of the potential practical implications for the processing time required for overseas applicants to vote in UK elections of removing the 15-year rule for UK citizens living abroad being able to vote.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64723","64723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692429","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the Government has made of the number and proportion of UK citizens living abroad who would apply to be overseas electors for a UK parliamentary election or national referendum in the event that the 15-year rule for UK citizens living abroad being able to vote were removed.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64724","64724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692431","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress has been made on introducing legislative proposals to remove the 15-year time limit on British people living abroad being able to vote in elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64725","64725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692433","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are registered to vote in more than one constituency because they have not de-registered after moving house.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64726","64726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692434","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are registered to vote in more than one constituency because they are students.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64727","64727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692435","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in the UK are registered to vote but are ineligible to do so having been convicted and detained for an offence.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64728","64728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692436","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to A democracy that works for everyone: British citizens overseas, a policy statement, published on 7 October 2016, whether increased staff time and resources were a criterion in determining the amount of additional funding to be provided to electoral registration officers in relation to the removal of the 15-year time limit on British citizens living abroad being able to vote in elections.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64729","64729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692437","2017-02-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he plans to respond to the letter of 1 June 2016 relating to a mock vote in the House originally addressed to the then Prime Minister, which was transferred to his Department and then to the Department for Exiting the European Union, which has declined to reply to the correspondence as it pre-dates that Department's existence.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64790","64790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692438","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons the Financial Reporting Council placed the Parliamentary Contributory Pension Fund in the secondary tier for compliance with the Financial Stewardship code; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64885","64885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692439","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2017 to Question 63244, from which organisations or individuals the Trustees of the Parliamentary Contributory Pension Fund (PCPF) sought professional advice regarding the long-term risks to the financial performance of the PCPF of that fund's investments in the fossil fuel extractive industry.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64917","64917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692440","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason Treasury Ministers will not hold pre-Budget meetings with representatives of the alcohol industry in 2017.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64828","64828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692441","2017-02-24","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make further payments to people affected by regulatory failings at Equitable Life.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64869","64869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692443","2017-02-24","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason HM Revenue and Customs experienced difficulties with the 2015-16 tax calculation producing correct repayments due for that year; and when those difficulties are likely to be resolved.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64856","64856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692445","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been accrued to the public purse from fines levied by HM Revenue and Customs for late submission of tax returns in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64838","64838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692446","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps are being taken to ensure that more women participate in pension schemes and company share ownerships.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64798","64798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692447","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the ratio of men to women who have applied for auto-enrolment pensions.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64799","64799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692448","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the planned expenditure is on the HM Revenue and Customs identity assurance system planned to replace the Government Gateway service from March 2018.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64720","64720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692449","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which departments plan to use the HM Revenue and Customs identity verification service planned to replace the Government Gateway service from March 2018.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64721","64721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692450","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which transactions are planned to be processed via the (a) new identity verification service planned by HM Revenue and Customs and (b) Government Digital Service platform Verify when the Government Gateway service expires in March 2018.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64722","64722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692451","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much income has been accrued to his Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64743","64743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692453","2017-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much income has been accrued to his Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64737","64737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692454","2017-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much (a) the Government and (b) local authorities in England spent on adult social care in each year since 2010 by region.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64733","64733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692455","2017-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the amount that councils are required to pay back in right to buy receipts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64700","64700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692456","2017-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what comparative estimate his Department has made of the number of homes to be built between 2015 and 2020 and the Government's target for the number of homes to be built in that period.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64796","64796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692458","2017-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the level of provision for small businesses of ATM access.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64768","64768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692459","2017-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the closing date is for the submission of (a) objections to the proposal submitted by some Dorset local authorities on 9 February 2017 for local government reorganisation and (b) any alternative or counter-proposals for change to local government structures in Dorset.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64857","64857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692460","2017-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letter from the Mayor of Christchurch, dated 6 February 2017, on local government reorganisation.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64858","64858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692461","2017-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2017 to Question 63312, on unitary councils, how the principles enunciated in that answer apply to councils opposed to a particular proposal for reorganisation but with whom other councils refuse to collaborate or work jointly.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64859","64859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692463","2017-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2017 to Question 63310, on local government: conditions of employment, whether partnership arrangements in place between sovereign councils can be terminated against the will of those sovereign partners.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64860","64860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692464","2017-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on high streets and local communities of reduced access to ATMs.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64817","64817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692466","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the effect of changes to the level of access to free ATMs on high streets and local communities.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64818","64818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692467","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer and other cabinet colleagues on measures to maintain free ATM provision following reports of a review being undertaken by LINK.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64819","64819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692468","2017-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received on the outcomes of Phase two of the Troubled Families programme since its introduction in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64805","64805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692469","2017-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that all newly built homes comply with building regulations.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64806","64806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692470","2017-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the revenue accrued by the BBC from online advertisements outside the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64868","64868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692471","2017-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with S4C on her Department's contribution to that company's funding over the period of the independent review of S4C.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64854","64854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692472","2017-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the value of BBC revenue streams excluding the licence fee in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64866","64866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692473","2017-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to announce the terms of reference for the independent review of S4C.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64898","64898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692474","2017-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on what date she plans to publish her consultation on legislative proposals on the accountability of named directors of firms responsible for breaches of the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations and the related imposition  of fines for such breaches by the Information Commissioner's Office.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64780","64780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692475","2017-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government has made representations to the US Administration related to allegations made by Sebastian Gorka on bias and the impartiality of the BBC on Newsnight on 16 February 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64782","64782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692476","2017-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with the BBC on social mobility.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64749","64749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692477","2017-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding of the National Audit Office in its report, entitled The Equipment Plan 2016-2026, published in January 2017, that his Department must generate £5.8 billion of new savings from projects within the Equipment Plan to meet its new commitments; and how his Department plans to make such savings.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64755","64755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692478","2017-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to promote the participation of young people in the Sea Cadets organisation.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64774","64774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692479","2017-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which financial year (a) war pensions, (b) contributions to UN peacekeeping missions, (c) the Single Intelligence Account and (d) pensions for retired personnel were first included in his Department's reporting to NATO on defence expenditure.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64762","64762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692480","2017-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the nine Boeing P8 Poseidon aircraft to (a) be delivered and (b) come into service.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64763","64763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692481","2017-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's most recent estimate is of the total cost of developing and delivering the UK's maritime patrol capability to 2026; and how much of that cost relates to (a) P8 Poseidon aircraft, (b) wages and training, (c) infrastructure and (d) support at RAF Lossiemouth.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64764","64764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692482","2017-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date his Department plan to publish the National Shipbuilding Strategy.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64890","64890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692483","2017-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to ensure it provides robust and consistent advocacy on behalf of human rights defenders and in support of civic space in countries where the UK has strategic security and military interests.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64847","64847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692484","2017-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many army leavers aged under 25 have received (a) financial and (b) other assistance with housing resettlement in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64783","64783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692485","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the costs of establishing a pilot initiative based across two or more locally authority areas make provision for children who were born prematurely in the summer months to provide flexibility around timing of school entry to summer-born children in order to gather evidence to inform implementation of the School Admissions Code policy changes.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64815","64815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692486","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the potential effect of the new school funding formula on the level of funding for schools in Coventry South constituency in real terms for each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64821","64821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692487","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to promote the awareness of cyber security among school-aged children.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64861","64861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692488","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 63760, on GCE A-level, where the information requested is held.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64862","64862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692489","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students who are eligible for the service pupil premium have not received that premium in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64881","64881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692490","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 63761, on GCE A-level, where the information requested is held.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64865","64865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692491","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 63762, on GCE A-level, where the information requested is held.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64863","64863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692492","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been in receipt of the service pupil premium each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64874","64874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692493","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has a programme to encourage former teachers to return to that profession; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64894","64894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692494","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from (a) schools and (b) other bodies on the likely effect of the proposed funding formula on schools in Warrington; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64908","64908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692495","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the effect of changes of the Schools National Funding Formula on funding for schools in Calderdale.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64914","64914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692496","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what advice her Department is providing to schools projected to see reductions in funding under the Schools National Funding Formula on how to balance their budgets.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64915","64915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692497","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much additional funding her Department would require in order to ensure that no school saw a cut in its budget for 2017-18 as part of the Schools National Funding Formula.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64913","64913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692498","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2017 to Question 59084, on Educational Psychology, how many educational psychologists were employed in Norfolk in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64896","64896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692499","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the take-up of the service pupil premium in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64903","64903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692500","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the benefits of the Erasmus Plus programme for UK learners from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64930","64930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692501","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the benefits of the Erasmus Plus programme for UK (a) vocational education staff, (b) vocational students and (c) apprentices.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64933","64933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692502","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what contribution his Department has (a) made and (b) plans to make to discussions with the British Council on the future development of the Erasmus Plus programme in the vocational and technical skills sectors.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64934","64934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692503","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with higher education providers and institutions on continued UK participation in the Erasmus Plus programme (a) in the next two years and (b) when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64931","64931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692504","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the British Council on the merits of the continued UK participation in the Erasmus Plus programme (a) in the next two years and (b) after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64932","64932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692505","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils who took A-levels in government and politics in 2016 were recipients of free school meals during any of their time in secondary school.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64718","64718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692506","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils of each ethnicity took an A-level in government and politics in 2016.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64719","64719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692507","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that nurseries have access to adequate funding to afford well-qualified staff.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64713","64713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692508","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students (a) eligible and (b) not eligible for free school meals have taken (i) art, (ii) music and (iii) drama GCSE in each of the last six years; and what proportion of all students taking each of those GCSEs those figures represent.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64791","64791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692509","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of post-16 education institutions entered at least one pupil for an A-level in government and politics in 2016.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64717","64717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692510","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2017 to Question 59691, of the 30.7 per cent of children who did not achieve a good level of development in 2016, how many and what proportion did not attend any funded hours of child care.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64779","64779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692511","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2017 to Question 59691, of the 30.7 per cent of children who did not achieve a good level of development in 2016, how many and what proportion attended a childminder.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64778","64778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692512","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students (a) eligible and (b) not eligible for free school meals have taken (i) art, (ii) music and (iii) drama A-level in each of the last six years; and what proportion of all students taking each of those A-levels those figures represent.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64792","64792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692513","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of students eligible for free school meals have taken (a) art, (b) music and (c) drama GCSE in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64793","64793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692514","2017-02-24","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of students eligible for free school meals have taken (a) art, (b) music and (c) drama A-level in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64794","64794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692515","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total value is of public land transferred to free schools since the establishment of such schools.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64751","64751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692516","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to issue guidance alongside the new primary school framework.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64752","64752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692517","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much income has been accrued to her Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64738","64738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692518","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of environmental protections for chalk streams.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64775","64775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692519","2017-03-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what budget and staffing resources have been allocated by her Department and its agencies to Angling Trust Alert (ATA); what meetings officials of her Department and its agencies have had with ATA in the last three years; and what agreements have been reached at each of those meetings.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64765","64765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692520","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to tackle animal cruelty in puppy farms.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64919","64919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692521","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to remove the right of the RSPCA to prosecute cases of animal cruelty.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64920","64920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692522","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will consider invoking Articles 15 and 11 of the 1964 London Fisheries Convention after triggering Article 50 of the Lisbon Treaty.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64928","64928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692523","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political stability of Libya; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64922","64922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692524","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received recent representations from (a) parliamentarians and (b) the public on the legalisation of gay marriage in the overseas territories.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64904","64904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692525","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Tanzanian counterpart on that Government's proposals to publish lists of homosexuals.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64921","64921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692526","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his Israeli counterparts the effect of the Land Regularisation Bill recently passed by the Israeli Knesset on the number of Israeli settlements on the West Bank.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64925","64925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692527","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of LGBT rights in Tanzania.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64906","64906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692528","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to open negotiations with the Libyan Government on that country's frozen assets and provision for UK victims of Libyan-sponsored terrorism.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64879","64879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692529","2017-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic and development-related steps his Department is taking to support peace groups in Israel.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64916","64916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692530","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the next Overseas Territories Joint Ministerial Council is due to take place; and what is on the agenda for that meeting.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64870","64870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692531","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Government of Cyprus on assistance with the exploitation of gas and oil off the Cyprus coastline.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64840","64840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692532","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance the Government is giving to the Government of Nigeria to help tackle the activities of Boko Haram; and whether that assistance includes the provision of aircraft or helicopter support.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64841","64841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692533","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of China on organ harvesting in that country; and what the outcome of those representations has been.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64842","64842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692534","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to visit any of the overseas territories in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64882","64882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692535","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Palestinian Authority on death sentences imposed on Palestinians for the alleged collaboration with the Israeli Authorities.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64883","64883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692536","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure free and fair elections in Zimbabwe; and what discussions his Department has had with the UN on international action in that area.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64839","64839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692537","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2017 to Question 58527, what assessment he has made of the validity of the findings of the Saudi-led Coalition's Joint Incident Assessment Team's Investigations of eight airstrikes, published on 4 August 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64848","64848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692538","2017-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in South Sudan.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64823","64823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692539","2017-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed the case of Mr Juhel Miah, a British National who was removed from a flight from Reykjavik to New York on 16 February 2017, with his (a) Icelandic and (b) American counterparts.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64824","64824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692540","2017-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reason Mr Juhel Miah was removed from a flight from Reykjavik to New York on 16 February 2017.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64825","64825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692541","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) the US and (b) other NATO member states on a potential NATO Membership Action Plan for Georgia.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64816","64816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692542","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the draft statement on non-use force produced by the co-chairs of the Geneva International Discussions; and what assessment he has made of the prospects for an agreement on that draft among all parties to the discussions.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64813","64813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692543","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Georgian counterpart on maintaining diplomatic and economic ties between the UK and Georgia after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64814","64814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692544","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is providing to the EU Monitoring Mission in Georgia; and what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the work of that mission.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64809","64809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692545","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in the South Ossetia and Abkhazia regions of Georgia.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64810","64810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692546","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he expects the next round of the Geneva International Discussions to be held; and what the Government's priorities will be for those discussions.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64811","64811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692547","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who represented the Government at the 38th round of the Geneva International Discussions in December 2016; and what assessment the Government has made of the outcome of those discussions.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64812","64812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692548","2017-02-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he plans to respond to the letter of 7 June 2016 relating to the EU referendum that was previously transferred to the Department for Exiting the European Union following that Department's refusal to reply to the correspondence.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64789","64789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692549","2017-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Chinese Government on the recent expulsion of missionaries from the Chinese border region with North Korea.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64800","64800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692550","2017-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of the Central African Republic on the recent murder of a pastor with the Eglise du Christ en Centrafrique and destruction of his church's property.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64801","64801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692551","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has made to the governments of other EEA countries on funds owed to the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64750","64750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692552","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much income has been accrued to his Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64739","64739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692553","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse has been of an individual prescription of Fucithalmic viscous eye drops in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64698","64698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692554","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2017 to Question 63167, what proportion of the 217 vacant properties are (a) freehold, (b) leasehold, (c) other formal tenure agreements and (d) other.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64731","64731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692555","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS and its agencies spent on mental health services in each year since 2010 by region.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64732","64732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692556","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the rate of blood donation.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64703","64703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692557","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people on the organ transplant register died while waiting for a donated kidney in the last financial year.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64704","64704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692558","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment he has made of the potential effect on the NHS budget of increasing the number of people receiving kidney transplants to reduce the average waiting time on the transplant register and providing long-term dialysis for the same number of people.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64705","64705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692559","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made a comparative assessment of the average waiting time on the organ transplant register in (a) England and (b) each of the other devolved nations.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64706","64706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692560","2017-03-01","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 11 January 2017 and 24 January 2017 to Questions 58829 and 59987, if he will require Ambulance Service NHS Trusts to collect and hold centrally data on the usage of private ambulances and their crews provided by (a) St John's Ambulance, (b) Jigsaw Medical Services and (c) other providers.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64802","64802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692561","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what duty of care he has for residents and NHS patients in Liverpool following the Capsticks report and while the Kirkup Review is taking place before allowing local community services to be taken over by Bridgewater NHS Trust whose Care Quality Commission inspection report released on 6 February 2017 rates that Trust as requiring improvement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64786","64786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692562","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many families of newborn babies did not receive a mandated health visitor antenatal visit in the last year; and how many families did not receive a (a) new baby review, (b) 6 to 8 week assessment, (c) one-year assessment and (e) two to two-and-a-half year review.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64884","64884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692563","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for surgery to vacuum cancerous breast tumours to be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64830","64830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692564","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department makes available for elderly people on how to avoid harmful falls.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64831","64831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692565","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on the adequacy of provision in A&E departments for patients presenting with heart problems.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64832","64832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692566","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with hepatitis E in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64833","64833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692567","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the NHS is taking to help detect hidden genetic heart defects or conditions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64834","64834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692568","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the NHS has made of the potential merits of using laser technology to treat Alzheimer's disease in its early stages.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64835","64835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692569","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions clinical bodies have had with pharmaceutical companies on the development of new malaria prophylactics.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64836","64836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692570","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the NHS has made of potential links between anxiety and depression and the onset of cancer; and what recent steps his Department has taken to promote wellbeing.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64837","64837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692571","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what opportunity stakeholders will have to respond to the NICE's draft updated guideline on the management of Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64880","64880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692572","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the costs to the public purse of the treatment of side effects from long-term use of antidepressants.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64853","64853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692573","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 53721, what estimate he has made of the number of sustainable transformation plan areas with stroke service reconfiguration in their plans.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64864","64864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692574","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the accessibility of NICE-recommended treatments for patients at risk of recurrent depression in England.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64850","64850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692575","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 53721, what guidance his Department has given to clinical commissioning groups on the commissioning of stroke-specific services.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64867","64867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692576","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many acute mental health beds there were, and what the occupancy rate of such beds was, in Birmingham and Solihull Mental Health Foundation Trust in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64887","64887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692577","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with health providers in Warrington on proposals for a new hospital for Warrington; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64909","64909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692578","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what factors are taken into account when deciding on the location of proposed new hospitals; and what weighting is given to each of those factors.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64910","64910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692579","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the effectiveness of the new records movement service being piloted in West Yorkshire by Capita.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64876","64876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692580","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to extend the new records movement service, currently being piloted in West Yorkshire, to the rest of the country.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64877","64877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692581","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data (a) Clinical Reference Groups and (b) the Prescribed Specialised Services Advisory Group are required to collect and consider in the course of making their decisions.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64912","64912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692582","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on patient care of moving Newcastle's Child and Adult Heart Surgery Unit from the Freeman Hospital to the Royal Victoria Infirmary.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64936","64936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692583","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government takes to ensure minimal disruption to quality of service when NHS services are moved from one site to another.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64937","64937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692584","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 63820, if he will take steps to increase the maximum length of time for which data can be collected on treatments funded from the Cancer Drugs Fund from two to three years.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64926","64926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692585","2017-02-24","Department of Health","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the public consultation process for moving NHS services between two locations.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64940","64940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692586","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the then Minister for Policing, Crime and Criminal Justice on 20 January 2016, Official Report, column 1479, what progress her Department has made on the use of cannabis for the purposes of medicinal research.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64923","64923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692587","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to proactively identify unaccompanied refugee children and vulnerable families in Greece and Italy who can be brought to join family members in the UK; and what use her Department has made of the discretionary powers under the Dublin III Regulations to take charge of such children and families.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64924","64924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692588","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's press release of 29 December 2016, psychoactive substances ban six months on: almost 500 arrests and first convictions, of the 500 people arrested how many were (a) charged with an offence and (b) prosecuted with an offence under the Psychoactive Substances Act 2016; how many of those prosecutions were (i) unsuccessful and (ii) successful; and of the four prosecutions that resulted in prison sentences, if she will list for each case (A) the grounds for prosecution, (B) how the defendants pleaded, (C) whether those defendants were found guilty of any other offences and (D) what sentence was given by the court.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64918","64918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692589","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the reasons why no local authority has yet implemented an early morning alcohol restriction order.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64899","64899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692590","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many premises and prohibition (a) notices and (b) orders have been issued since the Psychoactive Substances Act 2016 came into force.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64907","64907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692591","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations her Department has received from local authorities on the merits of early morning alcohol restriction orders.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64900","64900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692592","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's press release of 29 December 2016, psychoactive substances ban six months on: almost 500 arrests and first convictions, what the alleged offences were for each person arrested; and which police force carried out each arrest.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64878","64878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692593","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the seizure of assets of human traffickers at the point of arrest, rather than conviction.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64829","64829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692594","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to consult with local authorities on whether they can make more places available under Section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64871","64871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692595","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that children outside of formal camps in Greece and Italy are assessed for relocation to the UK under the Dublin Regulation and Section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64872","64872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692596","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the eligibility criteria for the 150 remaining places announced under Section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016, and for any further transfers to the UK, will prioritise individual vulnerability and the best interests of children.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64873","64873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692597","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62659, on sex establishments: licensing, for what reason there is no right given to objectors to appeal against a local authority licensing committee's decision to grant a sexual entertainment licence.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64808","64808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692598","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the merits of short-term study visas for EU citizens wishing to study in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64851","64851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692599","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of this effect of any changes to the short-term study visa system arising from the UK's decision to leave the EU, on the number of foreign nationals seeking to study English.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64852","64852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692600","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded instances there were of police cells being used as places of safety for people detained under section 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983 in 2015-16.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64804","64804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692601","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people convicted of human trafficking in the UK who returned to their country of origin to serve their sentence have had their assets (a) in the UK or (b) overseas seized to compensate (i) victims of trafficking, (ii) police forces and (iii) HM Treasury; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64701","64701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692602","2017-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how often each out of court disposals panel met in each constabulary area in England in 2016; how many cases were examined by each of those panels during that period; how many of those cases (a) related to a caution, (b) were dealt with by restorative justice, (c) related to a youth caution, (d) were dealt with by a fixed penalty notice and caution, (e) were dealt with by youth triage and (f) were dealt with by a conditional caution during that period; and how many of those cases related to (i) youths and (ii) adults.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64766","64766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692603","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Walsall North of 16 January 2017 on behalf of a constituent, on asylum claims from people fleeing torture and repressive regimes.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64777","64777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692604","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures were in place to ensure that members of the Cleveland Police Authority were required to declare any relevant business interests arising from procurement or outsourcing partnership arrangements instigated by Cleveland Police prior to Operation Sacristy.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64772","64772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692605","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of reports that young people are receiving criminal records for sending indecent images without having been charged with an offence.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64787","64787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692606","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures were in place to ensure that members of the Cleveland Police Authority did not benefit financially from any procurement or outsourcing partnership arrangements instigated by Cleveland Police prior to Operation Sacristy.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64770","64770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692607","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will reconsider the requirement to record as a crime the sending of indecent images by young people while not charging them formally.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64788","64788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692608","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the anti-corruption strategies that Cleveland Police had in place in accordance with the ACPO police integrity model prior to Operation Sacristy.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64771","64771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692609","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much income has been accrued to her Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64740","64740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692610","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the potential to increase the number of unaccompanied child refugees received by Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64756","64756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692611","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions have taken place between HM Inspectorate of Constabulary and the Chief Constable of Cleveland Police on the terms of reference for Operation Sacristy; and what representations she has received on potential concerns raised by the Chief Constable of Cleveland Police on those terms of reference during those negotiations.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64757","64757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692612","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department took to protect witnesses during the Operation Sacristy investigation into corruption allegations at Cleveland Police Authority.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64758","64758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692613","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ensure that (a) evidence was not destroyed and (b) witnesses were not intimidated by members of Cleveland Police during Operation Sacristy.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64759","64759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692614","2017-02-24","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Operation Sacristy in (a) identifying instances of corruption in Cleveland Police and (b) preventing future such corruption.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64760","64760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692615","2017-02-23","Department for International Development","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is giving to non-governmental organisations promoting human rights in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64773","64773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692616","2017-02-23","Department for International Development","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her South Sudanese counterpart on the flow of emergency aid into areas affected by the UN-declared famine in South Sudan.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64807","64807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692617","2017-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to answer Question 55553, on prison sentences: Lancashire, tabled by the hon. Member for Preston on 30 November 2016; and what the reasons are for the time taken to answer that Question.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64826","64826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692618","2017-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether she plans to increase the pay of frontline prison staff outside of the South East.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64822","64822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692619","2017-03-02","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2017 to Question 59530, if she will provide a breakdown of the £450,000 cost of procurement activity for the supplier of the new electronic monitoring tags based on satellite tracking technology.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64827","64827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692620","2017-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many buildings within the prison estate have exceeded their intended life cycle.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64889","64889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692621","2017-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many dog patrol officers have been employed in prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64886","64886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692622","2017-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will publish Fair and Sustainable pay scales for all staff grades incorporating changes made as a result of her announcement of 19 February 2017 on steps to strengthen prison frontline and attract new recruits.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64901","64901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692623","2017-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many serving band 3 prison officers, by prison establishment, are eligible for a (a) pay increase and (b) £5,000 pay increase as a result of the announcement of 19 February 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64935","64935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692624","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officer posts are currently vacant in each region.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64927","64927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692625","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff in the prison service have worked on investigations into alleged corruption in prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64699","64699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692626","2017-02-23","Attorney General","2017-02-21","To ask the Attorney General, whether any individuals under investigation during Operation Sacristy were charged with perverting the course of justice.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64769","64769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692627","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been given an immediate custodial sentence of less than six months in courts used by North Wales Police in North Wales by (a) gender and (b) offence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64767","64767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692628","2017-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what dates she has held discussions with the (a) Prison Service Pay Review Body, (b) Prison Governors Association and (c) Prison Officers Association on pay increases for Band 2 operational support grades, Band 4 supervising officers and Band 5 custodial managers in HM Prison Service.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64715","64715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692629","2017-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what dates she met the (a) Prison Service Pay Review Body, (b) Prison Governors Association and (c) Prison Officers Association to discuss pay increases for Band 3 prison officers.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64716","64716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692630","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to ensure that judges in family courts receive training on preventing gender bias.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64754","64754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692631","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork assessors are employed in each public sector prison.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64707","64707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692632","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) Band 3 Prison Officer job offers have been made by HM Prison Service and (b) prison officer entry level training starts have been recorded since 3 November 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64708","64708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692633","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will list what mental health training courses are available to prison officers who are not Assessment, Care in Custody and Teamwork assessors after those officers have completed prison officer entry level training.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64709","64709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692634","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many candidates (a) started and (b) did not complete prison officer entry level training in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64710","64710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692635","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) Band 2 operational support grades, (b) Band 3 to 5 prison officers and (c) other grades of staff have been employed at HM Prison Northumberland in each quarter since December 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64711","64711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692636","2017-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria she used to identify 31 prisons where Band 3 prison officers will receive salary increases of up to £5,000 as announced by her Department on 19 February 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64712","64712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692637","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much income has been accrued to her Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64741","64741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692638","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) procedures and (b) timescales are by which findings of not guilty are entered into the criminal record database; and at what point a person found not guilty receives a clear Disclosure and Barring Service check.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64746","64746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692639","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment tribunal fee remission claims there have been in each month of the last five years; and how many of those claims have been successful.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64747","64747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692640","2017-02-23","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Republic of Ireland has implemented enhanced employment equality legislation as required by paragraph 9 of the Chapter on rights, safeguards and equality of opportunity in the Belfast Agreement of 1998.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64844","64844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692641","2017-02-23","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Republic of Ireland has ratified the Council of Europe Framework Convention on National Minorities as required by paragraph 9 of the Chapter on rights, safeguards and equality of opportunity in the Belfast Agreement of 1998.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64845","64845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692642","2017-02-23","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Republic of Ireland has established a human rights commission with a mandate and remit equivalent to that within Northern Ireland as required by paragraph 9 of the Chapter on rights, safeguards and equality of opportunity in the Belfast Agreement of 1998.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64846","64846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692643","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make arrangements for an early state or official visit to the UK by the recently elected President of Germany.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64905","64905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692644","2017-02-23","Department for Transport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to introduce legislative proposals to prevent vehicles parking on pavements.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64875","64875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692645","2017-03-01","Department for Transport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cars powered by (a) petrol, (b) diesel and (c) alternative fuel are currently registered for use on public roads; and how many such cars were registered in each of these categories in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64902","64902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692646","2017-02-24","Department for Transport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) Hackney Carriage and (b) private hire licences are currently issued in each local authority in England and Wales.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64785","64785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692648","2017-02-23","Department for Transport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much income has been accrued to his Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64742","64742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692649","2017-02-24","Department for Transport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the fast-track security clearance charge has raised at each airport in each year since that charge's implementation.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64761","64761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692650","2017-02-24","Department for Transport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the abolition of vehicle tax discs on the number of drivers avoiding paying road tax.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64734","64734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692651","2017-02-23","Department for Transport","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the provision of additional junctions to decrease ramp times on the strategic road network (a) in general and (b) at the missing Junction 6 of the M27.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64776","64776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692652","2017-02-24","Wales Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers of the Welsh Government on the building of a train station at Cardiff Airport.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64911","64911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692653","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Proposal for the future of Liverpool Edge Hill and Liverpool Wavertree jobcentres, published in January 2017, (a) how many work coaches will be available to serve claimants who previously used the jobcentres in Wavertree and Edge Hill and (b) for how many hours a week such coaches will be available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64888","64888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692654","2017-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on the funding of adult social care of the reclassification of new homes bonus as an adult social care grant.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64893","64893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692655","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what special provision is made for veterans aged under the age of 25 related to housing benefit eligibility, and how many veterans have benefited from such provision in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64784","64784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692656","2017-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps his Department has taken to help people with long-term illness return to work.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64843","64843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692657","2017-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to ensure funds of equivalent value to the UK's allocation from the European Social Fund are made available for the same purposes after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64849","64849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692658","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to increase the amount which people individually save through auto-enrolment into pension schemes.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64795","64795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692659","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to introduce new rules which will not require reassessments for employment and support allowance for people with severe life-long conditions; and if he will publish the criteria by which severe life-long conditions are defined as such for the purposes of exemption from those assessments.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64797","64797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692660","2017-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department last met representatives of Allied Steel and Wire pension scheme members.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64781","64781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692661","2017-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much income has been accrued to his Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64744","64744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692662","2017-02-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much income has been accrued to his Department from premium rate telephone lines in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64735","64735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692663","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are in place to ensure that companies which find evidence of modern slavery within their supply chains are required to report such evidence.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64745","64745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692664","2017-02-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to review the effect of post office closures on older people.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64714","64714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692665","2017-02-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department takes steps to monitor the availability of post offices for local communities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64730","64730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692666","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies on support for fuel-poor households of the report by National Energy Advice of February 2017 entitled, In from the cold.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64855","64855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692667","2017-02-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of EU structural funding, such as the European Regional Development Fund, on the UK's ability to build research capacity in less economically developed regions of the UK.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64803","64803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692668","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the future asset value of the UK Green Investment Bank's investments in the Galloper and Rampion wind farms upon completion of their construction.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64820","64820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692669","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of energy was generated from renewable sources in (a) the UK and (b) Greater London in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64895","64895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692670","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post offices are currently operational in Scotland.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64891","64891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692671","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether Post Office Ltd includes a count of temporarily closed post offices in meeting the Government's criteria for ensuring fair and reasonable access to post offices.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64892","64892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692672","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the number of jobs in the green economy.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64897","64897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692673","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what (a) coal, (b) gas, (c) hydro, (d) wind and (e) solar energy projects his Department's Prosperity Fund has invested in during each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64938","64938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692674","2017-02-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post offices in Scotland have closed since 2010.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64939","64939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692675","2017-02-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much public funding has been supplied to the Green Investment Bank in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64929","64929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692676","2017-02-23","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the 51 economic sectors are which have been identified by his Department during its work on the UK's negotiations to leave the EU; and if he will place a list of those sectors in the Library.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64702","64702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693178","2017-02-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to build and develop more homes.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908913","908913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693249","2017-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to issue new guidance to local authority air quality monitoring units after the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908921","908921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693250","2017-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to issue new guidance to local authority air quality monitoring units after the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908929","908929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/693251","2017-02-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to issue new guidance to local authority air quality monitoring units after the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908925","908925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706371","2017-03-01","Scotland Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on income tax rates.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908911","908911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706372","2017-03-01","Scotland Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the level of government funding for the energy sector in Scotland.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908906","908906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/706373","2017-03-01","Scotland Office","2017-02-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the effect of City Deals on cities in Scotland.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908912","908912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691760","2017-02-22","Attorney General","2017-02-20","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Law Officers' Departments have spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64367","64367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691761","2017-02-22","Attorney General","2017-02-20","To ask the Attorney General, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by the Law Officers' Departments was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate he has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64388","64388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691762","2017-02-22","Attorney General","2017-02-20","To ask the Attorney General, whether the Law Officers' Departments operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of his Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64523","64523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691763","2017-02-22","Attorney General","2017-02-20","To ask the Attorney General, what discussions he has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64537","64537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691764","2017-02-22","Cabinet Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64538","64538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691765","2017-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for updates to the Cyber Essentials scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64527","64527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691766","2017-02-22","Cabinet Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many equality impact assessments have been carried out in the last three years on public service reforms which impact on (a) departmental staff and (b) members of the public; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64440","64440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691767","2017-02-22","Cabinet Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of his Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64465","64465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691768","2017-02-22","Cabinet Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64368","64368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691769","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average income for (a) men and (b) women in Coventry South constituency was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64649","64649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691770","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to make available the free software from HM Revenue and Customs to enable compliance with quarterly reporting obligations being imposed under the Making Tax Digital programme.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64652","64652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691771","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a revision of his Department's forecast of the annual impact of leaving the EU on the UK after 15 years which was published in his Department's analysis entitled the long-term economic impact of EU membership and the alternatives Cm 9250, published in April 2016,  to reflect proposals published in The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, of February 2017.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64645","64645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691772","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64553","64553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691773","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse will be of the decision to keep salary sacrifice schemes in place for school fees for each year until 2020-21.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64682","64682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691774","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's policy is on how the money raised by the Apprenticeship Levy will be spent.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64684","64684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691775","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential VAT owed to his Department in respect of supply of passenger transportation services arising as a result of the employment tribunal ruling of 28 October 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64347","64347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691776","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64384","64384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691777","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by his Department was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate he has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64408","64408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691778","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what right to buy receipts local authorities have paid to the Exchequer including (a) capital receipts, (b) any interest accrued and (c) any other relevant amount in each financial year from 2012-13.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64412","64412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691779","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential costs to the public purse of increasing compensation to members of the Equitable Life Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64459","64459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691780","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to reopen the Equitable Life Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64460","64460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691781","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2017 to Question 63181, for what reasons the $400 million loan provided to GE Oil & Gas via UK Export Finance in January 2017 to support the development of oil and gas fields off the coast of Ghana is not considered a subsidy to fossil fuel production or consumption by the Government.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64417","64417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691782","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many equality impact assessments have been carried out in the last three years on public service reforms which impact on (a) departmental staff and (b) members of the public; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64452","64452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691783","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2017 to Question 63181, for what reasons the VAT exemption for aviation kerosene is not considered a subsidy to fossil fuel production or consumption by the Government.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64418","64418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691784","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2017 to Question 63181, for what reasons the funding provided through the Capacity Mechanism to diesel, coal and gas-fired electricity generation is not considered a subsidy to fossil fuel production or consumption by the Government.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64419","64419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691785","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2017 to Question 63181, for what reasons the contract awarded by the Government to PGS and Western Geo to collect seismic data in the North Sea UK is not considered a subsidy to fossil fuel production or consumption by the Government.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64420","64420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691786","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of HM Revenue and Customs budget is allocated to investigate landfill tax fraud.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64488","64488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691787","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate HM Revenue and Customs has made of the amount of landfill tax outstanding from landfill operators.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64532","64532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691788","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints HM Revenue and Customs has received of non-payment of landfill tax in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64528","64528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691789","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many visits to landfill sites in the (a) UK and (b) North East HM Revenue and Customs has conducted to check landfill tax payments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64529","64529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691790","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many criminal prosecutions for non-payment or other breaches of the law related to the landfill tax there have been in each of the last five years in  the (a) UK and (b) North East.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64531","64531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691791","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of his Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64481","64481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691792","2017-02-23","HM Treasury","2017-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57196, when his Department will publish its response to the consultation on Making Tax Digital.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64587","64587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691793","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64539","64539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691794","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of his Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64466","64466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691795","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2017 to Question 63539, what the time period will be over which he plans the additional fee income to be generated.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64421","64421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691796","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of properties purchased through the Help to Buy scheme were purchased on a leasehold basis.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64498","64498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691797","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people have had a fair rent registered in (a) Tynemouth constituency and (b) North Tyneside borough since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64499","64499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691798","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on the number of houses sold of the proposal to extend the right to buy to homes built by council housing companies in the Housing White Paper.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64500","64500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691799","2017-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to require whoever is Chair of the Leasehold Advisory Service to have no business interests in the leasehold sector.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64504","64504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691800","2017-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to require at least one member of the Board of the Leasehold Advisory Service to be an independent representative of leaseholders.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64505","64505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691801","2017-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a new homes ombudsman.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64456","64456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691802","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the lack of a cost floor on housing associations whose tenants purchase their home through the right to acquire.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64439","64439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691803","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the judgment of 29 July 2015 in Woolway v. Mazars on eligibility for small business rate relief among small businesses.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64410","64410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691804","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities have in place a selective licence scheme for private rented properties within their area; when each such scheme began; and when each such scheme is due to end or need renewal.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64411","64411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691805","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with Ministerial colleagues at the Department of Health on (a) how the proposed cap on residential care costs is to be funded and (b) when that cap is planned to be implemented.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64340","64340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691806","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by his Department was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate he has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64389","64389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691807","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64369","64369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691808","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish a list of all three pump fire stations in England, by name and local authority.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64686","64686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691809","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much has been spent from the public purse on advertising and other promotional material for the Own Your Home initiatives in each year since 2010-11 by (a) region, (b) local authority area and (c) constituency.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64665","64665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691810","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the criteria are for the Government's decisions on how much funding for help to rent projects to allocate to local authorities; and whether the Government plans to increase such funding.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64621","64621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691811","2017-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding for help to rent projects the Government has provided to local authorities in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64623","64623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691812","2017-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with relevant stakeholders on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on horse-racing and bloodstock industries in the UK and Ireland.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64597","64597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691813","2017-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to promote and develop cricket in (a) St Helens, (b) Merseyside and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64598","64598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691814","2017-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate her Department has made of the contribution of the horse-racing industry to the economy in the (a) North West and (b) UK.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64595","64595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691815","2017-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding she has provided to libraries in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64667","64667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691816","2017-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department has spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64370","64370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691817","2017-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by her Department was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate she has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64390","64390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691818","2017-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much information her Department holds on the number of metres of last-mile copper line laid or refurbished over the last five years which was funded from the public purse.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64348","64348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691819","2017-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what government funding is available to community groups who wish to take over the running of libraries from local authorities.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64455","64455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691820","2017-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her plans are to ensure that there is sufficient competition in the mobile phone industry after the sale of mobile phone spectrum.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64457","64457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691821","2017-02-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of metres of copper line laid by British Telecom in 2013, 2014, 2015 and 2016.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64364","64364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691822","2017-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many equality impact assessments have been carried out in the last three years on public service reforms which impact on (a) departmental staff and (b) members of the public; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64441","64441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691823","2017-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of her Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64467","64467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691824","2017-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64540","64540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691825","2017-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to promote the sharing of facilities between different areas of the arts.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64566","64566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691826","2017-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what financial support she provides to small football clubs to improve disabled access at such clubs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64567","64567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691827","2017-02-23","Cabinet Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the letter of 14 February 2017 from the Minister of State for Digital and Culture to the hon Member for Birkenhead, which services and benefits he plans to include within the affirmative procedures for public service delivery under the Digital Economy Bill.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64586","64586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691828","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64541","64541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691829","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of his Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64468","64468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691830","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many equality impact assessments have been carried out in the last three years on public service reforms which impact on (a) departmental staff and (b) members of the public; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64442","64442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691831","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the scheduled end-of-service date is for each Trafalgar class submarine.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64489","64489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691832","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timescales for the in-service delivery of Astute class boats are.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64490","64490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691833","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions his Department has had with NATO on the UK contribution to Operation Resolute Support and the number of UK personnel supporting that operation.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64491","64491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691834","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel are deployed in South Sudan.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64492","64492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691835","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the value to UK national gross domestic product of the Global F-35 Lightning II programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64493","64493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691836","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department provides for servicemen and women's children who have an autism diagnosis.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64426","64426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691837","2017-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Government's policy is on NATO Transformation.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64514","64514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691838","2017-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officers in the armed forces, at what rank and position, are attached to NATO Transformation Command.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64515","64515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691839","2017-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by his Department was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate he has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64405","64405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691840","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64371","64371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691841","2017-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2017 to Question 59060, what sort of activities his Department defines as physical security breaches.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64613","64613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691842","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's Major Projects Portfolio data 2015, published in July 2016, whether the increasing risk to Initial Capability of the F-35 Lightning II programme as a result of manning issues is extant.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64606","64606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691843","2017-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's Major Projects Portfolio data 2015, published in July 2016, whether the number of Royal Navy and Royal Air Force specialists required to support the F-35 Lightning II programme capability has been increased.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64607","64607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691844","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to evaluate the effect of the implementation of the new national curriculum on (a) teacher workload, (b) Special and Educational Needs and Disability inclusion and (c) school budgets.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64588","64588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691845","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2017 to Question 63434, whether she plans to visit any schools in Haringey in the next six months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64612","64612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691846","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Minister of State for Vulnerable Children and Families' reference to local authorities seeking exemptions during the committee stage of the Children and Social Work Bill on 10 January 2017, if she will publish a list of those local authorities and which exemptions they sought.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64674","64674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691847","2017-02-27","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has any plans to introduce the teaching of Welsh as an optional modern language in schools on the England-Wales border.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64655","64655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691848","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings her Ministers have had with (a) G4S, (b) Serco and (c) Virgin Care on children's social care in the last two years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64675","64675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691849","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the article in The Times of 14 February 2017 in the name of the Minister of State for School Standards, what evidence her Department has for the positive response of the Archbishop of Canterbury to proposals to lift the 50 per cent cap on religious selection by free schools.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64669","64669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691850","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish the (a) letter sent from the chief social worker to local authorities in October 2016 on the Children and Social Work Bill and (b) responses received.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64676","64676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691851","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number and proportion of eligible two-year-olds who have not taken up a funded early education place (a) nationally and (b) in each local authority.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64677","64677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691852","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the extent of any early years development gap measured by the Early Years Foundation Stage between those children eligible for free school meals and their peers (a) nationally and (b) in each local authority for the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64678","64678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691853","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of how much has been allocated from the public purse on average to local authorities for each early years place for a two-year-old eligible for a free early education place.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64680","64680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691854","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what number and proportion of eligible two-year-olds who benefit from  early years education are among the lowest quintile of disadvantaged two-year-olds.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64681","64681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691855","2017-02-23","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps her Department has taken to promote physical activity among school pupils.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64690","64690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691856","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64372","64372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691857","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by her Department was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate she has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64391","64391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691858","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consultation her Department has conducted with parents on nursery staff qualifications.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64496","64496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691859","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many early years teachers she expects to be recruited over the course of this Parliament; and whether the new early years workforce strategy will include details of dedicated funding for the recruitment of new early years teachers.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64494","64494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691860","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the poorest children start primary school with a good level of development.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64495","64495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691861","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many equality impact assessments have been carried out in the last three years on public service reforms which impact on (a) departmental staff and (b) members of the public; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64443","64443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691862","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of her Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64469","64469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691863","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64542","64542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691864","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64543","64543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691865","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that GM food products are safe to eat and do not harm the environment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64561","64561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691866","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the planting of mature trees.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64562","64562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691867","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that fast food wrappers do not contain substances which are harmful to human health.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64583","64583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691868","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to discourage farming methods which lead to the overuse of antibiotics.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64565","64565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691869","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for the farming sector of the UK leaving the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64584","64584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691870","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect on the environment of wood-burning stoves.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64585","64585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691871","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of her Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64470","64470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691872","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many enforcement notices have been taken out against landfill operators in the (a) UK and (b) North East in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64530","64530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691873","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on the implementation of the Central Equine Database.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64423","64423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691874","2017-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to tackle unduly lenient sentencing for animal cruelty offences.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64497","64497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691875","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to support an extension of the commercial hook and line fishing moratorium into April, May and June 2017 in areas where there is evidence of spawning among bass stocks.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64484","64484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691876","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to make commercial fishermen aware of new rules and enforcement measures to deter illegal netting of bass agreed by the Council and set out in Article 9 of Council Resolution (EU) 2017/127.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64485","64485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691877","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by her Department was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate she has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64392","64392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691878","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans for the UK to be compliant with the 2008 Ambient Air Quality Directive.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64339","64339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691879","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the potential cost to the public purse of introducing mandatory food waste collections by local authorities.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64349","64349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691880","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will commission research into the operation of zero-waste grocery shops in overseas territories to identify potential benefits that such shops could bring to the UK.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64345","64345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691881","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64373","64373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691882","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Hunting Act 2004 in each police force area in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64671","64671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691883","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of which exclusive and mixed international environmental agreements in which the EU currently participates the Government plans to seek to be party to or otherwise maintain the provisions of after the UK leaves the EU; and which of those agreements (a) the Government will have to renegotiate and (b) will remain in force as the UK is a signatory in its own right.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64664","64664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691884","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Wild Animals (Protection) Act 1996 in each police force area in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64648","64648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691885","2017-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to introduce a ban on the export of live animals for slaughter.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64580","64580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691886","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Protection of Badgers Act 1992 in each police force area in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64591","64591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691887","2017-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Deer Act 1991 in each police force area in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64592","64592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691888","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received recent representation from (a) parliamentarians and (b) members of the public on the independence of the judiciary in the US.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64610","64610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691889","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to raise with the (a) Government of Syria and (b) UN the need for unhindered access by independent international monitors to all places of detention in Syria.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64651","64651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691891","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will prioritise the issue of extrajudicial executions and torture in detention in its discussions with (a) the Syrian authorities and (b) states that support the Syrian Government, in its role as a member of the International Syria Support Group.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64688","64688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691892","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the government has had with the governments of (a) Cameroon and (b) other countries on the political situation in Cameroon.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64344","64344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691893","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64375","64375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691894","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received on the humanitarian situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64346","64346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691895","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by his Department was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate he has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64394","64394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691896","2017-02-22","Department for Education","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by the Government Equalities Office was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate she has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64395","64395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691897","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will take steps to work with UK allies to expel the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps and its proxies from Syria, Iraq and Yemen and to impose sanctions on that organisation.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64415","64415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691898","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps' and the (a) persecution of dissidents and dual nationals in Iran, (b) exporting of terrorism abroad and (c) need to proscribe that organisation.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64414","64414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691899","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62082, what recent assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of allegations that the Palestinian Authority honours those who have killed Israelis.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64413","64413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691900","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will support an independent international investigation into human rights violations committed by the Burmese military against the Rohingya Muslin community in Rakhine state as set out in the recent report of the Office of the UN High Commissioner for Human Rights at the forthcoming session of the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64437","64437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691901","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many equality impact assessments have been carried out in the last three years on public service reforms which impact on (a) departmental staff and (b) members of the public; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64444","64444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691902","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the talks on a Cyprus settlement are scheduled to reconvene.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64424","64424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691903","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political and international security situation in Algeria.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64425","64425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691904","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Government of Algeria on the political and security situation in that country.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64427","64427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691905","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of his Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64472","64472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691906","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64544","64544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691907","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when a Minister of his Department last undertook an official visit to Cyprus.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64564","64564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691908","2017-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will take steps to ensure that alleged crimes perpetrated by the Syrian Government at Saydnaya detention facility are investigated.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64590","64590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691909","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to make (a) single injection cancer treatments and (b) intra-beam radiotherapy available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64569","64569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691910","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Department for Exiting the European Union on the contents of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64545","64545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691911","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing and other health bodies on a virtual reality game to detect and treat schizophrenia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64582","64582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691912","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice the NHS provides to pregnant women over the age of 40.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64570","64570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691913","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Academy of Medical Royal Colleges on advice provided to patients on the necessity for appendix operations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64571","64571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691914","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to make blood tests for the diagnoses of Parkinson's disease available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64572","64572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691915","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to promote wellbeing among people aged 16 to 24.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64573","64573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691916","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department operates a ban the box employment policy in respect of ex-offender job applicants with unspent convictions; and how many employees of his Department have unspent convictions.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64474","64474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691917","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that sex change drugs are not prescribed to children without parental consent.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64557","64557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691918","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the cost of prescription pain-killers to the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64558","64558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691919","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to make intraoperative radiotherapy for breast cancer available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64559","64559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691920","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will set out the Government's plans to address Seasonal Affective Disorder.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64556","64556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691921","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to make the coupler to reduce high blood pressure available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64560","64560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691922","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice is given to patients and families of deceased patients who no longer require prescribed medicines, aids and medical equipment.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64526","64526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691923","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 61600, if he will amend the guidelines in line with the consensus of contemporary scientific thinking on homeopathy; and if he will establish a timetable for the consultation on homeopathy announced in November 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64534","64534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691924","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with East Midlands Ambulance Service on its response times to calls.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64429","64429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691925","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the potential effect on the four-week diagnostic standard for cancer of any increase in the demand for endoscopy services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64458","64458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691926","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many equality impact assessments have been carried out in the last three years on public service reforms which impact on (a) departmental staff and (b) members of the public; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64446","64446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691927","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on proposals for the strategy and objectives of the organisation planned to be formed from NHS Property Services and Community Health Partnerships.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64433","64433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691928","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2016 to Question 52599, what progress his Department has made on working with NHS Property Services to resolve complex billing-related disputes arising from the move to market rents.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64432","64432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691929","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients waited more than 18 weeks for bariatric surgery in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2014-15, (c) 2013-14 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64503","64503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691930","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the use of compounds with pharmacological effects at any stage of the procedures licenced under the Human Fertilisation and Embryology (Mitochondrial Donation) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64501","64501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691931","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the target uptake rate is for the bowel cancer screening programme in England; how many clinical commissioning groups are meeting that target uptake rate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64518","64518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691932","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total (a) number and (b) value of Government contracts that have been contracted out by his Department was in each year since 2010; what the value of pro bono costs was in each such year; and what estimate he has made of the number of work days contracted out in each such year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64396","64396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691933","2017-02-28","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department plans to fund the proposed cap on residential care costs.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64365","64365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691934","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to align the work of Cancer Alliances and Sustainability and Transformation Plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64434","64434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691935","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what amount is owed from each European Economic Area country in respect of healthcare provided to citizens of those countries by the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64435","64435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691936","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the proportion of NHS staff from European Economic Area countries was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64436","64436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691937","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is responsible for agreeing salary increases for executive, GP and lay members of a clinical commissioning group's governing body; and whether NHS England or his Department is required to sign off salary increases above a specified amount or proportion of existing salary.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64355","64355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691938","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what salary increases have been awarded to (a) executive, (b) GP and (c) lay members of Liverpool Clinical Commissioning Group's governing body in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15, (iii) 2015-16 and (iv) 2016-17.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64356","64356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691939","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many X-rays have been carried out at Eltham Community Hospital since that hospital opened; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64357","64357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691940","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to Greenwich Clinical Commissioning Group is of commissioning 17 beds for patients preparing to return home from St Mary's Hospital, Sidcup; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64358","64358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691941","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many beds Greenwich Clinical Commissioning Group has commissioned for respite or rehabilitation of patients returning home from hospital stays; and what the costs are of that activity at (a) Eltham Community Hospital and (b) each other location within that Group's area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64359","64359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691942","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS is of maintaining an empty ward at Eltham Community Hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64360","64360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691943","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of changes in the value of supplier costs in the NHS as a result of the change in the value of sterling against the (a) euro and (b) dollar since 23 June 2016","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64361","64361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691944","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the change in the value of sterling against the (a) euro and (b) dollar since 23 June 2016 on the ability of the NHS to achieve the efficiency target set out in the Carter review of NHS efficiency.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64362","64362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691945","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on (a) Uber for Business and (b) other Uber transactions since 28 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64376","64376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691946","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in (a) England, (b) Greater London and (c) the London Borough of Newham have been treated by the NHS for (i) drug and (ii) alcohol abuse in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64691","64691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691947","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62814, on NHS Pay, what estimate he has made of what the real-terms change in the salary has been for a member of NHS staff who was at the top of their pay band between 2009-10 and 2015-16, who remained in the same job, worked as a full-time employee and was not in receipt of unsocial hours pay (a) on average across all Agenda for Change staff groups and (b) by Agenda for Change pay band.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64685","64685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691948","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the side effects of long-term use of anti-depressants.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64673","64673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691949","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for anti-depressant medication were issued in England in each of the last 10 years to (a) adults and (b) children.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64672","64672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691950","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with how many families the family nurse partnership has worked (a) nationally and (b) in each local authority area that it has been in place in each year since that partnership scheme was established.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64679","64679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691951","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average NHS ambulance response times in (a) England, (b) Greater London and (c) the London Borough of Newham were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64694","64694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691952","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of compensation available to people who have become disabled as a result of taking the Pandemrix vaccination; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64695","64695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691953","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to ensure that NHS staff are aware of the stopping over-medication of people with a learning disability pledge; and what steps are being taken to ensure that people with autism or a learning disability are not prescribed unnecessary antipsychotic or antidepressant drugs.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64622","64622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691954","2017-02-23","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2017 to Question 63032, and with reference to the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health of February 2016, what the reason is for the time taken for the publication of the Mental Health Workforce Strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64641","64641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691955","2017-02-22","Department of Health","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current availability of palbociclib is on the NHS; and what steps are being taken to ensure that all breast cancer patients who would benefit from that drug are able to access it.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64627","64627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691956","2017-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 February 2017 to Question 61605, for what reason there is no reference to any investigation into self-inflicted death in prison in that Answer.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64640","64640"
