"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126487","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps his Department has taken to support communities to set up renewable energy co-operatives.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254193","254193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126488","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase take-home pay for low-paid workers.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254189","254189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126489","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister's letter of 10 May 2018 to Sir Martin Moore-Bick, what the timetable is for appointing the two additional panel members to the Grenfell Tower Inquiry.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254137","254137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126490","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the timeframe is for a report on phase one of the Grenfell Tower inquiry led by Sir Martin Moore-Bick will be published.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254138","254138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126491","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when phase two of the Grenfell Tower inquiry led by Sir Martin Moore-Bick is planned to start.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254139","254139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126492","2019-05-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the names are of each Local Enterprise Partnership; and which partnerships have appointed a board member with responsibility for rural issues.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254102","254102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126493","2019-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) adequacy of the methodology used to measure rough sleeping and (b) accuracy of the data produced as a result of deploying that methodology.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254208","254208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126494","2019-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of regional job centre closures on trends in the level of homelessness in those regions.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254209","254209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126495","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which EU countries he has (a) started and (b) completed negotiations on reciprocal mobility agreements for workers in the creative industries who require short-term visas.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254210","254210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126496","2019-05-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-05-14","To ask the Department for Exiting the European Union, by which date he plans to have completed negotiations with EU27 countries on the reciprocal mobility agreements for workers in the creative industries that require short-term visas.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254211","254211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126497","2019-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to undertake a public consultation on a Code of Practice under the Parking (Code of Practice) Act 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254191","254191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126498","2019-05-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to extend the role of Community Land Trusts in rural areas.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254103","254103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126499","2019-05-20","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that remote rural areas have access to free to use cash machines.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254104","254104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126500","2019-05-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what criteria is used by National Grid ESO to determine acceptable levels of regional electricity system restoration capability.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254267","254267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126501","2019-05-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how essential electricity system restoration capability will be provided in a zero-carbon electricity system.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254268","254268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126502","2019-05-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the financial sustainability of retaining synchronous synchronous generation capability to provide restoration capability to the National Grid.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254269","254269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126503","2019-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps is he taking to ensure that social media companies tackle the advertising of online sales of knives and other weapons used in violent crime.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254190","254190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126504","2019-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to (a) ensure local authorities have a duty to provide access to a fully trained Animal Welfare Inspector with responsibility for enforcement of the Animal Welfare Act 2006 and (b) provide additional funding for that role; what estimate he has made of the number of local authorities that  do not employ an Animal Welfare Inspector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254174","254174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126505","2019-05-20","Department for Education","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions (a) he (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have had with AET on the benchmarking exercise for AET secondary schools in London; and whether his Department approved benchmarking process; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the benchmark against which AET secondary schools in London are being assessed.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254192","254192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126506","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in the Newport East constituency have been required to repay Carer’s Allowance as a result of an overpayment in the last 12 months; and how many of those overpayments were as a result of fraudulent claims.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254166","254166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126507","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he holds information on when the hon. Member for West Lancashire will receive a response to correspondence sent to Lancashire Care Foundation Trust on 14 March 2018 on mental health care.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254165","254165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126508","2019-05-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress has been made on making (a) Orkambi and (b) Symkevi available on the NHS for people diagnosed with cystic fibrosis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254113","254113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126509","2019-05-16","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-05-14","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will make and publish an urgent assessment of how many local returning officers failed performance standard one in relation to European Parliament elections because polling cards were delivered without adequate time to allow people to (a) change their registration details and (b) apply for an absent vote; what the (i) earliest, (ii) latest and (iii) average date was that local authorities sent out polling cards for the European Parliament elections; what effect the delay between commencement of the statutory election timetable on 15 April 2019 for all regions and formal Cabinet level confirmation on 7 May 2019 that the European Parliamentary elections would go ahead had on the decisions of local authorities on when to send out polling cards; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254175","254175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126510","2019-05-20","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) clear and (b) up to date information is provided to airlines operating in the UK on changes to visa requirements for EU citizens and their families visiting the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254117","254117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126511","2019-05-20","Department for International Trade","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of number of SMEs that (a) export, and (b) expressed an intention to stop exporting in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254053","254053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126512","2019-05-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of additional accredited vets that will be required in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254054","254054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126513","2019-05-20","Department for Transport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to increase the (a) level of storage and (b) access to storage for bikes on trains at all stops on the route between Birmingham and Bristol.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254105","254105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126514","2019-05-20","Department for Transport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the (a) dates on and (b) reports of all recorded (i) safety breaches and (ii) safety incidents involving (A) the Thames Clipper fleet and (B) other passenger boats on the River Thames since 2010.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254187","254187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126515","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the amount of economic activity lost to Yemen as a result of aerial bombing in that country since the Stockholm peace agreements were signed in December 2018.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254122","254122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126516","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department has taken to help reduce the price of (a) food and (b) sanitary goods imported into Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254123","254123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126517","2019-05-20","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to tackle organised crime.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254118","254118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126518","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 May 2019 to Question 252018 on Housing Benefit: Domestic Abuse, if she will make it her policy to collect data on the proportion of discretionary housing payment funding that is allocated to claimants affected by domestic abuse in each local authority area.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254246","254246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126519","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding his Department has allocated to support the reconstruction of infrastructure in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254124","254124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126520","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of Official Development Assistance for Yemen has been allocated to (a) peacebuilding and (b) conflict management in (i) 2016, (ii) 2017, (iii) 2018 and (iv) 2019.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254125","254125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126521","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what diplomatic steps his Department has taken with his international counterparts to establish safe travel routes for international humanitarian organisations.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254126","254126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126522","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish information held by is Department on the incidents of violence in each region of Yemen in each year since 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254127","254127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126523","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department has taken to provide a rapid humanitarian response to victims of violent incidents in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254128","254128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126524","2019-05-20","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the corruption of public officials at the UK's borders by those involved in organised crime.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254119","254119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126525","2019-05-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what (a) plans and (b) timetable he has to review the (i) Hydro Benefit Replacement Scheme and (i) Common Tariff Obligation.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254259","254259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126526","2019-05-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release of 9 May 2019, Government to fund and speed up vital cladding replacement, whether his Department has made an estimate of how many blocks with aluminium composite cladding will have their cladding remediation funded by that fund.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254194","254194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126527","2019-05-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has calculated the average cost per dwelling of remediating aluminium composite cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254195","254195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126528","2019-05-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has calculated the average cost per block of remediating aluminium composite cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254196","254196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126529","2019-05-20","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department taking to tackle polio in (a) Afghanistan and (b) Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254120","254120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126530","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the amount of tax revenue accrued was from UK small businesses in 2017-18.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254129","254129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126531","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of facial recognition in CCTV.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254130","254130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126532","2019-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that social media companies respect freedom of speech when regulating content.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254131","254131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126533","2019-05-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have taken enforcement action where owners of private sector high-rise residential buildings with unsafe aluminium composite material have refused to remediate those buildings.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254197","254197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126534","2019-05-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to make an estimate of the number of high-rise buildings with different forms of non-aluminium composite material cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254198","254198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126535","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the future of the tonnage tax regime.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254181","254181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126536","2019-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 May 2019 to Question 249313 on Buildings: Insulation, when the BS 8414 test of a High Pressure Laminate cladding system will be carried out by the Fire Protection Association.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254199","254199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126537","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what response her Department makes when notified by a local authority of an error in a resident’s universal credit calculation.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254086","254086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126538","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which organisations her Department defines as partners in the delivery of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254087","254087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126539","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department provides to local authorities to help (a) identify and (b) remedy errors in universal credit calculations.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254088","254088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126540","2019-05-20","Leader of the House","2019-05-14","To ask the Leader of the House, what steps she is taking to ensure that the Committee on Standards is supplied with sufficient information to enable its members to fulfil their remit under Standing Order 149(1) to oversee the work of the Parliamentary Commissioner On Standards in the exercise of her duties under Standing Order 150.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254100","254100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126541","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the overpayment of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254089","254089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126542","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the extent of the overpayment of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254090","254090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126543","2019-05-20","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what response the Prime Minister has given to the Report of the Committee on Standards in Public Life submitted to her on 3 July 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254101","254101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126544","2019-05-20","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many knife amnesty bins there were in the UK in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254162","254162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126545","2019-05-20","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many knife amnesty days there have been in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254163","254163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126546","2019-05-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Governments of (a) China and (b) South Korea on the forced repatriation to North Korea of (i) Choi Byai and (ii) six other North Korean defectors.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254176","254176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126547","2019-05-20","Department for Education","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what work is outstanding under his Department's contracts with Morning Lane Associates as (a) sole provider and (b) part of a consortium.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254203","254203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126548","2019-05-20","Department for Education","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 250518 on Morning Lane Associates, what the start and end dates were of the contracts that Morning Lane Associates undertook, in partnership with KPMG, in relation to the national assessment and accreditation system for children and family social workers.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254204","254204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126549","2019-05-20","Department for Education","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 250518, Morning Lane Associates, for what reason the £4.4 million awarded to Morning Lane Associates to implement the Reclaiming Social Work approach in five local authorities was not included in that Answer.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254205","254205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126550","2019-05-20","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the Government has made towards implementing the measures set out in the Government’s response to the Call for Evidence on Access to Elections; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254271","254271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126551","2019-05-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has plans to include a heightened role for rural areas in the Government’s Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254106","254106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126552","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy to ensure that dual nationals have to submit only UK documents when applying to renew their British passport.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254261","254261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126553","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on victims of historical child sexual abuse of providing them with an alternative to court proceedings involving a jury trial.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254206","254206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126554","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether advice and training is in place for jury members deciding on cases of historical childhood sexual abuse; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254207","254207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126555","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254064","254064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126556","2019-05-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254065","254065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126557","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254066","254066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126558","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254067","254067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126559","2019-05-16","Department for International Trade","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254068","254068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126560","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254069","254069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126561","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254070","254070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126562","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254071","254071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126563","2019-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254072","254072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126564","2019-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254073","254073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126565","2019-05-16","Department for Education","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254074","254074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126566","2019-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254075","254075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126567","2019-05-16","Attorney General","2019-05-14","To ask the Attorney General, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254076","254076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126568","2019-05-16","Wales Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254077","254077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126569","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254078","254078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126570","2019-05-16","Scotland Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254079","254079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126571","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in his Department; and what the cost was to his Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254080","254080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126572","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of officials in her Department office took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in her Department; and what the cost was to her Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254081","254081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126573","2019-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of officials in her Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in her Department; and what the cost was to her Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254082","254082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126574","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of officials in the Prime Minister's office took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last 12 months; what proportion that leave was of total sick leave taken in her Department; and what the cost was to her Department of officials taking sick leave over that period.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254083","254083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126575","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the (a) recruitment and (b) retention of adequate levels of NHS staff in cancer pathology units.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254258","254258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126576","2019-05-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2019 to Question, 251894 on Caravan Sites, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit owners of caravan holiday home parks from being able to make assessments of potential purchasers of caravans before granting authority for that sale; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254114","254114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126577","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2019 to Question 249315 on Railways, how many proposals for a Southern Rail Link to Heathrow were received following his market-led proposals invitation of 20 March 2018, how many of those proposals remain under active consideration by his Department; on what dates he last (a) met and (b) corresponded with the promoters of schemes under active consideration; and when he plans to announce the process for selecting a preferred developer.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254200","254200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126578","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2019 to Question 249314 on Railways, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) a Western Rail Link to Heathrow Airport and (b) a Southern Rail Link to Heathrow Airport on the level of emissions of (i) greenhouse gases and (ii) other atmospheric pollutants in relation to (A) the existing configuration and (B) the addition of the North West Runway at London Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254201","254201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126579","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2019 to Question 249314, what (a) meetings, (b) correspondence and (c) other engagement his Department has had with (i) local authorities, (ii) the Mayor of London and (iii) the aviation industry on Western and Southern Rail Access to London Heathrow Airport since the publication of the Nicholls-Agilia reports on 19 December 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254202","254202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126580","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the contribution has been from the public purse to the EU since 29 March 2019.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254167","254167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126581","2019-05-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the Government's policy is on a second referendum on EU membership.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254168","254168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126582","2019-05-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether mobile roaming charges will be reintroduced in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254169","254169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126583","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions has she had with Home Secretary on the level of the cyber threat facing the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254170","254170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126584","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many 16 year olds signed up to the armed forces in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254171","254171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126585","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what her Department's policy is on the deployment of armed personnel to countries where UK citizens have been assessed as at risk.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254172","254172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126586","2019-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many (a) private tower blocks and (b) social housing blocks in Birmingham have been identified as requiring the removal and replacement of unsafe aluminium composite cladding.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254115","254115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126587","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what he Department's policy is on the modernise of training bases in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254173","254173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126588","2019-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding has been allocated to Birmingham city council to remove and replace unsafe aluminium composite cladding in council and housing association blocks since such funding was made available in 2018.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254116","254116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126589","2019-05-16","Department for Education","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the review of post-18 education and funding will assess the way in which the student finance system is communicated to (a) current and (b) prospective (i) students, (ii) graduates, (iii) parents and (iv) others.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254159","254159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126590","2019-05-16","Department for Education","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the review of post-18 education and funding is planned to report before the parliamentary summer recess.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254160","254160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126591","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on local authority budgets of the Government's no recourse to public funds policy.","Biography information for Chris Philp","Chris Philp","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254245","254245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126592","2019-05-20","Attorney General","2019-05-14","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 8 May 2019 to Question 249931 on Prosecutions: West Midlands, what the average time was for the CPS to reach a decision in the West Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254257","254257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126593","2019-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 April 2019 to Question 243315, how many universal credit claimants in the central London broad rental market area are in receipt of the shared accommodation rate of the housing element of that benefit.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254093","254093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126594","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 April 2019 to Question 243314 on Local Housing Allowance: Greater London, what the 960 Local Housing Allowance rates are ranked according to the share of the market they afford, starting with the most divergent.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254094","254094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126595","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much additional funding was made available to the Independent Case Examiner in 2018-19 to recruit 13 extra staff.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254095","254095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126596","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the budget for the Independent Case Examiner has been in each year since 2011-12; and how many members of staff have been employed by that body in each of those years.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254096","254096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126597","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that cataract removal surgery is available to everyone who would benefit from it.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Dame Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254121","254121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126598","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken to reach a determination on a complaint escalated to the Independent Case Examiner was in 2018-19.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254097","254097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126599","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints that were rejected by the independent Case Examiner were referred to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254098","254098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126600","2019-05-20","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether staff at the Office of the Registrar of Consultant Lobbyists are instructed to check and assess the relevancy of codes of conduct that registrants declare.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254140","254140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126601","2019-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of the 158 complaints about the Independent Case Examiner in 2017-18 were on the length of time it took to investigate a complaint.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254099","254099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126602","2019-05-16","Department for International Trade","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase the proportion of exports linked to design; what estimate he has made of the number of businesses involved in exports linked to design; .and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254275","254275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126603","2019-05-20","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if his Department will conduct a review of the codes of conduct accepted by the Office of the Registrar of Consultant Lobbyists in light of the number of registrants declaring their own self-authored code.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254141","254141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126604","2019-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the gross value added by the design sector in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254276","254276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126605","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will extend the definition of abuse of positions of trust in the Sexual Offences Act 2003 to cover all adults working with children in extra-curricular activities.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254179","254179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126606","2019-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to suicides in the farming sector, what steps he is taking to monitor levels of distress in that sector.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254107","254107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126607","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his South Sudanese counterpart on the (a) kidnapping and subsequent death of opposition member Aggrey Idri and human rights lawyer Doug Samuel Luak and (b) need to bring the perpetrators of those crimes to justice.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254108","254108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126608","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the amendment to the EU VAT Directive agreed in October 2018, whether there is any impediment preventing the UK from zero-rating VAT on e-publications.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254223","254223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126609","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons ebooks are not zero-rated to protect the accessibility of knowledge.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254224","254224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126610","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the level of detentions of political activists in South Sudan; and what representations he has made to his South Sudanese counterparts on those detentions.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254109","254109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126611","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the level of famine is in South Sudan; and what food aid the Government is making available to that country.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254110","254110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126612","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2019 to Question 228557 on RAF Northolt: Repairs and Maintenance, what progress he has made on (a) the runway and (b) associated infrastructure construction works; what estimate his Department has made of the cost of those works; and if he make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254092","254092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126613","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the prevalence of rape in South Sudan; and what programmes he has established to educate (a) women and (b) men that rape is unacceptable.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254111","254111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126614","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Defence on awarding the Long Service and Good Conduct medal to firefighters working for the Ministry of Defence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254272","254272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126615","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to fast-track refunds to people who have paid the new higher-rate Immigration Health Surcharge when their cases require them to pay only the lower pre-2019 rate.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254262","254262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126616","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of child soldiers actively deployed in the conflict in South Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254112","254112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126617","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the review of shared parental leave is planned for completion; and at what stage of that review stakeholders will be called to give evidence.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254256","254256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126618","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what changes have been made to the burden of proof required to prove eligibility for welfare support for (a) EU nationals and (b) non-EU nationals following the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254247","254247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126619","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the (a) number of non-UK nationals who have been denied universal credit due to their immigration status and (b) average time taken to verify the immigration status of claimants.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254248","254248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126620","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of mandatory reconsiderations which have taken longer than 30 days.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254249","254249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126621","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what mental health support are NHS trusts required to make available to staff employed on neonatal intensive care units.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254230","254230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126622","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department holds figures on the number of neonatal unit clinical staff who have taken long term sick leave in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254231","254231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126623","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of long-term mental health support given to parents of babies discharged from neonatal units.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254232","254232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126624","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women in prison are on the autistic spectrum.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254060","254060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126625","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) male and (b) female people in young offending institutions have autism.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254061","254061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126626","2019-05-20","Department for Transport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to aircraft noise nuisance, which communities will receive compensation and noise insulation as a result of the third runway at Heathrow airport; and on what criteria that decision was based.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254062","254062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126627","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people convicted of a crime and sentenced to time in prison in each of the last five years had been excluded from their primary school.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254063","254063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126628","2019-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 April 2019 to Question 242790 on State Retirement Pensions: Reciprocal Arrangements, which non-EU countries have made requests for reciprocal social security agreements with the UK since 1992.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254152","254152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126629","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will seek a guarantee from the Health and Care Professions Council that there will be no further increases to their registration fees for at least the next four years.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254161","254161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126630","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2019 to Question 251408 on Prisons: Contracts, which versions of the Model for Operational Delivery have previously been made available to potential private prison contractors.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254234","254234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126631","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which of the recommendations made by the Taylor Review of the Youth Justice System, published in December 2016, have been (a) fully, (b) partially and (c) not achieved.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254235","254235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126632","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which of the recommendations made in the Youth Custody Improvement Board report, published in February 2017, have been (a) fully, (b) partially and (c) not achieved.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254236","254236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126633","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of children in custody were held on remand in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254237","254237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126634","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of looked-after children in custody have a resettlement care plan confirmed 10 working days prior to their release from custody.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254238","254238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126635","2019-05-20","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many looked-after children are currently held in custody.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254239","254239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126636","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) young offenders institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s homes do not have a formal written procedure for the identification, assessment and care planning of looked-after children.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254240","254240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126637","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many looked-after children were released from (a) young offenders institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s homes without a confirmed education, training or employment placement in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254241","254241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126638","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many looked-after children were released from (a) young offenders institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s homes without a confirmed address to go to in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254242","254242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126639","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many looked-after children were held in (a) young offenders institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s homes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254243","254243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126640","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many looked-after children were held in each (a) young offenders institution, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s home in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254244","254244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126641","2019-05-20","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant the Answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 250791 on Saudi Arabia: Military Aid, what the (a) roles and (b) functions are of the 60 RAF personnel not embedded with BAE stationed inside Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254260","254260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126642","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to respond to the enquiry of 21 March 2019 from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central on behalf of her constituent, Ms Sheikh.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254220","254220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126643","2019-05-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of disinformation in the media on the integrity of the 2019 European Parliament elections.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254091","254091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126644","2019-05-20","Home Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been extradited from the UK to Nigeria in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254218","254218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126645","2019-05-20","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what comparative assessment his Department has made of trends in the rate of death from asthma per 100,000 people in the UK and other European countries.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254219","254219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126646","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the  trends in the level of unemployment in Great Grimsby constituency.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254225","254225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126647","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the level of unemployment in Great Grimsby constituency.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254226","254226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126648","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of universal credit in assisting claimants into sustainable employment in Great Grimsby constituency.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254227","254227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126649","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that claimants of universal credit in North East Lincolnshire remain in sustainable employment when they find work.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254228","254228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126650","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister's letter to Sir Martin Moore Bick of 10 May 2018 announcing her intention to appoint two additional panel members to the Grenfell Tower Inquiry for Phase 2, and the Grenfell Tower inquiry's subsequent update on 17 April 2019 explaining that preliminary work, for Phase 2 has already started, when the Prime Minister plans to appoint the two additional panel members to the Grenfell Tower inquiry.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254277","254277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126651","2019-05-20","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether legislative changes would be required to allow EU citizens living in the UK that are registered for local elections to be registered automatically to vote in EU elections.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254251","254251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126652","2019-05-16","Department for Education","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 14 May 2019 to Question 250743 on Special Educational Needs: Finance, how many and what proportion of children and young people had an Education Health and Care Plan in each year since 2013 and 2019; and how much funding his Department allocated to high needs in each of those years.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254085","254085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126653","2019-05-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimates he has made the number of children in absolute child poverty in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254154","254154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126654","2019-05-20","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total value is of land and property sold by the Government since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254142","254142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126655","2019-05-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 250763 on Opiates: Prescriptions, if he will make it his policy to include direct hyperlinks to reports or materials referenced in written answers to hon. Members.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254155","254155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126656","2019-05-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support an international criminal justice mechanism for the human rights crimes committed against Tamils.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254188","254188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126657","2019-05-20","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations she has made to the Government of Turkey on its potential acquisition of a Russian S-400 missile.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254055","254055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126658","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of reports of Hezbollah’s presence in Venezuela in support of President Maduro.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254229","254229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126659","2019-05-20","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many companies in each region and nation of the UK secured contracts from her Department in each of the last five years; and what the value of each contract was.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254156","254156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126660","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the top ten firms by value of sales that have purchased government land and property since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254143","254143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126661","2019-05-20","Wales Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, on what dates (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have met with counterparts in the Department for Work and Pensions to discuss poverty rates for disabled people in Wales in each of the last two years; and what the outcomes were of those meetings.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254157","254157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126662","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many sites identified for sale from the government estate are currently in use.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254144","254144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126663","2019-05-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the objectives of the Government's diplomatic and political policy on Turkey are for 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254056","254056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126664","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria are used to evaluate whether Government-owned land and property should be made available for purchase.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254145","254145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126665","2019-05-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any Ministers have plans to visit Iran in the next six months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254252","254252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126666","2019-05-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 May 2019 to Question 251918, what assessment he has made of the decline in home ownership rates among NS-SEC classification routine occupations.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254158","254158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126667","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has plans to receive Iranian government ministers in the next six months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254253","254253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126668","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the National Audit Office's 2 May 2019 report entitled Investigation into the Government’s land disposal strategy and programmes, if he will publish the 176 sites that were disposed of for £1 or less from the government estate.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254146","254146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126669","2019-05-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart regarding the sentencing of Aras Amiri.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254254","254254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126670","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the National Audit Office's 2 May 2019 report entitled Investigation into the government’s land disposal strategy and programmes, for what reasons 176 sites from the government estate were disposed of for £1 or less.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254147","254147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126671","2019-05-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking in response to the sentencing of Aras Amiri.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254255","254255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126672","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the effect of one person occupying both the roles of National Security Adviser and Cabinet Secretary on the effectiveness of those roles.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254148","254148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126673","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions the Cabinet Secretary has had with the representatives of the Metropolitan police on the alleged leak of information from a meeting of the National Security Council.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254149","254149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126674","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many contingent workers are working on IT projects across government.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254150","254150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126675","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many workers hired through supplier resource are working on IT projects across government.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254151","254151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126676","2019-05-20","Department for International Development","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether his Department has allocated funding to Marie Stopes International to fund political advocacy to change laws on abortion in (a) Malawi and (b) South Sudan.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254177","254177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126677","2019-05-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the paper entitled, Continuation of Unintended Pregnancy published by the Catholic Medical Association in March 2019, what plans his Department has to develop and improve support for mothers who wish to continue with a pregnancy.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254178","254178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126678","2019-05-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeframe is for NHS prescription forms to be amended to include tick boxes for universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254153","254153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126679","2019-05-20","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) UK and (b) global economy of a US-China trade war.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254057","254057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126680","2019-05-20","Treasury","2019-05-14","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has made to the (a) US Administration and (b) Government of China on the potential effect on the UK economy of a US-China trade war.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254058","254058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126681","2019-05-20","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-05-14","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2019 to Question 248046 on European Parliament: Elections, which sections of the (a) Representation of the People Act 1983 (as amended), (b) Representation of the People (England and Wales) Regulations 2001 (as amended) and (c) European Parliamentary Elections (Franchise of Relevant Citizens of the Union) Regulations 2001 apply to that Answer.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254222","254222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126682","2019-05-20","Cabinet Office","2019-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2019 to Question 252605 on Huawei: 5G, and with reference to the February 2019 blog by the technical director of the National Cyber Security Centre on Huawei, whether the National Cyber Security Centre monitors the number of UK telecoms operators that utilise HCSEC advice and guidance.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 254274","254274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125999","2019-05-15","Northern Ireland Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of Tier 3 obesity services in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253572","253572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126000","2019-05-15","Northern Ireland Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans her Department has to establish a Tier 3 obesity service in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253573","253573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126001","2019-05-15","Northern Ireland Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March to Question 236379 on Obesity: Northern Ireland, what representations her Department has (a) received from and (b) made to the Northern Ireland Department of Health on the establishment of a bariatric obesity service; whether she has plans to undertake a public consultation on the potential merits of establishing that service; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253574","253574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126002","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of medical nutrition on clinical outcomes for cancer patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253575","253575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126003","2019-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on which occasions he requested legal advice on the revocation of General Licences 04/05/06 in the last year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253444","253444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126004","2019-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Herald article entitled MoD stops using toxic chromium paint on tanks published on 17 April 2019, (a) when and (b) by whom the decision was taken to discontinue the use of paints containing hexavalent chromium on military vehicles.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253590","253590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126005","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to respond to the open letter of 11 April 2019 on the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme ;and if he will meet with the signatories of that letter.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253552","253552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126006","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the EU Withdrawal Agreement enables the UK to invoke Hague Preference during the implementation period.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253554","253554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126007","2019-05-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the UK is able to leave the EU without a deal before 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253451","253451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126008","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much the Government has spent on TV and radio advertising to promote smart meters.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253634","253634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126009","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the extent to which the Data Communications Company will install upgraded communication software to SMETS1 smart meters by 2020.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253635","253635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126010","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of conducting a new cost-benefit analysis of the smart meter roll-out over the last five years.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253636","253636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126011","2019-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2019 to Question 212664 on Universal Credit: Domestic Violence, what recent discussions her Department has had with the Scottish Government on the implementation of separate universal credit payments by default; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253698","253698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126012","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trees have been felled by Network Rail as part its lineside tree felling programme to date.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253699","253699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126013","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trees Network Rail plans to fell as part of its lineside tree felling programme up to the expected conclusion of that programme in 2024.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253700","253700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126014","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trees Network Rail are planning to replant to replace the loss of biodiversity resulting from its lineside tree felling programme.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253701","253701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126015","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support increased (a) home and flexible working and (b) provision of co-working spaces.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253477","253477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126016","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessments Network Rail carry out to classify a lineside tree as safety critical.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253702","253702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126017","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the contribution to the economy of home and flexible working.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253478","253478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126018","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the independent review of Network Rail’s lineside vegetation management, published in November 2018, for what reasons Network Rail has felled trees during the nesting season.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253703","253703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126019","2019-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to use planning policy to support the provision of co-working spaces outside London.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253479","253479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126020","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of home and flexible working to reducing congestion on (a) rail and (b) road networks.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253480","253480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126021","2019-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with the hospitality sector on supporting working spaces within hotels and cafes.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253481","253481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126022","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will expedite the process by which the NICE publishes its decisions.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253483","253483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126023","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average wait is for mandatory reconsideration of (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment support allowance claims in each of the last three years in Wrexham constituency.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253531","253531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126024","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what analysis his Department has undertaken to identify green belt land close to train stations.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253471","253471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126025","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what analysis his Department has undertaken to identify green belt land close to train stations and within an hour's travel time of London.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253472","253472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126026","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce (a) disposable and (b) non-recyclable waste on public transport services.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253704","253704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126027","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce (a) disposable and (b) non-recyclable waste on aviation services arriving to or departing from the UK.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253705","253705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126028","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the right to apply for UK citizenship without a fee to people born in the Republic of Ireland and who have lived in the UK for most of their life.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253726","253726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126029","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons VAT will be charged on food for assistance and therapy dogs.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253520","253520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126030","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that parents are given adequate advice and information on vaccination programmes.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253521","253521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126031","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) dementia and (b) Alzheimer’s are diagnosed (i) correctly and (ii) as quickly as possible.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253522","253522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126032","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care and the Secretary of State for Defence on the annual tapered allowance and its effect on the recruitment and retention of doctors in the NHS and armed forces.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253507","253507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126033","2019-05-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253603","253603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126034","2019-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253604","253604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126035","2019-05-15","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253605","253605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126036","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253606","253606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126037","2019-05-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253607","253607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126038","2019-05-15","Department for International Development","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253608","253608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126039","2019-05-15","Department for International Trade","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253609","253609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126040","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253610","253610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126041","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253611","253611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126042","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253612","253612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126043","2019-05-16","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to monitor the application of the statutory guidance entitled Promoting the health and well-being of looked-after children - Statutory guidance for local authorities, clinical commissioning groups and NHS England, with particular reference to foetal alcohol syndrome.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253564","253564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126044","2019-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much her Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253613","253613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126045","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253614","253614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126046","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253615","253615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126047","2019-05-15","Scotland Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253616","253616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126048","2019-05-15","Wales Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253617","253617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126049","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253618","253618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126050","2019-05-15","Northern Ireland Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253619","253619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126051","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253620","253620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126052","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253621","253621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126053","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253622","253622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126054","2019-05-16","Attorney General","2019-05-13","To ask the Attorney General, how much his Department has paid to hon. Members under section 4 of the Ministerial and other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991 since 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253623","253623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126055","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department has planned to support the alcohol and drug treatment system.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253691","253691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126056","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the BBC of the additional employers' national insurance contributions due as a result of the ruling by HMRC on personal service companies.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253536","253536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126057","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the BBC on potential tax liabilities arising on the beneficiaries of any settlement reached by the BBC with HMRC over the tax now due by presenters who had previously been paid through personal service companies.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253537","253537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126058","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost is to the public purse of the provision of free television licences to people over 75 years of age.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253538","253538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126059","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many vacancies there are in (a) mammography and (b) breast radiology in each Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253555","253555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126060","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Missing Persons Register will be published.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253651","253651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126061","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of ensuring it is made clear whenever health research is commercially funded.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253523","253523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126062","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to promote Refugee Week 2019; and if he will take steps to ensure his Department promotes the value of refugees and asylum seekers to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253539","253539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126063","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether army personnel have been issued with (a) mobile handsets and (b) other devices (i) manufactured by Huawei and (ii) manufactured by Huawei but provided by and badged with the names of other companies; and what her Department's policy is towards the use of telecommunications equipment manufactured by Chinese companies.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253438","253438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126064","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to establish a cross-departmental taskforce to address the issues and recommendations outlined in the report of the all-party parliamentary group on acquired brain injury entitled Acquired brain injury and neurorehabilitation - time for change.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253567","253567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126065","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which defence contracts were granted exemption from the single source regulation regime in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18; and what was the value of each of those contracts.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253527","253527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126066","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how soon he is informed of deaths in prisons.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253596","253596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126067","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prisoners were prescribed medication for mental health issues in 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253597","253597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126068","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on training prison officers on the use of PAVA spray.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253598","253598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126069","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to open bids for contracts to operate HMP Wellingborough and HMP Glen Parva.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253599","253599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126070","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria his Department will use to judge the effectiveness of the Education and Employment Strategy 2018 in improving education for adult prisoners.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253600","253600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126071","2019-05-15","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2019-05-13","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, pursuant to the Answer of 7 May 2019 to Question 249206 on Members: Allowances, what the (a) forecast and (b) final cost was of the new IPSA IT system; and what assessment was made of additional costs that would be incurred by MPs' staff to work on the new system.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253492","253492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126072","2019-05-15","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2019-05-13","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, what the cost has been of the move by IPSA to new premises in central London; and what assessment was made of the potential merits of moving the organisation to a cheaper location outside London.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253493","253493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126073","2019-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost to the public purse has been of the case Turks and Caicos islands against Mr Michael Misick and others.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253494","253494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126074","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of whether local Clinical Commissioning Groups are implementing NICE guidelines on cataract removal.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253495","253495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126075","2019-05-16","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils received the pupil premium in each primary school in Leeds City Council area in 2017-18.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253712","253712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126076","2019-05-15","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils do not have English as their first spoken language in each primary school in the Leeds City Council area.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253713","253713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126077","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference paragraph 7.20 of HM Courts & Tribunals Service response to the consultation paper entitled Fit for the future: transforming the Court and Tribunal Estate, what steps he is taking to determine appropriate capacity utilisation of the HM Courts & Tribunals estate; and what the date is for the completion of that analysis.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253542","253542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126078","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to include adult and child safeguarding in the Life in the UK Test.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253714","253714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126079","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the Government’s policy is on the cancellation of debts owed by Sierra Leone; and what steps the Government is taking (a) nationally and (b) internationally to reduce that country’s debt overhang.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253484","253484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126080","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects with a value of more than £1m his Department has commissioned in Sierra Leone; and (a) what those projects are and (b) which organisations are carrying out the work on those projects.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253485","253485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126081","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court buildings in the south west of England were inaccessible to (a) defendants and witnesses, (b) members of the public and (c) court staff with disabilities in the week beginning 6 May 2019; and how many of those buildings were only temporarily inaccessible in that week because of broken lifts; and how many of those courts were inaccessible to at least one of those groups for (i) more than one week and (ii) more than one month in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253543","253543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126082","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court buildings in the south east of England, excluding Greater London, were inaccessible to (a) defendants and witnesses, (b) members of the public and (c) court staff with disabilities in the week beginning 6 May 2019; and how many of those buildings were only temporarily inaccessible in that week because of broken lifts; and how many of those courts were inaccessible to at least one of those groups for (i) more than one week and (ii) more than one month in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253544","253544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126083","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court buildings in the Greater London were inaccessible to (a) defendants and witnesses, (b) members of the public and (c) court staff with disabilities in the week beginning 6 May 2019; and how many of those buildings were only temporarily inaccessible in that week because of broken lifts; and how many of those courts were inaccessible to at least one of those groups for (i) more than one week and (ii) more than one month in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253545","253545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126084","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court buildings in the Midlands were inaccessible to (a) defendants and witnesses, (b) members of the public and (c) court staff with disabilities in the week beginning 6 May 2019; and how many of those buildings were only temporarily inaccessible in that week because of broken lifts; and how many of those courts were inaccessible to at least one of those groups for (i) more than one week and (ii) more than one month in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253546","253546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126085","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court buildings in the north west of England were inaccessible to (a) defendants and witnesses, (b) members of the public and (c) court staff with disabilities in the week beginning 6 May 2019; and how many of those buildings were only temporarily inaccessible in that week because of broken lifts; and how many of those courts were inaccessible to at least one of those groups for (i) more than one week and (ii) more than one month in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253547","253547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126086","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  how many court buildings in the north east of England were inaccessible to (a) defendants and witnesses, (b) members of the public and (c) court staff with disabilities in the week beginning 6 May 2019; and how many of those buildings were only temporarily inaccessible in that week because of broken lifts; and how many of those courts were inaccessible to at least one of those groups for (i) more than one week and (ii) more than one month in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253548","253548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126087","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many court buildings in Wales were inaccessible to (a) defendants and witnesses, (b) members of the public and (c) court staff with disabilities in the week beginning 6 May 2019; and how many of those buildings were only temporarily inaccessible in that week because of broken lifts; and how many courts were inaccessible to at least one of these groups for (i) more than one week, and (ii) more than one month in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253549","253549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126088","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases were rescheduled in (a) Greater Manchester and (b) Greater London due to insufficient court space in the months of (i) February, (ii) March and (iii) April 2019.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253550","253550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126089","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 249921 on Ministry of Justice: Telephone Services, how many calls did each of those helplines receive in the last year.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253551","253551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126090","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit claimants have had money deducted as a result of (a) council tax arrears, (b) rent arrears and (c) historical tax credit debt.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253637","253637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126091","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of a ban on all caged farming.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253508","253508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126092","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the trends in the level of vacancy rates in  town centre business properties.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253694","253694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126093","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Minister in her Department authorised UK participation in Exercise Joint Warrior; and what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of participation in that exercise.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253528","253528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126094","2019-05-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the level of the National Minimum Wage on the income of people in employment aged under 18.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253695","253695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126095","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that staff delivering probation services through (a) private companies and (b) the National Probation Service are treated equally in terms of (i) pay and (ii) terms and conditions.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253668","253668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126096","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many UC50 forms were issued by her Department to residents of Bristol South constituency between the  June 2018 and December 2018.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253638","253638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126097","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken in relation to poor performance by community rehabilitation companies in the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253669","253669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126098","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many financial penalties his Department has issued to community rehabilitation companies as a result of poor performance; and what the value was of those penalties in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253670","253670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126099","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of his Department’s policy of suspending fines for community rehabilitation companies for poor performance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253671","253671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126100","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many ESA50 forms were issued by her Department to residents of Bristol South constituency between June 2017 and December 2017.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253639","253639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126101","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether community rehabilitation companies with a record of poor performance will be allowed to bid for future probation contracts.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253672","253672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126102","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of returning probation services to the public sector.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253673","253673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126103","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many UC50 forms were returned to her Department by residents of Bristol South constituency between June 2018 and December 2018.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253640","253640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126104","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of returning offender management services in Wales to the public sector.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253674","253674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126105","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of probation services in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253675","253675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126106","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that community rehabilitation companies maintain adequate levels of staff.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253676","253676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126107","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the workload of (a) community rehabilitation companies and (b) the National Probation Service.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253677","253677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126108","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to rebuild confidence in community rehabilitation companies with judges.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253678","253678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126109","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to encourage the involvement of third-sector organisations in the delivery of probation services.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253679","253679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126110","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that future community rehabilitation company contracts will encourage increased levels of involvement of third-sector organisations in delivering probation services.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253680","253680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126111","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the National Probation Service of remaining in the public sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253681","253681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126112","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of trends in the level of wellbeing of probation officers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253682","253682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126113","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to undertake a review the quality of the clinical supervision provided to probation staff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253683","253683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126114","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have left the National Probation Service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253684","253684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126115","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff that left the National Probation Service cited work stress as a contributing factor in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253685","253685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126116","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have left the National Probation Service within two years of qualifying in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253686","253686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126117","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to (a) reduce and (b) vary the workload of staff in the National Probation Service.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253687","253687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126118","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many ESA50 forms were returned to her Department by residents of Bristol South constituency between June 2017 and December 2017.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253641","253641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126119","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance joint claimant cases there are where both claimants have an underlying entitlement to severe disability premium.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253642","253642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126120","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, since January 2019 how many universal credit claimants who had an underlying entitlement to severe disability premium (SDP) have not been able to claim employment and support allowance (ESA) following the death of a partner who was the lead claimant in a previous joint ESA claim and who also had entitlement to SDP.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253643","253643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126121","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will confirm that none of the 870,651 alleged Tax Credit overpayments which were remitted as detailed in the HM Revenue & Customs Annual Report and Accounts 2011-12 have been transferred to his Department for collection through universal credit.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253644","253644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126122","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253452","253452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126123","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff of his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other Departments and (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253453","253453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126124","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253454","253454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126125","2019-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253455","253455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126126","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 May 2019 to Question 247013 on Shipping: training, how many Ratings have been trained using SMarT category (a) 3 and (b) 5 funding in each year since 1998.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253563","253563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126127","2019-05-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253456","253456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126128","2019-05-15","Cabinet Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253457","253457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126129","2019-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253458","253458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126130","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253459","253459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126131","2019-05-15","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253460","253460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126132","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253461","253461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126133","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253462","253462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126134","2019-05-15","Scotland Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253463","253463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126135","2019-05-15","Wales Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253464","253464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126136","2019-05-15","Attorney General","2019-05-13","To ask the Attorney General, how many staff of his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other Departments and (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253465","253465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126137","2019-05-15","Department for International Development","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253466","253466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126138","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff in his Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253467","253467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126139","2019-05-16","House of Commons Commission","2019-05-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what recent estimate the Commission has made of the amount of food waste produced by the kitchens on the parliamentary estate.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253486","253486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126140","2019-05-16","House of Commons Commission","2019-05-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the Commission is taking to reduce the amount of food waste produced by the kitchens on the parliamentary estate.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253487","253487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126141","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the conduct of maternity investigations into term intrapartum stillbirths will continue to be the responsibility of the Healthcare Safety Investigation Branch for the next three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253439","253439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126142","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the 2019-2020 budget for the Healthcare Safety Investigation Branch maternity programme will be finalised.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253440","253440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126143","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average cost to the public purse is of a Healthcare Safety Investigation Branch maternity investigation.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253441","253441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126144","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the number of years a person would need to spend in a residential care home before benefitting from a (a) £72,000 cap and (b) £100,000 cap on the cost of care; if he will make it his policy to introduce free personal care in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253553","253553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126145","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Healthcare Safety Investigation Branch maternity investigations were opened between April 2018 and September 2018; and how many of those investigations were completed in that period.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253442","253442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126146","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many staff are employed by the Healthcare Safety Investigation Branch to conduct maternity investigations; and how many such staff positions are vacant.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253443","253443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126147","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Rural Payments Agency will deliver outstanding countryside stewardship payments in full.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253688","253688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126148","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to provide support for on-going training for young farmers who have entered the farming industry, to help ensure the sustainability of that workforce.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253689","253689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126149","2019-05-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what level of evidence on the safety of modified tumble dryers would be required to prompt a full recall of all modified machines.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253482","253482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126150","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) prevalence of and (b) effectiveness of NHS treatment for back pain.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253576","253576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126151","2019-05-16","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 250518, what the individual payments were; and what work they were (a) for and (b) who they were authorised by.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253581","253581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126152","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 249276, if he will provide the figures for the number of workers in the offshore wind sector transported by helicopter (a) to and (b) from wind farms on the UK continental shelf in each year for which there are records.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253568","253568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126153","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to reduce demand for class A drugs.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253488","253488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126154","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of rooftop solar panels deployed on domestic homes since the closure of the Feed-In Tariff scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253489","253489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126155","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of body cameras worn by police forces across the UK were switched on in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253518","253518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126156","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of body cameras worn by police forces.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253519","253519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126157","2019-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 9 May 2019 on Labour Market Policy Update, HCWS1545, whether people currently serving a sanction for a period of over 26 weeks will have that sanction rescinded.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253631","253631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126158","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his (a) French and (b) New Zealand counterpart on reducing the amount of violent and terrorist content on social media.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253490","253490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126159","2019-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 9 May 2019 on Labour Market Policy Update, HCWS1545, when the ending of benefit sanctions of over six months will come into force.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253632","253632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126160","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the budget was for Prevent in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253602","253602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126161","2019-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 9 May 2019 on Labour Market Policy Update, HCWS1545, whether claimants previously sanctioned for periods over six months will be entitled to recompense.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253633","253633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126162","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 250787, what information his Department holds on whether BAE Systems supervised the (a) fusing of bombs and (b) final preparations of munitions for operational sorties in Yemen.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253696","253696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126163","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department provides for universal credit (a) claimants and (b) intended beneficiaries who are victims of economic abuse arising from provision of a single payment to one family.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253650","253650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126164","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken in response to its consultation on preserving the free use of public parks.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253715","253715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126165","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what support his Department provides to staff in his Department (a) in their transition to retirement and (b) to (i) maintain and (ii) increase the physical and mental wellbeing staff planning for retirement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253515","253515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126166","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support his Department provides to staff in his Department (a) in their transition to retirement and (b) to (i) maintain and (ii) increase the physical and mental wellbeing staff planning for retirement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253516","253516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126167","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support his Department provides to staff in his Department (a) in their transition to retirement and (b) to (i) maintain and (ii) increase the physical and mental wellbeing staff planning for retirement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253517","253517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126168","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2019 to Question 249214 on Buildings: Insulation, what assessment he has made of the nature of the risks to public safety.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253506","253506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126169","2019-05-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department has monitored deployment of new solar installations on (a) domestic rooftops, (b) community energy schemes and (c) commercial and industrial rooftop schemes since the closure of the Feed-In Tariff scheme.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253645","253645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126170","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the area of Victoria Tower Gardens to be occupied by the structures and hard paving of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre is in square metres under the (a) planning application submitted in December 2018 and (b) revised proposals of May 2019.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253496","253496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126171","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason the Government has allocated an additional £25 million to the construction of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253497","253497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126172","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the current estimated cost is for the construction of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre; and what proportion of that cost will be covered by funds from the public purse.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253498","253498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126173","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding from private sources has been promised towards the construction of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre; how many promises of funding exceeding £1 million have been made; and what conditions have been attached by the donors to those donations.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253499","253499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126174","2019-05-15","Northern Ireland Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff of her Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments and (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU have since returned to her Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253468","253468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126175","2019-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in her Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to her Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253469","253469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126176","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress her Department has made on achieving Sustainable Development Goal 1 to end poverty in all its forms everywhere.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253587","253587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126177","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made on achieving Sustainable Development Goal 8 to promote sustained, inclusive and sustainable economic growth, full and productive employment and decent work for all.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253588","253588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126178","2019-05-15","Women and Equalities","2019-05-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress her Department has made on achieving Sustainable Development Goal 10 to reduce inequality within and among countries in respect of inequality within the UK.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253589","253589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126179","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in her Department who were transferred or seconded to work (a) in other departments or (b) on other departmental briefs on preparations for the UK to leave the EU, have since returned to her Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253470","253470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126180","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has been monitoring the deployment of new (a) rooftop solar power since 1 April 2019, (b) ground mounted solar power less than or equal to 5MW since 1 April 2016 and (c) ground mounted solar power less than 5MW since 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253649","253649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126181","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the objectives of the Government’s diplomatic and political policy on Palestine are for 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253445","253445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126182","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the objectives of the Government’s diplomatic and political policy on Hungary are for 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253446","253446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126183","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the objectives of the Government’s diplomatic and political policy on Poland are for 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253447","253447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126184","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the objectives of the Government’s diplomatic and political policy on Italy are for 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253448","253448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126185","2019-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's definition is of a two-state solution for Israel and Palestine; and what steps the Government plans to take to help achieve that solution.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253449","253449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126186","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding the Government contributed to the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme prior to the privatisation of the scheme in 1994; when this money was paid in; and for what reason.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253540","253540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126187","2019-05-15","Department for International Development","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment he has made of the humanitarian situation in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253450","253450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126188","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has  ruled out the inclusion of the British Overseas Territories in plans to replace environment funding from the Financial Instrument for the Environment, LIFE, after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Dame Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253491","253491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126189","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, under what circumstances in cases involving historical sexual abuse are victims entitled to legal representation.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253582","253582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126190","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, under what circumstances in cases involving historical sexual abuse are victims entitled to have character references used in their defence.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253583","253583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126191","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what protections exist for victims of historical sexual abuse where the perpetrator remains living in the victim's locality.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253584","253584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126192","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance and training barristers receive on the cross-examination of victims of historical sexual abuse.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253585","253585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126193","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the wellbeing of victims of sexual assault of undergoing cross-examination during the court process.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253586","253586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126194","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of Professor James Malone-Lee's approach to treating urinary tract infections.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253693","253693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126195","2019-05-15","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the (a) level and (b) quality of (i) staff qualifications and (ii) in-service professional development in the pre-school childcare sector.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253524","253524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126196","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken is for a decision on an application for asylum.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253591","253591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126197","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken is for Home Office decisions on applications for asylum in the Yorkshire and Humber region.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253592","253592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126198","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of asylum claims are decided within the Home Office’s service standard that 98 per cent of straightforward claims will be decided within 6 months.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253593","253593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126199","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to allow individuals who have not received a decision on their asylum claim after six months the right to work.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253594","253594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126200","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken for asylum decisions to be made.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253595","253595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126201","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the 13th edition of the ILGA State Sponsored Homophobia Report, how many people were deported to each of the 71 countries where homosexuality is illegal in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253532","253532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126202","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce air pollution around schools.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253578","253578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126203","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to create safer cycling routes to schools.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253579","253579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126204","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the current contract for the Great Western franchise includes a requirement for a trolley-only catering service on trains.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253624","253624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126205","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the current contract for the Great Western franchise allows for the catering provision to be provided via a buffet café-bar counter service on trains.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253625","253625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126206","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department was consulted on the decision to remove the buffet café-bar service from all Great Western Intercity Express trains.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253626","253626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126207","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the level of customer demand for a trolley-only catering service on Great Western Intercity Express trains.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253627","253627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126208","2019-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterparts on the future of the village Khan al-Ahmar; and what steps he plans to take to prevent further threats to villages in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253601","253601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126209","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to promote cycling among school pupils.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253580","253580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126210","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what standards his Department used in the digital verification of people applying to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253725","253725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126211","2019-05-15","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to introduce mandatory SEN and disability law training for all SENCOs, SEN officers, managers and head teachers.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253525","253525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126212","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in the event that a UK driving test is taken and failed before a 12 month international licence expires, whether that international licence is revoked in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253577","253577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126213","2019-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities in England awarded a local business rates discount in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19; which local authorities made those awards; and what the level was of each discount.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253565","253565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126214","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which ecologists HS2 Ltd has employed to monitor tree and hedge netting along the route of High Speed Two; on what dates and at which locations nets were put in place; on what days and during which hours netted sites have been patrolled and checked by ecologists; and what wildlife has been caught in the nets and subsequently (a) perished or (b) been released.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253437","253437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126215","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much Government funding has been allocated to (a) Citizens Advice Bureau and (b) other organisations to support universal credit and other benefit claimants in Scotland.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253697","253697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126216","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea on their decontamination of the Grenfell Tower Fire site.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253716","253716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126217","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on their legal obligation to assess and quantify contaminated land within their local authority area.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253717","253717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126218","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a statutory requirement for industry to quantify the carcinogenic contents of combustible materials used in construction.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253718","253718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126219","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of health screening procedures to protect firefighters from carcinogen-related diseases.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253719","253719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126220","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the ability of firefighter health screening to detect cancers at an early stage.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253720","253720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126221","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the regularity of blood tests for firefighters.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253721","253721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126222","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the inclusion of effluents and carcinogens in public health checks after large-scale fires.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253722","253722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126223","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to introduce blood tests for effluents in public health checks after large-scale fires.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253723","253723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126224","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons his Department is unable to provide an essential interpreter for Namibian nationals undertaking a substantive asylum interview.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253648","253648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126225","2019-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support (a) under the Litigants in Person Support Strategy and (b) through the additional grant funding announced in February 2019 will be offered to (i) victims of domestic abuse and (ii) other people from the North West Durham constituency participating in family court proceedings in (A) Durham and (B) Darlington.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253724","253724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126226","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of commercial enterprises using water suppliers that are competing for customers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253652","253652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126227","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Sri Lankan Government on (a) their security concerns in the aftermath of the Easter Sunday bombings in that country and (b) cooperation on protection of endangered species since the decision to postpone the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Wild Fauna and Flora's World Wildlife Conference.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253662","253662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126228","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timeframe is for the roll-out of water competition between suppliers for domestic household consumers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253653","253653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126229","2019-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the number of people with mental health problems on social housing waiting lists.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253692","253692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126230","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many onshore wind turbine applications have been referred to and (b) approved by his Department in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253665","253665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126231","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which region has the (a) greatest and (b) least level of competition in the supply of water for commercial enterprises.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253654","253654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126232","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many onshore wind turbine applications  have been approved in each region since 2015.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253666","253666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126233","2019-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment her Department has made of the accuracy of media reports on 7 May 2019 that war graves on the Falkland Island are being disrespected; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure the protection of those graves.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253663","253663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126234","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many commercial enterprises have chosen a water supplier that was not the regional monopoly supplier in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253655","253655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126235","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of HGV lorry accidents caused by improperly secured cargo moving within a vehicle.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253509","253509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126236","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that health and safety checks are carried out to ensure that all HGV lorries carry cargo that is properly secured.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253510","253510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126237","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) fatal crashes caused by uninsured drivers and (b) speed cameras activated by uninsured drivers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253473","253473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126238","2019-05-15","Cabinet Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on local communities of parliamentary boundary changes that result in parliamentary constituencies covering three (a) district or (b) borough councils, in addition to a county council.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253664","253664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126239","2019-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the closure of the feed-in tariff scheme to new applicants, what proportion of Levy Control Framework funding across the lifetime of that scheme will be allocated to (a) schools, (b) community energy groups, (c) individual households, (d) business undertaking self-supply and (e) commercial solar developers.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253667","253667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126240","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of a national campaign to (a) reinforce recycling behaviour, (b) signpost recycling facilities and (c) ensure the public know what materials they can recycle.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253526","253526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126241","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the economy of road crashes resulting in (a) deaths and (b) serious injuries in the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253474","253474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126242","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the economy of road crashes resulting in (a) deaths and (b) serious injuries caused by uninsured drivers in the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253475","253475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126243","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made any assessment of the environmental effect of white goods manufacturers building in obsolescence to their products.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253628","253628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126244","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what has been Transport for London's budget for the British Transport Police (a) each year since 2015 and (b) what that budget proposal is for (i) 2019-20, (ii) 2020-21 and (iii) 2021-22.","Biography information for Greg Hands","Greg Hands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253533","253533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126245","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of (a) email or web form or webchat and (b) letter correspondence from (i) firms and (ii) consumers the Financial Conduct Authority provides a substantive response to within two working days of receipt; and how many such substantive responses in total there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253514","253514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126246","2019-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many visits Government Ministers have made to Hebron since 2010.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253629","253629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126247","2019-05-15","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers there have been on the Transport for London network in each of the last five years; and how many of those officers are planned to work on the Transport for London network in (a) 2019 and (b) each of the next three years.","Biography information for Greg Hands","Greg Hands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253534","253534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126248","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, on how many occasions Ministers in her Department have visited Hebron since 2010.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253630","253630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126249","2019-05-15","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of the 89 per cent conversion rate of uninsured drivers to insured under operation Tutelage in conjunction with the Motor Insurers' Bureau on police time spent processing individual PNC checks after manually downloading and cross-checking MIDAS hits from ANPR.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253476","253476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126250","2019-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference his announcement on 9 September 2018 of a review of the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme, whether his Department will extend the period of time for which survivors of child sexual abuse can claim compensation beyond 1964.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253690","253690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126251","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the aid budget is used to influence overseas governments to make policy changes.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253556","253556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126252","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) new services and (b) innovations have been introduced to the water market as a result of competition between water suppliers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253656","253656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126253","2019-05-16","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of students qualify for free school meals in each secondary school in (a) Ashfield constituency; and what the average number is of students that qualify for free school meals in secondary schools in England.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253541","253541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126254","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer what estimate he has made of the average annual savings to drivers as a result of fixing the level of fuel duty since 2010.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253559","253559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126255","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many water wholesalers operate in the water market.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253657","253657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126256","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he is taking to support the economic sustainability of the high street.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253560","253560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126257","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many water retail suppliers operate in the water market.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253658","253658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126258","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answers of 6 February 2019 to Question 214478 on Foetuses: Analgesics and of 26 February 2019 to Question 223137 on Abortion, whose role it is to oversee clinical practices to ensure (a) consistency of practice and (b) equality of patient advice and care.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253557","253557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126259","2019-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress her Department has made on the implementation of the veterans strategy.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253561","253561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126260","2019-05-16","Department for International Development","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) information his Department holds on and (b) what estimate his Department has made of the number of abortions in other countries that are funded by development spending in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253558","253558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126261","2019-05-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the UK’s contribution to tackling climate change; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253562","253562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126262","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much of the funding allocated to support the roll-out of electronic prescribing and medicines administration systems across the NHS will be allocated during the financial year 2019-2020.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253646","253646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126263","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of the funding allocated to support the roll-out of electronic prescribing and medicines administration systems across the NHS will be allocated to medicines administration systems.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253647","253647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126264","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimates his Department has made of increased demand on water supply over the next (a) 10 and (b) 20 years; and what his policy is to meet that increase in demand.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253659","253659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126265","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which region in England his Department estimates will have the (a) highest and (b) lowest demand in water supply in the next (a) 10 and (b) 20 years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253660","253660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126266","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether stocks of insulin will continue to be stockpiled to prepare for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253706","253706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126267","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of insulin procured before 29 March 2019 as part of preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal that has been (a) destroyed, (b) redistributed and (c) sold back to manufacturers.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253707","253707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126268","2019-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of England's water was produced by desalination in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253661","253661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126269","2019-05-16","Treasury","2019-05-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that musicians can transport instruments and equipment to EU27 countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253708","253708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126270","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has plans to update the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency's health and safety guidance on load securing for HGV lorries.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253511","253511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126271","2019-05-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture Media and Sport on the effect of freedom of movement on the (a) livelihoods of UK musicians and (b) UK (i) creative sector and (ii) overall economy.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253709","253709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126272","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the EU Directive 96/29/Euratom on safety standards relating to ionizing radiation, whether these is a national register of all persons potentially exposed to ionizing radiation.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253500","253500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126273","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the EU Directive 96/29/Euratom on safety standards relating to ionizing radiation, how the national register of persons potentially exposed to ionizing radiation can be accessed; and whether that register includes service personnel who have taken part in nuclear testing.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253501","253501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126274","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that cargo transported from abroad adheres to the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency's health and safety guidance when it is transported in Britain.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253512","253512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126275","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the EU Directive 96/29/Euratom on safety standards relating to ionizing radiation, whether  all persons potentially exposed to ionizing radiation are receiving independent examination for genetic damage as defined by the number of aberrant cells shown by translocation within chromosomes.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253502","253502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126276","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the EU Directive 96/29/Euratom on safety standards relating to ionizing radiation, whether all those persons potentially exposed to ionizing radiation are receiving regular medical screening by specialists in radiation medicine.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253503","253503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126277","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the EU Directive 96/29/Euratom on safety standards relating to ionizing radiation, whether (a) former armed service personnel involved in nuclear testing and (b) all those persons potentially exposed to ionizing radiation are receiving medical screening by specialists in radiation medicine independent of the Ministry of Defence.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253504","253504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126278","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the EU Directive 96/29/Euratom on safety standards relating to ionizing radiation, whether the Government is funding the implementation of the guidelines set out in that directive.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253505","253505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126279","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that non-UK based hauliers comply with the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency's health and safety guidance on load securing for HGV lorries when transporting cargo in Britain.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253513","253513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126280","2019-05-16","Cabinet Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent comparative assessment he has made of the job densities of (a) Newcastle Central, (b) the North East, (c) London and (d) the UK; and what period that assessment covers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253569","253569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126281","2019-05-16","Department for Education","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to promote international programmes of exchange in higher education after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253570","253570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126282","2019-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of funding provided for in the NHS Long Term Plan he plans to allocate to non-emergency patient transport home after hospital attendance.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253566","253566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126283","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he had with (a) the British Medical Association, (b) the Royal College of General Practitioners and (c) other representative groups before announcing the timetable for the creation of primary care networks.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253710","253710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126284","2019-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to allocate additional funding to GP practices to enable the recruitment and appointment of Primary Care Network medical directors.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253711","253711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126285","2019-05-16","Department for Transport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) legal (b) other costs to the public purse of the judicial review of the Airports National Policy Statement.","Biography information for Justine Greening","Justine Greening","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253535","253535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126286","2019-05-16","Home Office","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to help ensure that there is no increase in knife crime in Newcastle.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253571","253571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126287","2019-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on online protections for children and young people of the Internet Engineering Task Force DNS over HTTPS (DOH) protocol; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253529","253529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1126288","2019-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many internet browser providers have informed his Department that they will not be adopting the Internet Engineering Task Force DNS over HTTPS  (DOH) protocol.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253530","253530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125874","2019-05-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a statutory time limit for property management companies to issue a certificate of ownership to a new owner after selling a property.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252849","252849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125875","2019-05-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what  the value was of reductions to the local authority public health grant in each year since 2014; and what estimate he has made of trends in the level of funding for that grant in the next three years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252850","252850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125876","2019-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State Work and Pensions, whether her Department has plans to make an assessment of the potential merits of amending legislation on the transfer of ownership of high hazard sites to third parties.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252851","252851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125877","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the incidence of the taxation of carried interest has been annually since 2005.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252881","252881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125878","2019-05-15","Treasury","2019-05-10","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many public sector organisations paid workers through disguised remuneration loans.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252882","252882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125879","2019-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2018 to Question 193494 on Employment: Autism, if she will make it her policy to disaggregate data on Access to Work statistics to identify the number people with Autism Spectrum Disorders in those data sets.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252852","252852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125880","2019-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2018 to Question 193498 on Employment: Autism, over what time period was the Neurodiversity Toolkit was developed; what processes were used to develop that toolkit; and what assessment she has made of the effect of that toolkit on closing the autism employment gap.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252853","252853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125881","2019-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she make it her policy to provide autism awareness training for staff in (a) her Department and (b) Jobcentres.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252854","252854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125882","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2019 to Question 217138, what designation has been assigned to those complaints.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252883","252883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125883","2019-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2019 to Question 217138, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of her Department instructing the Independent Case Examiner to reopen complaints relating to the equalisation of the state pension age cases in the event that legal proceedings fall away.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252884","252884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125884","2019-05-15","Department for Education","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timeframe is for the Register of Training Organisations be open to new organisations.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252855","252855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125885","2019-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will commission an assessment of the effect of proposals in his Department's consultation on cleaner domestic burning of solid fuels and wood on fuel poverty in England;  and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252833","252833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125886","2019-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effects on competition of proposals in his Department's consultation on cleaner domestic burning of solid fuels and wood on fuel poverty in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252834","252834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1125887","2019-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions staff in his Department have had with their counterparts in the Department of Communications, Climate Action and Environment in the Irish Government on the effect of that Government's proposal on the burning of house coal in Ireland; and if he will make a statement","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252835","252835"
