"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818815","2018-01-10","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the security of examination answers as a result of Ofqual's recent decision to void a number of examinations due to the answers being leaked online.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121579","121579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818816","2018-01-11","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children in Sheffield Central constituency who are currently eligible for free school meals who would not be considered eligible under plans in the consultation entitled Eligibility for free school meals and the early years pupil premium under Universal Credit.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121580","121580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818817","2018-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of the 4 December 2017 to Question 116592, when the Government plans to publish its response to the Taylor Review of Modern Working Practices.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121581","121581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818818","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will remove the limitation that asylum seekers are only able to work in jobs on the shortage occupation list, when granted permission to work.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121582","121582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818819","2018-01-11","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will produce a National Refugee Integration Strategy.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121583","121583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818820","2018-01-11","Department of Health","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of the 4 December 2017 to Question 116582, if his Department will carry out an assessment of the long-term cost to the NHS of health problems and preventable deaths caused by cold homes.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121584","121584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818821","2018-01-11","Department for Transport","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has made to Volkswagen on (a) compensation to UK vehicle owners affected by the Volkswagen emissions scandal and (b) the completion of the required emissions and technological repair work for those vehicles affected.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121585","121585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818822","2018-01-11","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120011, whether she has made an assessment of the accuracy of the Ever 6 model in establishing entitlement to Pupil Premium in schools with growing pupil rolls; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121586","121586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818823","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps have been taken by the female genital mutilation unit and Forced Marriage Units to conduct outreach work among communities to highlight issues of female genital mutilation and forced marriages since 2016.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121587","121587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818824","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward proposals to hold collaborative discussions with victims and families affected by female genital mutilation in order to (a) gain insight into their perspectives on current female genital mutilation policies and efforts and (b) include victims' narratives in existing and future female genital mutilation policies and efforts.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121588","121588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818825","2018-01-11","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many representations has she received on the accuracy of the Ever 6 model in assessing the eligibility of Pupil Premium for all pupils in schools with growing pupil rolls;  and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121589","121589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818826","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken towards formal ratification of the Council of Europe Convention on the Protection of Children against Sexual Exploitation and Sexual Abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121590","121590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818827","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of hospital beds there are per one thousand of the population in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121591","121591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818828","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many copies of her Department's leaflet entitled Help for adult victims of Modern Slavery: Your immigration options if you’ve been trafficked into exploitation in the UK have been distributed; where and how those leaflets were distributed; and into which languages that leaflet has been translated.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121592","121592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818829","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on public access for walking and cycling on his Department's land.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121593","121593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818830","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which military bases, training centres, and other various military establishments are located in Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121594","121594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818831","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether potential victims of trafficking who are destitute and who have consented to a referral into the National Referral Mechanism will be accommodated under the victim care contract.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121595","121595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818832","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where recruits to the Royal Welsh regiment are based when not on active service.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121596","121596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818833","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where recruits to the Welsh Guards regiment are based when not on active service.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121597","121597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818834","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps have been taken to work with faith leaders to increase the number of signatories to the declaration condemning female genital mutilation and to use that declaration to help drive cultural change against such mutilation since 2016.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121598","121598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818835","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made an estimate of the contribution of the Welsh Guards regiment to the local economy around Woking where it is based; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121599","121599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818836","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimated contribution of the Royal Welsh regiment was to the local economy where that regiment based in Wiltshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121600","121600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818837","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many jobs the Lucknow Barracks in Tidworth, Wiltshire sustained in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121601","121601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818838","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many jobs the Elizabeth Barracks in Pirbright, Surrey sustained in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121602","121602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818839","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) civilian, (b) Royal Navy, (c) Army and (d) Royal Air Force personnel are stationed in each local authority area in Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121603","121603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818840","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to make an assessment within the framework of international humanitarian law of the nature of the violence which is taking place in Burma.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121604","121604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818841","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking on as penholder on Burma in the UN Security Council to pursue sanctions on senior military figures and businesses in Burma.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121605","121605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818842","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the agreement between the Governments of Bangladesh and Burma on the ability of Rohingya refugees to return safely to Burma.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121606","121606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818843","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Bangladesh on ensuring that no Rohingya refugees are forcibly returned to Burma.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121607","121607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818844","2018-01-10","Department for International Trade","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what advice his Department gives to UK companies on investment in Burma.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121608","121608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818845","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidelines his Department issues to people with mental health conditions with financial difficulties on accessing specialised support services.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121609","121609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818846","2018-01-11","Department of Health","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of labelling on energy drinks sold in the UK stating that such drinks are not recommended for children in preventing the consumption of energy drinks by under-18s.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121610","121610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818847","2018-01-11","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applicants were detained by the UK in 2017, broken down by grounds for detention.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121611","121611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818848","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential cost to the public purse of the renaming of his Department; and which new policy responsibilities his Department will discharge after it is renamed.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121612","121612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818849","2018-01-11","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied minors seeking asylum were detained by the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121613","121613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818850","2018-01-11","Department of Health","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to prevent the consumption of energy drinks by under-18s.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121614","121614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818851","2018-01-11","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have banned students from consuming energy drinks on school premises; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121615","121615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818852","2018-01-11","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the consumption of energy drinks by under-18s on their ability to concentrate at school.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121616","121616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818853","2018-01-11","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people were identified as suitable for appointment in the recruitment process for the board of the Office for Students but were not appointed.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121617","121617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818854","2018-01-11","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the response by the Universities Minister on the 8 January 2018 to the Urgent Question on the appointment of Toby Young to the board of the Office for Students, who was the Higher Education representative that served on the panel for appointments to the Board of the Office for Students.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121618","121618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818855","2018-01-11","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what briefing was prepared by her Department to ensure the panel for appointments to the Board of the Office for Students had sufficient background information on applicants' use of social media to ensure they were able to do due diligence on their decision.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121619","121619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818856","2018-01-11","Department for Education","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation of 8 January 2018, how many candidates deemed appointable by the most recent appointment panel for the Office for Students were not subsequently appointed.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121620","121620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818857","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of local authorities have adopted the voluntary policy requirement for adaptable and accessible homes.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121621","121621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818858","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of new homes built since 2015 which are in accordance with the voluntary policy requirement for adaptable and accessible homes.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121622","121622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818859","2018-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the environmental principles contained in EU treaties that are to be retained in UK law via the EU (Withdrawal) Bill will have general application across all environmental policy areas in the UK.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121623","121623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818860","2018-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of re-branding the Department of Communities and Local Government as the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121624","121624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818861","2018-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what changes are planned for the (a) structure and (b) personnel of his Department as a result of its re-branding as the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121625","121625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818862","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will investigate the time taken to investigate cases at Action Fraud; and if she will ensure Action Fraud has the resources necessary to investigate such cases.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121626","121626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818863","2018-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 22 December 2017 to Question 120511, on Construction: Industrial Health and Safety, what steps he is taking to support the implementation by industry of the Construction Skills Certification Scheme.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121627","121627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818864","2018-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 22 December 2017 to Question 120505, what discussions he has had with representatives of major banks on reforms to the insolvency framework since the publication of the summary of responses to the consultation.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121628","121628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818865","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to collate and assess the information which was published in brownfield registers by local authorities on or before 31 December 2017.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121629","121629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818866","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much brownfield land has been identified by each local authority in part (a) 1 and (b) 2 of their registers; and what the national figures are for such land in each category.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121630","121630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818867","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the names are of all the joint military exercises with other countries which Royal Navy vessels participated in during 2017.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121631","121631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818868","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what financial contributions the Government has made to the US administration to date to support the D5 Life Extension programme; and what future such payments the Government plans to make.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121632","121632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818869","2018-01-10","Ministry for Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning applications have been called in during the last five years; and how many of those applications related at least in part to development on or adjacent to an airfield.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121633","121633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818870","2018-01-11","HM Treasury","2018-01-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral contribution by the hon. Member for Cardiff South and Penarth on 8 January 2018, how many of the 5,000 new customs officials have been recruited.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121634","121634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818871","2018-01-11","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many new officials tasked with (a) immigration and (b) customs enforcement duties in backroom functions were recruited in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121635","121635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818872","2018-01-11","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many FTE Border Force officials tasked with immigration or customs enforcement duties were deployed to the ports of (a) Newport, (b) Cardiff, (c) Barry, (d) Swansea, (e) Pembroke Dock, (f) Milford Haven and (g) Fishguard in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121636","121636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818873","2018-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit live service claimants have been registered at (a) Cardiff and (b) Penarth JobCentre Plus in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121637","121637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818874","2018-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by what date her Department plans for legacy claimants at (a) Cardiff and (b) Penarth JobCentre Plus to have been migrated to full service universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121638","121638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818875","2018-01-11","Home Office","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many new officials tasked with (a) immigration and (b) customs enforcement duties at the UK border were recruited in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121639","121639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818876","2018-01-11","Women and Equalities","2018-01-08","If she will make a statement on her departmental responsibilities.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Ms Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903253","903253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818938","2018-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues to ensure that the industrial strategy does not discriminate against disabled people.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903241","903241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/819113","2018-01-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much additional funding is being provided to HMRC for it to comply with the planned increase in the national living wage in April 2018.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121790","121790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816666","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many new embassies and consulates the Government anticipates it will need to establish if the UK can no longer be represented by another EU member state when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121093","121093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816667","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the oral contribution of the Foreign Secretary of 27 November 2017, Official Report, column 55, how much additional funding will be provided to the NHS each week after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121094","121094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816668","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of devolving powers to the Greater London Authority on the regulation of emissions from non-road mobile machinery.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121095","121095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816669","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Mayor of London’s Office to devolve powers on the regulation of emissions from non-road mobile machinery.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121096","121096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816670","2018-01-09","Department for International Development","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many and what proportion of officials in her Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last year; and what proportion of total sick leave in her Department that leave was.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121097","121097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816671","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last year; and what proportion of total sick leave in his Department that leave was.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121098","121098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816672","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of officials in his Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last year; and what proportion of total sick leave in his Department that leave was.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121099","121099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816673","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of officials in her Department took sick leave for reasons relating to stress in the last year; and what proportion of total sick leave in her Department that leave was.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121100","121100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816674","2018-01-09","Department for International Development","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many days' sick leave officials in her Department took for reasons relating to stress in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121101","121101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816675","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many days' sick leave officials in his Department took for reasons relating to stress in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121102","121102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816676","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many days' sick leave officials in her Department took for reasons relating to stress in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121103","121103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816677","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many days' sick leave officials in his Department took for reasons relating to stress in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121104","121104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816678","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's policy is on the British Embassy and other UK Government offices in Myanmar purchasing goods or services from military-owned or controlled companies.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121105","121105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816679","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made recent representations to Aung San Suu Kyi on the continued detention of political prisoners in Myanmar.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121106","121106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816680","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost was to her Department as a result of officials taking sick leave in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121107","121107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816681","2018-01-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the cost was to her Department as a result of officials taking sick leave in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121108","121108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816682","2018-01-09","Department for International Development","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what was the cost to her Department of officials taking sick leave in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121109","121109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816683","2018-01-09","Department for International Trade","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the cost was to his Department as a result of officials taking sick leave in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121110","121110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816684","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was to his Department as a result of officials taking sick leave in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121111","121111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816685","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost was to his Department as a result of officials taking sick leave in the last year.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121112","121112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816686","2018-01-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the total cost was of compiling the sectoral analyses covering the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121113","121113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816687","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish transparency data for his meetings from March to December 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121114","121114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816688","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports his Department has received on slavery and abuse of migrants in Libya; and whether he has raised the subject of those reports with the Libyan Government.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121115","121115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816689","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of state for the Home Department, with reference to the Cabinet Office report on Implementing the Sustainable Development Goals published on 14 December 2017, what steps her Department is taking to implement the element of Sustainable Development Goal 5 on violence against women and girls.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121116","121116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816690","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the 100 metre residential impact figures for the proposed HS2 routes are for the number of properties affected at each location along the (a) M18 eastern route including the Blackwell spur, (b) 2013 consulted Meadowhall route, (c) full refined Meadowhall route from February 2016 and (d) two alternative M18 eastern route options detailed on page 82 of his Department's July 2017 publication entitled HS2 Phase 2b route refinements - advice to Government.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121117","121117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816691","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Bahraini Government on the alleged mistreatment of (a) Bahraini opposition leader Hasan Mushaima and (b) human rights activists Abdulhadi Al-Khawaja and Dr Abduljalil Al-Singace; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121118","121118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816692","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which institutions and organisations in Bahrain will directly benefit from the (a) Global Britain and (b) Integrated Activity Funds during the 2018 financial year; and which UK Government body is tasked with implementing any training for which those funds are used in Bahrain.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121119","121119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816693","2018-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2017 to Question 119037, how many Category B prisoners were held in Category C prisons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121120","121120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816694","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Markets and Competition Authority on the introduction of a cap on overdraft charges for personal current accounts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121121","121121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816695","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to encourage banks to impose the voluntary cap on overdraft charges for personal current accounts recommended by the Competition and Markets Authority in 2016; and what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of that cap on reducing repayments by customers where it has been imposed.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121122","121122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816696","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) children and young people and (b) their families or carers understand their rights when entering institutional mental health settings.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121123","121123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816697","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will recognise the partnership formed by local authorities in Lancaster, the South Lakes and Barrow in Furness to allow that partnership to develop its own local industrial strategy for the area served by the Morecambe Bay Economic Initiative.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121124","121124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816698","2018-01-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of Sate for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate the Government has made of the fiscal impact of each of the four options for reducing the maximum stake on fixed odds betting terminals set out in its consultation on maximum stakes for such terminals published on 31 October 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121125","121125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816699","2018-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120384, if he will place in the Library copies of any printed materials his Department still holds which were used in the pensions education communications campaign.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121126","121126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816700","2018-01-09","Department for International Trade","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to ensure (a) Parliamentary and (b) public scrutiny of future British-American trade talks.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121127","121127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816701","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to The Patents and Patents (Fees) (Amendment) Rules 2017, what assessment has made of the potential effect of the increase in fees on the number of patent applications.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121128","121128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816702","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent industrial fly-tipping.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121129","121129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816703","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to review fly-tipping penalties and sentences.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121130","121130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816704","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the powers of local councils to prevent fly-tipping.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121131","121131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816705","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of fly-tipping on local environments and wildlife.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121132","121132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816706","2018-01-09","Department for International Development","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's policy paper, Call to Action to End Forced Labour, Modern Slavery and Human Trafficking, published on 20 September 2017, what progress has been made on tackling the issues covered in that paper.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121133","121133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816707","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings he has had with trades unions in the past 12 months on developing a commercially sustainable proposition for the steel sector.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121134","121134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816708","2018-01-09","Department for International Trade","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many of the existing EU measures on steel and steel product dumping the Government plans to maintain after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121135","121135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816709","2018-01-09","Department for International Trade","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what process for receiving evidence on steel dumping will be established after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121136","121136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816710","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2017 to Question 114581 on iron and steel: research, if he will publish the results of the independent capability and capacity study.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121137","121137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816711","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how his Department determines main responsibility for receiving child tax credit and child benefit when care is split evenly.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121138","121138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816712","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria his Department uses to determine which parent has main responsibility for child tax credit and child benefit.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121139","121139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816713","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with pulmonary hypertension (a) nationally and (b) in South Yorkshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121140","121140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816714","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce incidences of pulmonary hypertension.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121141","121141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816715","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 115103 on electricity generation: waste, what steps he is taking to ensure that less biodegradable waste is disposed of through incineration rather than through (a) composting and (b) anaerobic digestion.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121142","121142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816716","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what waste his Department classifies as biodegradable waste.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121143","121143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816717","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to implement the EU Network and Information Systems Directive.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121144","121144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816718","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what parliamentary scrutiny there will be of the implementation of the EU Network and Information Systems Directive.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121145","121145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816719","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether any sector-specific guidance will be drafted to support the implementation of the EU Network and Information Systems Directive.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121146","121146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816720","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how compliance with the EU Network and Information Systems Directive will be (a) monitored and (b) enforced.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121147","121147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816721","2018-01-15","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2017 to Question 119260, whether his Department has a minimum acceptable level for the (a) accuracy and (b) completeness of the electoral register.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121148","121148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816722","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of local authorities provide radio aids hearing technology to assist deaf children in educational settings.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121149","121149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816723","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on animal welfare standards in that country.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121150","121150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816724","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions the Minister of State for Disabled People has had with  (a) the Motor Neurone Disease Association and (b) people with motor neurone disease on improving support for people with that condition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121151","121151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816725","2018-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve support for the families of servicemen and women during deployments.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121152","121152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816726","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve the quality and reliability of WiFi on rail services to and from Portsmouth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121153","121153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816727","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of funding sources available for charities and voluntary organisations.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121154","121154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816728","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what financial assistance her Department is providing to increase the number of visitors to Portsmouth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121155","121155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816729","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the cost of extending the HPV vaccine to teenage boys.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121156","121156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816730","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to expand routine outcome data collection for long-term conditions in children.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121157","121157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816731","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the implementation of NICE guidance on contraceptive services for people under 25.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121158","121158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816732","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage new mothers to breastfeed.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121159","121159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816733","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the take-up of the shingles vaccine by people aged over 70.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121160","121160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816734","2018-01-09","Northern Ireland Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when he plans to convene a plenary of the five main political parties in Northern Ireland to seek a resolution to the political situation in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121161","121161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816735","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has made to support the Solent’s ports and seafarers in the event that the EU and UK fail to negotiate a customs deal before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121162","121162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816736","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of school absences caused by girls’ inability to access free sanitary products.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121163","121163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816737","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last spoke to the State Counsellor of Burma in respect of her role in the Rohingya crisis.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121164","121164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816738","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether all women born in the 1950s affected by the change in state pension age have now been informed by letter of such changes.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121165","121165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816739","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Tobacco Control Plan for England will be funded.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121166","121166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816740","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to respond to the reports from the Tenancy Reform Industry Group working group submitted to him in October 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121167","121167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816741","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward proposals to implement the recommendation of the Tenancy Reform Industry Group made in October 2017 to allow tenants under the Agricultural Holdings Act 1986 to have the statutory right to assign those tenancies to assist with retirement and restructuring.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121168","121168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816742","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will implement the recommendation of the Tenancy Reform Industry Group made in October 2017 to require that contractual clauses in farm tenancies regulated by the Agricultural Holdings Act 1986 which seek to restrict farm tenants from investing in fixed equipment, diversifying or working off the holding should be subject to a test of reasonableness.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121169","121169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816743","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the recommendations from the Tenancy Reform Industry Group of October 2017, whether he has plans to encourage longer-term Farm Business Tenancies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121170","121170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816744","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer with regard to the recommendations made on taxation by the Tenancy Reform Industry Group in October 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121171","121171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816745","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has assessed the recommendations on taxation made by the Tenancy Reform Industry Group in October 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121172","121172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816746","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet the Tenant Farmers Association to discuss its proposals on taxation reform.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121173","121173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816747","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he is taking steps to ensure that local authorities obtaining best value from the management of their county council smallholding estates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121174","121174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816748","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward proposals to strengthen the accountability of local authorities in the management of their county council smallholding estates as proposed by the Tenancy Reform Industry Group in October 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121175","121175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816749","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Saad Hariri and (b) Hezbollah on securing a stable government for Lebanon.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121176","121176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816750","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the timetable is for the (a) re-establishment of full diplomatic relations with the Government of Syria including (b) re-opening the British Embassy in Damascus.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121177","121177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816751","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reason the Impact Assessment for the Draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill does not include statistical information on the (a) costs and (b) benefits of the proposals.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121178","121178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816752","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy for what reason the Impact Assessment for the Draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill does not include an assessment of the potential merits of not including an appeals process to the Competition and Markets Authority.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121179","121179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816753","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons his Department's impact assessment on the Draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill does not include an explanation for why it believes that Ofgem will be able to achieve an acceptable trade-off between the different criteria for setting the cap.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121180","121180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816754","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons his Department's impact assessment on the Draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill does not include analysis of the impact of the Pre-Payment Cap or retail price controls elsewhere.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121181","121181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816755","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy what steps his Department is taking to ensure that consumers on default or standard variable energy tariffs get a fairer deal.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121182","121182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816756","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to address the loyalty penalty faced by consumers who do not switch energy providers.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121183","121183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816757","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to sections 19 and 22 of the Transport Act 1985, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of his Department's proposed changes to section 19 and 22 permits on community groups and schools.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121184","121184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816758","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many DS1500 forms his Department has processed since the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121185","121185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816759","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken by his Department was to process a DS1500 form since the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121186","121186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816760","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has provided specific guidance to staff for dealing with terminally ill people claiming universal credit; and if he will place any such guidance in the Library.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121187","121187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816761","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the National Education Union report on Sexism in schools published in December 2017, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the relationships and sex education curriculum is designed to prevent sexism and sexual harassment among children and young people at all key stages.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121188","121188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816762","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much energy has been produced from each energy from waste facility currently operating and receiving local authority waste.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121189","121189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816763","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that medical students are acquiring the basic clinical skills to make a diagnosis of ME/CFS.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121190","121190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816764","2018-01-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to standardise the collection and disposal of plastic items from the doorstep.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121191","121191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816765","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much planned additional renewable energy capacity is estimated for each of the next five years, broken down by sector.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121192","121192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816766","2018-01-09","Department for International Development","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what measures her Department has put in place to assist children recovered from abduction in the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121193","121193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816767","2018-01-09","Department for International Development","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department has provided to Puerto Rico to assist with the reconnection of water and electricity as a result of the storms of September 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121194","121194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816768","2018-01-10","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish the minutes and other papers for the meetings between the Permanent Secretary at his Department and Shanker Singham of the Legatum Institute.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121195","121195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816769","2018-01-10","Scotland Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2017 to Question 118337, on Scotland Office: Buildings; what the equivalent costs were for the previous five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121196","121196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816770","2018-01-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to regulate Chlorothalonil and other fungicides after research from Cornell University showed the link between Chlorothalonil and other fungicides to the decline in bee populations.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121197","121197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816771","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will introduce a website similar to Operation Snap introduced in Scotland to help the public report road traffic offences in England.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121198","121198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816772","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what arrangements she has made with the US Department of Homeland Security and Transportation Security Administration with regard to UK citizens' access to visas.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121199","121199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816773","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received on researchers being excluded from EU research projects as a result of the UK’s decision to leave the EU; and if he will provide a breakdown of those representations by academia and industry.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121200","121200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816774","2018-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government plans to contribute to the EU Battlegroup planned for 2019.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121201","121201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816775","2018-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has for UK involvement in the European Defence Fund after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121202","121202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816776","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's news story of 18 December 2017 about the 200 suppliers who sign up to the Contracts Finder service each week, how many of those suppliers are SMEs; and if he will provide a breakdown of those firms by region.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121203","121203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816777","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities have applied to her Department for authorisation to make further deductions or variations to the limits set out in the School and Early Years Finance (England) Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121204","121204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816778","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120097, what his definition of first contact is.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121205","121205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816779","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of rising household debt on levels of child poverty.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121206","121206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816780","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to make consumer markets operate more fairly to reduce the costs of essential household items.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121207","121207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816781","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment of whether markets have been found to act against consumer interests.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121208","121208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816782","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to reduce the cap on the cost of credit offered by payday lenders.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121209","121209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816783","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to increase the ability of regulators and consumer enforcement bodies to order fines against companies that have been found to have broken consumer law and to deliver redress.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121210","121210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816784","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has a policy on the use by civil servants of instant-messaging apps for the purpose of completing their work.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121211","121211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816785","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the reasons why the average number of sick days taken by civil servants decreased in the past 12 months; and what assessment he has made of the effect of a potential culture of presenteeism on that trend.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121212","121212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816786","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that businesses make terms and conditions of online purchases clearer.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121213","121213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816787","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to implement a duty on regulators to identify vulnerable customers within the finance industry.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121214","121214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816788","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information the Government holds on the proportion of civil service sick days taken for reasons relating to (a) mental ill-health and (b) physical ill health.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121215","121215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816789","2018-01-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding the Scout Association received from the Government in each of the last seven years; and the purposes for which that funding was provided.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121216","121216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816790","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants have travelled abroad in relation to projects organised through the Government's Prosperity Fund since that fund was established.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121217","121217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816791","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the amount of government funding was on Cadet Forces in each of the last seven years; how much of that funding was allocated to the Cadet Expansion Scheme in each of those years; and on what the other funding was spent in each of those years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121218","121218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816792","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average cost has been of each project organised through the Government's Prosperity Fund since that fund was established.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121219","121219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816793","2018-01-10","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much government funding was received by public and private school Cadet Forces through the Combined Cadet Force in each of the last seven years; and on what that funding was spent.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121220","121220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816794","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many contracts were put out to tender for the purpose of completing projects organised by the Government's Prosperity Fund during 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121221","121221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816795","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding from the public purse the Volunteer Police Cadets received in each of the last seven years; and on what such funding was spent.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121222","121222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816796","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many projects organised through the Government's Prosperity Fund have included a partnership with the Behavioural Insights Team since that fund was established.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121223","121223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816797","2018-01-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much Government funding has been allocated to the National Citizen Service in each of the last seven years; how that money was allocated; and what the objectives were for that spending.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121224","121224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816798","2018-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what spending controls apply to projects funded through the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121225","121225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816799","2018-01-10","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications were received to serve on the board for the Office for Students.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121226","121226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816800","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the increase in level of capacity of the Register to Vote website was between June 2016 and the end of December 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121227","121227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816801","2018-01-11","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department when UK Visas and Immigration plans to respond to the letter of the hon. Member for Slough dated 26 September 2017, ref S1767125 on behalf of a constituent.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121228","121228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816802","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page five of the transparency data, RCDTS: gender pay gap report and data 2017, published on 21 December 2017, if he will break down the pay gap data by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121229","121229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816803","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the transparency data, DCMS gender pay gap 2016-2017, published on 18 December 2017, if she will publish the pay gap data for ordinary pay and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121230","121230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816804","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the transparency data, MHRA gender pay gap report: 2016 to 2017, published on 18 December 2017, if he will break down the pay gap data on (a) ordinary, (b) hourly and (c) bonus pay by profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121231","121231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816805","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the transparency document entitled Natural England Gender Pay Gap Report 2017, if he will set out the pay gap data on ordinary pay and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121232","121232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816806","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the transparency document entitled DCLG's Gender Pay Gap Report 2017, if he will set out the pay gap data for median, mean and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121233","121233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816807","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether targets are in place for maximum waiting times for diagnosis of children with behavioural disorders such as ADHD.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121234","121234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816808","2018-01-10","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the transparency document entitled Valuation Office Agency's Gender Pay Gap Report 2017, if he will set out the pay gap data for median, mean and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121235","121235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816809","2018-01-10","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to transparency data, DfT's gender pay gap report 2017, published 18 December 2018, if he will break down the pay gap data for median, mean and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121236","121236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816810","2018-01-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the transparency document entitled DEFRA's Gender Pay Gap Report 2017, if he will set out the pay gap data for median, mean and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121237","121237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816811","2018-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the transparency document entitled Department for Work and Pensions: Gender Pay Gap Report 2017, if he will set out the pay gap data for median, mean and bonus pay by (a) each specific grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121238","121238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816812","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the transparency document entitled Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy: Gender Pay Gap Report 2017, if he will set out the pay gap data for median, mean and bonus pay by (a) grade, (b) profession and (c) and whether the staff to whom that data applies are from (i) the core department or (ii) arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121239","121239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816813","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the transparency document entitled Marine Management Organisation Gender Pay Gap Report 2017, if he will set out the pay gap data for median, mean and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121240","121240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816814","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's transparency document entitled Gender Pay Gap Report 2016-2017, if he will set out the pay gap data for median, mean and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121241","121241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816815","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the e-mail sent on behalf of a constituent on 13 November 2017 by the hon. Member for Slough (ref A1829182).","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121242","121242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816816","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department collects data on the number of hospital admissions for people with (a) age-related macular degeneration, (b) glaucoma and (c) diabetic retinopathy.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121243","121243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816817","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a national eye health strategy to address the increase in the level of sight-threatening conditions.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121244","121244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816818","2018-01-10","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Gender Pay Gap Report 2016-2017: HM Treasury Group, if he will break down the data on the gender pay gap data for (a) median, (b) mean and (c) bonus pay by (i) grade and (ii) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121245","121245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816819","2018-01-09","Department for International Trade","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the UKEF Gender Pay Gap Report 2016-2017, if she will break down the pay gap data for (a) median, (b) mean and (c) bonus pay by (i) grade and (ii) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121246","121246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816820","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Home Office Gender Pay Gap Report 2017, if she will break down the pay gap data for (a) median, (b) mean and (c) bonus pay by (i) grade and (ii) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121247","121247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816821","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the transparency document entitled Foreign and Commonwealth Office Gender Pay Gap Report, if he will set out the pay gap data for median, mean and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121248","121248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816822","2018-01-09","Department for International Trade","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the 2016-17 data on the gender pay gap in his Department, if he will break down the pay gap data for (a) median, (b) mean and (c) bonus pay by (i) grade and (ii) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121249","121249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816823","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many contracts that involve processing personal data will be affected by Procurement Policy Note 03/17.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121250","121250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816824","2018-01-09","Department for International Trade","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 22 December 2017 to Question 119231, if he will place in the Library a copy of the analytical work his Department has undertaken examining the implications of the UK leaving the EU on all sectors of the UK economy.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121251","121251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816825","2018-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance is issued to Coroners on respect for religious beliefs which require speedy burial following death.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121252","121252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816826","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking (a) to increase the number of inspectors and (b) to raise the level of penalties to deal with employers who pay less than the minimum wage.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121253","121253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816827","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department taking with electric vehicle manufacturers to ensure that a common charging connection is used for all electric vehicles.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121254","121254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816828","2018-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Royal Navy vessels are on duty in the Gulf; and when those vessels are planned to return to the UK.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121255","121255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816829","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the spread of Xylella through the importation of infected plants.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121256","121256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816830","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding has been allocated for universal support in 2016-17; how much funding for universal support has been allocated to each local authority in 2016-17; and how many people have accessed universal support.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121257","121257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816831","2018-01-09","Department for International Development","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 117786, if she will answer that question with reference to all forms of representation, not only face-to-face meetings.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121258","121258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816832","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of children receiving free school meals who are entitled to them.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121259","121259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816833","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has sought legal advice on the relationship between the European Court of Justice and the European Aviation Safety Agency.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121260","121260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816834","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what funding his Department has allocated to nuclear fusion research to 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121261","121261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816835","2018-01-10","Department for International Trade","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which overseas trips Ministers of his Department have made since July 2016; and what were the costs of each such trip.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121262","121262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816836","2018-01-10","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which overseas trips Ministers of his Department have made since July 2016; and what were the costs of each such trip.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121263","121263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816837","2018-01-09","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department has issued on the target timescales for Ministerial responses to be sent to letters received from hon. Members.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121264","121264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816838","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120003, how many photovoltaics installations through Green Deal plans provided by Home Energy Lifestyle Management Systems were undertaken in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121265","121265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816839","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120003, what steps he has taken to ensure that the installation of photovoltaics at those home complied with the funding rules of the Green Deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121266","121266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816840","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120003, on Home Energy and Lifestyle Management, how many of those homes received (a) partial write off and (b) full cancellation of Green Deal Finance loans.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121267","121267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816841","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Slough to receive a written response to his email of 10 November 2017 to UK Visas and Immigration on behalf of a constituent, ref VAF345843.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121268","121268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816842","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 116748, how much of the £1.2 billion of funding for the Starter Home Land Fund has been spent to date.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121269","121269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816843","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 118353, on Temporary Accommodation, how much of that fund has been designated for use by England excluding London; and by what date he plans that fund to be rolled out to the rest of England.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121270","121270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816844","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has received any representations on difficulties experienced by GPs in obtaining (a) diamorphine and (b) other prescription drugs; and whether he is taking steps to increase the ease of access to such drugs by GPs.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121271","121271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816845","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether staple gluten-free foods will continue to be available on prescription for people with coeliac disease.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121272","121272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816846","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the reason is for the difference in the repayment thresholds for Plan 1 and Plan 2 loan schemes.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121273","121273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816847","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason students with a Student Loan living in countries with higher tax rates are subject to a lower repayment threshold than students living in the UK.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121274","121274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816848","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons the Student Loan repayment rate is calculated using gross salary levels.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121275","121275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816849","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the cap on Access to Work funding does not affect deaf employees (a) applying for a promotion or (b) developing a career.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121276","121276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816850","2018-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made by his Department on implementing the outcome of the research it carried out in 2016 on evaluating the adequacy of the guidance in the relevant building regulations for providing toilets equipped with changing facilities for people with disabilities; and whether a review of that guidance was an outcome of that research.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121277","121277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816851","2018-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to amend  the relevant building regulations to require all large buildings to have Changing Places toilet facilities for people with profound disabilities.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121278","121278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816852","2018-01-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much Arts Council England spent in each English parliamentary constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121279","121279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816853","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much and what proportion of the money committed to the East Midlands by his Department for the 2020 Mayflower Pilgrims 400th anniversary has been allocated to date.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121280","121280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816854","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many athletics tracks have been (a) closed and (b) opened since the 2012 London Olympic Games.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121281","121281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816855","2018-01-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding the Football Foundation has allocated to each English parliamentary constituency since its creation.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121282","121282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816856","2018-01-09","Church Commissioners","2018-01-05","To ask the hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what progress has been made on securing visitor toilets for Scrooby church.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121283","121283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816857","2018-01-09","House of Commons Commission","2018-01-05","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what discussions have taken place with the architect Ian Ward about the use of Portcullis House as a possible temporary Chamber.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121284","121284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816858","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many residential care homes inspected by the Care Quality Commission have been rated (a) inadequate and (b) outstanding in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121285","121285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816859","2018-01-10","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's transparency document entitled Gender pay gap report published on 18 December 2017, if he will set out the data on ordinary pay and bonus pay by (a) grade and (b) profession.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121286","121286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816860","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether there is a minimum limit above which charitable organisations must bid in applying for funding from the tampon tax fund.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121287","121287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816861","2018-01-10","Attorney General","2018-01-05","To ask the Attorney General, how much money has been spent from the public purse on training members of the CPS and its agents on the criminalisation of forced marriage and the breach of  forced marriage protection orders since the coming into force of the Anti-Social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014; what events took place relating to that training; and how many people attended those events.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121288","121288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816862","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number  of Overseas Visitors Managers employed by each acute NHS Trust in the North West as of 31 December 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121289","121289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816863","2018-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) charged and (b) convicted with (i) forcing someone to marry and (ii) the breach of a forced marriage protection order since the coming into force of the Anti-Social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121290","121290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816864","2018-01-10","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers have (a) applied for and (b) been granted an individual firearms licence since 2011.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121291","121291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816865","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 24 January 2017 to Question 59987 and pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 106993, what steps his Department has taken on the provision of ambulance services as part of NHS planning arrangements for winter 2017-18 and operational resilience planning to ensure the health and social care system is adequately prepared to cope with winter pressures in the North West; and what the avergage waiting times were for ambulances in that region on each day between 23 December 2017 and 2 January 2018 inclusive.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121292","121292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816866","2018-01-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which of his Department's Quarterly Transparency Returns contains the list of attendees at the meetings referenced in Questions 119375, 119359, 119349, 119342, 119051, 119043, 118993, 118986, 118972, 118958, 118954, 118951 and 118948.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121293","121293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816867","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many FP57 forms were processed by the NHS Business Services Authority in 2017 for people seeking a refund for prescription charges; and what the average cost of processing a FP57 form and returning the prescription charge to the applicant was in 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121294","121294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816868","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU nationals, both adults and children, have been refused citizenship in each year between 2010 and 2017.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121295","121295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816869","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU nationals have been refused the right to remain in each year between 2010 and 2017.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121296","121296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816870","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the operation of section 54 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 and the level of compliance by businesses.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121297","121297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816871","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to address safety concerns raised by driving test examiners in risk assessments in respect of the new driving test.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121298","121298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816872","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to use the powers of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 to challenge organisations that are late in filing their modern slavery statements.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121299","121299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816873","2018-01-09","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions the Government has had with European Union negotiators on proposals for associate EU citizenship for British nationals who wish apply for that status in the event that the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121300","121300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816874","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the membership of the Green Finance Taskforce and each such member's business interests and affiliation.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121301","121301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816875","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of (a) replacing the Emissions Trading System modernisation funding and (b) redirecting investment in coal power stations to clean energy after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121302","121302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816876","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the letter from the Minister for Employment to the hon. Member for Brighton Pavilion of 15 November 2017 on universal credit, what the evidential basis is for the Minister’s statement that those on universal credit are moving into work significantly faster and working longer than under the previous benefits system.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121303","121303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816877","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals for a new Environment Bill after the UK leaves the EU which reflects the policy aims of the devolved administrations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121304","121304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816878","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on establishing the biodiversity net gain approach in environmental law after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121305","121305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816879","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to use the biodiversity net gain approach to establish environmental performance criteria for farmers and landowners as part of his approach to public funding for agriculture.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121306","121306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816880","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will establish a new strategic framework for designating protected sites and species within UK environmental law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121307","121307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816881","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what technical support the UK Government is providing to the Colombian Government to ensure the establishment of the proposed Truth Commission in that country.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121308","121308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816882","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the Colombian Government in (a) progressing peace talks with the ELN, (b) extending the bilateral ceasefire and (c) dismantling the economic, political and military structures of the paramilitary groups.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121309","121309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816883","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart on (a) offering a date-specific official invitation  to the UN Special Rapporteur on Human Rights Defenders to visit Colombia and (b) ensuring that the mandate of the UN mission to Colombia with regards to the monitoring the human rights situation is maintained.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121310","121310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816884","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any funding for the new national economic crime centre will be allocated out of the budgets for the Serious Fraud Office or any of the other relevant agencies involved in the centre.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121311","121311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816885","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of online ticket platforms on the affordability of tickets to entertainment events.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121312","121312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816886","2018-01-10","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the selection criteria were for positions on the board of the Office for Students.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121313","121313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816887","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to take steps to limit the ability of online robots to purchase tickets for entertainment events.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121314","121314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816888","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff employed at (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals, (b) University Hospitals of Morecambe Bay, (c) Blackpool Teaching Hospitals are (i) being pursued for parking fines by their employers and (ii) are subject to deductions from wages or other actions by bailiffs to recoup such fines and other costs.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121315","121315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816889","2018-01-10","Cabinet Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the position of Crown Representative to Carillion was vacant during the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121316","121316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816891","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that care homes do not close as a result of the recent ruling on pay during sleep-in shifts.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121318","121318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816892","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made representations to the Egyptian Government on the arrest of 25 Ahmadi Muslims in that country on the grounds of their religion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121319","121319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816893","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Foreign Office has made to the Peruvian Government on environmental protection in that country as a result of the death of the deforestation campaigner José Napoleón Tarrillo Astonitas.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121320","121320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816894","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he is taking steps to reduce the production of single-use plastics in the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121321","121321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816895","2018-01-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to increase public investment in reprocessing facilities for plastics as a result of the imposition of the ban on imported plastics by China.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121322","121322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816896","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a Minister for the first 1001 Days to lead joint work with the Department for Education on that issue.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121323","121323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816897","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what advice he has received from the Hazardous Substances Advisory Committee on the existence of solid plastic particles in products other than rinse-off cosmetic and personal care products and their likelihood of entering the marine environment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121324","121324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816898","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many temporary exclusion orders have been imposed on people under the Counter-Terrorism and Security Act 2015 in each year.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121325","121325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816899","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to ban microbeads from (a) sunscreen and (b) all other leave-on cosmetic and personal care products.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121326","121326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816900","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people had passports seized and temporarily retained under section 1 of the Counter-Terrorism and Security Act 2015 in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121327","121327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816901","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any permits to return have been issued under section 5 of the Counter-Terrorism and Security Act 2015.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121328","121328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816902","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Japanese counterpart on the situation in North Korea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121329","121329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816903","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had any recent discussions with his international counterparts on the non-proliferation and reduction of nuclear weapons.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121330","121330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816904","2018-01-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he will be making representations to the UN Conference on Disarmament in 2018.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121331","121331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816905","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many penalties by type have been issued for employing illegal workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121332","121332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816906","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of no deal with the EU on (a) the implementation of the industrial strategy and (b) the ability to secure private research and development investment to achieve the target set out in that strategy.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121333","121333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816907","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of families that will become ineligible for free school meals as a result of proposed changes to the net earnings threshold and how many of those families would benefit financially by reducing their income in order to receive free school meals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121334","121334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816908","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of shale gas extraction with the domestic and international climate change commitments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121335","121335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816909","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2017 to Question 112129, on sign language: GCSE, whether a Level 2 qualification in British Sign Language would be accepted as equivalent to a GCSE for the English Baccalaureate.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121336","121336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816910","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2017 to Question 112129, on sign language: GCSE, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on disabled young people of there not being a GCSE available in British Sign Language.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121337","121337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816911","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2017 to Question 112129, on sign language: GCSE, when her Department plans to introduce new GCSEs.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121338","121338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816912","2018-01-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the cost to the public purse is of independent evaluations of the National Citizens Service in each year since that programme began.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121339","121339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816913","2018-01-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how newly built student accommodation is recorded in his Department's data set entitled Housing supply: net additional dwellings; whether each block of such accommodation counts as one unit or as a number of units corresponding to the number of students it accommodates; what steps his Department takes to ensure consistency in applying rules about recording student and other communal accommodation as net additional dwelling; and how many student accommodation units are included in his Department's most recent estimate of the number of net additional dwellings.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121340","121340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816914","2018-01-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether any of the £135 million announced by her Department on 4 January 2018 as pledged to Big Society Capital to fund stable and long-term accommodation for vulnerable groups has previously been allocated or announced.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121341","121341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816915","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons his Department decided against the introduction of a transitional protection period for people claiming support for mortgage interest after April 2018.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121342","121342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816916","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the contribution to the public purse of applications for immigration after all costs to the Department are covered in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121343","121343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816917","2018-01-10","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to protect (a) confidential patient records and (b) NHS services from (i) meltdown and (ii) spectre vulnerabilities in NHS computer processors.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121344","121344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816918","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department plans to issue to schools on tackling peer-on-peer sexual abuse.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121345","121345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816919","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to prevent peer-on-peer sexual abuse in schools.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121346","121346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816920","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to improve and strengthen the teaching of consent during sex and relationship education in schools.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121347","121347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816921","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether there is a time frame in which the DVLA must (a) respond and (b) take action after the reporting of untaxed or abandoned vehicles on public roads.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121348","121348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816922","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many outgoing Dublin III regulation transfers were made by the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121349","121349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816923","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average duration was for the Dublin III regulation procedure from the issue of outgoing request to the UK to the transfer to the Member State responsible.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121350","121350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816924","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average duration was of the Dublin III regulation procedure from a Member State accepting responsibility to the transfer from the UK to the Member State responsible.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121351","121351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816925","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many decisions to cease asylum support were made in 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121352","121352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816926","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many residents were accommodated in each asylum reception centre in the UK at the end of 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121353","121353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816927","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applicants were granted permission to work in the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121354","121354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816928","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applicants granted permission to work were employed in Government Departments in 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121355","121355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816929","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incoming Dublin III regulation requests were received by the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121356","121356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816930","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which three countries made the most Dublin III regulation requests to the UK in 2017; and how many such requests were made by each of those countries.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121357","121357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816931","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incoming Dublin III regulation requests based on Article 16 Regulation 604/2013 relating to the dependent persons clause were received by the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121358","121358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816932","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incoming Dublin III regulation requests based on the discretionary clause pursuant to Article 17(2) Regulation 604/2013 (“humanitarian clause”) were received by the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121359","121359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816933","2018-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on closing universal credit claims when income in any monthly assessment period results in a zero payment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121360","121360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816934","2018-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 68 of the Government's report, Improving Lives: The Future of health, Work and Disability, published in November 2017, Cm 9526, if he will consult with disabled people (a) on the proposed changes to the work and capability assessment and (b) on those proposed changes ahead of the publication of the Government's proposed consultation on statutory sick pay.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121361","121361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816935","2018-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish the Government's proposed consultation on statutory sick pay.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121362","121362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816936","2018-01-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support disabled people with high energy costs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121363","121363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816937","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to encourage the use of social prescribing by GPs; and what recent discussions has he had with NHS Clinical Commissioners on social prescribing.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121364","121364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816938","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with online gaming platform providers on ensuring that moderators identify and remove hate speech and ban offending users.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121365","121365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816939","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has had recent discussions with online gaming platform providers on strengthening user guidelines to ensure that hate speech is removed and that offending users are banned.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121366","121366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816940","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has had recent discussions with online gaming platform providers on the creation of a voluntary code of conduct for online gaming; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121367","121367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816941","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will include online gaming platforms in the UK Government’s code of practice for social media providers and if she will bake the code legally binding.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121368","121368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816942","2018-01-09","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what her Department’s policy is on tackling the use of hate speech on online gaming platforms.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121369","121369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816943","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Clinical Commissioning Groups have a policy of not accepting sponsorship from drug companies and similar organisations; and whether his Department plans to regulate or stop such sponsorship arrangements.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121370","121370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816944","2018-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests for legal assistance were made by asylum applicants during the first instance procedure in 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121371","121371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816945","2018-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests there were for legal assistance by asylum applicants during the first instance procedure in the UK in 2017 by type of procedure concerned.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121372","121372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816946","2018-01-09","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests for legal assistance by asylum applicants during the first instance procedure in 2017 resulted in a grant of legal assistance.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121373","121373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816947","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120015 on High Speed 2 railway line, if he will name (a) all 12 applications made to the HS2 Community and Environment Fund, (b) the six successful applicants and (c) identify which of those applicants have accepted the terms and conditions.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121374","121374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816948","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of the Oil and Gas Authority's remit to maximise the economic recovery of the UK's oil and gas resources with the responsibility given in the 30 November 2017 Direction to the Oil and Gas Authority, to take account of whether the conditions in section 4A of the Petroleum Act 1998 are met; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121375","121375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816949","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 December 2017 to Question 115696 on fracking: Ryedale, whether Regulation 19 of the Offshore Installations and Wells (Design and Construction) Regulations 1996 has been adequately adhered to in relation to both the drilling and workover phases of the KM8 well in Ryedale as required under section 4A of the Petroleum Act 1998.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121376","121376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816950","2018-01-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2017 to Question 117664, whether data on households in receipt of universal credit in which a child is or is about to be two years’ old is currently included in the information on qualifying households provided by his Department to the Department for Education.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121377","121377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816951","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2017 to Question 117664, what use her Department makes of the information on qualifying households in receipt of universal credit and other legacy benefits that is provided to her Department by the Department for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121378","121378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816952","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how local authorities are informed of households in their area in receipt of universal credit that include a child that is or is about to be two years’ old so that they can promote the free early years education entitlement for two-year-olds to qualifying households.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121379","121379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816953","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department will be taking account of families in receipt of universal credit when evaluating and benchmarking the take-up of the free early years education entitlement for two-year-olds in local authority areas.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121380","121380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816954","2018-01-09","Department for Education","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of families in Wansbeck constituency who would be entitled to free school meals under the pre-universal infant free school meals system.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121381","121381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816955","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to make the M5 in the South West a smart motorway.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121382","121382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816956","2018-01-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the cost to public purse is for China and other countries to take delivery of plastic waste from the UK.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121383","121383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816957","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Direction to the Oil and Gas Authority of 30 November 2017, relating to consent for fracking operations at the KM8 well in Ryedale, what the timetable is for his consultation with the Oil and Gas Authority; and if he will publish his recommendation to the Oil and Gas Authority on the hydraulic fracturing consent conditions required under section 4A of the Petroleum Act 1998 when that recommendation is made.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121384","121384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816958","2018-01-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that access to fast broadband is a planning condition for new housing estate and business park developments.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121385","121385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816959","2018-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he will implement a full defence review before 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121386","121386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816960","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of NHS appointments that have been cancelled or postponed in (a) Wakefield district and (b) West Yorkshire in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121387","121387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816961","2018-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost to public purse of introducing the new Mark 4A non-nuclear arming, fusing and firing system to the UK’s Mark 4 nuclear warhead.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121388","121388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816962","2018-01-09","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has received reports of imminent missile test launches by North Korea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121389","121389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816963","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Russian counterpart on the situation in North Korea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121390","121390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816964","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the effectiveness of UN Security Council sanctions in encouraging North Korea to cease its nuclear activities.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121391","121391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816965","2018-01-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the UK's Permanent Ambassador to the UN on the most recent UN Security Council resolution on North Korea.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121392","121392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816966","2018-01-09","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the provision of tampons and sanitary towels is for women in custody at each police station in each constabulary in the North West of England.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121393","121393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816967","2018-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2017 to Question 118806, on Social Fund: Credit, how many loans were provided through the Discretionary Social Fund in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121394","121394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816968","2018-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria are used to prioritise imprisonment for public protection cases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121395","121395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816969","2018-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to increase the transparency of Parole Board decisions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121396","121396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816970","2018-01-09","HM Treasury","2018-01-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government's planned Breathing Space scheme will include a full 12-month freeze on interest, charges and debt collection activity.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121397","121397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816971","2018-01-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to make people in receipt of the Support for Mortgage Interest scheme aware of forthcoming changes to that scheme; and what assessment he has made of the long-term effect on the security of the recipients' homes as a result of people moving from a benefit to an interest-bearing loan.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121398","121398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816972","2018-01-10","Home Office","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that police services provide access to sanitary care products and washing facilities to all female detainees who are menstruating.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121399","121399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816973","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce pressure on NHS A&E departments in (a) South Tyneside, (b) Gateshead, (c) the North East and (d) England.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121400","121400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816974","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people have travelled to work using public transport in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121401","121401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816975","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of people who travel to work by (a) car, (b) bus and (c) rail in (i) the North East, (ii) Tyne and Wear, (iii) England and (iv) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121402","121402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816976","2018-01-09","Department for Transport","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve road safety on the A19 road in north-east England.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121403","121403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816977","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Community Post Offices in each Parliamentary constituency receive funding from the public purse.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121404","121404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816978","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) main post offices, (b) local post offices and (c) community post offices have closed as a result of network transformation.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121405","121405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816979","2018-01-09","Department of Health","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the effect of changes in the value of the pound since June 2016 on NHS supply costs.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121406","121406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816980","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many cases of fraud have been detected in the management of (a) main post offices, (b) local post offices and (c) community post offices in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121407","121407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816981","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will list all cases of fraud or theft greater than £50,000 detected within the management of UK Post Offices in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121408","121408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816982","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the customer satisfaction levels (a) before and (b) after the transfer of Crown post offices to private sector management.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121409","121409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816983","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department  has taken to recognise and reward long-term service and loyalty of postmasters.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121410","121410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816984","2018-01-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average amount spent by his Department on training new entrant post-masters in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121411","121411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816985","2018-01-09","Prime Minister","2018-01-05","To ask the Prime Minister, who attended each meeting of (a) the European Union Exit and Trade Cabinet Committee, (b) the European Union Exit and Trade (Strategy and Negotiations) Cabinet sub-Committee, (c) the European Union Exit and Trade (International Trade) Cabinet sub-Committee, (d) the European Union Exit and Trade (Domestic Preparedness, Legislation and Devolution) Cabinet sub-Committee and (e) the European Union Exit and Trade (European Affairs) Cabinet sub-Committee.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121412","121412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/816986","2018-01-10","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment the Government has made of the effectiveness of its sex offender treatment programmes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121413","121413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/818667","2018-01-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs what the time frame is for local authorities to (a) respond and (b) take action in regard to a report of an untaxed or abandoned vehicle on a public road.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121431","121431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/793896","2017-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the conclusions of the Tell MAMA Annual Report for 2016 on Anti-Muslim Hatred on the gender of victims and the majority identity of perpetrators of such hatred.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 114985","114985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810701","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the United Kingdom will remain a member of the European Committee on Standardisation after we leave the EU.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121046","121046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810162","2018-01-08","Department for Transport","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which measures in addition to those set out in the Clean Growth Strategy will be required to keep aviation emissions to 37.5 MegaTonnes.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120628","120628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810400","2017-12-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-21","What recent assessment she has made of the potential effect on the digital and tech industries of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903087","903087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810401","2017-12-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-21","What steps the Government is taking to protect young people from gambling-related harm.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903088","903088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810402","2017-12-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-21","What steps her Department is taking to tackle problem gambling.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903090","903090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810403","2017-12-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-21","What steps her Department is taking to improve access to sports facilities.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903092","903092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810473","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for his Department to respond to the Sixth Report from the Joint Committee on Human Rights, Human Rights and Business 2017: Promoting responsibility and ensuring accountability, HC443 of Session 2016–17.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120819","120819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810474","2018-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many jobs will be relocated out of the UK as a result of the (a) European Banking Authority and (b) European Medicines Agency moving their headquarters out of London.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120820","120820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810475","2018-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Government of Bahrain on (a) the denial of adequate medical access and (b) family visits for (i) Abdulwahhab Husain, (ii) Abduljalil Al-Singace and (iii) Hassan Mushaima.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120821","120821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810476","2018-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, reference to his Department's Torture and Mistreatment Reporting Guidance how many reports he received from his staff in Bahrain between August 2016 and November 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120822","120822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810477","2018-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in how many states does the UK  (a) not have consular representation and (b) have consular representation for UK citizens provided for by consular authorities of another EU member state.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120823","120823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810478","2018-01-08","Home Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that her Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120824","120824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810479","2018-01-08","Department for International Development","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that have been allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120825","120825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810480","2018-01-08","Department for International Trade","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that his Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120826","120826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810481","2018-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that his Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120827","120827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810482","2018-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that his Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120828","120828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810483","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that his Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120829","120829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810484","2018-01-08","Department for Education","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that her Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120830","120830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810485","2018-01-08","Department for Transport","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that his Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120831","120831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810486","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that his Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120832","120832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810487","2018-01-08","Cabinet Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that his Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120833","120833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810488","2018-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the time spent by officials in his Department compiling impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date each such assessment was started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120834","120834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810489","2018-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions,what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that his Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120835","120835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810490","2018-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount of time and (b) resources that his Department allocated to the production of impact assessments on the UK leaving the EU; and on what date work on those impact assessments started.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120836","120836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810491","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on tackling incidences of mis-selling of green energy deals.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120837","120837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810492","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what powers are available to Ofgem to protect consumers against fraud by green deal energy providers.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120838","120838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810493","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2017 to Question 112819 on Carers: Young People, what the programme of work is for the cross-Government programme and whether it will include the support for young carers.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120839","120839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810494","2018-01-08","Home Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of (a) reported and (b) unreported hate crimes against (i) disabled people and (ii) homeless people in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120840","120840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810495","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that it has adequate medical importation and exportation customs expertise after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120841","120841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810496","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patient access to medicines currently available in the UK is maintained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120842","120842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810497","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many therapists are working in primary care at (a) March 2017 and (b) the most recent date for which data is available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120843","120843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810498","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Government is monitoring whether NHS hospitals have adopted good practice to enable appropriate patient flow through (a) more timely hand-offs between their A&E clinicians and acute physicians, (d) discharge to assess, (c) trusted assessor arrangements, (d) streamlined continuing healthcare processes, (e) seven day discharge capabilities and (f) other methods.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120844","120844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810499","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of effect of the UK leaving the EU on patients involved in EU clinical trails.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120845","120845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810500","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department taking to ensure access to European clinical trails for the treatment of rare diseases by UK patients after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120846","120846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810501","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to roll-out nationally Mental Health Support Teams in 2022-23 in the event that the pilot phase is successful.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120847","120847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810502","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of trends in the number of GPs.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120848","120848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810503","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of NHS 111 online.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120849","120849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810504","2018-01-08","Cabinet Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many patients were recording as having died as a result of malnutrition in NHS hospitals in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120850","120850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810505","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the paragraphs entitled (a) Inputting evidence to the development of the next tobacco control plan and (b) Undertaking activity to support effective communication of new regulations under the revised Tobacco Products Directive and the introduction of plain standardised packaging were removed from the draft 2016-17 grant agreement between his Department and Action on Smoking and Health.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120851","120851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810506","2018-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2017 to Question 3475 on Employment and Support Allowance: Motor Neurone Disease,  if he will publish the process required for the 600 people with motor neurone disease who were in the support group for Employment and Support Allowance on 29 September when the severe conditions exemption commenced and are due a reassessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120852","120852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810507","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on energy supplies of the estimated numbers of electric and hybrid vehicles on UK roads by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120853","120853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810508","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking as a result of the latest evidence on the diagnosis and treatment of Chronic Fatigue Syndrome.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120854","120854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810509","2018-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December to Question 118690, on Universal Credit: Telephone Services, what the evidential basis is to support the position that people abandoned calls to use the online service; what the cost to the public purse was of abandoned calls in each month since September 2016; and what  the average length of abandoned calls was in that time period.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121092","121092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810510","2018-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to recommendation eight of the Government’s response to the Second Independent Review of the Personal Independence Payment Assessment, Cm 9540, what the optimum timeframe is for the completion of assessment reports after the assessment has taken place.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120855","120855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810511","2018-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to recommendation six of the Government’s response to the Second Independent Review of the Personal Independence Payment Assessment, Cm 9540, what the timescale is for the proposed pilot due in early 2018 to understand the benefits of early case preparation in more complex cases.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120856","120856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810512","2018-01-08","Department for Transport","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve enforcement against drink-driving in light of recent report by the Institute of Alcohol Studies Running on empty, drink-driving law enforcement in England published on 8 December 2017.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120857","120857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810513","2018-01-08","HM Treasury","2017-12-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if it remains his policy to implement the Second Payment Services Directive after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120858","120858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810514","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to review and amend the Government's childhood obesity strategy over time to account for developments in the causes and extent of such obesity.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120859","120859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810515","2018-01-08","HM Treasury","2017-12-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the ability to transfer a Blind Person's Allowance to long-term partners who live together.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120860","120860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810516","2018-01-08","Cabinet Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for how many deaths was consumption of an excess of prescription drugs the primary cause between 2014 and 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120861","120861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810517","2018-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, who the multiple stakeholders within the private sector were at each Chevening business event listed in the Ministerial Meetings section of his Department's Transparency Data for July to September 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120862","120862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810518","2018-01-08","Northern Ireland Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether he has drawn up a shortlist of independent chairs for potential future talks about restoring the power-sharing Executive in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120863","120863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810519","2018-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, who was present at each roundtable discussion listed in the Ministerial Meetings section of his Department's Transparency Data for July to September 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120864","120864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810520","2018-01-08","Cabinet Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which reports or reviews have been commissioned or conducted by his Department in respect of the number of looked after children or children subject to child protection or child in need plans.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120865","120865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810521","2018-01-08","Scotland Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, for what reasons Lord Duncan held an introductory meeting with Caledonian Media on 24 August 2017; who he met from that organisation; and what was discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120866","120866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810522","2018-01-08","Department for International Trade","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2017 to Question 118624, on trade agreements, if he will list the organisations that submitted responses.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120867","120867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810523","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of employment regulations on micro-businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120868","120868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810524","2018-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on housing supply of the previous housing targets for local authorities established in the Regional Spatial Strategies.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120869","120869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810525","2018-01-08","Cabinet Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120870","120870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810526","2018-01-08","HM Treasury","2017-12-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120871","120871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810527","2018-01-08","Home Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by her Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120872","120872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810528","2018-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the quantum of under-supply in housing caused by local authorities pursuing housing supply targets from (a) the Regional Spatial Strategies and (b) other housing targets introduced prior to 2010.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120873","120873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810529","2018-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120874","120874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810530","2018-01-08","Department for International Trade","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to his Department's factsheet entitled 9th UK China Economic and Financial Dialogue 16 December 2017, whether David Cameron's new role on investment between the UK and China is a Government appointment.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120875","120875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810531","2018-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120876","120876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810532","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the performance indicators are for the Better Regulation Executive.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120877","120877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810533","2018-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union,  what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120878","120878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810534","2018-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120879","120879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810535","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what regulations the Better Regulation Executive has identified for (a) revocation and (b) amendment in order to reduce burdens on business.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120880","120880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810536","2018-01-08","Department for Education","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by her Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120881","120881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810537","2018-01-08","Women and Equalities","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities,  what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by her Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120882","120882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810538","2018-01-08","Department for International Trade","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade,  what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120883","120883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810539","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the one-in-two-out approach to regulatory costs is still being applied by the Government.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120884","120884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810540","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health,  what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120885","120885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810541","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which regulations affecting business his Department has withdrawn or amended in each year since 2010 to date; which regulations affecting business his Department plans to withdraw or amend in (i) 2018 and (ii) years beyond 2018; and what estimate he has made of the net cost to business to withdrawal or amendment of each withdrawn or amended regulation.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120886","120886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810542","2018-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120887","120887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810543","2018-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120888","120888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810544","2018-01-08","Department for Transport","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120889","120889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810545","2018-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120890","120890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810546","2018-01-08","Scotland Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland,  what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120891","120891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810547","2018-01-08","Wales Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120892","120892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810548","2018-01-08","Northern Ireland Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120893","120893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810549","2018-01-08","Cabinet Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose the (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120894","120894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810550","2018-01-08","Department for International Development","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by her Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120895","120895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810551","2018-01-08","Cabinet Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by his Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120896","120896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810552","2018-01-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the title was of each set of regulations introduced by her Department in each month since May 2010; which of those regulations have been (a) subject to the (i) one in one out and (ii) one in two out procedure and (b) (i) revoked and (ii) amended; and what the net cost to (A) the public purse; and (B) business of those regulations is.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120897","120897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810553","2018-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120898","120898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810554","2018-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120899","120899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810555","2018-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is considering to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120900","120900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810556","2018-01-08","Cabinet Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what processes his Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by his Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120901","120901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810557","2018-01-08","HM Treasury","2017-12-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what processes his Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by his Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120902","120902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810558","2018-01-08","Home Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what processes her Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by her Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120903","120903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810559","2018-01-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what processes his Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by his Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120904","120904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810560","2018-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120905","120905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810561","2018-01-08","Department for International Trade","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120906","120906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810562","2018-01-08","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what processes his Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by his Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120907","120907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810563","2018-01-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose the (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120908","120908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810564","2018-01-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what processes his Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by his Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120909","120909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810565","2018-01-08","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what processes his Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by his Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120910","120910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810566","2018-01-08","Department of Health","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120911","120911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810567","2018-01-08","Department for Education","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what processes her Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by her Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120912","120912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810568","2018-01-08","Women and Equalities","2017-12-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what processes her Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by her Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120913","120913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810569","2018-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120914","120914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810570","2018-01-08","Department for International Trade","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what processes his Department has put in place to (a) monitor, (b) collate cost information on, (c) review and (d) respond to requests to amend or revoke regulations introduced by his Department.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120915","120915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810571","2018-01-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120916","120916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810572","2018-01-08","Department for Transport","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose the (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120917","120917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810573","2018-01-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose the (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120918","120918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810574","2018-01-08","Scotland Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose the (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120919","120919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810575","2018-01-08","Wales Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120920","120920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810576","2018-01-08","Northern Ireland Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting his Department he is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120921","120921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810577","2018-01-08","Department for International Development","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting her Department she is planning to propose the (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120922","120922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810579","2018-01-08","Home Office","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting her Department she is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120924","120924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810580","2018-01-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which EU (a) Directives, (b) Regulations and (c) other legislation affecting her Department she is planning to propose (i) revocation and (ii) amendment of after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120925","120925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/810581","2018-01-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to protect claimants in the Employment and Support Allowance Support Group and its Universal Credit equivalent from financial loss if they engage in work-related activity and are subsequently transferred to the Work-Related Activity Group or its Universal Credit equivalent.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 120926","120926"
