"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141471","2019-09-03","Cabinet Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the voter ID pilot, what assessment he has made of the effect of the (a) poll card, (b) mixed ID, and (c) photographic ID model on people with protected characteristics under the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280955","280955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141472","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reforming Gift Aid so that the value of additional and higher-rate tax reliefs is automatically directed to charities, unless donors choose to opt out.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280956","280956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141473","2019-07-25","Treasury","2019-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of removing VAT from wills that include a charitable donation.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280957","280957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141474","2019-09-03","Treasury","2019-07-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to bring forward a review of legislation for Co-op societies, Credit Unions and Community Benefit Societies as proposed by the Financial Conduct Authority in its 22 July 2019 report Alternatives to high-cost credit.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280908","280908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141475","2019-09-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to appoint a Principal Regulator for Exempt Charities using the community benefit society legal form; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280909","280909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141476","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support rural post offices.","Biography information for Alberto Costa","Alberto Costa","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281127","281127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141477","2019-07-25","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what additional procedures companies will face in order to trade between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and whether those procedures will be different to procedures at any other UK border.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281128","281128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141478","2019-07-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what funding his Department allocated to support the provision of grassroots sports in Leicestershire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alberto Costa","Alberto Costa","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281129","281129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141479","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether UK workers spending longer than 90 out of 180 days in the EU will be subject to additional (a) administration, (b) costs, and (c) visas in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281130","281130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141480","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether businesses will be able to move skilled workers between UK and EU premises in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and what the rules governing that movement will be.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281131","281131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141481","2019-07-25","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when will companies know which (a) regulator will be overseeing their business and (b) which rules will they will need to follow from the day after the UK leaves the EU; and whether the Government plans to charge businesses for the creation of new regulatory agencies in the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281132","281132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141482","2019-07-25","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the means of (a) resolution and (b) redress will be for a UK company in dispute with an EU company in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281133","281133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141483","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257660 on Asthma: Health Services, what steps he is taking to ensure that severe asthma services are located within a reasonable travel distance for as large a number of patients as possible.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281134","281134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141484","2019-09-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the statement by the right hon. Member for Uxbridge and South Ruislip of 23 July 2019 that the UK will build more ships, what plans her Department has to expand the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281021","281021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141485","2019-09-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of free television licences issued to residents in (a) Kirklees borough and (b) Dewsbury constituency in each of the last three years; and what the total annual value of those licences was.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281135","281135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141486","2019-09-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of avoidable asthma attacks.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281136","281136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141487","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department allocated (a) to pathfinder local authorities to refurbish or build play areas as part of the national play strategy and (b) for other elements of the national play strategy in the (a) 2008-09 and (b) 2009-10 financial years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 281137","281137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140287","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average waiting time for an appeal for universal credit by a tribunal for people with a disability in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278907","278907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140759","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","What recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the funding allocated to local authorities for adult social services.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912091","912091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140760","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","What recent progress has been made on the introduction of mandatory electrical safety checks in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912092","912092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140761","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","What recent representations he has received on the effect of the out-of-area placement of families by borough councils on receiving local authorities.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912093","912093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140762","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","What steps he is taking to ensure that unsafe combustible cladding is removed from homes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912097","912097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140763","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","What recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of new homes for social rent since 2010.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 912098","912098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140790","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of deaths caused by asthma in (a) adults and (b) children exposed to high levels of air pollution during April 2019; and what comparative assessment he has made of the number of those deaths and the average number of deaths for asthma among those groups in April in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280363","280363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140791","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 May 2019 on Universal Credit: Mental Illness, whether her Department provides support visits for benefit claimants in secure psychiatric settings.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280236","280236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140792","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to facilitate international collaboration on research and development after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280237","280237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140793","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that all regions of the UK benefit from the target in the Industrial Strategy of spending 2.4 per cent of GDP on research and development by 2027.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280238","280238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140794","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of UK capacity in translational research.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280239","280239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140795","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to extend Energy Performance Certificates to include information on the health and safety of properties.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280240","280240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140796","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department's review of ventilation and energy-efficiency in building regulations includes indoor air quality; and whether the future homes standard will include benchmarking on indoor air quality.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280241","280241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140797","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to (a) establish a sub-committee of the Housing Taskforce to include stakeholders involved in the delivery of healthy and quality homes and (b) respond to the recommendations made in the all-party Parliamentary group for healthy homes and buildings white paper, published 24 October 2018.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280242","280242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140798","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to review the UK's existing housing stock to ensure that the oldest homes are fit for purpose and do not exacerbate or cause ill health.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280243","280243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140800","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that more women enter leadership and executive roles in companies.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280365","280365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140801","2019-07-25","Women and Equalities","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that women have access to full-time jobs.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280366","280366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140802","2019-07-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of the draft age appropriate code proposed by the Information Commissioner’s Office on access to UK broadcasters' content.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280140","280140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140803","2019-07-25","Church Commissioners","2019-07-22","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps are being taken to promote the new four year Grant Programme through the Churches Trust.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280172","280172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140804","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether Class B High Pressure Laminate cladding with combustible insulation can be reused on a building in the event that the combustible insulation is replaced.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280244","280244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140805","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients in Northern Ireland were (a) diagnosed and (b) treated for iron deficiency anaemia in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280245","280245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140806","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of reductions in public health funding on health inequalities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280246","280246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140807","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of reductions in public health funding on the health and wellbeing of the most marginalised people in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280247","280247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140808","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the percentage change has been in the (a) NHS budget and (b) local authority public health grant in each year from 2013-14 to 2019-20.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280248","280248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140809","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the recommendations of the independent assessment commissioned by the Joint Funds Unit  of Overseas Security and Justice Assistance policy were.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280367","280367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140810","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have made applications under the criminal injury compensation scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280249","280249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140811","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers were awarded compensation under the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280250","280250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140812","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total amount awarded was each year to prison officers under the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280251","280251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140813","2019-07-26","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of (a) trends in the level of traffic flows on the A5 through Towcester over the last 30 years and (b) the effect a relief road or bypass for the town would have on that level of traffic flow.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280252","280252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140814","2019-07-26","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the requirements and processes are for a road (a) to be given trunk road status and (b) to have that status taken away.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280253","280253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140815","2019-07-26","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the Air Quality Management Area (AQMA) within Towcester along the A5; and what effect a reduction in traffic movements through the town would have on the AQMA.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280254","280254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140816","2019-07-26","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will attend the next public meeting on the delivery of the Towcester relief road.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280255","280255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140817","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which components of Better Migration Management programs under the Khartoum Process have been suspended; and if there are any projects remaining which involve the Sudan Interior Ministry.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280368","280368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140818","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his policy is on risks to individuals from the Darfur or Nuba ethnicities in Sudan.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280369","280369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140819","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have worked in the Country of Origin Information Team in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280370","280370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140820","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff worked for the Trade Remedies Authority as of July 2019.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280256","280256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140821","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of his Department's budget is allocated to the Trade Remedies Authority.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280257","280257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140822","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department plans to announce a decision on extending the biometric residence permit collection service with Post Office Ltd.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280258","280258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140823","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of UK Export Finance spend was on renewable projects in developing economies in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280259","280259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140824","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2019 to Question 260045 on Department for Transport: Post Office, what the cost to the public purse was for this contract in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280260","280260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140825","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of funding of the Tradeshow Access Programme.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280261","280261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140826","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the proportion of fly-tipping incidents that were categorised as car boot sized in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280371","280371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140827","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the proportion of fly-tipping incidents that were categorised as small van sized in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280372","280372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140828","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the proportion of fly-tipping incidents that contained household waste in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280373","280373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140829","2019-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department will be carrying out its review of the guidance on the statutory duty placed on local authorities to provide appropriate local youth services, as set out in the Civil Society Strategy, published August 2018.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280262","280262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140830","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2019 to Question 273770 on Fines: Surcharges, how much funding has been allocated from the Victim Surcharge to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280263","280263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140831","2019-07-25","Department for International Development","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of UK aid to developing countries goes towards loan repayments.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280374","280374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140832","2019-07-25","Treasury","2019-07-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, on average how long the Government takes to negotiate double taxation treaties.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280375","280375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140833","2019-07-24","Treasury","2019-07-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with SWIFT on access to their database to help tackle economic crime.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280376","280376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140834","2019-07-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any of the weapons used in the airstrike by the Saudi-led coalition on Al-Kubra Hall in Sanhan, Yemen on 8 October 2016 were supplied by British companies under licence from the Government.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280116","280116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140835","2019-07-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any of the aircraft used in the airstrike by the Saudi-led collation on Al-Kubra Hall in Sanhan, Yemen on 8 October 2016 were supplied by British companies under licence from the Government.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280117","280117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140836","2019-07-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any of the personnel involved in the airstrike by the Saudi-led coalition on Al-Kubra Hall in Sanhan, Yemen on 8 October 2016 had previously received training in international humanitarian law from UK personnel.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280118","280118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140837","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government conducted an investigation into the airstrike by the Saudi-led coalition on Al-Kubra Hall in Sanhan, Yemen on 8 October 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280119","280119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140838","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has made an assessment of whether the airstrike by the Saudi-led coalition on Al-Kubra Hall in Sanhan, Yemen on 8 October 2016 was a legitimate military operation in line with international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280120","280120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140839","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU citizens (a) have been and (b) will be prevented from obtaining settled status due to the technical inability of the settlement scheme app to convert pre-settled status into settled status.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280173","280173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140840","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people involved in the criminal exploitation of vulnerable young people in county lines operations have been charged with modern slavery offences.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280174","280174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140841","2019-07-25","Department for International Development","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment he has made of the spread of Ebola to the city of Goma and the potential risk of the outbreak spreading to Rwanda.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280175","280175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140842","2019-07-24","Department for International Development","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to overcome the (a) local mistrust of health officials and (b) militia violence which have impeded efforts to prevent the Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo from spreading further.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280176","280176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140843","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the viability of return to Sudan for people from Darfur or Nuba ethnicities.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280177","280177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140844","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterparts on (a) the accuracy of its reporting of civilian casualties due to US drone strikes and (b) the lasting effect of US drone strikes on civilian populations in Somalia.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280178","280178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140845","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Italian counterpart on (a) the seizure of international NGO vessels and (b) its potential violations of international maritime law.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280179","280179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140846","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Emirati counterpart on the prison conditions of the Emirati prisoner of conscience Ahmed Mansoor.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280180","280180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140847","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July to Written Question 276505 on Abdullatif Nasser, if his Department will make representations to the US Administration for the release of Abdullatif Nasser.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280112","280112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140848","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the press release entitled, Leasehold axed for all new houses in move to place fairness at heart of housing market, published by his Department on 27 June 2019, what estimate he has made of the number of house buyers that were subject to the sale of their freehold before they had bought their homes.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280377","280377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140849","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how buyers that expressed an intention to purchase their freeholds to the developer pre-contract will receive their freeholds for no cost through redress with the developer.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280378","280378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140850","2019-07-24","Treasury","2019-07-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps in the forthcoming spending review to ensure that funding levels for childcare keep pace with the rising cost of living.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280124","280124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140851","2019-07-25","Treasury","2019-07-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to regulate complaints made by claims management companies on behalf of complainants on the same basis as independent and other financial advisors, banks and building societies.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280141","280141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140852","2019-07-25","Treasury","2019-07-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to bring pre-payment funeral plans under the regulation of the Financial Conduct Authority in line with other financial products.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280142","280142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140853","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions the reformed Advisory Military Sub Committee has met.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280264","280264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140854","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to create a centrally accessible database logging pets' microchip numbers and date of entry into the UK.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280181","280181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140855","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all dog and cat rehoming centres are adequately regulated.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280182","280182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140856","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she plans to take to limit a person's pension age rise when age eligibility for the state pension is increased.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280183","280183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140857","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish a response to EDM 2333 on the Islamic revolutionary guard corps.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280265","280265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140858","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to introduce digital IDs for migrants seeking to work in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280125","280125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140859","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the estimated cost is of introducing a digital ID system for migrants seeking to work in the UK.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280126","280126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140860","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to increase the use of algorithm-based software in the determination of immigration status for migrants seeking to (a) work and (b) visit the UK.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280127","280127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140861","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for administrative review have been made to the EU Settlement Scheme; how many of those applications were (a) successful and (b) successful due to new evidence or an error by the caseworker in the original decision.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280266","280266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140862","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to enhance biodiversity.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280128","280128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140863","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the badger culling programme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280129","280129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140864","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure water companies reduce the number of pollution incidents.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280130","280130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140865","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he has taken to support job creation from foreign direct investment in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280379","280379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140866","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people aged 16 to 18  years old who will benefit from the proposed introduction of a new discount railcard for that age group in (a) Mansfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280380","280380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140867","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the penalties incurred for (a) possession and (b) supply and production of synthetic cannabinoids.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280381","280381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140868","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what programmes there are in prisons to provide support for prisoners with synthetic cannabis drug dependency.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280382","280382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140869","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) availability and (b) waiting times for therapeutic services for mental health conditions in Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280383","280383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140870","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what human rights assessment was made before the approval of an export licence for telecommunications interception equipment to Hong Kong.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280384","280384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140871","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what criteria are used to assess whether to grant export licences to foreign governments for surveillance technology.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280385","280385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140872","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the use in Hong Kong of telecommunications interception equipment purchased from the UK; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280386","280386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140873","2019-07-25","Department for International Development","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the processing time for humanitarian supplies imported through the port of Aden in Yemen.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280387","280387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140874","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he plans to start the external recruitment for the new role of Her Majesty’s Trade Commissioner for Australasia.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280267","280267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140875","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, at what civil service grade the post of Her Majesty’s Trade Commissioner for Australasia will be.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280268","280268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140876","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the post of Her Majesty’s Trade Commissioner for Australasia will be combined with another post.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280269","280269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140877","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, where the next meeting of the Board of Trade will take place.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280270","280270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140878","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants have lost the severe disability premium following a change of circumstances since the inception of universal credit in (a) Wales and (b) each parliamentary constituency in Wales.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280184","280184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140879","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individuals are eligible for pension credit but not claiming the benefit in (a) Wales and (b) each parliamentary constituency in Wales.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280185","280185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140880","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether community centres and memorial halls in Elmet and Rothwell constituency are eligible to apply to the rural community energy fund; and what the application process is.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280271","280271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140881","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the largest number of previous convictions received by a person sentenced to immediate custody for the first time was in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280388","280388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140882","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) proportion, (b) value and (c) volume of (i) lamb, (ii) beef, (iii) pork and (iv) chicken consumed in the UK is imported (A) from the EU and (B) from the rest of the world.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280389","280389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140883","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the largest number of previous convictions received by a person convicted but not sentenced to an immediate custodial sentence was in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280390","280390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140884","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on the level of (a) household and (b) commercial waste taken to household waste recycling centres of local authorities introducing paid permits for vans to access those centres.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280272","280272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140885","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) the Royal National Institute of Blind People and (b) other NGOs on shared space schemes since his Department's announcement in July 2018 of a halt in the development of those schemes.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280186","280186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140886","2019-07-24","Department for International Development","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the decision to move Rohingya refugees in Bangladesh to the island of Bhasan Charan, which is at risk of severe flooding and cyclones.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280273","280273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140887","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve the punctuality of trains.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280131","280131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140888","2019-07-24","Department for International Development","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what further steps his Department is taking to stop the spread of Ebola in the Democratic Republic of the Congo since the World Health Organization declared the crisis a public health emergency of international concern.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280274","280274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140889","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the prospects for a peace deal in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280275","280275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140890","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the (a) involvement of civil society in the talks between the US and the Taliban in Afghanistan and (b) rights of women in any agreement that might be reached in those talks.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280276","280276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140891","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much Official Development Assistance funding his Department is providing to (a) Nigeria, (b) South Africa, (c) Kenya, (d) Ethiopia, (e) Colombia, (f) Peru, (g) Indonesia and (h) Bangladesh; and (i) for what purpose and (ii) under which programme is that funding being provided.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280391","280391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140892","2019-07-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a statutory levy in greyhound racing for greyhound welfare.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280187","280187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140893","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department (a) currently has or (b) has plans for Official Development Assistance-funded programmes other than the Investment Promotion Programme.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280392","280392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140894","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average sentence length in months was for people who pleaded guilty and received an immediate custodial sentence for (a) violence against the person (b) theft, (c) drug offences, (d) robbery, (e) common assault and battery, (f) burglary in a dwelling, (g) production, supply and possession with intent to supply a controlled drug - Class A, (h) possession of article with blade or point and (i) assaulting, resisting or obstructing a constable or designated officer and who had (i) no, (ii) between one and four, (iii) between five and nine, (iv) between 10 and 15, (v) between 16 and 25, (vi) between 26 and 50, (vii) between 51 and 75, (viii) between 76 and 100 and (ix) 101 or more previous convictions in each of last 10 years.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280393","280393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140895","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been paid by each private company with a contract with the Department in financial remedies and what the reason was for those financial remedies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280394","280394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140896","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours of overtime were worked by HM Courts & Tribunals Service staff in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280395","280395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140897","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours of overtime were worked by Her Majesty's Prison and Probation Service staff in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280396","280396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140898","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were released under home detention curfew having been imprisoned for (a) violence against the person, (b) theft, (c) drug offences, (d) robbery, (e) common assault and battery, (f) burglary in a dwelling, (g) production, supply and possession with intent to supply a controlled drug - Class A, (h) possession of article with blade or point and (i) assaulting, resisting or obstructing a constable or designated officer in execution of duty in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280397","280397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140899","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the (a) average length of sentence for and (b) the number of people convicted of (i) violence against the person, (ii) sexual offences, (iii) robbery, (iv) theft offences, (v) criminal damage and arson, (vi) drug offences, (vii) possession of weapons and (viii) public order offences for offenders for which this was their (A) first, (B) second, (C) third, (D) fourth, (E) fifth, (F) sixth, (G) seventh and (H) eighth or more conviction for that type of offence in each of the last five years; and what estimate he has made of the proportion of those offenders who were not given an immediate custodial sentence.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280398","280398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140900","2019-07-25","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations she has made to her Turkish counterpart on the implications for their NATO membership of their purchase of a Russian Anti-Air System.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280113","280113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140901","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the location of the Grace One oil tanker was when it was seized; and what the specific EU sanction is that it was seized under and impounded.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280399","280399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140902","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish an update on the commitment in the Inclusive Transport Strategy to develop a monitoring and enforcement framework for mandatory bus driver disability awareness training by 2018.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280132","280132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140903","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he will publish the adult commissioning guidance on adult eating disorder services.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280277","280277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140904","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the reason is for the difference in the number of extant arms export licences for Saudi Arabia for possible use in Yemen under review as a result of the court of appeal's Judgment of 20 June 2019 set out in (a) DEP2019-0710 that referenced 95 OIELS, (b) DEP2019-0711 that referenced 71 SIELS and 65 OIELS and (c) the 27 June 2019 witness statement to the Court of Appeal by Edward Bell that referenced 45 arms export licences.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280400","280400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140905","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timeframe is for her Department to bring forward legislative proposals for severe disability premium to be available under universal credit.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280278","280278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140906","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions her Department has registered the child maintenance debt of a non-resident parent with credit rating agencies.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280279","280279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140907","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government will be represented at the 12th Commonwealth Women's Affairs Ministers meeting in Kenya in September 2019.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280401","280401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140908","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Sudanese counterpart on engagement between the Sudanese population and the diaspora community in the UK.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280402","280402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140909","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's criteria is for registering the child maintenance debt of a non-resident parent with credit rating agencies.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280280","280280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140910","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Police Covenant will be introduced.","Biography information for Alberto Costa","Alberto Costa","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280281","280281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140911","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish the transcripts of conversations between his Department and its Iranian counterpart on the case of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe, referred to by the former Minister of State in his resignation letter of 22 July 2019.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280403","280403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140912","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date discussions between his Department and its Iranian counterpart on the possible release of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe were brought to a halt.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280404","280404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140913","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the MBRRACE-UK maternal deaths and morbidity statistics 2014-16 showing that (a) Asian women are nearly twice as likely, (b) mixed race women are twice as likely and (c) black women are five times as likely to die during or up to six weeks after pregnancy than white women.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280405","280405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140914","2019-07-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the negotiations between the UK and Iran to secure the release of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe were halted.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280406","280406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140915","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle the fall in the proportion of pupils achieving the expected standard in reading at Key Stage 2.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280188","280188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140916","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will increase the time available for pupils sitting the Key Stage 2 reading assessment to reflect the increase in the number of words included in that test since 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280189","280189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140917","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275165 on Wakefield City Academies Trust: Deloitte and Touche, how much he expects his Department will pay in total to Deloitte in relation to Wakefield City Academies Trust.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280190","280190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140918","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress is being made on the commitment to offer free sanitary products to schools by the start of the 2019-20 school year.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280133","280133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140919","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many finished consultant episodes there were with a (a) primary and (b) secondary diagnosis of HIV infection in (i) England and (ii) each region in each year since 1989.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280282","280282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140920","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) outpatient and (b) inpatient appointments were (i) emergency and (ii) elective with a (A) primary and (B) secondary diagnosis of HIV in (1) England and (2) each clinical commissioning group area in each of the last 12 months; and what the average waiting time was for each such appointment.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280283","280283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140921","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to Written Question 265470 on Department for Work and Pensions: Pay, how much her Department spent on performance-related awards for Senior Civil Service officials in (a) 2014, (b) 2015, (c) 2016, (d) 2017, (e) 2018 and (f) January to June 2019.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280191","280191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140922","2019-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many letters of delay the Veterans Agency is issuing to veterans awaiting an assessment appeal for their war pension on average.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280407","280407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140923","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2019 to Question 277859, whether he currently has the legislative authority to place guidance on school uniforms on a statutory footing.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280408","280408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140924","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the recent increase in diabetes-related amputations.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280192","280192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140925","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether integrated (a) care systems and (b) sustainability and transformation partnership will be required to publish local long-term plans in the Autumn.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280114","280114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140926","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will assess the potential contribution that (a) replacing and (b) repowering old onshore wind turbines would make to meeting the Government's net zero carbon emissions target.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280284","280284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140927","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how local areas will be held accountable for progress made on the five year deal to expand GP services.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280121","280121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140928","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Childhood Obesity Plan, Chapter two, what steps he is taking to ensure the halving of childhood obesity by 2030.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280122","280122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140929","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the proposed Green Paper on Prevention, what assessment of he has made of his Department's ability to improve healthy life expectancy by at least five extra years by 2035.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280123","280123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140930","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) China and (b) countries in east Africa on ending the international trade in donkey skins; and what recent steps he has taken to help implement an international ban on the trade in donkey skins.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280134","280134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140931","2019-07-25","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the recent golf open at Royal Portrush, if her Department will hold discussions with Invest Northern Ireland to promote Northern Ireland as a tourist and investment destination.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280193","280193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140932","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many pilot environmental land management schemes have been agreed, where those pilots will take place; and what the start date is for each such pilot.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280135","280135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140933","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding allocated to enterprise zones.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280194","280194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140934","2019-07-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the compatibility of the draft age appropriate code proposed by the Information Commissioner’s Office with his Department's responsibilities under the Data Protection Act 2018.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280195","280195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140935","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which were the 100 scheduled rail journeys which were most frequently (a) cancelled or (b) significantly late over the last six month period for which data are available; and what proportion of each were (i) cancelled or (ii) significantly late.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280409","280409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140936","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the effect of silicosis on the NHS budget and resources.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280410","280410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140937","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data his Department holds on whether there is a (a) genetic, (b) socio-economic and (c) ethnic bias to the condition of silicosis.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280411","280411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140938","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the effect of silicosis on her Department's budget.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280412","280412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140939","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of trains were (a) cancelled or significantly late and (b) on time in each year since 1996 from Market Harborough to London Terminals.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280413","280413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140940","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data her Department holds on the effect of silicosis on (a) productivity in the UK and (b) productivity of the construction industry in the UK.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280414","280414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140941","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to regulate exposure to silica; and what recent assessment her Department has made of the extent of compliance with those regulations.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280415","280415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140942","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data her Department holds on the groups most vulnerable to silicosis.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280416","280416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140943","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to (a) support local authorities managing and tackling elm disease and (b) ensure that Brighton and Hove City Council has adequate support to protect the National Elm Collection in the city.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280285","280285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140944","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data her Department holds on the effect on family members of silicosis sufferers.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280417","280417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140945","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps have been taken to encourage the construction industry to protect workers from exposure to silica.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280418","280418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140946","2019-07-24","House of Commons Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what recent assessment the Commission has made of the effect of the 25p surcharge on hot drinks served in disposable cups on the Parliamentary estate on (a) drinks sales and (b) disposable cup waste.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280286","280286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140947","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many unfilled NHS nursing posts there were in (a) London and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280143","280143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140948","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support the recruitment and retention of nurses in (a) London and (b) England.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280144","280144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140949","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has made to the Mayor of London on the date for the opening of Crossrail.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280145","280145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140950","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the July 2019 Progress Report to Parliament published by the Committee on Climate Change, for what reasons 21 of the 56 risks and opportunities identified in the UK’s Climate Change Risk Assessment have no formal actions in the National Adaptation Programme.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280287","280287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140951","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has commissioned research on the potential effect of electro-magnetic waves on levels of premature deaths in farm animals.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280136","280136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140952","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether (a) the United Arab Emirates, (b) Kuwait, (c) Bahrain and (d) Egypt will be invited to send a delegation to the defence and security equipment international exhibition on 10 to 13 September.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280419","280419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140953","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the potential merits of auto-enrolment on the electoral register of young people when they are given their national insurance number.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280146","280146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140955","2019-07-24","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which local authorities have failed one or more Electoral Commission performance indicators for electoral registration in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280148","280148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140956","2019-07-24","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information he holds on the cost to the public purse of (a) central and (b) local government spending on advertising to promote voter registration in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280149","280149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140957","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment has been made of the side-effects of the drug metamizole.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280288","280288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140958","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will have discussions with his Spanish counterpart on the effect of dispensing metamizole to (a) UK and (b) Spanish residents in Spain.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280289","280289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140959","2019-07-24","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of ring-fencing funds allocated by his Department to local government for the purpose of voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280150","280150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140960","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to raise awareness of the potential side-effects of the drug metamizole among UK citizens and tourists in Spain.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280290","280290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140961","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the implementation of the guidance on Commissioning Excellent Nutrition and Hydration 2015 to 2018.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280420","280420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140962","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the document entitled Guidance – Commissioning Excellent Nutrition and Hydration 2015 – 2018, published by NHS England in October 2015, how many commissioners have identified a local senior or executive champion to drive local work on nutrition and hydration and to make improvements.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280421","280421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140963","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of commissioners that (a) reviewed existing service provision and (b) agreed improvement trajectories as set out in the NHS England Commissioning Excellent Nutrition and Hydration 2015 to 2018 guidance.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280422","280422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140964","2019-07-24","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to collate information on the (a) amount spent by local authorities on electoral registration, (b) number of staff employed by local authorities on electoral registration and (c) local authorities with the (i) highest and (ii) lowest levels of electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280151","280151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140965","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to update the Commissioning Excellent Nutrition and Hydration 2015-2018 NHS England guidance.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280423","280423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140966","2019-07-24","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has made a recent assessment of the potential merits of using vehicle registration databases held by the Driving and Vehicle Licensing Agency to increase levels of voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280152","280152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140967","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what steps have been taken by the Electoral Commission to inform hon. Members of the performance of electoral registration officers in their (a) constituency and (b) local authority.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280153","280153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140968","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which electoral registration officers identified themselves as below standard at using information services to (a) verify entries in the register of electors and (b) identify potential new electors in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280154","280154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140969","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the announcement, Pay rise for prison officers 2019, published by his Department on 22 July 2019, how much additional funding the Treasury has allocated to his Department for the pay award.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280424","280424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140970","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many letters the Electoral Commission has written to hon. Members as a result of their electoral registration officers having failed at least one standard performance indicator in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280155","280155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140971","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many additional prison officers have been recruited since 31 March 2017; and how many of those posts were funded by the additional funding allocated by the Treasury at that time; and what additional funding the Treasury has allocated for the recruitment of prison offices since 31 March 2019.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280425","280425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140972","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the adequacy of palliative care arrangements and support in place for the victims of the contaminated blood scandal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280426","280426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140973","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, with reference to the Answer of 5 July 2011 to Question 63427 on Electoral Register, which electoral registration officers rated themselves too highly in their self-assessment and had their ratings reduced in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280156","280156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140974","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether all directly employed staff in his Department are paid at least the living wage.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280196","280196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140975","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which agencies supply staff working in his Department.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280197","280197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140976","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the trends in the level of non-compliance with the Energy Performance of Buildings Directive regulations, for the requirement to have a valid Display Energy Certificate across all public buildings.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280110","280110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140977","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations he has received on the efficiency of the UK Visa and Citizenship Application Services online appointment booking system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280157","280157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140978","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent discussions the Commission has had with (a) church and community leaders from black and minority ethnic communities and (b) Operation Black Vote on increasing registration levels for voters in those communities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280158","280158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140979","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of hospital admissions there were for adults with malnutrition as a (a) primary and (b) secondary condition in (i) England (ii) each Clinical Commissioning Group and (iii) each parliamentary constituency in each of the last ten years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280427","280427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140980","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many fixed penalty notices have been issued for not having a valid Display Energy Certificate under Energy Performance of Buildings Directive regulations.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280111","280111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140981","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many (a) press officers, (b) internal communications officers, (c) external communications officers, (d) communications strategy staff and (e) any other communications staff were employed by his Department in 2018-19; and what the total cost of their salaries and any on-costs was in that period.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280198","280198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140982","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children were admitted to hospital with malnutrition as a (a) primary and (b) secondary condition in (i) England, (ii) each clinical commissioning group and (iii) each parliamentary constituency in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280428","280428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140983","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, with reference to the Answer of 23 April 2012, Official Report, column 623W on Electoral Register, what steps he has taken to improve student registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280159","280159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140984","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many compromise agreements were agreed with staff leaving his Department in the last 12 months; how many such agreements contained confidentiality clauses; and what the value of severance and pension payments associated with those agreements was.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280199","280199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140985","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children were admitted to hospital with malnutrition as a (a) primary and (b) secondary condition in (i) England, (ii) each clinical commissioning group and (iii) each parliamentary constituency in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280429","280429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140986","2019-07-24","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of deaths in England with a (a) primary and (b) secondary cause of malnutrition in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280430","280430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140987","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients readmitted to hospital within (a) zero to seven and (b) eight to 180 days were recorded as suffering malnutrition as a primary or secondary condition in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280431","280431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140988","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which local authority had the biggest percentage (a) increase and (b) decrease in electoral registration in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280160","280160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140989","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people who are (a) paying council tax for the first time and (b) paying higher council tax as a result of the changes to council tax on 1 April 2017 have received a court summons for non-payment as of 22 July 2019.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280200","280200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140990","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions his Department has issued draft press releases to local authorities for completion using local statistics since May 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280201","280201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140991","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households have left their homes as a result of flooding in the past 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280202","280202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140992","2019-07-24","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2019-07-22","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the ranked order of spending per person on electoral registration by local authorities was in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280161","280161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140993","2019-07-24","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many individuals with ADHD have been given security clearance and then had that clearance withdrawn in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280432","280432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140994","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on software licences in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280203","280203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140995","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many officials in his office are working on matters relating to the UK's withdrawal from the the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280204","280204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140996","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of domestic fires in the private rented sector in England that have occurred as a result of (a) smoking and (b) electrical fires since 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280205","280205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140997","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of his Department's staff, excluding non-departmental public bodies, are (a) women in senior management posts, (b) women, (c) black and minority ethnic and (d) disabled.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280206","280206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140998","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what grants his Department has made to (a) Muslim, (b) Jewish, (c) Christian, and (d) inter-faith organisations to support integration and community cohesion, by organisation, in each year since May 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280207","280207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140999","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department has provided directly to the public to help (a) understand the threat from extremism and (b) promote integration; and whether such information has been made available in languages other than English.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280208","280208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141000","2019-07-24","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent steps he has taken to ensure the equity of the civil service recruitment process for people with ADHD.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280433","280433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141001","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of trends in the levels of young people who own their own home since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280209","280209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141002","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has provided funds through the Bellwin scheme to the Greater Manchester combined authority since July 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280210","280210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141003","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the planned expansion of Heathrow does not contribute to an increase in air pollution.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280434","280434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141004","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions his Department has transferred (a) a written parliamentary and (b) an oral parliamentary Question to a different answering Department since July 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280211","280211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141005","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the locations are of (a) specialist maths schools and (b) Institutes of Technology; and whether it is his policy to ensure that every major city in England has each of those institutions.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280435","280435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141006","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the real-terms changes in the level of funding for rape crisis centres were between 2010 and 2018.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280436","280436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141007","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he has taken in the last 12 months to tackle hate speech online.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280437","280437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141008","2019-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what funding the Government has allocated to tackle hate speech in sport; and what proportion of that funding has been spent, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280438","280438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141009","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to Ministerial Statement, Building safety update, HCWS1757, whether his Department plans to (a) commission large scale fire tests on or (b) issue advice on B-rated and D-rated timber cladding following the BS 8414 test result on high pressure laminate cladding and combustible insulation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280291","280291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141010","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to secure continued access to UK universities for eastern European students after 2020; and what steps his Department has taken to ensure that UK universities are affordable for European students after 2020.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280439","280439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141011","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum-seekers crossed the Channel between November 2018 and January 2019 inclusive; and of those how many (a) were returned to France for processing of their asylum applications, (b) have been granted asylum in the UK and (c) have applications being processed in the UK.","Biography information for Peter Heaton-Jones","Peter Heaton-Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280440","280440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141012","2019-07-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps the Government has taken to mitigate the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the supply of products listed in the consumer price inflation basket of goods.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280441","280441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141013","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment on changes in English for Speakers of other Languages funding.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280442","280442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141014","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new schools other than free schools have been (a) opened in each academic year since 2015-16 and (b) approved for opening in future years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280443","280443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141015","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that people who are granted refugee status and who do not speak English as their first language are offered a two-year course in English as a foreign language.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280444","280444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141016","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to ensure the adequacy of water supplies during heatwaves.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280445","280445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141017","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to protect future water supplies against potential disruption caused by climate change.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280446","280446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141018","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the real terms changes in Government funding for Further Education colleges was between 2010 and 2018.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280447","280447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141019","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average age is of MRI machines used by the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280292","280292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141020","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to improve the UK Visa and Citizenship Application Services online appointment bookings system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280162","280162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141021","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to increase funding for Further Education colleges.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280448","280448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141022","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people treated for a head injury by age-group for each of the last 25 years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280449","280449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141023","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to help protect small and medium-sized businesses against cyber-crime.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280450","280450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141024","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many rail stations were upgraded to step-free access in control periods one to five in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) England; and what was the cumulative spend was for each of those nations in that timeframe.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280293","280293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141025","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many railway stations will be upgraded to step free access in control period 6 in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) England; and what is the funding allocation for each region.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280294","280294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141026","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train stations there are in Scotland; and how many of those stations have step-free access.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280295","280295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141027","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train stations there are in England;  and how many of those stations have step-free access.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280296","280296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141028","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train stations there are in Wales; and how many of those stations have step-free access.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280297","280297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141029","2019-07-24","Treasury","2019-07-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether funding will be made available for policing in addition to that announced by the Chancellor of the Exchequer in the 2019 Spring Statement.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280451","280451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141030","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to allow individuals in receipt of continuing healthcare funding to transfer their funding between CCGs in the event they move home.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280298","280298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141031","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of police officers in the Borough of Wandsworth in (a) 2010 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280452","280452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141032","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the number of cancer clinical nurse specialist vacancies in the NHS.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280453","280453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141033","2019-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the central Government contribution to youth club spending in the Borough of Wandsworth in (a) 2010 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280454","280454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141034","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish an impact assessment of the effectiveness of the Homelessness Reduction Act 2017.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280455","280455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141035","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people living in temporary accommodation; and what steps he is taking to improve the living conditions of those people.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280456","280456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141036","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to tackle cancer workforce shortages in the NHS people plan.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280457","280457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141037","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of calls to the 101 service were (a) answered in under 30 seconds, (b) answered between 30 to 60 seconds, (c) answered between 60 seconds and 120 seconds, (d) answered between 120 and 180 seconds, (e) answered between 180 and 300 seconds (f) answered between 300 and 600 seconds (g) answered after 600 seconds, (h) unanswered in each of the last three years for which information is available; and how many calls there were in total in each of those years.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280458","280458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141038","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of free television licences issued to residents in (a) the Norwich City Council area (b) Norwich South constituency and (c) Norwich North constituency in each of the last three years; and what the total annual value was of those licences.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280459","280459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141039","2019-07-24","Treasury","2019-07-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure banks are able to effectively tackle cybercrime.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280460","280460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141040","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to encourage schools to consult parents on how Pupil Premium Plus funding should be spent.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280299","280299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141041","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring schools to provide on request to parents (a) a general outline of spending of Pupil Premium Plus funding and (b) information on where that funding has been pooled for the benefit of a cohort.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280300","280300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141042","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of requiring schools to develop separate policies for Pupil Premium funding and Pupil Premium Plus funding to recognise the differing needs of children and young people who are eligible for each.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280301","280301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141043","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of commissioning research to establish best practice on spending of Pupil Premium Plus funding in schools.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280302","280302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141044","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the (a) adequacy of funding available for rural pre-schools and (b) quality of the learning environment for children attending a rural pre-school.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280303","280303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141045","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect on pre-schools in Northamptonshire of the deduction of 14 per cent from the pre-school funding budget for administration costs.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280304","280304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141046","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect on pre-schools of the removal of funding for training of pre-school staff to level 3 standard.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280305","280305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141047","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the staff to children ratio at pre-schools in rural areas.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280306","280306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141048","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve the (a) provision, (b) delivery and (c) funding of rural education for all ages.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280307","280307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141049","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on collecting data on students missing school to take part in climate change protests.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280461","280461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141050","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance is in place for schools on the circumstances when they should provide information to the police on domestic extremists.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280462","280462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141051","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2019 to Question 277289 on guidance to schools in reducing their carbon footprint, how his Department plans to translate the results of the Condition Data Collection into developing future priorities for investment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280463","280463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141052","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2019 to Question 277289 on guidance to schools in reducing their carbon footprint, whether his Department has agreed a timescale over which to develop future priorities for investment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280464","280464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141053","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2019 to Question 277289 on guidance to schools in reducing their carbon footprint, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the Good Estate Management website in providing guidance on how individual institutions can become more environmentally-friendly.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280465","280465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141054","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2019 to Question 277289 on guidance to schools in reducing their carbon footprint what steps his Department is taking to ensure that schools are aware of the guidance on the Good Estate Management website.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280466","280466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141055","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2019 to Question 277289 on guidance to schools in reducing their carbon footprint, how his Department plans to ensure loans for development of cleaner technology are available to all institutions that need them.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280467","280467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141056","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2019 to Question 277289 on guidance to schools in reducing their carbon footprint, what the timescale is for the introduction of loans to develop cleaner technology in schools.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280468","280468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141057","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of changing places toilets with hoist and a bench throughout the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280137","280137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141058","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to introduce (a) a right to lifelong learning in digital skills and (b) a right for all employees to request leave for training.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280308","280308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141059","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect freeholders and leaseholders from high service charges.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280309","280309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141060","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to tackle uncapped service charges on freeholders and leaseholders.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280310","280310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141061","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure accountability and transparency in service charges.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280311","280311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141062","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to ensure fairness between freeholders and leaseholders on challenging high service charges.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280312","280312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141063","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that developers are accountable to local authorities when appointing sub-contractors to build roads and other infrastructure; and what powers local authorities have to ensure that developers contribute adequately to the cost of maintaining roads once adopted by the local authority.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280313","280313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141064","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to (a) ensure that local authorities in Northamptonshire transition successfully to the two new unitary authorities on time and on budget and (b) prepare for the proposed new unitary authorities not being operational on time and on budget.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280314","280314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141065","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of including adult social care provision within housing development plans.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280315","280315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141066","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of including adult social care provision in housing development plans.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280316","280316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141067","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to provide a single jobs portal for all schools to advertise vacancies.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280317","280317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141068","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people who claimed personal independence payment in Wales in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280163","280163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141069","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the integrity of the Hong Kong police service.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280212","280212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141070","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have claimed universal credit in Wales in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280164","280164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141071","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to introduce a UCAS-style portal for technical education.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280318","280318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141072","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in Hong Kong on potential collaboration between Hong Kong police and organised crime groups in response to recent protests.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280319","280319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141073","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for conducting and publishing research on why taxi and PHV drivers continue to refuse to transport assistance dogs.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280320","280320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141074","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people employed by local authorities in England in (a) 2010 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280165","280165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141075","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for carrying out and publishing a consultation on revised best practice guidance to support local licensing authorities to use their powers more effectively when dealing with Taxi and PHV drivers refusing to transport assistance dogs.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280321","280321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141076","2019-07-25","Cabinet Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many local authorities in England have reduced their total workforce by (a) 500-999 employees, (b) 1,000-1,999 employees and (c) over 2,000 employees since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280166","280166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141077","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,how many independent schools have become involved in academy sponsorship or the founding of free schools in the state system since 2017.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280322","280322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141078","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of climate change on social and economic inequality in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280167","280167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141079","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which Cabinet colleagues will attend the Defence and Security Equipment International 2019 event.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280323","280323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141080","2019-07-24","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what support the Government is providing to the Defence and Security Equipment International 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280324","280324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141081","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value of the Youth Justice Board grant to each local authority was in 2018-19.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280325","280325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141082","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value was of the Youth Justice Board grant to each local authority in 2019-20.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280326","280326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141083","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is his policy to make it a condition for universities to become involved in academy sponsorship or the founding of free schools in order for them to charge maximum tuition fees.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280327","280327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141084","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the mean average salary for a Band 3-5 prison officer in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280328","280328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141085","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the mean average salary for a band 3-5 prison officer with less than one year's experience in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280329","280329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141086","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the mean average salary for a band 2 prison officer in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280330","280330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141087","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the mean average salary for a band 2 prison officer with less than one year's experience in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280331","280331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141088","2019-07-25","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken  to introduce discounted bus and train travel for apprentices since June 2017.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280469","280469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141089","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department will review the use of orders for assessment and treatment under the 1983 Mental Health Act in cases where the patient only has a learning disability or autism.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280332","280332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141090","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of orders for assessment and treatment under the 1983 Mental Health Act on patients with learning disabilities or autism.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280333","280333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141091","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people in England subject to an order under the 1983 Mental Health Act (a) have a learning disability or autism and (b) only have a learning disability or autism and no other mental health condition.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280334","280334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141092","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency plans he has for the repatriation of UK defendants from the EU in the event the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement and is therefore no longer party to the European Arrest Warrant procedure.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280335","280335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141093","2019-07-25","Treasury","2019-07-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to operate a triage system for imports in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280336","280336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141094","2019-07-25","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking in prisons to (a) reduce reoffending rates and (b) improve offender rehabilitation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280337","280337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141095","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on patients of the accreditation of the Society of Homeopathy by the Professional Standards Authority.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280213","280213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141096","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with the Department of Health and Social Care on the proposed pilot scheme merger of the provision of social care and health care in Northamptonshire under one new organisation.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280338","280338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141097","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of Complete Elimination of Autistic Spectrum Expression therapy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280214","280214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141098","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what parts of the Government’s plan for trading in drug precursors in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280339","280339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141099","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what parts of the Government’s plan for accessing animal medicine IT systems in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280340","280340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141100","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what parts of the Government’s plan for registration of veterinary medicines in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280341","280341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141101","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what parts of the Government’s plan for regulation of veterinary medicines in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280342","280342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141102","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) primary and (b) secondary legislation will be required as a result of the Government's response to the review of the Modern Slavery Act 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280138","280138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141103","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what parts of the Government’s plan for sanctions policy in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280343","280343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141104","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what parts of the Government’s plan for satellites and space programmes in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280344","280344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141105","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what parts of the Government’s plan for getting an exemption from maritime security notifications in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280345","280345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141106","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what parts of the Government’s plan for recognition of seafarer certificates of competency in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280346","280346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141107","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy,  what parts of the Government’s plan for state aid in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280347","280347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141108","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what parts of the Government’s plan for travelling in the Common Travel Area in the event of a no deal Brexit have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280348","280348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141109","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what parts of the Government’s plan for workplace rights in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280349","280349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141110","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2019 to Question 276184, if he will estimate the (a) number of staff and (b) departmental resources which have been allocated to (i) maritime, (ii) road transport and (iii) aviation aspects of the UK leaving the EU since April 2019 to 22 July 2019.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280350","280350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141111","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will launch an official market access database to provide information on tariffs by commodity in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280351","280351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141112","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department's technical review of the Building Regulations statutory guidance on fire safety (Approved Document B) will include a review of the regulations covering the self storage industry.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280352","280352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141113","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department will inform businesses of the rule of origin they need to comply with in order to satisfy international tariff and quota arrangements in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280353","280353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141114","2019-07-25","Department for Transport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment the Government has made of whether businesses will be able to use air travel for the delivery of goods and services immediately after the UK's departure from the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280354","280354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141115","2019-07-25","Department for International Trade","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has to (a) roll-over and (b) replace on a bilateral basis outstanding EU trade agreements in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280355","280355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141116","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will survey small businesses to measure the potential effect of the UK's departure from the EU on their viability.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280356","280356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141117","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria his Department used to calculate the £250 cost for nationality status letters issued by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280357","280357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141118","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019,   on the supply of fresh produce.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280215","280215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141119","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019 on the UK’s food warehousing and storage capacity.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280216","280216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141120","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of assaulting a police officer in each police force area in each year since 2007; how many received a sentence other than an immediate custodial sentence; and what the average sentence was received by those who received a custodial sentence.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280470","280470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141121","2019-07-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of business failures due to uncertainty over the UK's departure from the EU in (a) the last two quarters of 2018-19 and (b) the first quarter of 2019-20; and if he will make an estimate of that number for the current quarter.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280358","280358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141122","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the GOLD Group on Operation GIANNA overseeing the Metropolitan Police Department of Professional Standards investigation into allegations in relation to Gurpal Virdi, how many participants in the GOLD Group had the rank or role of (a) Deputy Commissioner, (b) Deputy Assistant Commissioner, (c) Commander, (d) Chief Superintendent, (e) Superintendent, (f) Detective Chief Inspector, (g) Detective Inspector, (h) Detective Sergeant, (i) member of SCD2 Sapphire, (j) member of the Department of Media and Communications and (k) member of the Department of Legal Services; whether representatives of the Crown Prosecution Service were ever present; how many meeting were held; which attendees asked whether there was any evidence that Gurpal Virdi was present at the arrest of the complainant in autumn 1986; which attendees asked whether there was evidence taken from PC Markwick on the arrest for which he was the officer in charge; which attendees asked why evidence was not sought from PC Mady on the arrest of the complainant in spring 1987; what assessment he has made of the equity of the only review of the investigation being conducted by the Department of Professional Standards into its original investigation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280115","280115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141123","2019-07-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to tackle the rise of in-work poverty.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280471","280471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141124","2019-07-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of north-south health inequalities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280359","280359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141125","2019-07-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to devolve further powers on (a) transport and (b) employment to the North of Tyne Combined Authority.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280360","280360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141126","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019 on (a) the Industrial Strategy and (b) sector deals.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280361","280361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141127","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Education on the financial implications for universities of delays in the processing of free visa applications for international students who have been offered places by universities to study in the UK.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280139","280139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141128","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with representatives from Cardiff University on delays in the processing of visa applications for international students who are enrolling in autumn 2019.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280168","280168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141129","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Education on increasing the number of free appointments for international students who require visas to allow them to enrol at Cardiff university in autumn 2019.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280169","280169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141130","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of UK Visa and Citizenship Applications Services in providing free appointments for international students at (a) its Cardiff centre and (b) its other five centres.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280170","280170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141131","2019-07-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the EU Standing Committee on Plants, Animals, Food and Feed decision on 17 July 2019 to suspend the 2013 European Food Safety Authority guidance on bee safety tests for new pesticides, how the UK voted in that Standing Committee meeting; and what plans he has to prevent the approval of pesticides that can (a) destroy wild bee populations and (b) cause long-term harm to honeybees.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280362","280362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141132","2019-07-25","Home Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on the adequacy of procedures to process tier 4 visa procedures.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280171","280171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141133","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of cases of sudden infant death syndrome.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280217","280217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141134","2019-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the British Horseracing Authority on the sponsorship of horseracing in the UK by Qatar; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280218","280218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141135","2019-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he is taking steps to monitor Qatar's role in the (a) governance and (b) sponsorship of British horseracing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280219","280219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141136","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his department is taking to  increase the availability of orthodontists in Havering.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280220","280220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141137","2019-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding his Department has allocated to projects to support grassroots sports facilities in Havering in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280221","280221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141138","2019-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which units of the British Army will be deployed to Mali on peacekeeping operations in the first troop rotation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280222","280222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141140","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase participation in cricket in state schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280224","280224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141141","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on the illegal seizure of the Stena lmpero.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280225","280225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141142","2019-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent steps she has taken to strengthen defence and security cooperation with Bangladesh.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280226","280226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141143","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to tackle the mice infestation on Gough island.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280227","280227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141144","2019-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the benefits of training F35 pilots in (a) the UK and (b) the US.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280228","280228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141145","2019-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of developing hypersonic propulsion systems for military aircraft.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280229","280229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141146","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the percentage of marine plastic pollution originating from the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280230","280230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141147","2019-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps she has taken to strengthen defence and security co-operation with Pakistan.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280231","280231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141148","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the percentage of the UK's plastic waste made up of straws.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280232","280232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141149","2019-07-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent steps she has taken to strengthen defence and security cooperation with Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280233","280233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141150","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the removal of Section 21 of the Housing Act 1996 on a landlord's ability to evict tenants responsible for (a) persistent non-payment of rent and (b) anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280234","280234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1141151","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department's definition is of eviction at short notice.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 280235","280235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139945","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the amount of revenue lost by shops and small businesses because of roadworks or road closures annually.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278467","278467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139946","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on compensation for businesses for revenue lost as a result of roadworks or road closures.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278468","278468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140517","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for resources to engage parents and carers of children in receipt of therapeutic services within school; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279406","279406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140518","2019-07-23","Department for International Development","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the merits of a Global Plan of Action for Education as called for by UNESCO in its report of July 2019 entitled meeting commitments: are countries on track to achieve SDG 4; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279358","279358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140519","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the statement in the press release by Save the Children on 3 July 2019, that 30,000 families on universal credit face paying up to £800 in childcare costs this summer.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279359","279359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140520","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the safety and food hygiene rules for the transport of smoked fish (a) within and (b) to the UK is governed by (i) UK or (ii) EU regulations.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279407","279407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140521","2019-07-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on the regulation of third-party sellers on online marketplaces; and whether he plans to include those sellers in the forthcoming online harms legislation.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279408","279408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140522","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 263790 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service: Reform, whether the academic research for evaluation of reform was made publicly available; and what plans he has for further research on that topic in the current financial year.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279404","279404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140523","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of occasions when there have been mental-health beds available in hospital wards in England in (a) 2018 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279409","279409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140524","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of occasions when a patient needed a mental-health bed but none were available in each CCG area in (a) 2018 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279410","279410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140525","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of occasions when a patient was transported to a mental-health bed in a different area because none were locally available in each CCG area in (a) 2018 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279411","279411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140526","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275723, what the total spend of his Department was on translation services (a) in the 2017-18 financial year and (b) since 1 April 2018.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279405","279405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140527","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275723 on Translation Services, how much funding was allocated to each  provider of translation services in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279412","279412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140528","2019-07-24","Cabinet Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the status is of the national underground asset register trial; whether the information on that trial has been shared with stakeholders; and what opendata access is available from that trial.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279413","279413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140529","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2019 to Question 273502 on Schools: Uniforms, what the timeframe is to bring forward legislative proposals on guidance for school uniform policies.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279414","279414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140530","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the prevention Green Paper before the summer recess.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279415","279415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140531","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding his Department has allocated to (a) Barnsley local authority and (b) local authorities in England to encourage them to search and seize vehicles of suspected fly-tippers.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279416","279416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140532","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding that will be allocated to local welfare assistance provision in the Local Government Finance Settlement for 2020-21.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279417","279417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140533","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of local authorities that no longer provide local welfare assistance schemes.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279418","279418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140534","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make it her policy to extend the eligibility for budgeting loans to all families in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279419","279419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140535","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make it her policy to extend eligibility for local welfare assistance to families with dependent children that have no recourse to public funds conditions attached to their leave to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279420","279420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140536","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many enforcement actions have been carried out by local authorities against fly-tippers in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England in each year since 2010; and of those actions how many were fixed penalty notices.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279421","279421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140537","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent on clearance costs for tipper lorry load fly-tipping by (a) Barnsley local authority and (b) other local authorities in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279422","279422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140538","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent on clearance costs for significant multi-load fly-tipping by (a) Barnsley local authority and (b) other local authorities in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279423","279423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140539","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the proportion of fly-tipping incidents that were categorised as tipper lorry load size or larger in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279424","279424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140540","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on public engagement in the NHS of the proposed merger of five clinical commissioning groups in the North East.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279425","279425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140541","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many instances of fly-tipping have been recorded in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279426","279426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140542","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the merits of the change from primary care trusts to clinical commissioning groups for the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279427","279427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140543","2019-07-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2019 to Question 268565 on Buildings: Insulation, if his Department will publish video footage of the BS 8414 test or tests on high pressure laminate cladding carried out on his Department's behalf by the Fire Protection Association.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279428","279428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140544","2019-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the hon. Member for Blenau Gwent's oral contribution of 8 July 2019, Official Report, column 11, when the full-time trained strength target for the Army will be reached.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279429","279429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140545","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to tackle the use of shape shifting practices by employers to avoid meeting pension obligations to employees; and if he will make a statement .","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279430","279430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140546","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21124, what (a) premium and (b) subsidy payments the Northern franchisee is expected to make or receive in each year of that franchise's duration.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279431","279431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140547","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the prison population was in England and Wales in (a) 12 months to June 1997 and (b) 12 months to June 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279432","279432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140548","2019-07-23","Cabinet Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to simplify Government procurement processes to increase access to contracts by small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279433","279433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140549","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to publicise whistleblower rights and protections for GPs.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279434","279434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140550","2019-07-24","Treasury","2019-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to undertake a review of the business taxation system.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279435","279435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140551","2019-07-24","Treasury","2019-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the Valuation Office Agency budgeted for appeals against revaluations of business rate liabilities in each financial year since 2010-11; and how much of that budget was spent in each of those years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279436","279436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140552","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to require local authorities to identify brownfield rather than green belt sites for development.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279437","279437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140553","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps his Department has taken to protect the green belt from housing developments.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279438","279438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140554","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish a response to the consultation document entitled, Aviation 2050-the future of UK aviation, published in December 2019.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279439","279439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140555","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2019 to Question 244157 on Post Offices: Pay, for what reasons exceptional payments are made by Post Office Ltd; and how (a) many payments were made and (b) much was paid under each category of reason in (i) Scotland, (ii) Wales, (iii) Northern Ireland, and (iv) each region of England, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279440","279440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140556","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Supreme Court ruling of July 2019, if her Department will review the assessment criteria for personal independence payments for claimants with mental health illnesses that requires assessors to make a distinction between whether a claimant needs prompting to engage with other people or social support.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279441","279441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140557","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of (a) the potential cost savings of improving early identification and treatment of Kawasaki disease and (b) the potential consequent reduction in demand for long-term specialist care for children with that disease.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279381","279381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140558","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support his Department is providing to (a) enable early treatment and (b) increase awareness amongst healthcare providers of Kawasaki disease .","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279382","279382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140559","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing a patient registry on Kawasaki disease.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279383","279383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140560","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent comparative assessment he has made of the UK level of research funding into Kawasaki disease with that of other EU member states.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279384","279384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140561","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 263790 on HM Courts and Tribunals Service: Reform, whether the (a) content of and (b) responses to the Social Security and Child Support digital capability survey will be made publicly available.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279442","279442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140562","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times Thameslink Service trains ran without a second member of staff and stopped at unstaffed or part-time staffed stations in 2018.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279443","279443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140563","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) driver controlled operation and (b) stations which are unstaffed or staffed part-time on accessibility for disabled people who wish to travel without pre-booking on Southern Railways.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279444","279444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140564","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many British Transport Police officers worked on the Southern Rail network in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279445","279445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140565","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2019 to Question 230103 on Southern Railways, what proportion of the trains cancelled due to there being no conductor was due to (a) official and (b) alleged unofficial industrial action.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279446","279446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140566","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on driver controlled operation on Southern Rail services.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279447","279447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140567","2019-07-23","Home Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for asylum the Home Office has received from Uighurs since 2015; and what proportion of those applications have been successful.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279448","279448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140568","2019-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department policies of (a) the March 2019 The Children’s Society report entitled Nowhere to turn and (B) the finding that since the devolution of crisis support in 2013, the number of people receiving crisis support from either national or local government has reduced by 75 per cent.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279449","279449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140569","2019-07-23","Cabinet Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271324, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279360","279360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140570","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) training, (b) capacity building and (c) assistance (i) the UK Government and (ii) Scotland Yard provides to the Hong Kong Police Force.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279392","279392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140571","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271325, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279361","279361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140572","2019-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271326, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279362","279362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140573","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271327, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279363","279363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140574","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271328, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279364","279364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140575","2019-07-23","Department for International Development","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271330, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279365","279365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140576","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271332, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279366","279366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140577","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271334, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279367","279367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140578","2019-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271335, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279368","279368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140579","2019-07-23","Treasury","2019-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271336, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279369","279369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140580","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to help improve the standard of student housing.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279376","279376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140581","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271348, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279370","279370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140582","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to issue guidance to health professionals on the Serious Shortage Protocol.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279389","279389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140583","2019-07-23","Home Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 271345, for what reasons his Department does not offer a payroll deduction service to enable employees to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279371","279371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140584","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has provide information to patients on changes to the provision of medicines as a result of the serious shortage protocol; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279390","279390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140585","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions the Government has had with (a) patient groups and (b) professional bodies on the development of the serious shortage protocol.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279391","279391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140586","2019-07-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the adequacy of provision of treatment for people with migraines.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279402","279402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140587","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department provides to employers on support to employees with migraines.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279403","279403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140588","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the counsellor to student ratio in (a) secondary schools and (b) primary schools in each local authority area in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279377","279377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140589","2019-07-23","Home Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an  assessment of the potential merits of granting Uighur asylum seekers the automatic right to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279450","279450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140590","2019-07-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of benefit appeals to HM Courts and Tribunal Service made against Department of Work and Pensions decisions were overturned on appeal in (a) Wales and (b) Newport East constituency in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279393","279393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140591","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve the provision of mental heath training for teachers and lecturers at universities.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279378","279378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140592","2019-07-24","Treasury","2019-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) longest and (b) average response time was to answer an HMRC helpline; and how many complaints about telephone response times to those helplines have been made in the last six months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279394","279394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140593","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what criteria his Department uses to estimate the average cost per year in England on treating non-EEA surcharge payers.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279372","279372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140594","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) average and (b) longest response time was to answer universal credit freephone numbers; and how many complaints about telephone response times for those numbers have been made in the last six months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279395","279395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140595","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 166508 on South Western Railway: Industrial Disputes, what estimate he has made of (a) lost revenue and (b) other costs incurred by South Western as a result of official industrial action.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279373","279373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140596","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 166508 on South Western Railway: Industrial Disputes, what payments have been made to reimburse the company for revenues lost as a result of official industrial action.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279374","279374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140597","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 166508 on South Western Railway: Industrial Disputes, whether (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have provided advice South Western on payments that will be made to reimburse that company for revenues lost as a result of official industrial action.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279375","279375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140598","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to start the universal credit managed migration pilot.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279396","279396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140599","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on people applying to the EU Settlement Scheme of charges issued by private operators for biometric services.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279451","279451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140600","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing a timescale for the information gathering exercise on the public sale of fireworks.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279452","279452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140601","2019-07-24","Home Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which local authorities have applied for a grant from the youth endowment fund.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279453","279453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140602","2019-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 July 2019 to Question 273399 on HIV Infection: Salford, if he will take steps to ensure that gay and bisexual men in Salford have access to PrEP.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279454","279454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140603","2019-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times the Child Maintenance Service registered the maintenance debt of a non-resident parent with credit rating agencies in the last year.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279455","279455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140604","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish its study on improvements to rail capacity and speeds on the South Wales Mainline.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279397","279397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140605","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to include provisions in the proposed Environment Bill to tackle the use of netting on hedges, hedgerows and trees on development sites.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279456","279456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140606","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Counter Terrorism Associated Prosecutory Reforms initiative monitors the number of death sentences handed down by the civilian anti-terror court in Pakistan.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279457","279457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140607","2019-07-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions the Government’s Overseas Security and Justice Assistance assessment for the Counter Terrorism Associated Prosecutorial Reforms Initiative programme in Pakistan has been reviewed; how many times the risk assessment for that programme has been revised; and on how many occasions a Minister in his Department has approved the continuation of this programme.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279458","279458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140608","2019-07-24","Department for Education","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children in Coventry (a) eligible and (b) not eligible for free school meals who achieved five or more GCSEs at grades 4 to 9 in (i) 2017 and (ii) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279379","279379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140609","2019-07-24","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to ensure that all airlines operating in the UK have a carbon offset scheme to which customers can sign up.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279385","279385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140610","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for patents in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279459","279459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140611","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for trademarks and design in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279460","279460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140612","2019-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for telecoms business in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279461","279461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140613","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by his Department, what parts of the plan for accounting and audit in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279462","279462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140614","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by his Department, what parts of the plan for providing services including those of a qualified professional in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279463","279463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140615","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by his Department, what parts of the plan for structuring businesses in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279464","279464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140616","2019-07-23","Treasury","2019-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for banking, insurance and other financial services in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279465","279465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140617","2019-07-23","Treasury","2019-07-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, published by the Department for Exiting the European Union, what parts of the plan for VAT for businesses in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279466","279466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140618","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, which parts of the Government’s plan for geo-blocking online content in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279467","279467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140619","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, which parts of the Government’s plan for consumer rights in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279468","279468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140620","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, which parts of the Government’s plan for industrial emissions standards in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279469","279469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140621","2019-07-23","Department for Transport","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, which parts of the Government’s plan for reporting CO2 emissions for new cars and vans in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279470","279470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140622","2019-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, which parts of the Government’s plan for maintaining environmental standards in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279471","279471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140623","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, which parts of the Government’s plan for meeting climate change requirements in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279472","279472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140624","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, which parts of the Government’s plan for civil nuclear regulation in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279473","279473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140625","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, what parts of the Government’s plan for generating low-carbon electricity in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279474","279474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140626","2019-07-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, which parts of the Government’s plan for nuclear research in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279475","279475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140627","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, what parts of the Government’s plan for running an oil or gas business in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279476","279476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140628","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, what parts of the Government’s plan for trading gas with the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279477","279477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140629","2019-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's Guidance on how to prepare for Brexit if there's no deal, what parts of the Government’s plan for trading electricity in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal have been implemented.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279478","279478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140630","2019-07-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to compensate women born in the 1950s who were adversely affected by changes to the state pension age.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279380","279380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140631","2019-07-24","Department for International Development","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether his Department provides support to Africa Trade Ltd.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279398","279398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1140632","2019-07-24","Department for International Development","2019-07-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether his Department provides support to Africa House London Ltd.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 279399","279399"
