"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823629","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether planned changes related to viability assessments will include the introduction of a standard methodology for such assessments.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123088","123088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823631","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for the Armed Forces of 15 January 2018, Official Report, column 605, how many former pilots who had left the RAF have applied to re-join since the announcement that his Department would purchase nine P-8A Poseidon Maritime Patrol Aircraft in July 2016.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123089","123089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823632","2018-01-19","Department for International Trade","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January to Question 121983, if he will list each of the 14 trade working groups and 21 countries; and where that information has previously been made public.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123090","123090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823633","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what reciprocal health agreements he plans to put in place to allow continued access to health care for disabled UK citizens in EU member states after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123091","123091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823634","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for his policies of the finding of the survey of childcare providers in England, conducted by the Pre School Learning Alliance in December 2017, that 66 per cent of childcare providers plan to make changes to how they offer the 30 hours over the next 12 months most commonly by increasing fees and charges.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123092","123092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823635","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 15 January 2018, Official Report, column 610, what steps he is taking to secure future orders of the Hawk aircraft and, which countries he is talking to about such orders.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123093","123093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823636","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for his policies of the finding of the survey of  childcare providers in England, conducted by the Pre School Learning Alliance in December 2017, that 38 per cent of providers are uncertain whether or not they will be offering 30 hours places in a year's time.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123094","123094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823637","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people graduated with a STEM degree in each of the last four years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123095","123095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823638","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what impact assessment his Department has undertaken on the effect of implementing a new recognition test on EU/EEA trained medical professionals on timescales for appointment of medical professionals.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123096","123096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823639","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to negotiate for continued UK membership of the Blue Badge disability parking scheme.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123097","123097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823641","2018-01-19","HM Treasury","2018-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made on improving the quality of statistics available to quantify levels of e-commerce.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123098","123098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823642","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total number of disability projects is that have been funded by European Social Funding in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123099","123099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823643","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing a new train station at Welborne and the effect that station would have on connectivity between Portsmouth and Southampton.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123100","123100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823644","2018-01-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the establishment is by rank and number of HQ Royal Armoured Corps.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123101","123101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823645","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support SMEs and their employees in Carillion's supply chain following that company's liquidation.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123102","123102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823646","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women have been in one-star postings or above in the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123103","123103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823647","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of European Investment Bank funding on the UK's green industry.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123104","123104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823648","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many BAME personnel have been in one-star postings or above in the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123105","123105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823649","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to review legislation related to VAT paid on community-purchased defibrillators after the UK leave the EU.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123106","123106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823651","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 December 2017 to Question 120348, when Natural England will finalise the allocation of funding for national trails for 2018/19.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123107","123107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823652","2018-01-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps he has taken to promote tourism in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123108","123108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823653","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to review funding streams for children who are not of reception age to access additional support services whilst at nursery.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123109","123109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823654","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage language teaching in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123110","123110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823655","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were in good or outstanding schools in each of the last seven years in (a) Kirklees, (b) West Yorkshire, (c) England and (d) UK.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123111","123111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823656","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what studies his Department is conducting into the prospects for survival of the ash tree.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123112","123112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823657","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to require academy schools to have a curriculum which includes personal, social and health education.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123113","123113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823658","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to ensure that every teacher in all state-funded schools has or is working towards Qualified Teacher Status.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123114","123114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823660","2018-01-19","Cabinet Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the liquidation of Carillion, whether any services provided by the other 29 strategic suppliers to Government are similarly exposed.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123115","123115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823661","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of Ash Dieback on tree numbers in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123116","123116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823662","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research his Department has conducted on the effect of the removal of Education Maintenance Allowance on families where a child received that allowance.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123117","123117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823663","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what land his Department has declared to be surplus to its requirements in (a) West Sussex and (b) the Coast to Capital area.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123118","123118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823664","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to ensure adequate supplies of the PPV23 vaccine.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123119","123119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823665","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department still plans to procure 589 Ajax vehicles.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123120","123120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823666","2018-01-18","Cabinet Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress the Government Property Unit has made on the sale of Government Departments' surplus land.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123121","123121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823667","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on the NATO Allied Command Transformation Programme.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123122","123122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823668","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the budget for the Social Mobility Commission was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123123","123123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823669","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department had made of the (a) reasons for and (b) extent of the decline in the puffin population.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123124","123124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823670","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans next to undertake a census of seabirds.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123125","123125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823672","2018-01-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many studies his Department has conducted on the economic effect of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123126","123126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823673","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support the development of skills specifically to help deliver the Government's infrastructure programmes.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123127","123127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823674","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans next to renew the Net Limitation Order.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123128","123128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823675","2018-01-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the titles are of the studies his Department has conducted on the effect on small businesses of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123129","123129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823676","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of health visitors.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123130","123130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823677","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many health visitor positions there are in England; and how many of those positions are vacant.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123131","123131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823678","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports he has received on increased Russian submarine operations in the North Atlantic.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123132","123132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823679","2018-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of religious freedom in Vietnam; and what steps the Government is taking to promote and protect the right to freedom of religion or belief in that country.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123133","123133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823681","2018-01-18","Wales Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used and (b) sent for recycling each year by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123134","123134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823682","2018-01-18","Northern Ireland Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123135","123135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823683","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on the 50 per cent cap on faith-based admissions in faith schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123136","123136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823684","2018-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123137","123137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823686","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of responses to his Department's call for evidence on measures to reduce littering of plastic drinks containers, issued on 2 October 2017; and whether he plans to proceed with the introduction of deposit return and reward schemes.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123138","123138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823687","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used and (b) sent for recycling by his Department each year.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123139","123139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823688","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123140","123140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823689","2018-01-18","Home Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123141","123141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823690","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate has been made of the number of single-use disposable cups that are (a) used and (b) sent for recycling by his Department each year.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123142","123142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823691","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123143","123143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823692","2018-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123144","123144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823694","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that new standards within the updated driving examination meet health and safety requirements for (a) the applicant, (b) the driving instructor and (c) other road users.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123145","123145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823695","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123146","123146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823696","2018-01-18","Department for International Trade","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123147","123147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823697","2018-01-18","Department for International Development","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123148","123148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823698","2018-01-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123149","123149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823699","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123150","123150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823700","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123151","123151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823701","2018-01-18","Scotland Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate has been made of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used each year and (b) sent for recycling by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123152","123152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823703","2018-01-18","Cabinet Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate has been made by his Department of the number of single use disposable cups that are (a) used and (b) sent for recycling each year.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123153","123153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823704","2018-01-19","Home Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers waited over six months for a decision on their asylum application in 2017.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123154","123154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823705","2018-01-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress is being made on delivering the recommendation of the Mental Health Taskforce Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in January 2016, on revisiting membership of the Advisory Committee on Resource Allocation with the specific goal of ensuring that mental health expertise is adequately represented across the disciplines involved.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123155","123155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823706","2018-01-18","Prime Minister","2018-01-16","To ask the Prime Minister, how many times she has visited food banks in Maidenhead constituency in her official capacity.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123156","123156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823707","2018-01-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress is being made on delivering the recommendation of the Mental Health Taskforce Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in January 2016, for his Department to carry out a review of existing regulations of the Health and Social Care Act 2012 to identify disparities and gaps between provisions relating to physical and mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123157","123157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823709","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average length of service has been for (a) Chief Executives and (b) Chairs of NHS or Foundation Trusts over the last 30 years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123158","123158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823710","2018-01-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the membership is of the Advisory Committee on Resource Allocation (ACRA); who the chair of ACRA is; and if he will place copies of the agendas for each of ACRA's last ten meetings, together with supporting papers, in the Library.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123159","123159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823711","2018-01-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what financial support her Department provides to increase the number of visitors to Cornwall.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123160","123160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823712","2018-01-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress is being made on delivering the recommendation of the Mental Health Taskforce Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in January 2016, on disaggregating the inequalities adjustment from the baseline funding allocation for clinical commissioning groups and primary care to make the value of that adjustment more visible.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123161","123161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823713","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to recover the £1.7million of unauthorised redundancy payments made by HS2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123162","123162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823714","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what mechanisms exist to recover unauthorised redundancy payments made by a company funded by the Government through grant in aid.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123163","123163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823716","2018-01-19","HM Treasury","2018-01-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff were employed in (a) HM Revenue and Customs; and (b)  departments of HM Revenue & Customs in each of the last ten years; and what the budget for each of those departments was in each of those years.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123164","123164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823717","2018-01-19","HM Treasury","2018-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many arrests have been made under the provisions of the Export Control Order 2008 in each year since that Order came into effect; how many charging decisions have been received on such breaches from the CPS; on what dates such decisions were received; and how many criminal convictions have resulted from each such charging decision.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123165","123165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823718","2018-01-18","Department for International Development","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to support the maintenance of the operation of medical facilities during an electricity crisis in the Gaza strip.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123166","123166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823719","2018-01-19","Home Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect of the introduction of minimum unit pricing for alcohol on the number of assaults on emergency service workers.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123167","123167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823720","2018-01-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Social Housing Regulator has taken to protect tenants of Old Ford Housing Association in Tower Hamlets as a result of its downgrading of Circle, now Clarion Housing in December 2016.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123168","123168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823721","2018-01-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, under what circumstances he would intervene in a case handled by the Social Housing Regulator in the event that there was reason to believe it was failing in its responsibility to ensure that tenants are protected from serious detriment by the performance of their housing association.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123169","123169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823722","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the National College for Teaching and Leadership has ever reached the recruitment target of 2,400 early years teachers per year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123170","123170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823723","2018-01-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many times the Social Housing Regulator has found that there has been serious detriment to tenants by the poor performance of a housing association.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123171","123171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823725","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Pupil Referral Units there are for early years pupils.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123172","123172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823726","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 117198, if he will place a moratorium on new incinerators until he has made an assessment of what future capacity may be needed for incineration.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123173","123173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823727","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 118316, on what date work was last carried out on the children's centres consultation.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123174","123174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823729","2018-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis have been awarded the enhanced rate of personal independence payment (a) mobility, (b) daily living and (c) mobility and daily living component by award length.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123175","123175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823730","2018-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis placed in the employment support allowance (ESA) support group at initial work capability assessment have been placed in the ESA work-related activity group at their repeat assessment in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123176","123176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823731","2018-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people with multiple sclerosis have been placed in the employment support allowance Support Group on the basis of (a) physical or mental health risk, (b) pregnancy risk or (c) severe functional disability since 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123177","123177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823732","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2018 to Question 121998, how many eligible children there are for 30 hours of funded childcare in (a) England, (b) each region of England and (c) each local authority area in England.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123178","123178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823733","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of children's progress in specialist maths schools.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123179","123179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823734","2018-01-18","Department for International Trade","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the level of exports from the UK to Lebanon in was in (a) 2010, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123180","123180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823736","2018-01-18","Department for International Trade","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has plans to appoint a trade envoy to Lebanon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123181","123181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823737","2018-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to convene an international conference to help to resolve tensions between Iran and Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123182","123182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823738","2018-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the compliance with international law of the Israeli occupation of Shebaa Farms.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123183","123183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823739","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to ensure people with Huntington's disease have appropriate access to emerging treatment methods.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123184","123184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823740","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 108254, when he intends to set out further steps on the review of higher education student finance.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123185","123185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823742","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children with special educational needs and disabilities who are home schooled.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123186","123186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823743","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prescriptions of (a) individual benzodiazepine drugs and (b) individual antidepressants were dispensed in the community in 2016.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123187","123187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823744","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on contracts between (a) schools and (b) further education colleges in England and Carillion Group.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123188","123188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823745","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools Carillion provides building or maintenance services to; and what the total value of those contracts is.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123189","123189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823746","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools Carillion provides school meals or related services to.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123190","123190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823747","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many contracts are held by public bodies with Carillion Group for the construction of new school buildings; and what the value of those contracts is.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123191","123191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823748","2018-01-19","Department for Education","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that the delivery of school meals is not affected by Carillion entering liquidation.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123192","123192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823749","2018-01-19","Cabinet Office","2018-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to his oral statement of 15 January 2018, Official Record, column.627, on Carillion, which schools are holding contracts with Carillion in England.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123193","123193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823750","2018-01-19","HM Treasury","2018-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the financial effect on the High Speed Two project of Carillion entering liquidation; and if he will he publish that assessment.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123194","123194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823751","2018-01-19","Department for Transport","2018-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the financial effect on the High Speed Two project of Carillion entering liquidation; and if he will publish that assessment.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123195","123195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821528","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government  if he will publish the (a) pay and (b) other benefits of the (i) chair, (ii) vice chair, (iii) non-executive and (i) executive directors of each Local Government Pension Scheme pool.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122446","122446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822735","2018-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","What progress he has made on implementing the National Shipbuilding Strategy and procuring the Type 31e frigate.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903279","903279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822809","2018-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2017 to Question 115593, on Employment Tribunals Service: Eastern Region, how many lay members there were in (a) the Eastern Region and (b) Bedford in each year from 2012 to 2017.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122492","122492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822810","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on business and public confidence of the HM Revenue and Customs' guidance note which maintains that data concerning company registration from Companies House should not be relied upon because this data is obtained only on a trust basis.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122493","122493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822811","2018-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it possible for people to claim for Personal Independence Payments through an online platform in line with the Government’s digital by default agenda.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122494","122494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822812","2018-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will change the rules for the audio recording of medical assessments for employment and support allowance, personal independence payments, and universal credit to allow claimants to record assessments on digital devices.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122495","122495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822813","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with the company INEOS  on the suitability of Easington constituency as a location for (a) advanced manufacturing and (b) the automotive industry.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122496","122496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822814","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the new duty band for high strength white cider on the lives of homeless people.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122497","122497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822815","2018-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide an email address for the submission of personal independence payments claim forms and medical evidence.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122498","122498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822816","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with Queen's University on funding for that institution for medical research.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122499","122499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822817","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the rate of early diagnosis of cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122500","122500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822818","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of local authorities' powers to deter pigeons and pests in town centres.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122501","122501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822819","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce workload-related strain on doctors in hospitals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122502","122502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822820","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of introducing 20mph speed limits on reducing the number of road traffic-related deaths.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122503","122503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822821","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help aid to reach people in Yemen.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122504","122504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822822","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help bring about a settlement in Yemen.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122505","122505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822823","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of birds of prey who have died as a result of impacting with wind turbines in the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122506","122506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822824","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to increase the population of game birds in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122507","122507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822825","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were diagnosed with testicular cancer in each of the last five years; and what the age groups of those people are.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122508","122508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822826","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to a Hepatitis C elimination plan in order to meet the WHO target of eliminating the disease as a public health threat by 2030; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122509","122509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822827","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to discuss with the pharmaceutical industry steps to ensure that all patients who suffer from Hepatitis C have access to the full range of available medicines.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122510","122510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822828","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the Hepatitis C treatment rates were for each Operational Delivery Network in 2016-17.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122511","122511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822829","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how his Department plans to increase the number of Hepatitis C patients who are diagnosed and treated.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122512","122512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822830","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to (a) increase the extent and frequency of testing and (b) improve treatment for Hepatitis C for people who inject drugs .","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122513","122513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822831","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) amount and (b) proportion of municipal waste collected as recyclable waste was (i) recycled, (ii) sent for incineration and (iii) sent to landfill in 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122514","122514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822832","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the extent of the practice of insolvent companies failing to pay redundancy payments to staff they have dismissed.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122515","122515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822833","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to tackle the loyalty penalty faced by consumers who do not switch bank providers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122516","122516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822834","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities children's services departments are exempt from statutory guidance; what those exemptions are; and what steps his Department takes to monitor and review those exemptions.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122517","122517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822835","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will take steps to encourage the uptake of private health insurance to relieve pressures on the NHS.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122518","122518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822836","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list the titles of all assessments undertaken by his Department relating to the impact of the UK's departure from the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122519","122519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822837","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the war widow(er) pension payment rates will be for the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122520","122520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822838","2018-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance is issued to jobcentre staff on handling requests to split universal credit payments between members of a household.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122521","122521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822839","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that disabled people are represented on the working group on taxi and private hire vehicle licensing.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122522","122522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822840","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2018 to Question 121212, what changes the Government plans to make to the Civil Service People Survey in order to measure the extent of presenteeism.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122523","122523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822841","2018-01-18","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of a minimum unit price for alcohol in England on rates of alcohol-related crime.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122524","122524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822842","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of minimum unit pricing on alcohol-related hospital admissions.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122525","122525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822843","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of minimum unit pricing on the level of alcohol-related deaths.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122526","122526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822844","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of minimum unit pricing for alcoholic drinks on health inequalities.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122527","122527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822845","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent from the public purse on legal fees excluding sums relating to clinical malpractice in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122528","122528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822846","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much was spent from the public purse on legal fees in connection with the junior doctors strike in 2016.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122529","122529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822847","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much has been spent by his Department from the public purse on legal fees in relation to tendering and awarding contracts in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122530","122530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822848","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much has been spent by his Department from the public purse on legal fees from external legal firms in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122531","122531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822849","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of the establishment of Iranian rocket factories in Lebanon under the control of Hezbollah.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122532","122532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822850","2018-01-18","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January 2018 to Question 121223, on Prosperity Fund: Behavioural Insights Team, what the eight projects referred to are.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122533","122533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822851","2018-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2018 to Question 120661, on Community Orders: Females, how many women received a community sentence by status of (a) foreign national and (b) British national in each of the last five whole reporting years; and what the offence category for each of those nationalities was in that time period.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122534","122534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822852","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will make an assessment of the implications for local communities of the closure of RBS branches in (a) Penicuik and (b) Bonnyrigg later this year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122535","122535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822853","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made about the financial effect of Autumn Budget 2017 on (a) women and (b) people with protected characteristics.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122536","122536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822854","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to change its guidance on the Severe Weather Emergency Protocol and extended weather provision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122537","122537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822855","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to change legal protections for people sleeping rough in England during severe weather; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122538","122538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822856","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2017 to Question 106304, whether his Department has set a date for the roundtable event with consumer groups to discuss negotiations on the UK leaving the EU and their implications for consumers in the UK.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122539","122539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822857","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount lost to the public purse as a result of the Personal Savings Allowance in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18 to date.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122540","122540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822858","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress is being made on the sale of the Valuation Office Agency testing facility in Shrewsbury.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122541","122541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822859","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospital trusts in England have considered installing a pay on exit or similar scheme since the publication of his Department's guidance on NHS patient, visitor and staff car parking principles, last updated on 29 October 2015; and how many hospital trusts (a) are planning to install such a scheme in 2018 and (b) have decided against installing such a scheme.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122542","122542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822860","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's guidance on NHS patient, visitor and staff car parking principles, last updated on 29 October 2015, how many NHS trusts, NHS hospitals or establishments providing NHS healthcare in England have imposed a requirement for parking contractors to be members of a parking trade association, such as the British Parking Association and the Independent Parking Committee, since the initial publication of that guidance on 23 August 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122543","122543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822861","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's guidance on NHS patient, visitor and staff car parking principles, last updated on 29 October 2015, how many NHS hospitals in England prioritise parking for staff whose daily duties require them to travel by car.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122544","122544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822862","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's guidance on NHS patient, visitor and staff car parking principles, last updated on 29 October 2015, how many NHS hospitals in England provide internal travel arrangements between hospital sites for staff who routinely travel between hospital sites.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122545","122545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822863","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's guidance on NHS patient, visitor and staff car parking principles, last updated on 29 October 2015, how many hospital trusts in England have installed a pay on exit or similar scheme since the initial publication of that guidance on 23 August 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122546","122546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822864","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care whether his Department has issued guidance in the procedure for using rape kits on children under 16 and the gender of the medical professional using that rape kit.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122547","122547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822865","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what specialised training medical professionals have for using rape kits and medical assessments of victims of sexual assault aged 16 and under.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122548","122548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822866","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what provisions are in place to enable access to 30 hours of free childcare for parents working unusual and anti-social hours.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122549","122549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822867","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department are taking to improve post-natal mental health care provision.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122550","122550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822868","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to assist young people diagnosed with dyslexia to improve their writing skills for their A-level exams.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122551","122551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822869","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to review or update the Housing Health and Safety Rating System (HHSRS).","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122552","122552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822870","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to protect employees from losing their statutory redundancy pay as a result of a company restructuring.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122553","122553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822871","2018-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the proportion of staff turnover in the universal credit helpline centres was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122554","122554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822872","2018-01-18","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the closure of illegal immigrants' bank accounts will not affect people with a legal right to reside in the UK.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122555","122555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822873","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has plans for local authorities to provide independent oversight housing for asylum seekers.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122556","122556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822874","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has plans to extend 30 hours of free childcare to the parents of two-year-old children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122557","122557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822875","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much and what proportion of the Parliamentary Contributory Pension Scheme is invested (a) directly and (b) indirectly in (i) oil, (ii) gas and (ii) coal industries.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122558","122558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822876","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much and what proportion of the Parliamentary Contributory Pension Scheme is invested in companies or conglomerates involved in the (a) extraction, (b) transportation, (c) sale and (d) supply of (i) oil, (ii) gas and (iii) coal.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122559","122559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822877","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much and what proportion of the Parliamentary Contributory Pension Scheme is invested (a) directly and (b) indirectly in tobacco industries.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122560","122560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822878","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much and what proportion of the Parliamentary Contributory Pension Scheme is invested (a) directly and (b) indirectly in renewable energy industries.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122561","122561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822879","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department awarded any development contracts to the Ministry of Defence in 2016-17; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122562","122562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822880","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will include Portsmouth in funding allocations for Housing First pilot schemes to reduce homelessness.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122563","122563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822881","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to announce a reduction in the number of Royal Marines during the current Parliament.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122564","122564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822882","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that more women are prepared for and encouraged to takeup positions in senior command.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122565","122565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822883","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the 17 surface naval ships to protect the new aircraft carriers.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122566","122566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822884","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to implement capital improvements to (a) Portsmouth Harbour Station and (b) other railway stations in Portsmouth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122567","122567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822885","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure value for money for rail commuters.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122568","122568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822886","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has discussed rail fares with his counterparts in (a) Italy, (b) Germany and (c) France.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122569","122569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822887","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Minister in his Department has responsibility for patient transport.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122570","122570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822888","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to avoid a repetition of this year’s winter crisis in the NHS.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122571","122571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822889","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure patients at accident and emergency departments do not spend an extended period of time waiting in ambulances before they are seen.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122572","122572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822890","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department are taking to replace the services of overseas qualified doctors that (a) are planning to leave and (b) may leave in the next five years.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122573","122573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822891","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to encourage use of the Epilepsy Passport.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122574","122574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822892","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the UK retains the regulatory standards set out in REACH after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122575","122575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822893","2018-01-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department has prepared any impact assessments covering the defence manufacturing industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122576","122576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822894","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people discharged from mental health treatment in hospitals have had support from crisis resolution teams in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122577","122577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822895","2018-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will respond to Early Day Motion 677 on the Falun Gong and harvesting organs.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122578","122578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822896","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the Government to appoint a mental health equalities champion as recommended in the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122579","122579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822897","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of care packages that were commissioned by Local Authorities in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122580","122580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822898","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to make available data about delayed transfers of care involving people with dementia for the last five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122581","122581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822899","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Parliamentary and Health Ombudsman’s report, Ignoring the alarms: how eating disorder services are failing patients, HC 634, published on 6 December 2017, when (a) his Department, (b) NHS England and (c) NHS Improvement plan to make a formal response to the recommendations of that report.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122582","122582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822900","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to make available data for each condition on delayed transfers of care for the last five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122583","122583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822901","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many applications were received for the On-street Residential Chargepoint scheme in the current funding round.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122584","122584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822902","2018-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications of recent and ongoing protests in Tunisia for the political stability of that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122585","122585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822903","2018-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Tunisia on the arrest and detention of participants in recent and ongoing protests in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122586","122586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822904","2018-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the intimidation and harassment of journalists covering recent and ongoing protests in Tunisia.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122587","122587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822905","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport what steps his Department is taking to work with airlines and airports to enable wheelchair users to board and travel on aeroplanes with comfort and dignity.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122588","122588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822906","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to work with airlines and airports to enable wheelchair users to board and travel on aeroplanes with comfort and dignity.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122589","122589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822907","2018-01-18","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps have been taken by the Government in response to the recommendation in paragraph 6.2. of the Council of Europe Resolution 2036 (2015) on promoting reasonable accommodation within the principle of indirect discrimination; and what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of introducing a formal mechanism of reasonable accommodation for religious belief in the workplace.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122590","122590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822908","2018-01-18","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps have been taken by the Government in response to the recommendation in paragraph 6.2.2 of the Council of Europe Resolution 2036 (2015) on upholding freedom of conscience in the workplace while ensuring that access to services provided by law is maintained and the right of others to be free from discrimination is protected.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122591","122591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822909","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps have been taken by the Government in response to the recommendation in paragraph 6.2.3 of the Council of Europe Resolution 2036 (2015) on respecting the right of parents to provide their children with an education in conformity with their religious or philosophical convictions, while guaranteeing the fundamental right of children to education in a critical and pluralistic manner in accordance with the European Convention on Human Rights, its protocols and the case law of the European Court of Human Rights.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122592","122592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822910","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps have been taken by the Government in response to the recommendation in paragraph 6.2.4 of the Council of Europe Resolution 2036 (2015) on enabling Christians to fully participate in public life.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122593","122593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822911","2018-01-18","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken in response to the recommendation in paragraph 6.4. of the Council of Europe Resolution 2036 (2015) on upholding the fundamental right to freedom of expression by ensuring national legislation does not unduly limit religiously motivated speech.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122594","122594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822913","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on community and inter-faith relations of attacks on churches in the UK including Christ Church on Infirmary Road in Londonderry on 12 September 2017, St John's Church in Keynsham in September 2017, Holy Trinity Church in Back Hamlet in August 2017, St James’ Church in Dursley in August 2017, St Mary and St Nicolas Church in August 2017, Airdrie Clarkston Parish Church in August 2017, All Saints Parish Church on Church Street, Gainsborough on 26 July 2017, St Winifred RC Church, Bootle in July 2017, Church of the Venerable Bede in July 2017, St Thomas’s Church in Stopsley in July 2017, St Botolph’s Church in Skidbrooke in July 2017, Murston Old Church in July 2017, St Editha's Church, in Tamworth in June 2017, Castlemilk Evangelical Church of Christ in April 2017, Wylde Green United Reformed Church in Sutton Coldfield in March 2017, St Faith’s Church in Lincoln in March 2017, Blackford Parish Church in February 2017, St. Mary’s Church, Pateley Bridge in January 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122596","122596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822914","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps have been taken by the Government in response to the recommendation in paragraph 6.6 of the Council of Europe Resolution 2036 (2015) on combatting and preventing cases of violence, discrimination and intolerance and on carrying out effective investigations in order to avoid any sense of impunity among the perpetrators.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122597","122597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822915","2018-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps have been taken by the Government in response to the recommendation in paragraph 6.7 of the Council of Europe Resolution 2036 (2015) on encouraging the media to avoid negative stereotyping and communicating prejudices against Christians, in the same way as for any other group.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122598","122598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822916","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing a Wireless Emergency Alert system in the UK similar to that currently available in the United States.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122599","122599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822917","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research is being conducted on the effect of organophosphates on people that operate sheep dips.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122600","122600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822918","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Guy's hospital poisons unit on organophosphates in sheep dips.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122601","122601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822919","2018-01-17","House of Commons Commission","2018-01-15","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what plans the Commission has to increase the range of food available for both vegetarians and vegans in catering facilities in the House.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122602","122602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822920","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with Gloucestershire Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust on its decision to create a SubCo; and what advice his Department provided to the Trust.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122603","122603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822921","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of public bodies that have created subsidiary companies with the intention of reducing VAT liability.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122604","122604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822922","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will (a) publish the Government's contracts with Carillion for all works relating or connected to High Speed Two and (b) place copies of those contracts in the Library.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122605","122605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822923","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable and process is for appointing new members to the Advisory Council for the Misuse of Drugs; and by when the Government plans to have filled existing vacancies.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122606","122606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822924","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 9 December 2015 to Question 19392, how much his Department has spent on studies to support whether to refurbish or replace the existing Trident warhead design to date.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122607","122607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822925","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the in-service date is for the UK Trident Mark 4A modified warhead; what the estimated cost of the Mark 4A programme is; and what progress has been made in delivering that programme.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122608","122608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822926","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in which Top Line Budget allocation the costs of the Mark 4A modification to the UK Trident warhead are included.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122609","122609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822927","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, (a) what role the National Security Council will have in the decision on whether to replace the Trident nuclear warhead, (b) whether that decision will be discussed by the full Cabinet and (c) whether Parliament will have a final vote on that decision.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122610","122610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822928","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions his Department has had with the US Administration on options for the replacement of the UK Trident nuclear warhead.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122611","122611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822929","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the US Administration on options for the replacement of the UK Trident nuclear warhead.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122612","122612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822930","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on Hezbollah’s weapons arsenal.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122613","122613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822931","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of academies in (a) Hull and (b) England contract Carillion plc for catering services.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122614","122614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822932","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the criteria his Department used to award construction contracts for High Speed Two to Carillion plc in July 2017; and what due diligence his Department undertakes before awarding contracts to companies that have issued profit warnings.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122615","122615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822933","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of local authority maintained schools receive school maintenance services from Carillion plc in (a) Hull and (b) England.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122616","122616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822934","2018-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisons receive prison support services provided by Carillion plc.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122617","122617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822935","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what rail improvement contracts Carillion plc holds in (a) the North East, (b) the North West and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122618","122618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822936","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths were related to (a) benzodiazepines, (b) Z-drugs and (c) antidepressants in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122619","122619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822937","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which NHS Trusts contract Carillion plc for NHS maintenance; and the dates on which each of those contracts were awarded.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122620","122620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822938","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he had made an assessment of the potential merits of adding a tick box for Cornish nationality in the next census; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122621","122621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822939","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the average age of service vehicles in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122622","122622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822940","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the take-up rate for cervical screening was in (a) the West Midlands (b) Coventry in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122623","122623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822941","2018-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce levels of violence in Young Offenders Institutions in England and Wales.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122624","122624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822942","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) primary and (b) secondary school children who are eligible for free school meals in (i) the West Midlands and (ii) Coventry attend a school rated good or outstanding by Ofsted.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122625","122625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822943","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of (a) primary and (b) secondary age children in (i) the West Midlands and (ii) Coventry who attend a school rated (A) outstanding and (B) good by Ofsted.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122626","122626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822944","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry who are (i) eligible and (ii) not eligible for free school meals have achieved school readiness standards at the end of the Early Years Foundation Stage in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122627","122627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822945","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on an attack using chlorine gas in the Eastern Ghouta region of Syria on 13 January 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122628","122628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822946","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2017 to Question 117143, whether any redundancies made by contractors as a result of the implementation of Project Hestia have been funded in full or in part by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122629","122629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822947","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Administration on reports of an attack using chlorine gas in the Eastern Ghouta region of Syria on 13 January 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122630","122630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822948","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2017 to Question 118851, on Money Laundering, what steps he is taking within the reform to the SARs regime to drive up engagement with (a) Trust or Company Service Providers and (b) other reporting sectors on improvements to SAR reporting.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122631","122631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822949","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with officials from the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons on reports of an attack using chlorine gas in the Eastern Ghouta region of Syria on 13 January 2018; and what steps he plans to take to facilitate an investigation of such reports by the OPCW Fact-Finding Mission in Syria.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122632","122632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822950","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to raise the use of chemical weapons by the Government of Syria at the 87th Session of the Executive Council of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons in March 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122633","122633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822951","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2017 to Question 118852, on Money Laundering, how frequently and in relation to which comparative data are Companies House's systematic checks of the Companies Register conducted.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122634","122634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822952","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the email correspondence on an immigration case from the hon. Member for Aberavon dated 24 November 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122635","122635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822953","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2017 to Question 111729, on what dates Royal Parks expressed its support for locating in Victoria Tower Gardens (a) the Holocaust Memorial and (b) the Learning Centre; and if he will place in the Library copies of the communications from Royal Parks indicating that support.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122636","122636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822954","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2017 to Question 117268, on National Holocaust Memorial Centre and Learning Service, what conclusions the Government drew on visitor numbers to the proposed Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre from its comparative assessment of visitor numbers to Holocaust memorials around the world; and if he will place a copy of that comparative assessment in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122637","122637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822955","2018-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government will match the level of EU funding provided to British Overseas Territories after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122638","122638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822956","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2017 to Question 106183, concerning the number of visitors to the proposed Holocaust Memorial, if he will place in the Library a copy of the assessment commissioned from Barker Langham.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122639","122639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822957","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library, a copy of the letter from Lord Feldman of October 2015 proposing that the Holocaust Memorial be located in Victoria Tower Gardens, and a copy of his Department’s response of November 2015.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122640","122640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822958","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 20 December 2017 to Question 118847, what proportion of HM Revenue and Customs staff were engaged with their Learning Framework in the last 12 months; and which specialist areas those staff engaged with most frequently in that time period.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122641","122641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822959","2018-01-18","Scotland Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the effect of the liquidation of Carillion plc on jobs in Scotland.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122642","122642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822960","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support he will provide to those Scottish military sites which had planned to use Carillion facilities management contracts.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122643","122643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822961","2018-01-17","Scotland Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on finding a replacement organisation for facilities management of those military sites in Scotland which were due to be under Carillion facilities management.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122644","122644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822962","2018-01-18","Scotland Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on the cost of replacing Carillion facilities management of his Department's sites in Scotland.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122645","122645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822963","2018-01-17","Scotland Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the future of those jobs provided under the Carillion Scotland and Northern Ireland region contract.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122646","122646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822964","2018-01-18","Scotland Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on improving the provision of telecommunications services in rural Scotland.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122647","122647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822965","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas included letters from RBS confirming the business funds available to the applicant in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122648","122648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822966","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas included letters from Santander confirming the business funds available to the applicant in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122649","122649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822967","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas included letters from HSBC confirming the business funds available to the applicant in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122650","122650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822968","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas included letters from Lloyd's Bank confirming the business funds available to the applicant in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122651","122651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822969","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas included letters from Natwest confirming the business funds available to the applicant in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122652","122652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822970","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas included letters from Barclays confirming the business funds available to the applicant in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122653","122653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822971","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas included letters from Clydesdale Bank confirming the business funds available to the applicant in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122654","122654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822972","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas included letters from the Bank of Scotland confirming the business funds available to the applicant in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122655","122655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822973","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visas included letters from TSB confirming the business funds available to the applicant in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122656","122656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822974","2018-01-18","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, If she will investigate reports by the Road Haulage Association that French authorities are turning off heartbeat monitors at the French border; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122657","122657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822975","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2018 to Question 121612, what the cost to the public purse is of renaming of his Department.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122658","122658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822976","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of religious freedom in Turkey; and what steps the Government is taking to promote and protect the right to freedom of religion or belief in that country.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122659","122659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822977","2018-01-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has made an estimate of the number of people currently employed in the UK on testing products to ensure that they meet EU requirements.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122660","122660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822978","2018-01-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether it is his policy for Turkey to be included in any trade agreement reached with the EU.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122661","122661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822979","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many recommendations from the Farmer Review of the UK Constrction Model have been (a) fully and (b) partly accepted or implemented to date.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122662","122662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822980","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what powers he plans for the Tree Champion to have; what the annual budget of that champion will be; and to whom that champion will report.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122663","122663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822981","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has to mark the UN International Decade for People of African Descent.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122664","122664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822982","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons his Department was not represented at the UN Regional Meeting on People of African Descent of 23 to 24 November 2017 in Geneva.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122665","122665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822983","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what analysis his Department has undertaken of the financial viability of those construction companies that have won public procurement projects with a contract value of more than £5m in the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122666","122666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822984","2018-01-18","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information she holds on the number of Hezbollah (a) members and (b) supporters there are in the UK.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122667","122667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822985","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment has been made of the risk of contagion from the collapse of Carillion plc to other private companies and contracts in the public and private sector.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122668","122668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822986","2018-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress GovCoin, Barclays, RWE npower and University College London on behalf of the Department have made in developing technology that welfare claimants can easily adopt to handle their payments through a mobile app.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122669","122669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822987","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of schools which have contracts with Carillion plc; and what the value of those contracts is.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122670","122670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822988","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has assessed the feasibility of maintaining services provided by Carillion plc to schools by offering directly to employ former Carillion staff at schools.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122671","122671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822989","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to maintain services supplied by Carillion plc to local councils.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122672","122672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822990","2018-01-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of religious freedom in the Palestinian Territories; and what steps the Government is taking to promote and protect the right to freedom of religion or belief in that country.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122673","122673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822991","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent results have been achieved from medical research conducted by British and Israeli scientists through the Britain-Israel Research and Academic Exchange Partnership.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122674","122674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822992","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of women and men detained under the provisions of the Mental Health Act 1983 who were the primary carers of children in 2016-17.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122675","122675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822993","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 16 of the report of the Parliamentary and Health Services Ombudsman, Ignoring the alarms: how NHS eating disorder services are failing patients, HC 634, published on 6 December 2017, what steps he plans to take to tackle the significant geographical variation that report identifies in access to good quality specialist adult eating disorders services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122676","122676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822994","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the UK no longer having access to the EU portal and database through which all European clinical research is processed and stored after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122677","122677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822995","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an estimate of the value of early-phase research to the UK economy in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122678","122678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822996","2018-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to provide for the continuity of services supplied by Carillion plc to prisons.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122679","122679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822997","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to protect animal welfare standards in slaughterhouses after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122680","122680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822998","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what value of contracts awarded by Government departments to Carillion plc was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122681","122681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/822999","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help ensure that slaughterhouse vets who are non-UK EU citizens can continue to work here after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122682","122682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823000","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with officials regarding future payments of housing benefit to women's refuges.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122683","122683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823001","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the First Secretary of State, what the target time is for the Government to make payments to small and medium-sized enterprises; and (a) how many and (b) what percentage of payments by the Government met that target in 2017.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122684","122684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823002","2018-01-17","Scotland Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he has plans to visit a food bank in February 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122685","122685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823003","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support is available to families to repatriate a family member who dies abroad and for whom they cannot afford the cost of repatriation.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122686","122686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823004","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Re-entry Systems Options project has concluded its work.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122687","122687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823005","2018-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of people employed by Carillion plc at HMP Bedford.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122688","122688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823006","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of part-worn tyres imported into the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122689","122689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823007","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to (a) draw up contingency plans and (b) identify alternative suppliers to provide public services to schools in (i) Oxfordshire and (ii) England that are currently provided by Carillion.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122690","122690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823008","2018-01-18","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 115281, if he will place in the Library of the House of Commons every risk assessment relating to Government contracts secured by Carillion since January 2015.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122691","122691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823009","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the fail rate of tyres on vehicles stopped by the Vehicle and Operator Services Agency during roadside spot checks.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122692","122692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823010","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward proposals to increase minimum tyre depth treads to prevent used tyre imports and improve road safety.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122693","122693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823011","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) draw up contingency plans and (b) identify alternative suppliers to provide the public services to the NHS in (i) Oxfordshire and (ii) England that are currently provided by Carillion.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122694","122694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823012","2018-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what facilities management services are provided by Carillion plc at HMP Bedford.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122695","122695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823013","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have applied for continuing healthcare; and how many people have received such care since 2010.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122696","122696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823014","2018-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what dates contracts were awarded to Carillion plc in relation to HMP Bedford; and what the value of those contracts was.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122697","122697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823015","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will ensure that retired semi-submersible drilling rigs from the UK continental shelf are decommissioned in the UK.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122698","122698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823016","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the number of semi-submersible drilling rigs on the UK Continental Shelf which will be decommissioned in each year to 2025.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122699","122699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823017","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which facilities on the east coast of (a) Scotland and (b) England have the capacity to recycle steel and other material from decommissioned infrastructure from the offshore oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122700","122700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823018","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the UK has the capacity to (a) decommission, (b) recycle and (c) scrap the retired semi-submersible drilling rigs (i) Ocean Guardian, (ii) Ocean Princess and (iii) Ocean Nomad; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122701","122701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823019","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the number of jobs that will be created by the North Sea decommissioning market by 2025.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122702","122702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823020","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what guidance the Oil and Gas Authority provides to drilling companies on the decommissioning of semi-submersible drilling rigs.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122703","122703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823021","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the carbon footprint of the North Sea decommissioning market in each year to 2025.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122704","122704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823022","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pedicab riders have received cautions or arrests for the last twelve months for which records are available.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122705","122705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823023","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many civil penalties have been used by local authorities since their introduction in April 2017.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122706","122706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823024","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment the Government has made of the effectiveness of hostile vehicle mitigation measures in relation to pedicabs.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122707","122707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823025","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to extend mandatory licencing schemes for landlords in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122708","122708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823026","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department had made of amount of tax collected from self-employed pedicab riders in the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122709","122709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823027","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many procedural errors have been made in applications for leave to remain in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122710","122710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823028","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been affected by procedural errors in applications for leave to remain in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122711","122711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823029","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of procedural errors occurring in applications for leave to remain.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122712","122712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823030","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many explanations and apologies have been issued to people affected by procedural errors in applications for leave to remain in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122713","122713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823031","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how long her Department has taken to clarify with each person affected by procedural errors in application for leave to remain in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122714","122714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823032","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people applying for leave to remain have been asked to pay an additional fee for the Immigration Health Surcharge after paying the full amount for the application in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122715","122715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823033","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department’s policy is on refunding people who have overpaid for their application for leave to remain.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122716","122716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823034","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many IS.96 notices have been incorrectly sent to individuals who have not had their applications for leave to remain refused in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122717","122717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823035","2018-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on whether any staff employed by Carillion plc at HMP Bedford have been served notice since 1 January 2017.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122718","122718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823036","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what explanations were sent to individuals who were not refused leave to remain but were incorrectly sent IS.96 notices in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122719","122719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823037","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken by her Department to contact people who were incorrectly sent an IS.96 notice in each of the last five years was.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122720","122720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823038","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many accidents involving pedicabs have been reported in each of the last three years; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce accidents involving those vehicles.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122721","122721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823039","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of IS.96 notices that are sent in error.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122722","122722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823040","2018-01-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the proposed energy price cap will end the surcharge on energy bills for the Highlands.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122723","122723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823041","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how he categorises different submissions that have been made through the Companies House's register of companies Report It feature; and what submissions he has received by category through that feature since its launch.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122724","122724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823042","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) passenger (b) roll-on roll-off passenger ships registered on the Paris MoU on Port State Control’s White List have been detained  by Maritime and Coastguard Agency inspectors for breaches of Standards in Title 2, Conditions of Employment in the Maritime Labour Convention, to date; and under what flag each such vessel was registered.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122725","122725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823043","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many general cargo ships registered on the Paris MoU on Port State Control’s White List have been detained by Maritime and Coastguard Agency inspectors for breaches of Standards in Title 2, Conditions of Employment in the Maritime Labour Convention, to date; and under what flag each such vessel was registered.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122726","122726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823044","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many bulk carriers registered on the Paris MoU on Port State Control’s White List have been detained by Maritime and Coastguard Agency inspectors for breaches of Standards in Title 2, Conditions of Employment in the Maritime Labour Convention, to date; and under what flag each such vessel was registered.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122727","122727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823045","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many offshore supply vessels registered on the Paris MoU on Port State Control’s White List have been detained by Maritime and Coastguard Agency inspectors for breaches of Standards in Title 2, Conditions of Employment in the Maritime Labour Convention, to date; and under what flag each such vessel was registered.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122728","122728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823046","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to improve the opportunities for NHS staff to receive on-going education and training; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122729","122729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823047","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take as a result of reported violations of the South Sudan cessation of hostilities agreement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122730","122730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823048","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) chemical and (b) oil tankers registered on the Paris MoU on Port State Control’s White List have been detained by Maritime and Coastguard Agency inspectors for breaches of Standards in Title 2, Conditions of Employment in the Maritime Labour Convention, to date; and under what flag each such vessel was registered.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122731","122731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823049","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the ability of humanitarian aid to access South Sudan since the 9 November 2017 order from President Salva Kiir Mayardit on that access.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122732","122732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823050","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the number of non-clinical, non-patient facing staff who are employed in the NHS; and what proportion of those staff were employed in the NHS in (a) England and (b) Gloucestershire in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122733","122733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823051","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was for A&E at Arrowe Park Hospital in Wirral in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122734","122734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823052","2018-01-17","Attorney General","2018-01-15","To ask the Attorney General, how many sentences have been successfully appealed under the Unduly Lenient Sentences Scheme in each year for which statistics are available.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122735","122735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823053","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who the members of the Government’s official delegations were at all meetings of the International Maritime Organisation’s Marine Environment Protection Committee since May 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122736","122736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823054","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy,  what discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues on the inclusion of the shipping industry in the UN Framework Agreement on climate change.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122737","122737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823055","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new businesses have been started in (a) Swindon and (b) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122738","122738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823056","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what sum his Department has spent on the UK space sector since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122739","122739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823057","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total value of goods and services procured from companies in Swindon by (a) all Government departments, and (b) all public bodies was in 2017.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122740","122740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823058","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many disabled people joined the Civil Service Fast Stream in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122741","122741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823059","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, (a) how many and (b) what percentage of ambulances arriving at Arrowe Park hospital in Wirral exceeded the 30-minute wait target in each of the past 12 months.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122742","122742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823060","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to display the annual cash value of changes in income tax on PAYE pay slips.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122743","122743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823061","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) North Swindon constituency, (b) Swindon, (c) England and (d) the UK were (i) removed from paying income tax and (ii) paid reduced income tax as a result of increases to the personal allowance in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122744","122744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823062","2018-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to assess the accuracy of rates of (a) access and (b) take-up for superfast broadband.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122745","122745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823063","2018-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of people using public libraries in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122746","122746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823064","2018-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the BBC on the introduction of subscription for non-core services provided by that corporation.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122747","122747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823065","2018-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to support the arts sector to become self-funding and financially sustainable.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122748","122748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823066","2018-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of progress on the targets set out in Sporting Futures: a new strategy for an active nation, published in December 2015.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122749","122749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823067","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many elective operations were cancelled at Arrowe Park Hospital in Wirral in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122750","122750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823068","2018-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) men and (b) women regularly participated in sport in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122751","122751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823069","2018-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many people aged (a) under 18 and (b) over 18 regularly participated in sport in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122752","122752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823070","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time for A&E at Arrowe Park Hospital in Wirral was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122753","122753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823071","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will make it a condition of any new school funding agreement that the school in question must make its sports facilities available for public use outside the school day.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122754","122754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823072","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much schools in (a) North Swindon constituency and (b) Swindon have received in Pupil Premium in each year since it was established.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122755","122755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823073","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much schools in (a) North Swindon constituency, (b) Swindon and (c) England have received in Sport Premium in each year since it was established.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122756","122756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823074","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Palestinian Authority on accepting Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu's invitation to return to direct peace negotiations without preconditions.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122757","122757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823075","2018-01-18","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many live contracts Government Departments and agencies have with Carillion, including all Carillion’s subsidiary companies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122758","122758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823076","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the processes in place to prevent the misuse of reconstruction material in Gaza.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122759","122759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823077","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which regulations govern the rental of houseboats; and whether he plans to amend those regulations.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122760","122760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823078","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy of the Medical Technology Group’s 2017 report, Keeping Britain Working: how medical technology can help reduce the cost of ill health to the UK economy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122761","122761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823079","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to broaden the scope of NICE guidance to include social care spending.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122762","122762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823080","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the extent to which NHS organisations comply with NICE guidance.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122763","122763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823081","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 Jan 2018 to Question 121068, on NHS logos, who paid the fees on each occasion; and for what purpose those fees were paid.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122764","122764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823082","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 Jan 2018 to Question 121068, on NHS logos, what his Department’s policy is when the logo is used without permission.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122765","122765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823083","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many winding-up orders HMRC has issued in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122766","122766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823084","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much solar energy has been contracted under the contract for difference scheme since 2015.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122767","122767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823085","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons a second pot 1 auction has not taken place under the contract for difference scheme; and what plans he has to conduct such a second pot 1 auction.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122768","122768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823086","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many planning inspectorate decisions there were in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available; and what proportion of those decision were found in favour of the applicant.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122769","122769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823087","2018-01-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the level of Government investment there was for arts and culture in Ellesmere Port & Neston constituency in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122770","122770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823088","2018-01-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, Communities and Local Government, how many public health funerals took place in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122771","122771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823089","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much compensation was paid to prisoners in respect of prison health issues in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122772","122772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823090","2018-01-18","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to every contract that the Government currently has with Carillion and its subsidiary companies: (a) when the contract was awarded; (b) which Department or agency awarded the contract; (c) how much the contract is worth; and (d) whether the contract is a joint venture.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122773","122773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823091","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that planned maintenance to service family accommodation at Leuchars Station is not be affected by the difficulties facing Carillion plc.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122774","122774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823092","2018-01-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take to reassure service families at Leuchars Station that accommodation improvement plans will not be affected by the difficulties facing Carillion plc.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122775","122775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823093","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people were in (a) short-term and (b) long-term supported housing on the most recent date for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122776","122776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823094","2018-01-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse of providing housing benefit for people in (a) short-term and (b) long-term supported housing was in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122777","122777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823095","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons he has proposed the introduction of different systems to fund short-term and long-term supported housing.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122778","122778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823096","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average cost was to a local authority of preparing for and supporting Ofsted in conducting the Single Inspection Framework for Children's Services in 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122779","122779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823097","2018-01-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the economic effect of reducing the maximum stake on fixed odds betting terminals (FOBTs) taking account of gains elsewhere in the economy from spending diverted from FOBTs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122780","122780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823098","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what duty is placed on inspectors under the Single Inspection Framework for Local Authority Children's Services to (a) observe social workers in practice and (b) speak with (i) children, (ii) parents and (iii) carers inclusive of foster carers.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122781","122781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823099","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research has been done by his Department into the levels of temporary labour and agency workers from the EEA in food processing and agriculture; and whether his Department plans to commission further research on this topic.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122782","122782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823100","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether an external evaluation has been completed on the Single Inspection Framework for local authority children's services departments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122783","122783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823101","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, by what means Departments select hold music for Government telephone services.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122784","122784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823102","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will include Cornish as an ethnicity in the 2021 census.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122785","122785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823103","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what processes his Department has in place to make sure that patients access the correct health services to reduce unnecessary A&E admissions.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122786","122786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823104","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the use of blockchain technology on strengthening security for patient information and medical files.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122787","122787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823105","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will mandate junior doctors to work in the NHS for at least one year after completion of training.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122788","122788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823106","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue was raised for the public purse from the stamp duty levy on second homes in the financial year 2016-17.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122789","122789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823107","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in frequency and scale of algal blooms on the health of the marine environment in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122790","122790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823108","2018-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of instances of a people aged 18 or under being held in solitary confinement in the youth secure estate in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122791","122791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823109","2018-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect on mental health of prisoners of being held in solitary confinement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122792","122792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823110","2018-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's policy is on the use of solitary confinement within the youth secure estate.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122793","122793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823111","2018-01-18","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Oral Answer to the Honourable Member for Ogmore of 15 January, 2018, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that local authorities are reimbursed for costs incurred by continuing services that were provided by Carillion.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122794","122794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823112","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will provide a list of the local authorities contacted by his Department following the liquidation of Carillion plc; and on what dates those local authorities were so contacted.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122795","122795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823113","2018-01-18","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in other EU member states on the implications for their own contributions of reports that the US Administration will reduce its contribution to the UN Works and Relief Agency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122796","122796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823114","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 22 December 2017 to Question 120096, on Tobacco, what informal or other communication his Department has had with those groups; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122797","122797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823115","2018-01-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of Carillion's remaining outstanding liabilities to the local government sector.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122798","122798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823116","2018-01-18","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to  publish her Department's position on the UN Global Compact for Migration.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122799","122799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823117","2018-01-18","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with officials in the US Administration on the decision of that Administration to withdraw from UN negotiations on the Global Compact for Migration.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122800","122800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823118","2018-01-18","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help meet the United Nations Development Programme's Sustainable Development Goal 2 on zero hunger.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122801","122801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823119","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications of the collapse of Carillion plc on (a) the current rail electrification works between Blackpool and Preston and (b) the continuation of line improvements between Blackpool and Manchester.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122802","122802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823120","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprentices are employed by Carillion plc in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122803","122803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823121","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money was allocated to Carillion plc from the public purse to deliver apprenticeships in 2017-18.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122804","122804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823122","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that all Carillion plc apprentices are able to complete their apprenticeship qualifications.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122805","122805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823123","2018-01-18","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to support the UN Relief and Works Agency to provide aid and services to Palestinian refugees following the announcement by the US Administration of a reduction in its contribution to that agency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122806","122806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823124","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December to Question 118739, on Pupil Premium, what steps his Department is taking to make the free school meal registration process more efficient.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122807","122807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823125","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations her Department has made to the US Administration on its proposal to reduce funding to the UN Relief and Works Agency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122808","122808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823126","2018-01-18","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2017 to Question 111278, on Cabinet Office procurement, whether he now has an estimate of the value on contracts awarded to Carillion.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122809","122809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823127","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of religious freedom in Kazakhstan; and what steps the Government is taking to promote and protect the right to freedom of religion or belief in that country.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Dame Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122810","122810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823128","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2017 to Question 119088, how his Department measures food insecurity.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122811","122811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823129","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support post-hurricane relief in the the British Virgin Islands and Anguilla.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122812","122812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823130","2018-01-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of tree planting rates in urban areas to counter air pollution.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122813","122813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823131","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 15 January 2018, HCWS401, on Tax-Free Childcare, for what reason the number of users of 30-hours of childcare does not match the number released by the Department for Education in its Management information on the number of 30 hours free childcare codes issued and validated for the spring term 2018.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122814","122814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823132","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to boost tourism and other sustainable development projects on Pitcairn Islands.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122815","122815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823133","2018-01-18","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of users have experienced technical glitches when using the Childcare Choices website since its creation.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122816","122816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823134","2018-01-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to retain EU nationals working in the NHS.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122817","122817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823135","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what preparations her Department is making to provide humanitarian assistance to the Philipines in the event of the eruption of the Mayon volcano.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122818","122818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823136","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made any assessment of the effect on development of basic income trials taking place in Namibia.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122819","122819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823137","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her Chinese counterpart on the extent of China's future role in global development finance.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122820","122820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823138","2018-01-18","Wales Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if his Department will ensure that the number of apprenticeships funded in Wales through EU funding programmes is matched by the number of apprenticeships funded in Wales under the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122821","122821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823139","2018-01-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment her Department has made of the financial viability of amateur sports clubs involved in (a) cycling, (b) rugby and (c) football.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122822","122822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823140","2018-01-18","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of establishing and maintaining the Office for Students in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122823","122823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823141","2018-01-18","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Written Statement of 27 November 2017, HCWS269, how many crimes or recorded incidents involved drones flying above 400 feet in 2017.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122824","122824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823142","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to monitor the (a) use and (b) spending of UK aid in the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122825","122825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823143","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that UK aid to the Palestinian Authority does not fund radicalisation.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122826","122826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823144","2018-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122827","122827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823145","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122828","122828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823146","2018-01-17","Home Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many ministerial directions were issued to her Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122829","122829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823147","2018-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122830","122830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823148","2018-01-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122831","122831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823149","2018-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122832","122832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823150","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122833","122833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823151","2018-01-17","Department for International Trade","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122834","122834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823152","2018-01-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122835","122835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823153","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122836","122836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823154","2018-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many ministerial directions were issued to her Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122837","122837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823155","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122838","122838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823156","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122839","122839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823157","2018-01-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122840","122840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823158","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many ministerial directions were issued to her Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122841","122841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823159","2018-01-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122842","122842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823160","2018-01-17","Attorney General","2018-01-15","To ask the Attorney General, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122843","122843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823161","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122844","122844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823162","2018-01-17","Northern Ireland Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many ministerial directions were issued to her Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122845","122845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823163","2018-01-17","Scotland Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122846","122846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823164","2018-01-17","Wales Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122847","122847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823165","2018-01-17","Cabinet Office","2018-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many ministerial directions were issued to his Department in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122848","122848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823166","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the humanitarian situation in Kurdish-controlled northern Syria.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122849","122849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823167","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the coordination of emergency relief across Yemen.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122850","122850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/823168","2018-01-17","Department for International Development","2018-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of supporting basic income models in developing countries through International Development spending.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122851","122851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/820891","2018-01-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether UK businesses will be required to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (2016/679) after 25 May 2018.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122309","122309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821463","2018-01-16","HM Treasury","2018-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made by his Department on its proposed consultation on off-payroll working rules in the private sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122381","122381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821464","2018-01-16","HM Treasury","2018-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to review entitlement to employee benefits as part of his Department's proposed consultation on off-payroll working rules in the private sector.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122382","122382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821465","2018-01-16","HM Treasury","2018-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that his Department's proposed consultation on off-payroll working rules in the private sector includes proactive consultation with UK businesses, people and organisations directly affected by those rules.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122383","122383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821466","2018-01-16","HM Treasury","2018-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer,  if he will prioritise a review of the accuracy of the IR35 Digital Tool known as CEST as part of his Department's proposed consultation on off-payroll working rules in the private sector.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122384","122384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821467","2018-01-16","Home Office","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of hate crimes that have been reported to police in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122385","122385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821468","2018-01-16","Home Office","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to run a consultation on the proposed Domestic Violence and Abuse Bill.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122386","122386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821469","2018-01-16","Home Office","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the findings of the recent report from the Higher Education Policy Institute on the financial contribution of overseas students and staff; and if she will review the classification of students in immigration statistics as a result of those findings.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122387","122387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821470","2018-01-16","Department for International Trade","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade,  if he will make it a precondition for any increase in trade between the UK and Iran that the Government of Iran adheres to international human rights norms by allowing peaceful demonstrations and protests against its policies.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122388","122388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821471","2018-01-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the metro-mayor system from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122389","122389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821472","2018-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions in the last 12 months have prison staff from prisons in England had to cover staff shortages at HMP Swansea.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122390","122390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821473","2018-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions in the last 12 months have prison staff from prisons in England had to cover staff shortages at HMP Cardiff.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122391","122391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821474","2018-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions in the last 12 months have prison staff from prisons in England had to cover staff shortages at HMP Parc.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122392","122392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821475","2018-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions in the last 12 months have prison staff from prisons in England had to cover staff shortages at HMP Usk/Prescoed.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122393","122393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821476","2018-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions since opening have prison staff from prisons in England had to cover staff shortages at HMP Berwyn.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122394","122394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821477","2018-01-16","HM Treasury","2018-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of low productivity growth since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122395","122395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821478","2018-01-17","Department for Transport","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on passengers living outside of East Anglia of the advertising the new 26-30 railcard pilot for East Anglian residents on train booking websites while that scheme is in the trial period.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122396","122396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821479","2018-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to integrate health and social care policy.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122397","122397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821480","2018-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what cooperation programmes his Department has with the Government of Israel for research and trade in the agricultural sector and what assessment he has made of the potential for future collaboration in that sector after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122398","122398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821481","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the six week postnatal GP appointment for new mothers is a full check on the mother's physical and mental health in addition to a separate appointment on the health of the newborn child.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122399","122399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821482","2018-01-17","Department for Education","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many authorised pupil absences for illness were there in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in each (i) spring term and (ii) autumn term in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122400","122400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821483","2018-01-16","Home Office","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether holders of a biometric residence permit can have special characters such as an apostrophe in their name recorded in those documents as is already permitted with passports.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122401","122401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821484","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many non-UK EU nationals were employed by the NHS in cardiology in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122402","122402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821485","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many non-UK EU nationals were employed by the NHS in dermatology in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122403","122403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821486","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many non-UK EU nationals were employed by the NHS in neurology in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122404","122404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821487","2018-01-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many non-UK EU nationals were employed by the NHS in gynaecology in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122405","122405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821488","2018-01-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many non-UK EU nationals were employed by the NHS in children’s services in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122406","122406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821489","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average monthly amount is that (a) parents and (b) the Government has paid into tax free childcare accounts since those account were introduced.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122407","122407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821490","2018-01-17","HM Treasury","2018-01-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families with disabled children have registered for a tax free childcare account.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122408","122408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821491","2018-01-16","Department for Education","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what due diligence was carried out during the appointment process for board members for the Office for Students.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122409","122409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/821492","2018-01-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether any journalist has been given access by his Department to non-public Market Access reports pertaining to the UK’s withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122410","122410"
