"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001917","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to promote the export of British game meat.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188117","188117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001918","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether officials in his Department have had discussions with the Scottish Government on the (a) Patient and Clinician Engagement system, (b) its effect on approval rates for new rare disease medicines in Scotland and (c) potential lessons from that system for NHS England.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188233","188233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001919","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 4.12 the UK Rare Diseases Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of whether the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence’s Single Technology Appraisal Programme meets the ambition of suitability for assessing rare disease treatments.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188234","188234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001920","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of providing support to  to steel companies for the construction of electric arc furnaces on Teesside; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188118","188118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001921","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will set out the timeframe for implementing her Department's response to the court judgement of June 2018 on the payment of Severe Disability Premium to claimants who are already in receipt of Universal Credit.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188119","188119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001922","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that a claimant will not receive less money in benefits as a result of moving to universal credit under the managed migration process.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188120","188120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001923","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2018 to Question 183583 on Health Service: Prisons, whether the Under-Secretary of State for Health met healthcare professionals on her visits to HMP Chelmsford.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188121","188121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001924","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October to Question 183513 on Health Services: Prisons, where the Under-Secretary of State for Health met the providers who are responsible for healthcare services at HMP Liverpool.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188122","188122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001925","2018-11-12","Department for International Development","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether UK official development assistance supports the work of agencies cited for human rights abuses in the October 2018 Human Rights Watch report Two authorities, one way, zero dissent.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188039","188039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001926","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Tunisia on the closure of its Truth and Dignity Commission; and what steps he is taking to encourage that Government to fulfill its promises of justice for victims of human rights abuses under the previous regime.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188040","188040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001927","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether provision was made in the July 2018 agreement on natural gas with the Cameroon Government for the allocation of revenues from that deal to improve the lives of Cameroon's poorest people.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188041","188041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001928","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will publish its map of women's centres and rape crisis centres.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188123","188123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001929","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what resources his Department has allocated to fund (a) magistrates and (b) judges visiting women's centres since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188124","188124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001930","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what resources his Department provided to fund the production and distribution of information on women's centres for (a) magistrates and (b) judges since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188125","188125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001931","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions the illegal use of drones in the vicinity of the prison estate has resulted in convictions in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188007","188007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001932","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children under the age of 15 were convicted in youth courts in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188008","188008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001933","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the level of fine was for each successful prosecution of an employer paying an employee less than the minimum wage in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188009","188009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001934","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government was informed about allegations of violations of electoral law against (a) Vote Leave and BeLeave and (b) Leave.EU by (i) the police and (ii) any other public service.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187981","187981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001935","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what target he has set for investment in research and development in the aviation and aerospace industries.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188126","188126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001936","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial support he has made available to schools for the commemoration of the centenary of Armistice Day.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187991","187991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001937","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department provides to (a) primary and (b) secondary schools on the amount of financial education that should be provided to students.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187992","187992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001938","2018-11-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2018 to Question 907182 on Defence: Scotland, if he will estimate the total defence spending by (a) current and (b) capital expenditure in Scotland in each year for which information is available since 2010-11.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188235","188235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001939","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 183310 on Vote Leave: Election Offences, what steps he has taken as a result of the findings of the report of the Electoral Commission into the activities of Vote Leave.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188042","188042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001940","2018-11-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2018 to Question 907182 on Defence: Scotland, how much of the £1.592 billion of his Department's expenditure in 2016-17 was spent on (a) maritime, (b) land and (c) air equipment.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188236","188236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001941","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the sustainability of the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action with Iran.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187993","187993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001942","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in the north of Nigeria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187994","187994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001943","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with his counterparts in the US Administration on the US trade embargo of Cuba.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187995","187995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001944","2018-11-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to decide whether to raise the limit on prize values for the Health Lottery .","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188237","188237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001945","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 September on Quadrennial valuations of the public service pension schemes, HCWS945, whether (a) he and (b) the Minister of State for Policing and the Fire Service held discussions with (i) the Chief Secretary to the Treasury and (ii) the Chancellor of the Exchequer prior to that Statement's publication on the implications of those valuations on policing.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188127","188127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001946","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of lengthening the period that a funding settlement covers for (a) local policing and (b) Counter-Terror policing.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188128","188128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001947","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the EU Mortgage Credit Directive on access to lower mortgage rates.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187982","187982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001948","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of giving asylum seekers the right to work after six months.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188238","188238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001949","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if his Department will publish (a) the actions, (b) the minutes and (c) any completed actions of the Serious Violence Taskforce relating to the minutes of that taskforce's meetings on (i) 11 June 2018, (ii) 17 July 2018 and (iii) 22 October 2018.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188129","188129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001950","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help prevent cases of secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188239","188239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001951","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2018 to Question 177313 on Driving under Influence, and with reference to the 2017 Institute of Alcohol Studies report Running on empty: Drink driving law enforcement in England which found that the number of breath tests performed reduced by one quarter between 2011 and 2015, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of rigorous enforcement and serious penalties for drink drivers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188130","188130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001952","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to increase the number of private prisons.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188131","188131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001953","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of cancer clinical nurse specialists in (a) England , (b) London and (c) the London Borough of Lewisham.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188240","188240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001954","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the 2019 Loan Charge on individuals that had made financial plans on the basis of previous arrangements; and what support he is able to provide to those individuals.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188241","188241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001955","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department to include vets on the shortage occupation list.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188242","188242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001956","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to include vets on the shortage occupation list.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188243","188243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001957","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of vets required in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188244","188244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001958","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what changes to the rabies regime he plans for domestic pets crossing the UK's borders in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188245","188245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001959","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether officials in (a) his Department and (b) the Indonesian Embassy have met the non-governmental organizations (i) Tapol and (ii) Etan to discuss human rights in West Papua.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188246","188246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001960","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to ensure that the Red Ensign is flown at British ports after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188010","188010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001961","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people (a) currently and (b) previously working on developing the Common Platform Programme have had past employment with Agilesphere.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187996","187996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001962","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his speech to the APCC and NPCC joint summit 2018, published on gov.uk on 31 October 2018, what meetings he has held with police leaders to seek to build a smarter and better police system which is more collaborative, more innovative, more tech-savvy and less fragmented.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188132","188132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001963","2018-11-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the Royal Navy’s autonomous mine warfare capabilities.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188247","188247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001964","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his statement of 31 October 2018 to the APCC and NPCC joint summit that there needs to be more of an emphasis on crime prevention, what research his Department holds on the effect of a reduction in police resources on the levels of proactive policing.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188133","188133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001965","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many sites currently provide the HPV vaccine to gay and bisexual men by region.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188248","188248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001966","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the uptake has been of the HPV vaccine for gay and bisexual men by region since April 2018.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188249","188249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001967","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled Taking our health for granted: Plugging the public health grant funding gap, published in October 2018, if he will make an assessment of the effect of reductions to sexual health budgets highlighted in that report.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188043","188043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001968","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the radical upgrade in prevention discussed in the NHS Five Year Forward View of October 2014 has been achieved.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188044","188044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001969","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled Taking our health for granted: Plugging the public health grant funding gap, published in October 2018, whether he plans to increase central government funding for local authority public health services as a result of that report.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188045","188045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001970","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the uninterrupted supply of veterinary vaccines in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187984","187984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001971","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which farming sectors his Department has identified as most at risk from a potential shortage of veterinary medicines in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187985","187985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001972","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that policy to improve the health of livestock is a) included in the Agriculture Bill, and b) effectively implemented.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187986","187986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001973","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184372 on Optical Fibres: Non-domestic Rates, what estimate his Department has made of the income for the public purse from rates on (a) new build (b) the existing stock of all fixed and mobile telecommunications infrastructure for each year for which his Department has such projections.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188011","188011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001974","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Birmingham City Council is planned to receive any funding from central government to implement the measures in the Local Cycling and Walking Infrastructure Plan.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187997","187997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001975","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to monitor emissions from shale gas sites once they have been decommissioned.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188134","188134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001976","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful applications for exceptional case funding were made in relation to an application for refugee family reunion in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188250","188250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001977","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing providing legal aid support to potentially trafficked people to ensure that they are able to make an informed decision on whether to enter the National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188251","188251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001978","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential air quality effects of shale gas extraction since the completion of the Air Quality Expert Group report n that subject in 2015.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188135","188135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001979","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the waste water disposal system at the Preston New Road Shale Gas site.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188136","188136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001980","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what comparative assessment his Department has made of geological activity in Fylde (a) since the commencement of exploratory drilling at the Preston New Road Shale Gas site and (b) prior to such drilling.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188137","188137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001981","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled Fair funding for mental health: Putting parity into practice, published by the Institute for Public Policy Research in October 2018, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the finding in that report on the additional funding required for mental health care.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187998","187998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001982","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment the Environment Agency has made of the level of compliance by Cuadrilla Resources with relevant environmental restrictions at its shale gas site at Preston New Road.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188138","188138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001983","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of service cancellations by Northern Rail since April 2018; and what assessment he has made of the effect of those service cancellations on passenger outcomes.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188139","188139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001984","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to hold Northern Rail to account for its level of service performance.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188140","188140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001985","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Northern Rail on recent timetable problems.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188141","188141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001986","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what comparative assessment he has made of the average amount of time taken for (a) probation officers and (b) other public sector employees to reach the top of the pay scale.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188252","188252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001987","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the allocation of funds to the probation service since the probation service was combined with the prison service.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188253","188253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001988","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to amend the regulations on the sale or use of fireworks (a) to reduce the maximum decibel level of fireworks purchasable by the general public and (b) encourage the use of low noise fireworks.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188142","188142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001989","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much it will cost to users to use the enhanced user-pay service in 50 local libraries as part of the new UK Visa and Citizenship Application Services.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188143","188143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001990","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether members of the legal profession and the judiciary were (a) consulted as part of the review of the (i) civil legal aid means test threshold in 2008 and (ii) criminal legal aid means test threshold in 2009 and (b) consulted when the government has evaluated the legal aid means test thresholds since those dates.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188144","188144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001991","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate the Government has made of the cost to the Ministry of Justice budget of the increased number of litigants in person as a result of the means test threshold not being uprated in line with inflation in (a) civil legal aid since 2008 and (b) criminal legal aid since 2009.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188145","188145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001992","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful applications for exceptional case funding were made in relation to an application for refugee family reunion in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188146","188146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001993","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing providing legal aid support to potentially trafficked people to ensure that they are able to make an informed decision on whether to enter the National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188147","188147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001994","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.60 of the Budget 2018 Red Book, whether the funding for state-funded schools to cover pension costs will be allocated from the £4.7bn extra DEL in the reserve for 2019-20.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188148","188148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001995","2018-11-12","Department for International Development","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to attend the Gavi mid-term review meeting in Abu Dhabi in December 2018.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188149","188149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001996","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress has been made on securing healthcare agreements with the EU similar to those set out in EU Regulations (a) 883/2004 and (b) 987/2009.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187987","187987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001997","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent progress has been made on securing UK participation in the plurilateral Government Procurement Agreement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187988","187988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001998","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October to Question 176664 on Public Health England: Drinkaware Trust, for what reason it was decided that Public Health England would not consult its Alcohol Leadership Board before beginning a partnership with Drinkaware.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188254","188254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1001999","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will place in the Library a copy of the terms of reference for the Public Health England Alcohol Leadership Board.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188255","188255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002000","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of recent concerns raised by British public health academics on the potential threat to Public Health England’s reputation of partnering with an alcohol industry-funded body.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188256","188256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002001","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2018 to Question 179178, on Cannabis: Misuse, whether the results of the monitoring of cannabis seized by The National Crime Agency in (a) 2005, (b) 2008 and (c) 2016 concurred with the findings of the research on the strength of cannabis covering that same time period by King’s College London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188046","188046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002002","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether there is provision in place to equalise universal credit entitlement when a couple separates.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188012","188012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002003","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department takes to ensure that there is a fair division when recovering advance payments when a couple separate.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188013","188013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002004","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department take steps to ensures that the remaining claimant of universal credit is not held fully responsible for unpaid advance payments when a couple separates.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188014","188014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002005","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under Section 8 of the Animal Welfare Act 2006 in each police force area in each year between 2007 and 2012.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188015","188015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002006","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) proceeded against under and (b) convicted of dog fighting offences in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188016","188016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002007","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful applications for exceptional case funding were made in relation to an application for refugee family reunion in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188150","188150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002008","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing providing legal aid support to potentially trafficked people to ensure that they are able to make an informed decision on whether to enter the National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188151","188151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002009","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps have been taken to help ensure that Bahraini female political prisoners Hajer Mansoor, Medina Ali, and Najah Yusuf will be protected from reprisals when their case is raised at the (a) UK Parliament and (b) United Nations.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188257","188257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002010","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to authorities in Bahrain on the restrictions on (a) phone calls, (b) family visits and (c) allocated time outside the cell imposed on female political prisoners in Isa Town Prison.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188258","188258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002011","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to protest the Tanzanian government’s recent steps against gay citizens; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187989","187989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002012","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has made of the safety needs of horse riders for the Highway Code review.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188047","188047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002013","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his department will make an assessment of the potential merits of developing guidance on achieving permanence for (a) looked after children and young people and (b) people with special educational needs and disabilities; and whether such permanence is defined as a core purpose of children’s social care.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188259","188259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002014","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff Border Force has in place to deal with any expected additional workload at the port of Holyhead after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188017","188017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002015","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of developing a national outcomes framework to benchmark all children’s services provision on (a) value, (b) quality, (c) cost and (c) outcomes.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188260","188260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002016","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of  the potential merits of reinstating the Commissioning Support Programme; and whether his Department plans to develop an improved programme to support children’s services commissioners.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188261","188261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002017","2018-11-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many new recruits have been offered a place in the (a) Army, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Royal Air Force in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187999","187999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002018","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) applications it will receive for European Conference of Ministers of Transport multilateral road haulage permits and (b) the number of European Conference of Ministers of Transport permits that will be available to UK hauliers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188152","188152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002019","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how the status of women and the promotion of women’s rights are planned to be factored into the UK's Economic Partnership Agreements.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188048","188048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002020","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the UK’s trading arrangements with developing countries.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188049","188049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002021","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of potential challenges for producers exporting goods to the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188050","188050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002022","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effect of leaving the EU on the export of Scottish goods and services.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188051","188051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002023","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department plans to undertake (a) gender, (b) human rights and (c) sustainability impact assessments for future trade agreements.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188052","188052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002024","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what ethical considerations are undertaken by his Department in relation to the sale of arms and munitions to other countries; and what steps his Department takes to vet the award of arms export licences.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188053","188053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002025","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to seek mutual recognition of geographical indicators with the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188054","188054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002026","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the economic importance of the UK’s trade with the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188055","188055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002027","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department plans to take to help businesses manage (a) administrative and (b) tariff changes in UK customs after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188056","188056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002028","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what types of munitions and arms have been traded to Saudi Arabia in each year since 2016.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188057","188057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002029","2018-11-12","Department for International Development","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2018 to Question 176532 on South Sudan: sexual offences, what steps her Department is taking to encourage aid workers in South Sudan to report sexual violence.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188153","188153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002030","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government news release of 1 October 2018 entitled Citizens Advice to provide support to Universal Credit claimants, how much funding she plans to allocate to Citizens Advice in Scotland to provide that support; and what plans she has to provide funding for areas that do not have a Citizens Advice office.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188154","188154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002031","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184392, on what date he plans to publish the PwC report on High Speed Two.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188155","188155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002032","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many adult (a) male and (b) female inpatient facilities are available for the treatment of anorexia nervosa, bulimia nervosa, binge-eating disorder and other specified feeding or eating disorders in (i) Lancashire and (ii) England.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188018","188018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002033","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people in England have been referred for BRCA1 and BRCA2 testing in each year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188156","188156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002034","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of Clinical Commissioning Groups fund family history clinics.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188157","188157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002035","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people her Department plans to migrate from employment support allowance to universal credit in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Birmingham, Edgbaston in (i) 2019-20, (ii) 2020-21, (iii) 2021-22 and (iv) 2022-23.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188158","188158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002036","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many hours of training is planned to be given to her Department's decision-makers to identify people who may be vulnerable or have complex needs for the purposes of the universal credit managed migration.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188159","188159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002037","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to introduce hydrogen-powered emission-free trains.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188058","188058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002038","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department takes to ensure that MOT tests are being conducted to a satisfactory standard.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188059","188059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002039","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of motorcycle licences issued in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188060","188060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002040","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has a policy on earlier diagnosis of dementia.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188061","188061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002041","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prevent patients from gaining commercially from prescriptions.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188062","188062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002042","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to help older people on low incomes who need supported accommodation.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188063","188063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002043","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has plans to require schools to provide advice on mental health to pupils.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188064","188064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002044","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2018 to Question 171423 on Speed Limits: Cameras, how much revenue has accrued to the public purse as a result of all forms of traffic enforcement in (a) the West Midlands (b) England and (c) the UK in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188160","188160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002045","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the his Department's consultation, E10 petrol, consumer protection and fuel pump labelling, published on 20 July 2018, for what reason that consultation did not consider the mandatory introduction of E10 fuels.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188161","188161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002046","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned £85 million cuts to local authority public health budgets for 2019-2020 on (a) access to sexual health services and (b) rates of sexually transmitted infections.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188162","188162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002047","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the consultation, E10 petrol, consumer protection and fuel pump labelling, published by his Department on 20 July 2018, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of combining a mandated introduction of E10 fuels with a scrappage scheme for incompatible vehicles.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188163","188163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002048","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the publication of the Government’s response to the  consultation entitled E10 petrol, consumer protection and fuel pump labelling, published by her Department on 20 July 2018.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188164","188164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002049","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on the feasibility of establishing an alternative mechanism for money transfers autonomous from the Society for Worldwide Interbank Financial Telecommunication.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188065","188065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002050","2018-11-12","Department for International Development","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department had allocated funding to the Oxfam-supported (a) water supply system and (b) cholera treatment centres in Yemen which were hit by Saudi coalition air strikes in (i) April and (ii) June 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188066","188066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002051","2018-11-12","Department for International Development","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many facilities and projects in Yemen in receipt of funding from her Department have been hit by Saudi coalition air strikes since the start of the conflict in that country in 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188067","188067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002052","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to table a resolution calling for (a) a humanitarian ceasefire and (b) the safe passage of food and other aid to Yemen at the UN Security Council this week.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188068","188068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002053","2018-11-12","Department for International Development","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the compliance with (a) Article 23 of the Fourth Geneva Convention and (b)  Rule 55 of the International Committee of the Red Cross’s Customary International Law Study of the restriction of supplies of food and medicine through the port of Hodeidah in Yemen.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188069","188069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002054","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the proportion of Saudi-led coalition air strikes in Yemen that hit non-military targets in September; and what proportion he considers indicative of a risk that those air strikes are being conducted indiscriminately.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188070","188070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002055","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Egyptian counterpart on the arrest of Huda Abdelmonem and eighteen other human rights activists in that country on 1 November.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188071","188071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002056","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Egyptian counterpart on the whereabouts of human rights lawyers Ezzat Ghoneim and Azzoz Maghoub.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188072","188072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002057","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Egyptian counterpart on reports of the arrest of Abdel Khalik Farouk and Ibrahim el-Khateib on 21 October 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188073","188073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002058","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how his department defines good outcomes for (a) children and young people with special educational needs and disabilities and (b) looked after children and young people; and if he will develop guidance on those outcomes for local authorities and providers.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188262","188262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002059","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Nigerian counterpart on reports of the use of live fire against peaceful Shia protestors in Abuja on 1 November 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188074","188074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002060","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Nigerian counterpart on the detention without trial of the leader of the Islamic Movement of Nigeria, Ibraheem El-Zakzaky, and his wife.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188075","188075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002061","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his US counterpart on President Trump’s proposed authorisation of the use of live fire against people throwing rocks at military personnel at the US border with Mexico.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188076","188076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002062","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the circumstances surrounding the death of United States missionary, Charles Wesco, in the town of Bamenda, Cameroon, on 30 October 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188077","188077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002063","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in Cameroon on the detention without charge of journalists Elvis McCarthy, Thomas Awah Junior, Michel Biem Tong, Tsi Conrad and Mancho Bibixy.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188078","188078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002064","2018-11-12","Women and Equalities","2018-11-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what plans she has to meet with civil society groups on measuring progress on Sustainable Development Goal five for the voluntary national review in 2019.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188165","188165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002065","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of (a) the effectiveness of the team around the child approach in children’s services provision and (b) whether that approach should be the default for children’s social care providers.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188263","188263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002066","2018-11-12","Women and Equalities","2018-11-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what consultations her Department has had with local authorities on the planned indicators to measure progress on Sustainable Development Goal five for the voluntary national review in 2019.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188166","188166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002067","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to conduct economic modelling on the effect of air passenger duty on the UK's global connectivity and competitiveness.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188167","188167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002068","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to (a) assess and (b) mitigate the risks that scrubber technology and its waste pose to the UK's coastal areas and marine ecosystem.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188168","188168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002069","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Airline Insolvency Review interim report, published by his Department on 12 July 2018, if he will make it his policy to (a) take steps in response to the final findings of the report and (b) take steps to set up a comprehensive model of insolvency and repatriation protection for consumers.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188169","188169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002070","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate the Government has made of the number of workless households in (a) Crawley constituency and (b) England.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188170","188170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002071","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what research his Department has commissioned on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on housing demand.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188019","188019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002072","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how his Department determines funding allocation levels for integration initiatives within communities.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188020","188020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002073","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of local authorities’ ability to (a) identify (i) current and (ii) future demand for children’s services and (b) supply the services demanded.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188264","188264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002075","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what financial support his Department provides to local authorities that serve coastal communities.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188022","188022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002076","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the announcement in Budget 2018, what his Department's timescale is for implementing school-based mental health support teams; and by what date he plans for mental health support teams to be extended across the country.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188023","188023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002077","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of young people who sleep rough and have spent time in foster care.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188024","188024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002078","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the announcement in Budget 2018, how much of the £400 million capital payment to schools will be allocated to schools in (a) Barnsley, (b) South Yorkshire and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188171","188171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002079","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 4.56 of the Budget 2018 Red Book, what estimate he has made of the number of new homes that will be built in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188172","188172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002080","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference paragraph 5.11 of Budget 2018 Red Book, how much and what proportion of the additional funding for air ambulance services will be allocated to South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188173","188173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002081","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the provision of  respiratory physiotherapy for (a) children and (b) adults with muscular dystrophy and neuromuscular conditions provided by (i) Leicester City Clinical Commissioning Group and (ii) University Hospitals of Leicester NHS Trust.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188000","188000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002082","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect young people who have suffered domestic violence and are homeless.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188025","188025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002083","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the total cost to the public purse is of new staff employed by his Department to assist in preparations for the UK leaving the EU since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188079","188079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002084","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2018 to Question 184876 on North Sea Oil, what assessment he has made of the effect of continued investment in new oil and gas on compliance with the timeframes set by the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change for the transition to a low-carbon economy.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188001","188001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002085","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support his Department provides to organisations that support people to stop smoking through the encouragement of the take-up of vaping.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188174","188174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002086","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the number of additional (a) child and adolescent psychiatrists, (b) psychotherapists and (c) mental health nurses that will be required to deliver school-based mental health support teams throughout England.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188026","188026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002087","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 5.10 of the Budget 2018 Red Book, what the (a) composition and (b) structure will be of the children and young people’s mental health crisis teams.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188027","188027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002088","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask the Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on low-income tenants of landlords adjust their rental prices in relation to section 24 of the Finance (No. 2) Act 2015.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188265","188265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002089","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has plans to improve the quality of social housing in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188266","188266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002090","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what contingency planning has been undertaken by his Department to ensure the maintenance of reciprocal health care arrangements between the UK and the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188028","188028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002091","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) schools, (b) hospitals and (c) care homes that are (i) clad and (ii) insulated with non-ACM combustible cladding materials.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188175","188175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002092","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has received applications to undertake fracking in (a) Ealing, Southall constituency, (b) Ealing local authority area and (c) Greater London.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188080","188080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002093","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 182295 on Renewable energy: feed-in tariffs, what estimate he has made of the additional cost to consumer bills from (a) photovoltaic and (b) non-photovoltaic installations through the export tariff of the feed-in-tariff in the financial year 2017-18.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188176","188176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002094","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many school fires involving combustible (a) cladding and (b) insulation have taken place in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188177","188177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002095","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the White Paper, Improving Lives  published in November 2017, when the funding for Jobcentre Plus Community Partners and additional Disability Employment Advisers is due to end; and whether the Department has plans to allocate additional funding for those initiatives.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188029","188029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002096","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has plans to undertake an assessment of the adequacy of the Jobcentre Plus Personalised Support Package for disabled people.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188030","188030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002097","2018-11-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his news release of 5 November Armed Forces to step up Commonwealth recruitment, whether the lifting of the five-year residency in the UK requirement for applicants who wish to serve in the armed forces will apply also to citizens of UK Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188178","188178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002098","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Home Office immigration removal charter flights have departed from Royal Air Force bases in the UK since June 2018; and what the (a) date of departure (b) name of the air base (c) (i) country or (ii) countries of destination (d) operational name of and (e) number of (i) removal directions issued for (ii) people removed on (iii) removal directions withdrawn from and (iv) criminal deportees on the flight was in each case.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188081","188081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002099","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of immigration removal charter flights departing from Royal Air Force bases in the UK since May 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188082","188082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002100","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many unqualified teachers work in schools in (a) Dulwich and West Norwood, (b) London and (c) England.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188179","188179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002101","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of teaching staff are unqualified in (a) maintained state, (b) academy and (c) free schools.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188180","188180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002102","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students in London schools have been taught by unqualified teachers in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188181","188181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002103","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's Advice Note 19, Advice for owners of buildings which include spandrel panels/ window panels/ infill panels, when the Government plans to publish the findings of its investigation into the risks of non-ACM combustible cladding materials.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188182","188182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002104","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's Advice Note 19, Advice for owners of buildings which include spandrel panels/ window panels/ infill panels, whether his Department has examined high-pressure laminate cladding as part of its investigation into the risks of non-ACM combustible cladding materials.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188183","188183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002105","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people in the (a) West Midlands and (b) England who experience Pathological Demand Avoidance.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188184","188184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002106","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2018 to Question 178321 on Railway signals, what assessment he has made of the merits of the ongoing use of the Intercity Express Programme Class 800/801 on the Great Western route following the Office for Rail and Road’s decision not to authorise the use of the same trains on the London and North Eastern Railway.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188185","188185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002107","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department remains the ministerial lead for the medicinal use of cannabis-based products.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188186","188186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002108","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department made prior to enactment of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 of the annual number of cases that would be funded as exceptional cases.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188187","188187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002109","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department made prior to the enactment of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 of the total annual cost of exceptional case funding after its enactment.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188188","188188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002110","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prisons have (a) healthcare and (b) drug rehabilitation and care services provided by private healthcare providers.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188189","188189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002111","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prisons have (a) healthcare and (b) drug rehabilitation and care services provided by NHS healthcare providers.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188190","188190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002112","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what was the total (a) expenditure (b) number of cases granted under exceptional case funding in each year following the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188191","188191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002113","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many inquests was legal aid granted in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188192","188192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002114","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the spend by (a) each Government department and (b) the Government on legal representation at inquests in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188193","188193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002115","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 184996 on Probation: Death, if he will provide that information for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188194","188194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002116","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) Northamptonshire police, (b) West Yorkshire police and (c) the National Police Chiefs' Council on the reduction of neighbourhood policing.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188195","188195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002117","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of updating the Highway Code to include the British Horse Society’s advice to drivers on how to pass horses safely on roads.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188196","188196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002118","2018-11-12","Attorney General","2018-11-05","To ask the Attorney General, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in the (a) Serious Fraud Office, (b) Government Legal Department, (c) Crown Prosecution Service and (d) HM Crown Prosecution Service Inspectorate.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188197","188197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002119","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in the (a) Crown Commercial Service, (b) Government Property Agency and (c) Civil Service Commission.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188198","188198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002120","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which organisation (a) undertook investigations and (b) ensured mandatory compliance with Article 2 of the European Convention on Human Rights before the establishment of the Fatal Accident and Sudden Deaths (Scotland) Act 2016.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188199","188199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002121","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of the reduction in police officer numbers on levels of serious violence.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188200","188200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002122","2018-11-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support theatres and touring companies in the Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188267","188267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002123","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations she has received from (a) trades union and (b) the Trade Union Congress in relation to the managed migration of universal credit.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188268","188268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002124","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the meetings held by her Department (a) trades unions and (b) the Trade Union Congress on the managed migration of universal credit in 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188269","188269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002125","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral evidence of the Minister for Policing and the Fire Service of 19 June 2018 to the Home Affairs Select Committee, on Policing for the future, Q 564, HC 515, for what reasons neighbourhood policing has degraded.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188201","188201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002126","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to reply to the letter of the 29 June 2018 from the hon. Member for Delyn on the Offensive Weapons Bill.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188031","188031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002127","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to reply to the letter of 4 October 2018 from the hon. Member for Delyn on statutory maternity pay and maternity allowance.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188032","188032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002128","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in the (a) HM Land Registry, (b) Ofgem, (c) Competition and Markets Authority, (d) Companies House, (e) Insolvency Service, (f) Intellectual Property Office, (g) Met Office and (h) UK Space Agency.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188202","188202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002129","2018-11-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the contracted hours are for the highest paid member of staff in the (a) National Archives, (b) Royal Parks, (c) Arts Council England, (d) Big Lottery Fund, (e) Sport England and (f) Information Commissioner's Office.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188203","188203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002130","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made on consolidating guidance on legislation to protect people who are pregnant or on maternity leave as recommended by the Taylor review of modern working practices.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188083","188083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002131","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Low Pay Commission will publish the response to its consultation on (a) the effect of a higher minimum wage for non-guaranteed hours in a contract and (b) alternative means for tackling one sided flexibility.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188084","188084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002132","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to further promote better employee engagement and workforce relations in response to the Taylor review of modern working practices.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188085","188085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002133","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made in producing a unified framework of employability skills as agreed to in the Government’s response to the Taylor review of modern working practices.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188086","188086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002134","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support the 17 universities with a decline in student numbers of more than 10 per cent since 2012.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188033","188033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002135","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to enhance the moral hazard powers of the Pensions Regulator.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188087","188087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002136","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to enhance the (a) information-gathering and (b) anti-avoidance powers of the Pensions Regulator.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188088","188088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002137","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress her Department has made on proposed verification and security measures for individual users of the proposed Pensions Dashboard.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188089","188089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002138","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the participation of pension schemes in the Pensions Dashboard will be compulsory.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188090","188090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002139","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of ending the supplementary funding to maintained nursery schools in 2019-20  on the ability of those schools to support children with SEND needs.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188270","188270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002140","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of reports to Action Fraud are referred to a (a) local police force and (b) Regional Organised Crime Unit.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188204","188204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002141","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions his officials have had with the CBI on the content of that organisation's education and skills annual report published this month.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188034","188034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002142","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to protect students at universities on the brink of bankruptcy.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188035","188035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002143","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the governments of (a) Bangladesh and (b) Myanmar on agreement between those countries on the repatriation of Rohingya refugees.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188002","188002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002144","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that Primary Care practices have the ability to submit securely information on patients that have been subjected to female genital mutilation to the statutory database.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188271","188271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002145","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2018 to Question 185590 on A303 and Lower Thames Crossing: Private Finance Initiative, whether private finance will be used for the upgrade of the A303 and the Lower Thames Crossing.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188205","188205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002146","2018-11-12","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to her Answer of 5 November 2018 to Question 185592 on Waste Disposal: Northern Ireland, what guidance she plans to issue to the Northern Ireland Department for Infrastructure on the use of private finance for the funding of infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188206","188206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002147","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of including horse riders and carriage drivers in the forthcoming review of the highway code.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188207","188207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002148","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps is his Department is taking to ensure agricultural policy across the constituent parts of the UK does not distort market prices within the UK.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188091","188091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002149","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of climate change on GDP in the next four decades.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188092","188092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002150","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment his Department has made of the viability of removing fossil fuels from the UK's energy generation mix.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188093","188093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002151","2018-11-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that it is ready to respond to potential emergency events caused by climate change.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188094","188094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002152","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 50 of the report entitled, Police Efficiency 2016, published by Her Majesty's Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire & Rescue Services, what estimate he has made of the prudent level of unallocated general reserves in police forces.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188208","188208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002153","2018-11-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure UK defence readiness is not compromised by incidents related to climate change.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188095","188095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002154","2018-11-12","Department for International Trade","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he has taken to protect arms exports after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188096","188096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002155","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of climate change on the capacity for an increase in domestic food production.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188097","188097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002156","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the public consultation on Healthy Start vouchers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188098","188098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002157","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the risk of climate change to the food and farming sector.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188099","188099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002158","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to mitigate the effects of climate change on the food and farming sector.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188100","188100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002159","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2018 to Question 182186 and with reference to the oral contribution of 5 November 2018 by the Minister for Immigration, what further assessment he has made of the potential merits of waiving the application fee for (a) any victim and (b) any dependent of trafficking or modern slavery with a positive reasonable grounds or conclusive grounds decision when applying for settled status.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188209","188209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002160","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs,  what estimate he has made of the number of properties at threat of (a) flooding and (b) destruction from an average rise in global temperature of (i) 1.5 degrees and (ii) 2 degrees Celsius.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188101","188101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002161","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the level of Co2 emissions from private transport in (a) London, (b) England and Wales and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188102","188102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002162","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to ensure the financial sustainability of universities.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188036","188036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002163","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children with ADHD that have been excluded from school in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188272","188272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002164","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on including age as a criterion for decisions on health funding.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188210","188210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002165","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October to Question 183925 and with reference to the announcement of 22 April, by what date his Department expects to have employed the final 500 additional prison staff.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188211","188211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002166","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October to Question 183925, what steps his Department is taking to improve support for prisoners in the early days in custody.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188212","188212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002167","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to accept all of the recommendations in the independent Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman report, Ignoring the alarms: how NHS eating disorder services are failing patients.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188213","188213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002168","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October to Question 182159 on Prisons: Sexual Offences, what support his Department provides to prisoners who report sexual assault.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188214","188214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002169","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 184982 on UK Visas and Immigration: South Wales, whether the contract with Sopra Steria includes any requirement on (a) opening and (b) access hours.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188215","188215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002170","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 175782 on Prostitution, to list the institutions that tendered unsuccessfully for funding to carry out research into the nature and prevalence of prostitution in England and Wales.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187979","187979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002171","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the total staff hours it will take to process all of the applications for settled status from EU citizens living in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188216","188216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002172","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of staff that will be employed by his Department on 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188217","188217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002173","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department is planning for an increase in enforcement activity against EU citizens after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188218","188218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002174","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of premature births in (a) England, (b) London and (c) the London Borough of Lewisham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188219","188219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002175","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made any recent estimate of the average amount of time premature babies spend in neonatal units.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188220","188220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002176","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 175781 on Prostitution, if he will publish the assurances given by the Centre for Gender and Violence Research during the tendering process that their research would satisfy the criteria for the research project to be conducted in an impartial manner.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187983","187983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002177","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives of (a) the Syrian democratic forces and (b) his counterparts in neighbouring countries to Syria on the re-education and rehabilitation of Daesh indoctrinated children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188221","188221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002178","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Syrian democratic forces on assistance in managing and rehabilitating former captives of Daesh who originate from countries other than Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188222","188222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002179","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Turkish counterpart on reports of recent heavy weaponry attacks by that country on northern and eastern Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188223","188223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002180","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the President-elect of Brazil.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188003","188003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002181","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the end of means-tested grants in 2016 on the number of people applying to go to university.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188004","188004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002182","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Somalia.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188005","188005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002183","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the average amount of parental leave taken by (a) women and (b) men in (i) England, (ii) London and (iii) the London Borough of Lewisham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188224","188224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002184","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to promote voter registration in secondary schools.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188006","188006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002185","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions (a) he and (b) the Minister responsible for higher education has had with the Office for Students on universities that have experienced a decline in student numbers of more than 10 per cent since 2012.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188037","188037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002186","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to Answer of 5 November to Question 907432, how much discretionary housing payment was (a) awarded to and (b) spent by North Lincolnshire Council in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188225","188225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002187","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Government will publish the statutory orders for each of the electoral pilot schemes taking place at local government elections in 2019.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188226","188226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002188","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the June 2018 report of the Intelligence and Security Committee on rendition and torture, what progress has been made on restarting a judge-led inquiry into those issues; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188227","188227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002189","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the merits of strengthening the consolidated criteria for the sale of arms products by introducing an end use criteria post sale.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188228","188228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002190","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many two week run-on payments for (a) job seekers allowance and (b) employment support allowance will claimants being migrated to universal credit receive in the five weeks following their universal credit claim; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187990","187990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002191","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of charges of sedition against former members of the Government of Tanzania on the democratic process in that country.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188229","188229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002192","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Government of Tanzania on the level of the threat to (a) the LGBT community and (b) supporters of opposition parties in that country.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188230","188230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002193","2018-11-12","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions Army bomb disposal teams were called out between 1 July 2012 and 30 June 2014 as a result of (a) viable and (b) hoax devices.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188038","188038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002194","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and which (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have visited the Port of Belfast in the last 12 months; when those visits took place; and how long they spent at the port in each of those visits.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188273","188273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002195","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the use by the Metropolitan police of the Self Evident app is being discontinued; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187978","187978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000220","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of any potential increase in red tape from the proposed associate status of the EU Registration, Evaluation, Authorisation & restriction of Chemicals programme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187324","187324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000221","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications for democracy in the UK of the US imposing sanctions on the official leader of the UK opposition.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187325","187325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000222","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the number of closed-contact visits in prisons to prevent smuggling.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187326","187326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000223","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the merits of using video technology to allow relatives and friends to speak to convicted prisoners at appointed times.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187327","187327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000224","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) timetable, (b) cost and (c) estimated savings are for the Foxhound IT programme.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187356","187356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000225","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse has been of the Public Services Network; and what estimate he has made of the savings to be accrued to the public purse of that Network.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187357","187357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000226","2018-11-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will publish the successful bids to the Cyber Skills Immediate Impact Fund for each region.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187358","187358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000227","2018-11-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184409 on Cybercrime, how many of the 170 individuals have been (a) participating and (b) identified to take part.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187359","187359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000228","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support the Government plans to provide to Ineos for choosing the South Tees Development Corporation site as the manufacturing location of that company’s Projekt Grenadier 4x4 vehicles.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187360","187360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000229","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many data breaches were reported by each Government department to the Government Security Group in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187361","187361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000230","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs,  what recent representations his Department has made to the Myanmar authorities on the Rohingya crisis.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187308","187308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000231","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the workforce size of the National Crime Agency in Northern Ireland is expected to change in the next six months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187309","187309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000232","2018-11-12","Cabinet Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people earning less than £8.21 per hour.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187310","187310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000233","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on locum doctors and nurses of the 2019 loan charge for disguised remuneration schemes.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187296","187296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000234","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the number of manufacturing companies that have (a) shortened their supply chains and (b) relocated their production to the UK from abroad in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187311","187311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000235","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of applicants to the Criminal Cases Review Commission have had legal representation to assist them with their applications in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187362","187362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000236","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Ministry of Justice secures extra £52 million for targeted expenditure, published on 30 October 2018, how much of the £30 million allocated to prisons this financial year will be spent on (a) staff, (b) maintenance, (c) new equipment, (d) training and (e) other categories of spending.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187363","187363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000237","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total additional funding allocated to his Department for capital expenditure in Budget 2018 was.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187364","187364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000238","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total additional funding allocated to his Department for resource expenditure in Budget 2018 was.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187365","187365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000239","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number places in residential women's centres  that were funded by the Government in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187366","187366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000240","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Secretary of State launches dedicated strategy to 'break the cycle' of female offending, published on 27 June 2018, how many of the bids received by his Department for the £3.5m grant competition for community services and multi-agency, whole system approaches have come from companies and organisations that are currently under investigation by the Serious Fraud Office for overcharging his Department.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187367","187367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000241","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of women who do not disclose that they have a dependant child before they receive a custodial sentence.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187368","187368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000242","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests made under section 17 of the Criminal Appeal Act 1995 by the Criminal Cases Review Commission were refused by each category of public body in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187369","187369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000243","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions judicial review proceedings have been brought by the Criminal Cases Review Commission (CCRC) against a public body which has refused a request of the CCRC for information under Section 17 of the Criminal Appeal Act 1995 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187370","187370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000244","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions have Crown Court Orders obtained under Section 18A of the Criminal Appeal Act 1995 not been complied with in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187371","187371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000245","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of applicants to the Criminal Cases Review Commission (CCRC) have met in person with CCRC caseworkers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187372","187372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000246","2018-11-12","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October to Written Question 179070 on Trade Agreements, if he will publish the international treaties listed under the EU Treaties Office Database that (a) have been superseded, (b) are redundant and (c) are no longer relevant for the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187297","187297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000247","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment has he made of the financial sustainability of Laing O’Rourke and the ability of that company to fulfil its contractual responsibilities in relation to (a) railways and (b) highways.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187373","187373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000248","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer to Question 183314 on Children: Death, if he will make an assessment of the (a) number and (b) proportion of (i) referrals and (ii) successful referrals that have been made to the National Referral Mechanism as a result of  gang involvement in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187328","187328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000249","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the safety implications for (a) women, (b) LGBTQ  and (c) black and minority ethnic people visiting Brazil of the election of Jair Bolsonaro.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187329","187329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000250","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of potential risks to (a) democratic institutions, (b) the rule of law, (c) freedom of the press and (d) human rights in Brazil as a result of the election of Jair Bolsonaro as that country’s President.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187330","187330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000251","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the plans of the President-Elect of Brazil to move that country's embassy from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem on the UK foreign policy objective of achieving a two-state solution for Israel and the Palestinians.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187331","187331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000252","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of reported environmental policy plans of the President-Elect of Brazil on (a) the environment in that country and (b) global climate change targets.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187332","187332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000253","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the block allocation for individual maintained schools and academies for 2018-19.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187374","187374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000254","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the school block allocations are being released later than October in the school year.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187375","187375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000255","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Government plans to ratify and implement the Council of Europe Convention against trafficking in human organs signed on 23 March 2015.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187376","187376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000256","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 182850 on Mental Illness: Parents, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of collecting (a) such information and (b) information on the effect of such circumstances on the welfare of the children of such patients.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187377","187377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000257","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to close the legal loophole that allows human consumption of dog and cat meat in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187378","187378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000258","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take following the passage of EU Directive 2006/112/EC on the rates of value added tax applied to books, newspapers and periodicals.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187294","187294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000259","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had and with whom on (a) EU Directive 2006/112/EC and (b) the UK VAT regime on print and digital publications.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187295","187295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000260","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the taper that is applied to wages is not applied to pensions in relation to universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187333","187333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000261","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans next to increase the national funding rate for sixth form students.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187379","187379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000262","2018-11-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the food and farming sector has sufficient access to labour in order to sustain British food production (a) now and (b) in the future.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187334","187334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000263","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the implementation of the Creative Industries Sector Deal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187335","187335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000264","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what initiatives his Department is promoting to help ensure that (a) UK musicians are able to perform in the EU and (b) EU musicians are able to perform in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187336","187336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000265","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that that the new Digital Services Tax announced Budget 2018 does not disproportionately affect small digital businesses.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187337","187337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000266","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the target for a nationwide full-fibre broadband network by 2033.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187338","187338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000267","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Governor of the Bank of England on the person who will be represented on the new £50 note.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187380","187380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000268","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2018 to Question 185131 on Independent Case Examiner, if she will publish that same information for complaints by women on the equalisation of the state pension age.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187381","187381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000269","2018-11-12","Department for Education","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has plans to increase the national funding rate for sixth form students.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187339","187339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000270","2018-11-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect the US Steel tariffs have had on the UK steel sector since they came into place.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187382","187382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000271","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much money his Department has allocated to tackle sexual violence in conflict since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187340","187340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000272","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to tackle conflict-related sexual violence.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187341","187341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000273","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many nations have now signed up to the London Declaration from the International Wildlife Trade Conference 2018; and what assessment he has made of the implications of that number for the endangered species trade.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187342","187342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000274","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding will be allocated to the second round of pocket parks; and if any of those parks will be located in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187343","187343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000275","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the £420 million announced in Budget 2018 to be provided to councils to fix potholes and carry out other road repairs, how much of that funding will be allocated to (a) Sheffield City Region and (b) Barnsley.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187383","187383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000276","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made in securing support for a Marine Protected Area in the Weddell Sea.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187344","187344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000277","2018-11-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to introduce licensing laws for the sale of tobacco in England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187384","187384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000278","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding the Government plans to allocate to research to help Commonwealth countries prevent plastic waste from entering the oceans.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187345","187345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000279","2018-11-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the statistics from the Smoking Data Guide, published by Barnsley Metropolitan Borough Council's research and business intelligence team in August 2016, that 21.2 per cent of adults and 10.7 per cent of 15 year olds in Barnsley smoke, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of young adults who smoke.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187385","187385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000280","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, (a) how much and (b) what proportion of the UK's maritime estate including the Overseas Territories is planned to be covered by a blue belt of marine protected areas by 2022.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187346","187346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000281","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support his Department provides for unaccompanied child refugees when they arrive in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187347","187347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000282","2018-11-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November to Question 183261 on United Arab Emirates: Official Visits, whether a (a) private secretary and (b) Embassy official was present at any meetings he had with Ministers or officials from overseas governments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187300","187300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000283","2018-11-06","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of whether the Withdrawal Agreement maintains the (a) healthcare, (b) welfare, (c) pension and (d) other social security rights of (i) UK citizens living in the EU and (ii) EU citizens living in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187348","187348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000284","2018-11-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees in relation to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187301","187301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000285","2018-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations she has received from claimants of personal independence payment with myotonic dystrophy on personal independence payment assessments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187298","187298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000286","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees in relation to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187302","187302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000287","2018-11-06","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department has spent on consultancy fees in relation to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187303","187303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000288","2018-11-06","Scotland Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees in relation to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187304","187304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000289","2018-11-06","Wales Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on consultancy fees in relation to the UK leaving the EU since July 2016.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187305","187305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000290","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Mayor of London on levels of violent crime in London.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187349","187349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000292","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department taking to ensure that the agri-food sector is able to access non-UK seasonal workers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187350","187350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000293","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce littering in communities across the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187351","187351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000294","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure access by non-UK non-seasonal workers to the agri-food sector after UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187312","187312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000295","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the re-introduction of a Tier 3 visa category to support domestic food and meat production after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187313","187313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000296","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on the development of the infrastructure requirements for customs and veterinary border arrangements to ensure seamless trade in food with the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187314","187314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000297","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the sustainability of the livestock farming sector when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187315","187315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000298","2018-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November to Question 183252 on Ministry of Justice: ICT, what estimate he has made of the cost the full delivery of the Common Platform Programme.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187306","187306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000299","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November to Question 183259 on Home Office: ICT, how many of the 360 are classed as contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187307","187307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000300","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November to Question 183259 on Home Office: ICT, what the annual salary cost to his Department is of those 360 people.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187316","187316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000301","2018-11-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle allegations of bullying and harassment of staff in the NHS and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187299","187299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000302","2018-11-12","Department for Transport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November to Question 185132, Railways: Fares, on what date his Department was first notified of the roll-out.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187387","187387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000303","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2018 to Question 157090 on Ministry of Justice: Buildings, how many days each Minister of his Department spent in Petty France between 5 October 2017 and 5 November 2017.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187352","187352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000304","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on game meat producers of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187353","187353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000305","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2018 to Question 178322 on Train Operating Companies: Pay, whether he has asked the Rail Delivery Group to include executive pay in the development of a pay award system that uses CPI as the inflation measure for future pay deals.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187388","187388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000306","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the volume was of seizures at points of entry of illegal drugs destined for the UK, in each of the last ten years, and what estimate he has made of those seizures as a proportion of the total amount of illegal drugs consumed in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187389","187389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000307","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the Department for Transport has spent on research and development in (a) aviation and (b) aerospace in (i) 2015, (ii) 2016 and (iii) 2017.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187390","187390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000308","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of Talk Money Week.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187317","187317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000309","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his office have had with representatives of Talk Money Week.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187318","187318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000310","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions officials in his Department have had with representatives of Talk Money Week.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187319","187319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000311","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number UK residents who did not take a (a) domestic and (b) international flight in (i) 2015, (ii) 2016 and (iii) 2017.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187391","187391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000312","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of UK residents without a valid passport.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187392","187392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000313","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to introduce graphic warnings on fireworks packaging.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187354","187354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000314","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure young children are protected from firework-related injuries.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187355","187355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000315","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the money to be accrued to the public purse in tax from the profits made by gambling companies from fixed odds betting terminals between April 2019 and October 2019.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187320","187320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000316","2018-11-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which gambling companies he has held meetings with since he took up his current office.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187321","187321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000317","2018-11-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, on what dates he met with the hon. Member for Shipley since becoming Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187322","187322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000318","2018-11-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, on what day he read the Government's response to Gaming Machines and Social Responsibility Measures, published by the Gambling Commission on 17 May 2018.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187323","187323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1000319","2018-11-12","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department conducted impact assessments on levels of taxation of different implementation dates for reducing the maximum stakes on fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187393","187393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1002074","2018-11-12","Home Office","2018-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what meetings his Department has had with representatives of religious institutions on the places of worship security funding scheme in the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 188021","188021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999669","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-11-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many successful prosecutions have been made against employers for failing to pay that national minimum wage for intern roles since November 2017; and which employees were subject to such successful prosecutions.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187012","187012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/997668","2018-11-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many international treaties with third parties the UK is party to as a result of its membership of the EU; and how many of those treaties the UK plans to replicate after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 185557","185557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999380","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made on the effect of the standard three security equipment on the financial viability of regional airports.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186433","186433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999469","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the potential economic merits of improving the Reading to Gatwick airport road corridor.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907479","907479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999490","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the rate of insurance premium tax on the cost of insurance premiums since 2011.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187137","187137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999491","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Hungarian counterpart on the potential implications for UK NGO employees of that country's stop soros legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187138","187138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999492","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the legal basis is under which local authorities may establish drug consumption rooms.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187139","187139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999493","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the level of taxation on sanitary items in countries outside the EU.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187140","187140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999494","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of overall Government funding is allocated to (a) children's and b) adult hospices in England.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187123","187123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999495","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to secure progress for a One Yorkshire devolution deal.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187067","187067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999496","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on border access between the RAF bases Akrotiri and Dhekelia and Cyprus after the UK leave the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186914","186914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999497","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the viability of developing exemptions for fully recyclable coffee cups as part of any future levy.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186915","186915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999498","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government's policy is on suspected illegal migrants being arrested in public places.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187141","187141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999499","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how NICE (a) classifies and (b) regulates new treatments made up of a combination of active substances.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187142","187142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999500","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many provisions in financial and related regulations which require transposition into UK law in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal include thresholds measuring the proportion of (a) the entire EU market or (b) a specified number or grouping of member states.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187143","187143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999501","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2018 to Question 181237 on Carbon budgets: Climate change, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the fourth and fifth carbon budgets and place the UK on the steeper decarbonisation pathway recommended by the Committee on Climate Change.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186934","186934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999502","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what (a) representations his Department has received and (b) assessment his Department has made since the publication of the IPCC report on global warming of 1.5 degrees on the potential (i) economic and (ii) climatic merits of amending the UK's third, fourth and fifth carbon budgets.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186935","186935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999503","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional funding has been allocated to the Border Force at UK airports to ensure it is adequately funded after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187094","187094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999504","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the new Law Enforcement Data Service on the prospects for securing a data adequacy agreement when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187077","187077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999505","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the decrease in charge and summons rates for crimes.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187078","187078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999506","2018-11-06","Cabinet Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the ability of Government contractors to pay invoices submitted by subcontractors within 30 days.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187159","187159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999507","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 76 of Budget 2018, what proportion of the additional £160 million funding for counter-terror policing in 2019-20 is an increase on previously planned year on year spending; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187079","187079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999508","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statements by Ambassador Karen Pierce, UK Permanent Representative to the United Nations at the Security Council Briefing on Burma of 24 October 2018, what information he has on the timetable for the Burmese domestic commission of inquiry into the events that took place in Rakhine State.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186916","186916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999509","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on the political activist Khalida Jarrar.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186917","186917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999510","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the average cost of deposits required of businesses entering commercial tenancies; what assessment he has made of the effect of such costs on the viability of businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186925","186925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999511","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what financial support his Department makes available to support children with hearing difficulties.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187092","187092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999512","2018-11-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will allocate funding to local authorities that plan to implement heroin assisted treatment.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187009","187009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999513","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the terms of reference for the review of the market for illegal drugs.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187010","187010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999514","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to launch a review of the market for illegal drugs.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187011","187011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999515","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to increase the number of broadcasts which are required to include (a) audio description for people with sight loss and (b) subtitles for people with hearing loss.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187059","187059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999516","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make it a requirement that all broadcasters use audio description access on all television channels.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187060","187060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999517","2018-11-05","Department for Transport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department has received on whether rail companies amend rail operating timetables to avoid paying delay repay claims.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187093","187093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999518","2018-11-05","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his policy is on achieving parity of approach from law enforcement and the security services between domestic extremism and international counter-terrorism.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187080","187080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999519","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support his Department is providing to improve energy usage through better domestic insulation.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187128","187128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999520","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department has provided to the fishing sector to help it plan for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186974","186974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999521","2018-11-06","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2018 to Question 183461 on Teachers: pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to employers other than state-funded schools of increasing the employer contribution to the Teachers' Pension Scheme for the fiscal year 2020-21.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187042","187042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999522","2018-11-05","Department for Education","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference paragraph 5.18 of Budget 2018, how his Department will determine which local authorities receive funding for the children's social care improvement pilot schemes.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187043","187043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999523","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 5.16 of Budget 2018, how the £410 million made available for social care in 2019-20 will be allocated to individual local authorities; and what restrictions will be placed on how that funding can be spent.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187044","187044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999524","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the addresses are of the new UK Visa and Citizenship Application Service centres to be delivered under the contract with Sopra Steria; and what libraries will host services under that contract.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187058","187058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999525","2018-11-06","Cabinet Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of all jobs for which monthly earnings are less than the national average pay the employee (a) weekly, (b) fortnightly, (c) four-weekly and (d) monthly.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186920","186920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999526","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2018 to Question 181215 on South Africa: British Nationals Abroad, what steps are being taken to identify UK expatriates living in South Africa who will be affected by the motion to confiscate land without compensation.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187000","187000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999527","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184409, whether a participatory target was set for the cyber skills immediate impact fund.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187149","187149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999528","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many bids have been submitted to the cyber skills immediate impact fund.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187150","187150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999529","2018-11-06","Department for International Development","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many countries that receive UK official development assistance treat homosexuality as a criminal act.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186944","186944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999530","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled Existing UK residence documents for EU citizens, published on gov.uk, and with reference to the statement in that guidance that permanent residence documents will not be a valid proof of residence after 31 December 2020 and people will still need to apply for settled status to continue living in the UK after June 2021 even if they have a permanent residence document, whether that is planned to still be the case in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187006","187006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999531","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who will represent Her Majesty's Government at the celebration of 100 years of independence for Poland on the 11 November 2018.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187003","187003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999532","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many times the rough sleeping and homelessness reduction taskforce has met in 2018; what the current membership is of the taskforce; and how many changes to have membership have taken place since the announcement of the taskforce; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187019","187019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999533","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether (a) permanent residence and (b) settled status will be required to apply for citizenship after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187007","187007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999534","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the reason is for the invalidation of permanent residence documents after 31 December 2020.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187008","187008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999535","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional funding he plans to allocate to the National Economic Crime Centre in 2019-20.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187081","187081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999536","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on the safety and wellbeing of Rohingya refugees of the deal between Myanmar and Bangladesh to start repatriating those refugees.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187115","187115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999537","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has held with UN representatives on the agreement between Myanmar and Bangladesh on the repatriation of Rohingya refugees.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187116","187116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999538","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will formally support a referral of Myanmar military leaders to the International Criminal Court for their actions against the Rohingya people.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187117","187117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999539","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the average financial bid submission is for applications to the cyber skills immediate impact fund.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187151","187151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999540","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement of 1 November 2018, HCWS1053, on tackling serious and organised crime, what proportion of the £48 million will come from existing police budgets.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187082","187082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999541","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many homes (a) have been built and are occupied now and (b) are guaranteed to be built and occupied by the end of 2019 as a result of the Government's garden villages and towns policy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186945","186945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999542","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether claimants migrating from employment support allowance to universal credit will be have to provide medical evidence to demonstrate vulnerability.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187020","187020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999543","2018-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2018 to Question 177771 on Universal Credit, whether the Department’s plans to check evidence of complex needs will include a requirement to undertake a home visit.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187021","187021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999544","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2018 to Question 177771 on Universal Credit, whether the Department’s plans to check evidence of complex needs will include a requirement to contact a claimant’s healthcare professional where that information is known.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187022","187022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999545","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the effectiveness of reconciliation schemes for victimised religious minorities throughout the world which absolve persecuting individuals and institutions from blame or criminal prosecution.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186970","186970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999546","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to Answer of 29 October 2018 to Question 181533 on Planning Permission, whether intentional unauthorised development is still a material consideration in cases involving land outside the Green Belt.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186912","186912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999547","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland civil service on the (a) parliamentary timetable for the Agriculture Bill and (b) potential effect of its provisions on Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186971","186971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999548","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of railway stations have step-free access.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186946","186946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999549","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of fruit contamination in Australia on UK consumers.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186972","186972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999550","2018-11-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of exports from Great Britain to Northern Ireland of (a) live animals, (b) animal-derived food products and (c) plant-based products are subject to (i) controls and (ii) physical inspection.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186973","186973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999551","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the UK's strategic supply of technology metals (a) currently and (b) after the UK leaves the EU for the purpose of implementing the industrial strategy.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186978","186978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999552","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with (a) Kenyan and (b) Ugandan banks to close the financial and banking loopholes which enable money laundering in South Sudan.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186979","186979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999553","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to reports of the arrest and detention of 13 Christians in south Darfur in October 2018, what progress his Department has made through the UK-Sudan Strategic Dialogue on promoting freedom of religion or belief in Sudan.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186980","186980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999554","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the October 2018 report by The Sentry entitled The Profiteers: documentary shines new light on South Sudan's neighbours' role in the conflict, what steps his department is taking to improve the capacity of financial regulatory bodies in (a) Kenya and (b) Uganda.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186981","186981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999555","2018-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has allocated (a) funding and (b) other support to (i) independent journalism and (ii) Radio Dabanga in Sudan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186982","186982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999556","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the compatibility between the Oil and Gas Authority's remit of maximising revenues from oil and gas recovery and (a) the Government's decarbonisation commitments under the Paris Agreement and (b) the recommendations of the IPCC on the speed of decarbonisation required to limit global warming to 1.5 degrees.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186936","186936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999557","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the development of the Alligin oil field will be included in the UK's carbon budget.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186937","186937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999558","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the oil to be extracted from the Alligin oil field will be (a) used in domestic markets or (b) exported.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186938","186938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999559","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the decision to permit the development of the Alligin oil field by BP was taken by (a) the Oil and Gas Authority or (b) the Government.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186939","186939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999560","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with representatives from (a) the Football Association and (b) other football governance bodies on the number of gambling companies sponsoring football clubs.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186947","186947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999561","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings have been held between representatives from BP and (a) his Ministers, (b) his officials and (c) representatives from the Oil and Gas Authority in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186940","186940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999562","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish the outcome of his Department's consultation on society lottery reform which closed on 7 September 2018.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187023","187023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999563","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether (a) the Oil and Gas Authority and (b) his Department carried out an assessment on the potential effect on the climate of the development of the Alligin oil field before granting permission for that field to be developed.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186941","186941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999564","2018-11-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2018 to Question 184409, how many of the 170 individuals who have participated in initiatives supported by the cyber skills immediate impact fund pilot are (a) women, (b) BAME and (c) disabled.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187152","187152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999565","2018-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps, excluding the provision of legal aid, his Department is taking to widen access to justice for (a) individuals and (b) small businesses.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187147","187147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999566","2018-11-06","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) armed forces widows and widowers and (b) war widows and war widowers have had their pensions reinstated following the removal of the means tested application process and other changes to widows’ pension rights since April 2015.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187129","187129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999567","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2018 to Question 183872 on Bus Services: North West, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the decline in bus journeys in (a) the North West and (b) Merseyside.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186958","186958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999568","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with (a) Ministers and (b) officials at the Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on the potential effect on heritage railway services and UK tourism of the proposals in the Government's consultation on cleaner domestic burning of solid fuels and wood; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187001","187001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999569","2018-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with (a) Ministers and (b) officials in the Irish Government on (i) their experience of bringing forward policies on cleaner domestic burning of solid fuels and wood and (ii) the UK Government's consultation on similar proposals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187002","187002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999570","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department allocated to bus services serving (a) the North West, (b) Merseyside, (c) Wallasey constituency and (d) Surrey in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186959","186959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999571","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of prescriptions were issued to people using a prepayment certificate in England in (a) 2017 and (b) the latest period for which information is available.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187148","187148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999572","2018-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of trials in the North West resulted in a conviction in each year between 2010 and 2017.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186960","186960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999573","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding has been allocated to settlement agreements following the announcement that 74 Crown post offices will be closed or franchised.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187068","187068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999574","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for how long the Post Office is planning to subsidise the staff costs of franchised Crown post officers following the announcement that 74 Crown post offices will be closed or franchised.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187069","187069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999575","2018-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote the protection of LGBT rights in each member state of the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186948","186948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999576","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Post Office plans to subsidise the differential between WHSmiths' remuneration package and the Post Office remuneration package where post offices have been franchised to WHSmith.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187070","187070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999577","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse was allocated by his Department to enable local authorities in England to fund the full disregard of war pensions in social care financial assessments in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187153","187153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999578","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his oral contribution of 29 October 2018, Official Report, column 665, who the members will be of the working group that will be established to progress plans for short-haul air passenger duty devolution; and what criteria will be used to appoint those members.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186977","186977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999579","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 3 of the HMRC Annual Report and Accounts 2017-18, what steps HMRC has taken to ensure that computer applications it has using the SAP platform are accessible by disabled staff.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187052","187052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999580","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much the Post Office will spend on (a) retrofitting and (b) refurbishing WHSmith stores as a result of franchising agreements.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187071","187071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999581","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October to Question 182668 and to the Answer of 16 October to Written Question 175821, in what policy areas projects are behind schedule.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186918","186918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999582","2018-11-05","Department for International Trade","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October to Written Question 182665 on Department for International Trade: World Trade Organisation, how many additional (a) permanent staff and (b) representatives at the World Trade Organisation have been recruited to the UK Mission in Geneva at the World Trade Organisation in preparation for the UK’s independent trade policy; and what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of recruiting those additional staff.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186919","186919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999583","2018-11-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS trusts have ever been put in to special administration.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187096","187096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999584","2018-11-05","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has taken steps to help parents who have not claimed child benefit and as a result unintentionally missed years of accruing national insurance state pension credits.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187118","187118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999585","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will enable Post Offices that make a profit to remain as a Crown post office rather than being franchised.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187072","187072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999586","2018-11-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether all Crown post offices are planned to be closed or franchised.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187073","187073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999587","2018-11-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of NHS England’s outturn expenditure against its £25 million budget for discretionary investment in specialised services in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187127","187127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999588","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the HMRC guidance entitled Partnership pack: preparing for a no deal EU exit published on 22 October 2018, if HMRC will rescind any non-disclosure agreements they required organisations to sign in order to be able to discuss with them border arrangements in various scenarios for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187053","187053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999589","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HMRC employees are paid less than £8.21 per hour.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187054","187054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999590","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on the effect of fireworks on pets.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187029","187029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999591","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an estimate of (a) the amount of money raised for the public purse from fees paid by people undertaking speed awareness courses in the last five years and (b) the cost to the public purse of running such courses in that same time period.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186975","186975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999592","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much and what proportion of (a) total council borrowing and (b) council borrowing for housing was sourced through the public works loan board in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186949","186949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999593","2018-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to combat puppy smuggling into the UK.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187030","187030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999594","2018-11-06","Treasury","2018-11-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his oral contribution of 29 October 2018, if he will make an estimate of the number of of 800,000 jobs that are projected to be created by 2023 that will be created in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187031","187031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999595","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time taken has been to return a driving license revoked on the basis of a notifiable medical condition after evidence that the person is fit to drive has been received by the DVLA in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187047","187047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999596","2018-11-06","Department for Transport","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time taken to return a driving license revoked on the basis of a notifiable medical condition, after evidence that the individual is fit to drive has been received by the DVLA.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187048","187048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999597","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's definition is of a public consultation; and what parts of the closure and franchising of Crown post offices his Department plans to consult on.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187074","187074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999598","2018-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will reassess the case of Afghan interpreter Mohammed Nabi Wardak who translated for British armed forces on the front line in Helmand province between 2008 and 2011 and has been denied relocation to the UK.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187119","187119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999599","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether permanent residence cards for EEA nationals will remain valid if the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187049","187049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999600","2018-11-06","Home Office","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether permanent residence cards will remain valid for people who have those cards on the basis of being the family member of an EEA national if the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187050","187050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999601","2018-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the effect of the full roll out of universal credit on the number of children living in poverty in (a) the UK, (b) the north east, (c) Northumberland and (d) Wansbeck constituency.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187025","187025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999602","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the average annual ground rent paid on a leasehold property in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186950","186950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999603","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what is the average amount of ground rent charges by government office region based on the latest available English Housing Survey data.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 186951","186951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999604","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 4.88 of Budget 2018 Red Book, what powers the Government plans to confer on the South Tees special economic area.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187061","187061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999605","2018-11-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 4.88 of Budget 2018 Redbook, whether business rates that will be transferred to the  proposed South Tees special economic area will include business rates currently retained by Redcar and Cleveland Borough Council.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187062","187062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999606","2018-11-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment has he made of the effect of the business rates retention by the proposed South Tees special economic area on the financial sustainability of Redcar and Cleveland Borough Council.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187063","187063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/999608","2018-11-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has with Ineos on that company choosing the South Tees Development Corporation site as the manufacturing location for its Projekt Grenadier 4x4 vehicles.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 187064","187064"
