"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426252","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish its low-risk drinking guidelines.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14845","14845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426253","2015-11-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the likely demand for new UK-manufactured aircraft over the next 15 years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14700","14700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426254","2015-11-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the ability of the UK aerospace industry to meet demand for new aircraft over the next 15 years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14698","14698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426255","2015-11-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people are in receipt of a war widow or widower pension.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14971","14971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426256","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many public access defibrillators there are in (a) England and Wales and (b) public buildings in England.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14926","14926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426257","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of urticaria among (a) the general public and (b) health professionals in primary care.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14758","14758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426258","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patients with chronic spontaneous urticaria have access to appropriate treatments and care at specialist centres.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14699","14699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426259","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to improve the level of accurate chronic spontaneous urticaria diagnosis in primary care.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14697","14697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426260","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures her Department has in place to ensure that researchers assessing the expected severity level of animal experiments when applying for project licences do so objectively and thoroughly.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14731","14731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426261","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures her Department has in place to assess at the conclusion of any animal experiment whether the severity level expected by researchers before the experiment corresponded to what the actual severity level was.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14732","14732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426262","2015-11-09","Women and Equalities","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the Government plans to take steps to encourage financial services firms to publicise their gender diversity figures.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14727","14727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426263","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure that more women progress to senior levels in the financial services industry.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14728","14728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426264","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has to support the recommendation made in the review led by Jayne-Anne Gadhia on women in finance that pay packages for executives be linked to a financial services firm's gender balance.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14729","14729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426265","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department is investigating complaints made about the conduct and performance of the West London Coroner.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14835","14835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426266","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to advise local authorities, under Section 62 of the Criminal Justice and Public Order Act 1994, which powers are available to remove illegal traveller camps without recourse to the courts.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14704","14704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426267","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what measures the Government plans to take to address the concerns expressed by the Chief Inspector of Prisons in his Annual Report for 2014-15, published on 15 July 2015; and what those measures will be on each of the four assessed outcomes referred to in the introduction to that report.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14701","14701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426268","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what measures the Government plans to take to address the concerns expressed by the Independent Monitoring Board in its report, HMP Winchester, Annual Report June 2014 to May 2015, published on 2 November 2015.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14702","14702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426269","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the location of imprisonment of transgender prisoners.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14703","14703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426270","2015-11-09","Attorney General","2015-11-04","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2015 to Question 11456, whether any additional blockbuster funding has been requested by the Serious Fraud Office for 2015-16; and what assessment he has made of the likelihood of that office making further requests for additional blockbuster funding in the remainder of this financial year.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14694","14694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426271","2015-11-09","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans  his Department has to electrify the South Devon Banks section of the rail line between Newton Abbott and Plymouth by 2018.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14922","14922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426272","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what is being done to raise awareness of diabetes and to encourage people to seek medical advice for this condition.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14796","14796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426273","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to help raise awareness of diabetes in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14795","14795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426274","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what action can be taken within state aid rules to secure assets of national strategic significance to the British economy.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14928","14928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426275","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether monitoring activity was put in place by his Department to oversee the financial viability of SSI in Redcar.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14722","14722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426276","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when concerns were first raised with his Department over the financial viability of SSI in Redcar.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14916","14916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426277","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when his Department was first made aware that employer pension payments were not being made by SSI UK.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14917","14917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426278","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what due diligence was undertaken by his Department prior to the purchase of the Redcar coke ovens and blast furnace.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14918","14918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426279","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will provide financial assistance to councils to enable them to acquire new social housing to replace properties bought through the Right to Buy policy.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14723","14723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426280","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on job numbers in councils and housing associations of the measures contained in the Housing and Planning Bill.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14724","14724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426281","2015-11-09","Scotland Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his Answer of 4 November 2015 to Question 14206, for what reason his Department's quarterly report of transparency information from October to December 2014 was not ready for publication until 15 October 2015.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14923","14923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426282","2015-11-09","Scotland Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his Answer of 4 November 2015 to Question 14206, for what reason his Department's quarterly report of transparency information from July to September 2014 was not ready for publication until 15 October 2015.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14924","14924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426283","2015-11-09","Scotland Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his Answer of 4 November 2015 to Question 14206, for what reason his Department's quarterly report of transparency information from January to March 2015 was not ready for publication until 15 October 2015.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14925","14925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426284","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount received by his Department in VAT payments from further education and sixth form colleges in (a) the UK, (b) the North West and (c) Warrington in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14969","14969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426285","2015-11-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs in Warrington which are (a) dependent on and (b) directly related to Britain continuing to maintain an at-sea nuclear deterrent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14970","14970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426286","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of posts for teaching (a) English and (b) mathematics in further education colleges that are (i) unfilled and (ii) filled by teachers without a qualification in those subjects.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14825","14825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426287","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the likely change in the number of students in further education colleges after 2020; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14769","14769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426288","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason it is her policy that scores attained through the Reception Assessment baseline will not be scaled for age; if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policy of the findings of research published by the Institute for Fiscal Studies in October 2013 on the academic performance in school of pupils born later in the academic year; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14736","14736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426289","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the qualifying threshold for baseline assessment providers was set at 10 per cent of primary schools.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14860","14860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426290","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of primary schools signed up to (a) Centre for Education and Monitoring, Durham University, (b) Early Excellence, (c) GL Assessment, (d) Hodder Education, (e) National Foundation for Educational Research and (f) Speech Link as baseline assessment providers by 30 April 2015; and which schemes were subsequently approved by her Department.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14861","14861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426291","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department examined international comparators when developing the policy of a reception baseline assessment; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14862","14862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426292","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure that military vehicle licences granted by the UK to the Egyptian government will not contribute to human rights violations.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14874","14874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426293","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much (a) Bolton and (b) Wigan councils received in government grants in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14844","14844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426294","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS England spent providing structured education courses to people living with diabetes in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14849","14849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426295","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to review the transport provision on the A5225.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14848","14848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426296","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether there has been a review of the transport provision on the A5225 in Bolton West constituency since the proposals for the Westhoughton bypass were cancelled.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14887","14887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426297","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps he has taken to tackle clustering of betting shops in town centres.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14763","14763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426298","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of £100 a spin fixed odds betting terminal gaming machines on areas of social deprivation and vulnerable people and their families.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14764","14764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426299","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what facilities are in place to enable staff based at the tax credit office in Preston to pay money out of their wages into the Guild Money Credit Union.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14910","14910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426300","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he or Ministers in his Department will attend the heats and further stages of the Bar National Mock Trials Competition.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14838","14838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426301","2015-11-09","Women and Equalities","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2015 to Question 4418, which women's (a) rugby, (b) cricket and (c) football matches she has attended in an official capacity since taking office.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14833","14833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426302","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will assess the potential merits of arms-length funding to support community journalism and independent news start-ups to promote informed citizenship.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14719","14719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426303","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when Ofcom plans to publish its report on measuring frameworks for media plurality.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14720","14720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426304","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how the Government plans to implement Lord Leveson's recommendation that regulatory authorities should be able to impose structural remedies and remedies which will change behaviour which can relate, if appropriate, to editorial independence and journalistic standards.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14742","14742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426305","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Sir Peter Hendy's work to re-plan the Network Rail enhancements programme in Control Period 5, 2014-19, takes account of maximising the journey time benefit for the South West peninsula by use of the new high-speed AT300 trains which are due to be introduced in December 2018.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14781","14781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426306","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to revise his Department's position on the European Commission's Green Paper on safety of tourism accommodation services to take account of the recent coroner's report on the death of Christi and Bobby Shepherd.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14754","14754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426307","2015-11-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2015 to Question 8364, (a) how many and (b) in which countries British military personnel were embedded in (i) each of the last five years and (ii) 2015 to date.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14819","14819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426308","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the costs and benefits to the UK of implementation of the original EU Waste Framework Directive.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14706","14706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426309","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the costs and benefits to the UK of implementation of the EU Waste Oils Directive.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14707","14707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426310","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the costs and benefits to the UK of implementation of the EU Hazardous Waste Directive.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14708","14708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426311","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 13685, if she will make an assessment of the monetary benefits arising from implementation of the revised EU Waste Framework Directive in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14733","14733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426312","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his contribution of 28 October 2015, Official Report, column 429, on junior doctors hours, if he will publish the evidential basis for the proposition that hospitals are not rostering enough junior doctors at weekends.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14875","14875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426313","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on employing junior doctors in each of the last five years; and how many junior doctors were employed in each of those years.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14841","14841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426314","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of junior doctors who have opted out of the European Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14840","14840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426315","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received about the level of junior doctor cover at weekends.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14842","14842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426316","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how he plans to assess whether clinical commissioning groups in England have met the NHS England planning guidance requirement to give real terms spending increases to mental health services in 2015-16.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14957","14957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426317","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Chief Executive of NHS England on spending on mental health services during 2015-16.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14958","14958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426318","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each clinical commissioning group spent on mental health services in England in each year from 2013-14 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14961","14961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426319","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS England spent on mental health services in England for each year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14960","14960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426320","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Chief Executive of Monitor on spending on mental health services during 2015-16.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14959","14959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426321","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include commitments on the quality and provision of urgent care in his next annual Mandate to NHS England.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14915","14915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426322","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the planned increase in the national minimum wage on the level of provision of care homes.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14705","14705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426323","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people making telephone calls to NHS 111 that were categorised as life threatening in the South East Coast NHS Ambulance Service NHS Foundation Trust area waited longer than eight minutes for a response during the project the Trust ran on how emergency calls were dealt with in winter 2014-15.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14768","14768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426324","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who has overall ministerial responsibility for meeting the objectives set out in Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, Cm9098, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14839","14839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426325","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of car parking facilities at NHS hospitals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14725","14725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426326","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) affordability for and (b) effect on (i) patients and (ii) carers of hospital car parking; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14726","14726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426327","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people caring full-time for a relative; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14774","14774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426328","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people diagnosed with anorexia nervosa or bulimia nervosa requested and were granted access to local specialist mental health in-patient beds in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14747","14747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426329","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to accept into the UK refugee children from Syria who are travelling unaccompanied within Europe.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14691","14691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426330","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of women with perinatal mental health problems had access to specialist counselling in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14686","14686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426331","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has assigned to providing mental health services for patients with stroke diagnoses for 2015-16.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14687","14687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426332","2015-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complainants have agreed to special measures applied in court in cases of (a) childhood and (b) domestic abuse in the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14685","14685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426333","2015-11-06","Department for International Development","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is developing programmes to tackle the (a) interconnectivity of domestic abuse and disability and (b) interconnections between other vulnerable groups.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14688","14688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426334","2015-11-06","Department for International Development","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department identifies vulnerable refugees with intellectual impairment; and what support is provided to such people.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14689","14689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426335","2015-11-06","Department for International Development","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much support her Department makes available to refugees who have experienced trauma.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14690","14690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426336","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of slaughterhouses have CCTV.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14746","14746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426337","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of households in East Kilbride, Strathaven and Lesmahagow constituency that have access to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14748","14748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426338","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is proposed for welfare payments made by the Scottish Government, provided for under any Act arising from the Scotland Bill, to count as income for the purposes of calculating tax credits.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14750","14750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426339","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she has taken to support the development of a sustainable and integrated small-scale renewables sector in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14786","14786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426340","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect on the competitive parity of the Northern Ireland energy sector with that sector in other countries of the UK of the decision not to introduce a small-scale feed-in tariff scheme.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14787","14787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426341","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on the need for that Executive to help increase shared and integrated education.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14783","14783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426342","2015-11-06","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on further plans to increase the provision of shared and integrated education.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14784","14784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426343","2015-11-06","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on ensuring that as many schools as possible receive Shared Education Signature Project funding.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14785","14785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426344","2015-11-06","Department for International Development","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on introducing a facility for rolling over funding in her Department's budget in order to avoid expenditure being concentrated at the end of financial years and to ensure that annual targets for development expenditure are met.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14710","14710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426345","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proposals for changes to legislation he plans to make concerning the buying and selling of consumers' personal data.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14964","14964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426346","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations he has received from (a) businesses, (b) regulators and (c) the public on the terms and conditions of the sale of products and services that concern consumers' personal and private data.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14965","14965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426347","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the viability and competitiveness of UK oil refineries of the imposition of VAT and duty on products shipped by such refineries to another UK customs bonded oil storage location at the point of departure from the refinery.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14896","14896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426348","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to equalise the treatment of UK refinery manufactured finished petroleum products compared to imported fuels when products leave the UK customs bonded oil storage location in respect of imposition of VAT and duty.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14897","14897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426349","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14899","14899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426350","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what average time her Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14900","14900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426351","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what average time her Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14901","14901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426352","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what average time her Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14902","14902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426353","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will support a UN Inquiry into human violations against the Rohingya.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14884","14884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426354","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what impact assessment she has made of the proposed closure of the Visa and Entry Clearance Office in Dhaka; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14883","14883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426355","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many midwives per 1,000 births there were in each region of England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14967","14967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426356","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many lipid clinics there are in (a) England and (b) each clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14885","14885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426357","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many lipidologists work within NHS England in (a) England and (b) each clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14886","14886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426358","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Chief Executive of NHS England about perinatal mental health services; and what plans he has to improve such services.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14962","14962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426359","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14903","14903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426360","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on maternity services in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14966","14966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426361","2015-11-06","Department for International Development","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what average time her Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14904","14904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426362","2015-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14905","14905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426363","2015-11-06","Scotland Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14906","14906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426364","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14907","14907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426365","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the extent to which emissions type approval requirements are met during normal on road usage of each category of road vehicle.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14963","14963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426366","2015-11-06","Wales Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14908","14908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426367","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14909","14909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427331","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that funding is available to maintain work opportunities for researchers in the early stages of their careers.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902104","902104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427332","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage prompt payment to small businesses.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902101","902101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427333","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that the skills of steel industry employees are maintained.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902100","902100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427334","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of investments made through the British Business Bank has been made in the North East.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902102","902102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427335","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage competition and switching between providers in consumer markets.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902105","902105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425595","2015-11-05","Attorney General","2015-11-03","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2015 to Question 10237, when he expects to publish proposals for the future of the National Debt Fund.","Biography information for Mr Nick Hurd","Mr Nick Hurd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14565","14565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425596","2015-11-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will assess the performance of the Official Receiver during the liquidation of SSI UK.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14661","14661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425597","2015-11-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have accessed the Government support package for people affected by the closure of the SSI steelworks in Redcar.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14662","14662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425598","2015-11-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Prime Minister about the value of the Government support package for people affected by the closure of the SSI Steelworks in Redcar.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14663","14663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425599","2015-11-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what criteria were used to cap the value of the Government support package to £80 million for people affected by the closure of SSI Redcar.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14664","14664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425600","2015-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support UKTI has provided to Rio Tinto in locations where Rio Tinto invests or plans to invest.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14508","14508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425601","2015-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department is providing to higher education institutions to increase the number of post-doctoral positions offered; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14549","14549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425602","2015-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to encourage retailers to source their products from ethical and sustainable sources; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14532","14532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425603","2015-11-06","Cabinet Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether it is the Government's policy to increase the membership of the House of Lords by over 100 members during the course of this Parliament.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14479","14479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425604","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the funding was for the Digital Inclusion team in his Department in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14620","14620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425605","2015-11-06","Cabinet Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2015 to Question 11489, when the Chief Data Officer will be appointed.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14622","14622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425606","2015-11-06","Cabinet Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2015 to Question 11489, if he will make available the minutes of the Data Steering Group.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14621","14621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425607","2015-11-05","Cabinet Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the suicide rate was for young men in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14567","14567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425608","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much is expected to be allocated to Northern Ireland under the National Infrastructure pipeline in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14574","14574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425609","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the size of the current account balance in 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14589","14589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425610","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects manufacturing output to exceed the level of quarter one in 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14590","14590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425611","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will ensure that any agreement on a central registry of beneficial ownership in the British Virgin Islands will include access for the public with legitimate reason, in line with the Fourth EU Anti Money Laundering Directive.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14573","14573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425612","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects there to be an announcement on the extension of the Mersey Gateway free travel scheme to residents and businesses in Cheshire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14554","14554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425613","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax returns have been filed after the deadline in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14642","14642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425614","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14476","14476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425615","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Shares for Rights scheme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14471","14471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425616","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the level at which the apprenticeship levy should be set; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14491","14491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425617","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount which the proposed apprenticeship levy will raise in (a) Warrington and (b) the North-West.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14492","14492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425618","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the additional travel costs likely to be incurred by people not resident in Halton, of commuting using the bridge, arising from the Mersey Gateway Project in the first year that bridge is open.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14500","14500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425619","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assistance he proposes to provide to small businesses in Halton in relation to the completion of the Mersey Gateway Project.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14501","14501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425620","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will extend free use of the (a) Mersey Gateway and (b) Silver Jubilee Bridge to residents and UK firms across Merseyside; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14502","14502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425621","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how many people over the age of 55 are likely to be affected by the Government's changes to tax credits.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14540","14540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425622","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in devolved administrations on the merger of income tax and national insurance.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14542","14542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425623","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how many households are likely to be negatively affected by the measures announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14537","14537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425624","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how many working households including people under 25 are likely to lose income as a result of changes he has announced to tax credits.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14536","14536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425625","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he expects revenue to be generated to the public purse from the sale of assets, buildings and land in Northern Ireland during 2015-16; and if so for what amount.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14531","14531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425626","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish an equality assessment of the Government's changes to tax credits.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14538","14538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425627","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the Government has spent on raising awareness of scam activity associated with pension freedoms.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14539","14539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425628","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effects (a) to date and (b) in the future of the institutes of technology on UK productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14606","14606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425629","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on competition between different sectors in the gaming industry of different forms of gambling taxation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14503","14503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425630","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what preparatory work his Department has undertaken in advance of sending letters to tax credit recipients on changes to tax credits.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14528","14528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425631","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Pontypridd of 9 October 2015 on the cumulative effect on working families of his reforms to tax credits and benefits.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14534","14534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425632","2015-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the likely change in the pay gap between workers under and over 25 and those older than 25 over the course of the 2015 Parliament.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14535","14535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425633","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the London Olympic council tax precept (a) has raised in each year of its existence and (b) is predicted to raise in the remaining years of its existence.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14579","14579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425634","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government's aim to build 275,000 affordable homes during this Parliament will be in addition to the Government's aim to deliver 200,000 new Starter Homes.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14609","14609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425635","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14472","14472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425636","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support the Government will give communities hosting (a) new nuclear power stations and (b) other nationally significant infrastructure projects (i) during and (ii) after construction, to ensure that they have the infrastructure necessary to support the development.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14628","14628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425637","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department provided to Croydon Council in Homeless Prevention Grant in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15 and (d) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14624","14624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425638","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there was in the number of firefighter posts in Kent Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14597","14597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425639","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there was in the number of firefighter posts in the Isle of Wight Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14598","14598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425640","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there was in the number of firefighter posts in Hampshire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14599","14599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425641","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there was in the number of firefighter posts in Royal Berkshire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14595","14595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425642","2015-11-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there was in the number of firefighter posts in Oxfordshire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14596","14596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425643","2015-11-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assistance the Government is providing for housing associations in building more affordable homes for first-time buyers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14640","14640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425644","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he has held discussions with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on privatisation of Channel 4 in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14603","14603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425645","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings he has had with Ministers from the Cabinet Office at which the privatisation of Channel 4 was discussed in August and September 2015.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14604","14604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425646","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the privatisation of Channel 4 on the independent production sector in the UK.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14557","14557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425647","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will undertake an evaluation of the effectiveness of the self-exclusion pilot schemes introduced by bookmakers in Medway and Glasgow.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14483","14483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425648","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will encourage gambling organisations to share information with each other to help identify people with gambling addictions.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14494","14494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425649","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to ensure that the advertising of sports betting alongside televised sporting events is only broadcast after the 9pm watershed.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14495","14495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425650","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has held with the Senet Group on gambling addiction; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14496","14496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425651","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will use advertising to highlight the negative effects of gambling.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14497","14497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425652","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the extent of gambling addiction in young people in England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14498","14498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425653","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Cabinet Office on privatisation of Channel 4 in the last year.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14605","14605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425654","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the uptake of outdoor recreational activities by (a) children, (b) adults and (c) pensioners; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14533","14533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425655","2015-11-06","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of military operations across Iraq in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14576","14576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425656","2015-11-06","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the total operational cost of UK overseas military bases in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14577","14577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425657","2015-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the number of spare parts his Department has for equipment no longer in use; and what steps his Department has taken to ensure that spare parts for such equipment are not held in storage.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14530","14530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425658","2015-11-06","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers left the army voluntarily in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14520","14520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425659","2015-11-06","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14473","14473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425660","2015-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 10 June 2015 and 20 October 2015 to Questions 794 and 11461, when the decision was made not to commission an investigation into the reasons for the delay between ministerial endorsement of CWS and its entry into service referred to in the conclusions of the report attached to the first of those Answers; and what the reasons for that decision were.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14674","14674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425661","2015-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2015 to Questions 11484, on Army: Scotland, for what reasons the figures cited for 6 SCOTS and 7 SCOTS do not reflect the general increase in reserve numbers forecast in the Future Reserves 2020 programme.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14675","14675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425662","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department provides to local education authorities and academy trusts when they have been the victim of fire; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14619","14619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425663","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research she has received that sex and sexual relationships education in the primary years reduces the incidence of risky sexual behaviour, exploitation and abuse of children; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14670","14670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425664","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government response: Life lessons: PSHE and SRE in schools, page 9, Cm 9121, published in July 2015, which organisations and stakeholders are being consulted in order to develop further measures to improve the quality of PSHE; whether such organisations include representatives of parent advocacy and faith groups involved in running schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14671","14671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425665","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 9 of the Government Response: Life lessons: PSHE and SRE in schools, Cm 9121, published in July 2015, when she expects to report back on progress of the quality of PSHE; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14630","14630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425666","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary school aged pupils living in the Newark area travel out of that area to attend secondary schools in (a) Tuxford, (b) Southwell, (c) Bingham, (d) Nottingham and (e) Lincolnshire.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14629","14629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425667","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to implement the conclusions of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, Cm 9098, published in July 2015, and simplify and streamline the number of qualifications.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14623","14623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425668","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of the average cost to a (a) school and (b) local authority of employing a (i) teacher and (ii) classroom assistant; and what forecast she has made of that cost in each year from 2016-17 to 2019-20.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14477","14477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425669","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that school pupils are taught the dangers of gambling addiction; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14499","14499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425670","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the average amount spent on new school textbooks in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14510","14510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425671","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the average cost of a new uniform for secondary school students.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14511","14511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425672","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to encourage more teachers with qualifications in English and mathematics to take up posts in further education colleges.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14490","14490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425673","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the amount spent on advertising campaigns aimed at teacher recruitment in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14548","14548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425674","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much public funding has been spent by Magic Breakfast in each parliamentary constituency to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14580","14580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425675","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much from the public purse has been distributed in the UK by Magic Breakfast; and what objectives have been set for that expenditure.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14581","14581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425676","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the proportion of total UK energy production likely to be sourced from fracking in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14575","14575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425677","2015-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, under what timetable she will announce the mechanism for ensuring that hydraulic fracturing cannot be conducted from wells that are drilled at the surface of sensitive areas.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14552","14552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425678","2015-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect of the freezing of the carbon price floor on the Government's projected levy expenditure under the Levy Control Framework to 2020.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14553","14553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425679","2015-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment she has made of the performance of the Warm Homes Discount Scheme.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14541","14541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425680","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that (a) all UK electricity generators and operators and (b) developers of gas plants are able to compete on a level playing field after the planned increase in interconnector capacity after 2020.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14519","14519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425681","2015-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answers of 6 July 2015 to Question 4511 and 12 October 2015 to Question 10567, if she will (a) request that OFGEM assess whether the use of conventional hydro-power in the north of Scotland offsets the extra cost per unit of supply and (b) instruct OFGEM to cancel the 2p per kW hour excess charge in that region.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14512","14512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425682","2015-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answers of 6 July 2015 to Question 4511 and 12 October 2015 to Question 10567, if she will request that OFGEM explain what its justification is for allowing a higher charge for supply in the north of Scotland.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14513","14513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425683","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that new interconnector capacity is supported by robust cost analyses.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14518","14518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425684","2015-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2015 to Question 3036, whether the estimated reduction in household bills in 2030 indicated in that Answer has changed to take into account the deal on nuclear new build with the Chinese government.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14482","14482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425685","2015-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will publish her Department's (a) estimate of projected levy expenditure under the Levy Control Framework to 2020 before the changes announced in July 2015, (b) estimate of projected levy expenditure under the Levy Control Framework to 2020 since the changes announced in July 2015 and (c) assessment of the reasons for additional expenditure arising between the two estimates.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14613","14613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425686","2015-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2015 to Question 14012, what estimate her Department has made of the number of signatories to the Waste and Resources Action Programme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14616","14616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425687","2015-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the effect on productivity of privately-funded research and development in the agricultural sector; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14572","14572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425688","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2015 to Question 14012, what estimate her Department has made of the amount spent on the Waste and Resources Action Programme in each year since that programme's inception; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14627","14627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425691","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the objectives and value of the Landfill Communities Fund; what assessment he has made of progress in the reform process of that fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14582","14582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425692","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the security situation in Sri Lanka; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14578","14578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425693","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether attacks by ISIL against Iraqi Yazidis constitute to genocide.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14608","14608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425694","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress there has been on delivering support to NATO aspirant countries since the NATO summit in Wales in 2014.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14543","14543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425695","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his oral Answer of 22 October 2015, Official Report, column 444WH, what steps he has taken to assess whether British-manufactured arms have been used in a responsible manner in Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14515","14515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425696","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his oral Answer of 22 October 2015, Official Report, column 445WH, what steps he has since taken to try and persuade the parties to the conflict to adopt an immediate ceasefire in Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14516","14516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425697","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Democratic People's Republic of Korea officials the British Embassy in Pyonyang has met in the last year; and how many such officials were women.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14505","14505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425698","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will request information from the Democratic People's Republic of Korea on the measures it has taken to meet the recommendations of the UN Universal Periodic Review.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14506","14506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425699","2015-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what diplomatic support British Embassies have provided to Rio Tinto in locations where Rio Tinto invests or plans to invest.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14507","14507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425700","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress of Pakistan in securing justice for people killed in the 2007 Mumbai attacks.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14509","14509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425701","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had on extending the list of NATO aspirant countries.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14546","14546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425702","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his objectives are at the Joint Ministerial Council during the week of 30 November 2015 in respect of central registries of beneficial ownership in the Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14547","14547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425703","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14475","14475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425704","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is his policy to (a) support the Safe Schools Declaration which arose from the Oslo conference on safe schools in May 2015 and (b) implement the Guidelines on Protecting Schools and Universities from Military Use during Armed Conflict, published by the Global Coalition to Protect Education from Attack.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14484","14484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425705","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on whether cluster munitions have been used in Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14485","14485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425706","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with the Prime Minister of India during his forthcoming visit the welfare of elephants being trained to work in the tourism industry in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14480","14480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425707","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the government of Somalia in preparations for elections in that country in 2016; and what assistance the UK has offered for those preparations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14636","14636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425708","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Burmese government about (a) human rights and (b) conduct of the election in November 2015 in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14637","14637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425709","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the potential for Russia to use submarines to monitor internet traffic through undersea cables.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14633","14633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425710","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the return to Afghanistan of Al-Qaeda.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14634","14634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425711","2015-11-05","Department for International Development","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had on preventing an outbreak of cholera in Syria.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14635","14635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425712","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his oral contribution of 28 October 2015, Official Report, column 429, on junior doctors' pay, what assessment he has made of the proportion of the junior doctor workforce that will not have their pay reduced.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14600","14600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425713","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications to the Cancer Drugs Fund from people of Bolton West constituency have been successful; and what the financial value of such applications was.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14556","14556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425714","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of suicides by young men.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14566","14566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425715","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the first patients to be treated in new facilities  at Royal Sussex County Hospital as part of the 3Ts modernisation project.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14586","14586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425716","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the incidence of TB in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14655","14655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425717","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women in each age group have been treated for endometriosis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14658","14658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425718","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of when Dose Adjustment for Normal Eating programmes will be available throughout the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14659","14659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425719","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total amount that will be spent on pay for junior doctors in 2015-16; and how many junior doctors will be employed in that year.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14585","14585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425720","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with toxic shock syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14653","14653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425721","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with manufacturers of drugs for the treatment of AIDS on preventing rises in the prices of such drugs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14654","14654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425722","2015-11-05","Cabinet Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in each age group have been diagnosed with mouth cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14656","14656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425723","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Hospital Trusts have moved out of special measures since the Care Quality Commission inspection regime was introduced; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14618","14618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425724","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had an aortic aneurysm in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14657","14657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425725","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what value of NHS property has been (a) acquired and (b) sold in each (i) parliamentary constituency and (ii) clinical commissioning group area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14612","14612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425726","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in each age group were diagnosed with hepatitis C in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14651","14651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425727","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many amputations were performed on people with diabetes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14652","14652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425728","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of (a) changes in the number of cases of, and deaths from rotavirus (b) the number of rotavirus vaccinations given each year and (c) the cost of delivering that programme of vaccinations on an annual basis since the introduction of the rotavirus vaccine in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14562","14562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425729","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with manufacturers of drugs for cancer treatment on preventing rises in the prices of such drugs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14650","14650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425730","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in each of the last five years had Tourette's syndrome.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14646","14646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425731","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people diagnosed with cancer in each of the last five years were diagnosed as a result of attending (a) A&E departments, (b) a GP appointment and (c) a consultant appointment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14647","14647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425732","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with clinical bodies on the use of oestrogen to prevent brittle bones.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14648","14648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425733","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to prevent contamination from breast implants supplied by Silimed of women who have such implants.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14649","14649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425734","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of (a) changes in the number of cases of, and deaths from pneumococcal disease (b) the number of pneumococcal conjugate vaccine (PCV) vaccinations given each year and (c) the cost of delivering that programme of vaccinations on an annual basis since the introduction of PCV in 2006.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14561","14561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425735","2015-11-05","Cabinet Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been diagnosed with lung cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14645","14645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425736","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on developing a global strategy to tackle diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14643","14643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425737","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has made to manufacturers on minimising increases in the price of insulin for treating type 1 diabetes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14644","14644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425738","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his assessment is of the effect of his contractual proposals for junior doctors on the number of hours worked by such doctors in Liverpool.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14481","14481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425739","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the average cost to the NHS of employing a (a) nurse, (b) midwife and (c) doctor; and what forecast he has made of that cost in each year from 2016-17 to 2019-20.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14478","14478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425740","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many publicly-funded cognitive behavioural therapy appointments took place in each clinical commissioning group area in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14514","14514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425741","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time for a cognitive behavioural therapy appointment was in (a) Halton, (b) Merseyside and (c) England in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14521","14521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425742","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of how many people prescribed drugs funded from the Cancer Drugs Fund are likely to be affected by the planned ending of funding for that fund in March 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14504","14504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425743","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to release estimates of NHS expenditure on mental health services for financial year 2013-14; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14551","14551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425744","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on health and social care for people aged over 65 in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14583","14583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425745","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of junior doctors currently not working weekends.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14584","14584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425746","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals, Great Britain 2014, HC 511, published on 22 October 2015, how many animals of each of the species in that paper were subjected to procedures in establishments in Scotland; and what the (a) purpose and (b) level of security was of those procedures.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14610","14610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425747","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals, Great Britain 2014, HC 511, published on 22 October 2015, how many animals of each of the species in that paper were subjected to procedures in establishments in Wales; and what the (a) purpose and (b) level of security was of those procedures.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14611","14611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425748","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to page 8 of the consultation document Tackling Exploitation in the Labour Market, published in October 2015, if she will publish research conducted by her Department that shows that there has been a shift from abuses of employment regulation towards increasingly organised criminal activity engaged in labour market exploitation over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14607","14607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425749","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of the average cost to a police authority of employing a (a) police officer and (b) police community support officer; and what estimate she has made of that cost in each year from 2016-17 to 2019-20.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14522","14522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425750","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what average time her Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14474","14474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425751","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports submitted in support of an application for naturalisation as a British citizen were found to have a counterfeit Home Office stamp purporting to grant settlement in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14486","14486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425752","2015-11-05","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to prevent jihadists recruiting young people through social media sites.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14632","14632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425753","2015-11-05","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many seizures of illegal drugs took place in the UK in each of the last five years; and what the value was of the drugs seized in each such case.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14641","14641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425754","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 September 2015 to Question 9220, if she will place in the Library a full breakdown of all refusals since May 2015 for each Standard Occupational Classification code.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14626","14626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425755","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of its annual income has been held in reserve by Hertfordshire police in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14665","14665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425756","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of its annual income has been held in reserve by Lancashire Constabulary in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14666","14666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425757","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of its annual income has been held in reserve by Thames Valley Constabulary in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14667","14667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425758","2015-11-05","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees arrived in the UK through the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme in October 2015.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14617","14617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425759","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many transit visas her Department issued to Syrian nationals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14601","14601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425760","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many student visas her Department issued to Syrian nationals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14602","14602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425761","2015-11-06","Department for International Development","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the UK is offering to Yazidi people.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14625","14625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425762","2015-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the (a) gross and (b) net amount likely to be collected through the criminal courts charge in each of the next five financial years; and how much has been collected since that charge was introduced.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14487","14487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425763","2015-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many firms have written to the Legal Aid Agency indicating an intention to challenge a decision not to award them a contract in the Criminal Duty Tender; and how many firms have issued legal proceedings in respect of that decision.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14488","14488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425764","2015-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to take steps in response to recent allegations made by a former employee of the Legal Aid Agency about irregularities regarding the staffing and process in assessing duty tender bids.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14489","14489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425765","2015-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cause of death was on each occasion when a person took their own life in prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14517","14517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425766","2015-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) maximum, (b) minimum and (c) average sentence has been for people convicted under (i) Article 137; (ii) Article 139; (iii) Article 140; (iv) Article 141 and (v) Article 142 of the Air Navigation Order 2009 to date.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14563","14563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425767","2015-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2015 to Question 10800, when the potential closures of courts will be announced; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14631","14631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425768","2015-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there have been under (i) Article 137, (ii) Article 139, (iii) Article 140, (iv) Article 141 and (v) Article 142 of the Air Navigation Order 2009 since those Articles came into effect.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14564","14564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425769","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many meetings the Prime Minister has had with his European counterparts on the Green Paper on Safety and Tourism Accommodation Services COM (2014) 464.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14614","14614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425771","2015-11-06","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-11-03","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the efficacy of removing the current policy of absent votes on demand in favour of the previous absent votes criteria for the purpose of preventing electoral fraud; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14593","14593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425772","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on the appointment of two community board members to the Dover Harbour Board; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14555","14555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425773","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many air passengers have made claims against airline companies for flight delays in each of the last five years; and how many such claims have been successful.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14638","14638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425774","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recent findings of the UK Flag Advisory Panel on reform of the UK Ship Register.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14615","14615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425775","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 15 of the Office of Rail and Road's report, Monitoring Highways England, published in October 2015, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of existing data on the delivery of the road investment programme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14673","14673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425776","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of cascading Class 319 rolling stock to Southern's Coastway Stopping services once the full fleet of Class 700 trains are in operation on the Thameslink routes.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14587","14587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425777","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that drivers on public transport are trained to assist disabled passengers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14639","14639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425778","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to issue guidance on the implementation of the EU Cross Border Enforcement Directive.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14493","14493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425779","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date he plans to implement the EU Cross Border Enforcement Directive.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14523","14523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425780","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the likely causes of changes in the size of the UK Ship Register since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14550","14550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425781","2015-11-05","Women and Equalities","2015-11-03","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what estimate she has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from her Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14560","14560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425782","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14559","14559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425783","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of the welfare budget was spent on jobseeker's allowance claimants in 2014-15.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14558","14558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425784","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Trussell Trust on the placement of Jobcentre Plus advisers in foodbanks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14588","14588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425785","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to establish whether more senior staff were involved in fraudulent misuse of the Flexible Support Fund since the dismissal of two staff from Plaistow Jobcentre in May 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14591","14591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425786","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions between 1 June 2013 and 31 May 2014 Plaistow Jobcentre paid from the Flexible Support Fund for a jobseeker's two month Zone 1-4 Transport for London Travelcard.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14592","14592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425787","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households who have claimed universal credit have also applied for an alternative payment arrangement for their housing costs; and how many such applications have been successful.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14594","14594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425788","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of the welfare budget was spent on employment and support allowance, incapacity benefit and income support claimants or universal credit claims with sickness or disability elements in 2014-15.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14568","14568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425789","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much of the welfare budget was spent on the state pension in 2014-15.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14569","14569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425790","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the welfare budget was spent on child benefit in 2014-15.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14570","14570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425791","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants in 2014-15 were not British citizens.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14571","14571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425792","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2015 to Question 11786 and the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 10360, on universal credit, whether a box for universal credit exists on NHS charges claim forms.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14672","14672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425793","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 13246, what payment is given to libraries to partner with the Department on digital inclusion.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14668","14668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425794","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 13246 on digital technology, what support universal credit provides for people without digital skills to gain them.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14669","14669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425795","2015-11-06","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make representations to his Danish counterpart on reopening the inquest into the death of commercial diver Stephen O'Malley in 2012.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14660","14660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425796","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many war veterans have applied for personal independence payment.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14529","14529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425797","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has held with food bank providers on his Department's plans to locate job advisers in food banks.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14524","14524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425798","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many job advisers he plans to locate in food banks.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14525","14525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425799","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people have been helped back to work by the Access to Work scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14526","14526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425800","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent on publicising the changes to the basic state pension to date.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14544","14544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425801","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what work his Department has undertaken with the devolved administrations on communicating to the public changes to the new state pension.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14545","14545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425802","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the Fourth Report from the Work and Pensions Committee, on Support for housing costs in the reformed welfare system, Session 2013-14, HC 720, published on 2 April 2014.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14527","14527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426878","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the building of homes for social rent.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902071","902071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426879","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made on the proposed Edinburgh City Deal.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902063","902063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426880","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent progress has been made on increasing the provision of affordable and sustainable social housing in the East of England.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902065","902065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426881","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the level of housebuilding.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902070","902070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426882","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of home ownership since 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902068","902068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426883","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department is providing to local authorities who have not adopted or updated their Local Plan.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902069","902069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425296","2015-11-04","Attorney General","2015-11-02","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from The Law Officers' Departments in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14361","14361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425297","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs in the (a) steel industry and (b) energy efficiency, solar and low-carbon heating industries at the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14351","14351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425298","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the change in the number of jobs in the energy efficiency, solar and low-carbon heating industries during 2015 to date; what estimate it has made of the equivalent change in 2016; and what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse will be of support packages provided by the Government to people who have lost or will lose their jobs in those industries.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14352","14352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425299","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of jobs lost in the steel industry in 2015 to date; what estimate it has made of how many jobs in that industry will be lost in 2016; and what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of Government support packages to help people who have lost or are likely to lose their jobs in that industry.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14353","14353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425300","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14360","14360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425301","2015-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consideration his Department has given to suspending the UK's arms export licences to Saudi Arabia in the light of the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14382","14382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425302","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the portion of loan outlay that will never be repaid by graduates who have undertaken (a) full-time and (b) part-time higher education degrees.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14357","14357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425303","2015-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on (a) businesses affected by pre-pack insolvencies and (b) employees of such businesses of such insolvencies.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14312","14312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425304","2015-11-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate he has made of the predicted default rate of university maintenance loans.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14314","14314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425305","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings he has had with (a) business and (b) trade union representatives on job losses in the (i) steel and (ii) energy efficiency, solar and low carbon heating industries since his appointment to his current position.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14280","14280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425306","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the contribution of (a) crowdfunding businesses, (b) peer-to-peer lending businesses and (c) big data businesses to the UK economy.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14290","14290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425307","2015-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government applied to the European Commission globalisation adjustment fund to secure support funding for the British steel industry plants recently closed or under threat of closure.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14404","14404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425308","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent estimate he has made of the number of graduates who are (a) unemployed and (b) not in high-skilled jobs.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14436","14436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425309","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to address rates of university students taking their own lives.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14451","14451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425310","2015-11-04","Cabinet Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the International Network for Government Science Advice on improving scientific advice within UK Departments of State based on best practice worldwide.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14408","14408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425311","2015-11-04","Cabinet Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from the Prime Minister's Office in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14356","14356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425312","2015-11-04","Cabinet Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14362","14362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425313","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the loss of tax revenues from road fund licences arising from incorrect emissions figures for Volkswagen vehicles.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14358","14358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425314","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what fiscal steps he is taking to support the Government's aim of halving the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14320","14320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425315","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made in tackling international tax avoidance.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14328","14328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425316","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much of the projected increase in spend under the Levy Control Framework for 2020-21 is directly attributable to solar energy.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14336","14336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425317","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to increase the number of simple, low risk investment products that are available to charitable organisations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14269","14269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425318","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the change in projected Government expenditure for 2020 under the Levy Control Framework resulting from the decision to freeze the level of the carbon price floor in the 2014 Budget.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14291","14291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425319","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to ensure (a) British Overseas Territories and (b) the City of London comply with international standards for transparency in tax matters.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14294","14294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425320","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of money saved for the public purse as a result of the Government's policies on tackling international tax avoidance.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14295","14295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425321","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to prevent British multinational companies avoiding tax in developing countries.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14277","14277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425322","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the establishment of a UN body to lead the re-writing of tax rules to help prevent multinational companies from avoiding paying tax in developing countries.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14278","14278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425323","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14377","14377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425324","2015-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to press for the ending of the use of EU Common Agricultural Policy payments to support Spanish bullfighting.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14392","14392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425325","2015-11-05","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's press release, Infrastructure at heart of Spending Review as Chancellor launches National Infrastructure Commission, published on 30 October 2015, what transport projects are included in the £100 billion infrastructure spending; and what the projected spend on those projects is in each year to 2020-21.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14448","14448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425326","2015-11-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to introduce a separate planning category for hostels.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14415","14415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425327","2015-11-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to introduce statutory guidance on the definition of a hostel.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14416","14416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425328","2015-11-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the likely effect on house building of the Office of National Statistics reclassifying housing associations as public sector bodies.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14417","14417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425329","2015-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward proposals to increase the level of fines available to local authorities for fly-tipping.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14335","14335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425330","2015-11-05","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-11-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many (a) EU and (b) Commonwealth citizens from which countries were registered in each London borough to vote by October 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14317","14317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425331","2015-11-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had on the statutory pubs code, and the Government's policy on pubs, with people or bodies concerned with the pubs industry.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14315","14315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425332","2015-11-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14363","14363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425333","2015-11-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14364","14364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425334","2015-11-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with FIFA officials on the candidacy of Sheikh Salman bin Ebrahim al-Khalifa for FIFA President.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14429","14429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425335","2015-11-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether it is his policy to support the candidacy of Sheikh Salman bin Ebrahim al-Khalifa for FIFA President; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14403","14403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425336","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the running costs of the British naval base in Bahrain in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18; and what proportion of those costs will be borne by the Government.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14401","14401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425337","2015-11-05","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much is planned to be spent by the (a) Government and (b) Bahraini government on the building of the new British naval base in Bahrain.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14427","14427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425338","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent to date on the new British naval base recently opened in Bahrain by the (a) Government and (b) Bahraini government; and what the value has been of services provided by the Bahraini government to that naval base.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14402","14402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425339","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2015 to Question 13499, when the Civil Aviation Authority began its review of certain aspects of the safety of operations at RAF Northolt; if he will publish the full remit of the review and its conclusions; when he expects to receive the conclusions of the review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14459","14459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425340","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14365","14365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425341","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel who took part in the Seedcorn Initiative from 2011 to 2015 and are still currently serving were based on 1 November 2015 in (a) the UK, (b) the US and (c) elsewhere.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14355","14355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425342","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the licensing agreement is between his Department and Tata Steel for the production of super bainite steel; what the potential uses are of that steel in military platforms; whether super bainite is available outside the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14296","14296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425343","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department has provided to the Baker Dearing Trust in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14304","14304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425344","2015-11-05","Department for Education","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils (a) in each age group were enrolled at each university technical college (UTC) in the 2014-15 academic year and (b) were enrolled in each UTC in September 2015.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14305","14305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425345","2015-11-04","Department for Education","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with headteachers on (a) expanding childcare and (b) developing a right for parents to request that schools provide childcare.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14268","14268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425346","2015-11-04","Department for Education","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to (a) evaluate the piloting of 30 hours free childcare from September 2016 and (b) publish the outcome of such an evaluation.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14276","14276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425347","2015-11-04","Department for Education","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of the provisions of the Childcare Bill on the number of nurseries within schools.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14279","14279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425348","2015-11-04","Department for Education","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from her Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14366","14366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425349","2015-11-04","Department for Education","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of increasing free childcare provision to 30 hours per week on (a) the number of childcare places, (b) child to adult ratios in nursery settings and (c) the number of nurseries which offer free childcare provision.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14324","14324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425350","2015-11-04","Department for Education","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effects of open-plan teaching facilities on pupils' learning; and what provision is available to assist schools with conversion of facilities from an open-plan layout where that layout is shown to be having a detrimental effect on learning.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14393","14393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425351","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the agreed terms and retail price (a) with and (b) without an RPI-annual refix are of the recently announced China/EDF deals.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14398","14398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425352","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the contractual status is of the China/EDF deals; whether those contracts make provision for their terms to be reassessed at a future date; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14396","14396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425353","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department has taken to promote Energy Efficiency Week; how her Department has worked with non-governmental organisations on such initiatives; and what the cost to the public purse was of those initiatives.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14405","14405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425354","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department was (a) consulted on and (b) approved the newly-signed nuclear energy contract between China and EDF.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14397","14397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425355","2015-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13491, if she will make it her policy to designate all the areas supplying aquifers used for drinking water as Source Protection Zones 1.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14456","14456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425356","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the risk premium negotiated with EDF energy for the waste transfer contracts covering radioactive waste from Hinkley Point C is; and what advisers her Department appointed to assist in those negotiations.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14406","14406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425357","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to her Written Statement of 21 October 2015, HCWS 257, on energy investments, what the evidential basis is for her judgement that the waste transfer contract liabilities are likely to be very low.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14469","14469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425358","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to her Written Statement of 21 October 2015, HCWS 257, on energy investments, how many waste transfer contract documents for Hinkley Point C have been agreed; where such contract documents are being published; and how many such documents will be withheld for reasons of commercial confidentiality.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14470","14470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425359","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the installed capacity required to meet the Government's 2020 renewable heat target in each year from 2015 to 2020.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14330","14330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425360","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimates her Department has made of the amount of carbon dioxide displaced as a result of the introduction of the (a) domestic and (b) non-domestic Renewable Heat Incentive.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14331","14331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425361","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the estimated cost per household will be to suppliers of having to issue an in-home display as part of the smart meter home display.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14289","14289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425362","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from her Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14367","14367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425363","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent projection her Department has made of the (a) total installed capacity and (b) generation output of each renewable electricity technology in 2020-21.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14348","14348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425364","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she has made an estimate of what the change in electricity bills will be as a result of the withdrawal of market support mechanisms for onshore wind; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14344","14344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425365","2015-11-05","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many complaints the Energy Ombudsman has received about post-installation delays for feed-in tariff payments to customers by energy companies.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14381","14381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425366","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent projections her Department has made of the (a) total installed capacity and (b) generation output of each renewable heat technology in 2020-21.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14347","14347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425367","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 13263, whether energy produced by the proposed VikingLink project would be regarded as contributing towards the carbon reduction targets in the Climate Change Act 2008.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14359","14359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425368","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate her Department has made of the amount of carbon dioxide displaced in the UK by installed renewable heat technologies.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14346","14346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425369","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2015 to Question 12313, on energy, what the proportion by age group is of those customers referred to in that Question.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14286","14286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425370","2015-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from her Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14368","14368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425371","2015-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate she has made of the amount the EU will pay farmers in the UK in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14325","14325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425372","2015-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to tackle illegal fly grazing in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14450","14450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425373","2015-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the factors contributing to the reclassification of Atlantic puffins as endangered by the International Union for Conservation of Nature.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14437","14437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425374","2015-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the UK contributes to conserving the puffin population.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14438","14438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425375","2015-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether burbots are extinct within the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14409","14409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425376","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14369","14369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425377","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent conversations he has had with his Nigerian counterpart on steps to eliminate Boko Haram.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14407","14407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425378","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) targets and (b) goals the Bahraini authorities have been asked to work towards in the reform programmes in that country funded by his Department; and what progress has been made towards achieving those goals.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14428","14428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425379","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the UK funding of Bahraini reform programmes.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14430","14430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425380","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 12951, whether all directly employed and contracted staff of his Department are contractually permitted to write to him about their employment conditions or pay without having investigatory proceedings instigated against them.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14457","14457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425381","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the effects of the recent fires in Indonesia and neighbouring countries; and what steps he he has taken to ascertain whether any UK companies are responsible for those fires.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14453","14453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425382","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much the Government has (a) spent to date and (b) allocated for future spending to (i) his Department, (ii) the Department for International Development and (iii) the UNHCR to identify people for the vulnerable Syrian Refugee Resettlement Programme.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14454","14454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425383","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much total government funding the UK contributed towards the budget of the EU in each year since 1992.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14441","14441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425384","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had during his recent visit to the Gulf states to encourage those states to increase their involvement in the (a) war against ISIL and (b) resolution of the refugee situation in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14442","14442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425385","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with (a) EU organisations, (b) UN organisations and (c) charities regarding potential partial funding of the resettlement of Chagossians in the Chagos Archipelago.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14443","14443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425386","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's primary objectives are at the upcoming Commonwealth Heads of Government meeting.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14434","14434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425387","2015-11-04","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on (a) implementing the recommendations of the Second Report of the House of Lords Select Committee on Extradition Law, Session 2014-15, HL Paper 126 and (b) agreeing a memorandum of understanding with the US concerning the treatment of people extradited from the UK as recommended in paragraph 53, with particular regard to transfer, pre-trial detention and bail.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14468","14468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425388","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons representatives from Syria were not invited to the peace talks in Vienna commencing on 20 October 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14318","14318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425389","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support people affected by the rocket attack on Camp Liberty, Baghdad, on 29 October 2015.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14332","14332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425390","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international partners on Syrian representation at the talks in Vienna on 30 October 2015.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14343","14343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425391","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Indian government on re-opening border crossings to Nepal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14391","14391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425392","2015-11-05","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government plans to take, other than by offering support to other countries in the region, to ensure that the UK meets its international obligations to refugees from the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14389","14389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425393","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the government of Saudi Arabia on ending the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14384","14384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425394","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to protect civilians in Syria.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14385","14385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425395","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department plans to take to address the political crisis in Syria before March 2016.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14388","14388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425396","2015-11-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the Government plans to use its membership of the UN Security Council to facilitate diplomatic negotiations on the protection of civilians in Syria.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14387","14387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425397","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to boost exports to (a) Indonesia, (b) Vietnam, (c) Thailand, (d) Malaysia, (e) the Philippines and (f) other countries in South East Asia.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14282","14282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425398","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that UK citizens travelling to India, Thailand and other elephant-range states are made aware of the illegal practice of capturing and breaking the spirit of baby elephants for use in the tourist industry.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14292","14292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425399","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Indian counterpart on the illegal use of bull-hooks on Asian elephants in the tourism and logging industries.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14293","14293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425400","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Ms Patricia Hart was employed on a full-time basis continuously from 2011 until her retirement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14306","14306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425401","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements he plans to put in place to ensure that medicines for rare cancers can be appropriately evaluated after the Cancer Drugs Fund ends in March 2016.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14299","14299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425402","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for how many days Ms Patricia Hart worked on the Review of the NHS Hospitals Complaints Systems in 2013.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14307","14307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425403","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of individual funding requests for access to drugs for rare cancers are refused at (a) panel and (b) screening level.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14300","14300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425404","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements he plans to put in place to assess new drugs for rare cancers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14283","14283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425405","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress is being made on the accelerated access review for drugs for rare cancers; by what date he plans for that review to be concluded; and if he will set a deadline by which arrangements must be in place for the assessment of new drugs.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14284","14284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425406","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of interim or emergency measures to provide access to drugs for rare cancers during the period of the accelerated access review.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14285","14285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425407","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2015 to Question 11045, what the evidential base is for the statement in that Answer that the planned removal of drugs from the Cancer Drugs Fund would have no or minimal impact on survival rates for certain cancers; and what his definition is of minimal impact in that context.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14273","14273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425408","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what amount of Government funding was allocated to help reduce suicide rates in each year from 1995 to 2015.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14274","14274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425409","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many suicide attempts were recorded by health bodies in England for each year from 1995 to 2015; what that number was as a proportion of the population; what the ethnic backgrounds were of those people attempting suicide; and how many of those people were previously known to mental health services.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14275","14275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425410","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans for the public consultation on the Cancer Drugs Fund to begin.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14354","14354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425411","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the meningitis B vaccine will be available for children and young people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14390","14390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425412","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of how many additional GPs will be needed to supply the Battersea-Nine Elms development; and how many such GPs are planned to be provided.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14386","14386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425413","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the benefits of psychological support for (a) patients who have received and (b) the families of patients who have received a stem cell transplant.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14267","14267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425414","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that junior doctors do not suffer a reduction in pay as a result of the Government's proposals to change junior doctors' contracts.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14327","14327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425415","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of the doctors entering core and further specialty training were in each (a) specialty and (b) training region or deanery in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14322","14322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425416","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of doctors left foundation training and entered training posts in core or specialty training in each year between 2008 and 2015.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14323","14323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425417","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many permanent gastroenterologist consultants are currently employed in the NHS.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14311","14311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425418","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 13212, by when the assurance of clinical commissioning groups' (CCG) local transformation plans by NHS England's regional teams are planned to be completed; and whether he plans that the additional £30 million that has been allocated to CCGs will be spent in full in 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14464","14464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425419","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what equality impact assessment his Department has carried out on its proposals to reform the junior doctor contract.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14463","14463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425420","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 7476, when he expects Public Health England and the National Offender Management Services' health needs assessment of all prisons to be (a) complete and (b) published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14465","14465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425421","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are currently on an NHS referral to treatment waiting list.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14439","14439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425422","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number of additional midwives that would be required to enable all women to receive one-to-one care from a midwife during labour.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14419","14419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425423","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects (a) Monitor and (b) the Trust Development Authority to publish their 2015-16 second quarter performance reports.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14420","14420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425424","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will itemise savings made by the NHS that have been attributable to the provisions of the Health and Social Care Act 2012.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14421","14421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425425","2015-11-04","Cabinet Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of fatal opioid overdoses in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14411","14411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425426","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he was made aware of the project undertaken by South East Coast Ambulance NHS Foundation Trust in winter 2014-15 relating to prioritisation of NHS 111 calls.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14422","14422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425427","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of post-release prisoners who fatally overdose on opioids.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14412","14412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425428","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he had with Monitor on South East Coast Ambulance NHS Foundation Trust's project relating to the prioritisation of NHS 111 calls in winter 2014-15 before Monitor announced it was taking action on that matter.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14423","14423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425429","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the General Medical Council on their revalidation programme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14413","14413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425430","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any patients in Hove constituency were put at risk as a result of the South East Coast Ambulance NHS Foundation Trust's project relating to the prioritisation of NHS 111 calls in winter 2014-15.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14424","14424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425431","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of locums to the NHS arising from the General Medical Council's revalidation programme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14414","14414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425432","2015-11-05","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the weekend bed occupancy rates were in each mental health hospital in London in each weekend since 1 January 2015, taking account of patients on weekend leave.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14431","14431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425433","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of potential savings to the NHS arising from an expansion of the availability of Take-Home Naloxone.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14410","14410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425434","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14370","14370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425435","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the NHS workforce he expects to receive a real-terms pay increase over the next four years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14394","14394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425436","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average number of hours worked per week by junior doctors is.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14350","14350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425437","2015-11-04","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will take steps to ensure that reductions in police funding do not lead to the cancellation of Remembrance Day parades.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14399","14399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425438","2015-11-04","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from her Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14371","14371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425439","2015-11-04","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will take steps to ensure that it is aware of the criminal histories of all people admitted into the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14395","14395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425440","2015-11-04","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many British citizens have been extradited to the US under the US-UK extradition treaty since 2010; and how many US citizens have been extradited to the UK under that treaty in the same period.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14452","14452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425441","2015-11-04","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken has been for a successful extradition request from the US administration to be implemented for deporting a person to the US since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14433","14433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425442","2015-11-05","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Scottish Qualifications Authority on accreditation of its English for Speakers of other Languages qualifications.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14303","14303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425443","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2015 to Question 12970, for what reasons estate agents that do not hold client money fall within the scope of the Money Laundering Regulations 2007.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14333","14333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425444","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-11-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce red tape affecting estate agents subject to the Money Laundering Regulations 2007.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14334","14334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425445","2015-11-05","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been identified for resettlement in the UK as part of the vulnerable Syrian refugee resettlement programme since 20 September 2015.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14380","14380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425446","2015-11-05","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on students in Orkney and Shetland of reducing the accredited English language courses available to students in the highlands and islands of Scotland.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14302","14302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425447","2015-11-04","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the money pledged by the UK at the donor conference for Palestinians in Cairo in October 2014 has reached beneficiaries in the Gaza Strip; and what that money has been spent on.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14270","14270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425448","2015-11-04","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what provisions her Department has made for (a) child and adolescent friendly spaces and (b) other psycho-social support for children affected by the humanitarian crisis in Gaza.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14271","14271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425449","2015-11-04","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what provisions her Department makes for long-term humanitarian funding for children in protracted crises (a) in Central African Republic and (b) elsewhere where aid organisations are inhibited in providing psycho-social support for children affected by armed conflict because of short-term funding cycles.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14272","14272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425450","2015-11-04","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's policy is on aid graduation when a country transitions from low to middle income status.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14345","14345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425451","2015-11-05","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent progress the Government has made on providing humanitarian assistance to Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14383","14383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425452","2015-11-05","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which funding proposals developed by multilateral development banks her Department voted against in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14460","14460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425453","2015-11-05","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department plans to spend through multilateral development banks in the next three years; how much her Department spent through such banks in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14461","14461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425454","2015-11-05","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2015 to Question 12777, what assessment she has made of whether each party to the conflict is taking reasonable steps to allow access to Yemen's ports for (a) fuel for civilian use and (b) other commercial and humanitarian goods.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14458","14458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425455","2015-11-04","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are in place to protect orphaned children from exploitation subsequent to their being taken to the UK from (a) Syria and (b) other countries and removed from their extended family.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14440","14440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425456","2015-11-04","Department for International Development","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from her Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14372","14372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425457","2015-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14373","14373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425458","2015-11-05","Home Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many convictions there have been relating to forced marriage under the Anti-Social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14455","14455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425459","2015-11-05","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions his Department has had with the Department of Health on the rate of people taking their own lives in prisons.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14466","14466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425460","2015-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the availability of staff and resources in prisons to enable (a) Christian, (b) Muslim and (c) Jewish religious services to take place.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14298","14298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425461","2015-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what financial checks are carried out on prison officers and civilian staff in prisons after their initial employment period.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14297","14297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425462","2015-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what entry level qualifications are required by prison officers.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14301","14301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425463","2015-11-04","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate she has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from her Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14374","14374"
