"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139871","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to incentivise people to use public transport since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278509","278509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139872","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost of a UK global navigation satellite system.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278448","278448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139873","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Transport on reducing emissions on UK roads.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278510","278510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139874","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the effect of the price of commuting on unemployment.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278511","278511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139875","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2019 to Question 273385 on Offenders: Electronic Tagging, when he plans to publish the quantitative process evaluation of the GPS Pilot.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278484","278484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139876","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2019 to Question 264316 on Television: Licensing, how many (a) men and (b) women  were given a prison sentence for failure to pay fines imposed for non-payment of the BBC licence fee in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278485","278485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139877","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many additional staff his Department plans to recruit to Companies House to monitor the verification process outlined in his Department's consultation on corporate transparency and register reform published on 5 May 2019.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278461","278461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139878","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's public consultation on corporate transparency and register reform published on 5 May 2019, what enhanced (a) transparency and (b) accountability will be introduced in the verification process.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278462","278462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139879","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's public consultation on  corporate transparency and register reform published on 5 May 2019, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the verification process and the cross-checking system.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278463","278463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139880","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many incidences of fraudulent use of addresses through Companies House there have been in (a) Wales and (b) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278464","278464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139881","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many incidences of directors using fictitious names through Companies House there have been in (a) Wales and (b) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278465","278465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139882","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women were sentenced to imprisonment for (a) 1 month or less, (b) 3 months or less and (c) 6 months or less for each of the offences listed in the Home Office Offence Code that his Department classifies as (i) non-violent and non-sexual offences and (ii) violent and sexual offences.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278553","278553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139883","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the £40 million fund for Chagossians has been allocated to date by his Department; for what purposes that money has been allocated; and how much of that spending has been classified as Official Development Assistance.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278525","278525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139884","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans he has to investigate alternative sources of climate finance from (a) public and (b) private sources.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278526","278526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139885","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding his Department allocated to (a) educational, (b) healthcare and (c) infrastructure projects in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278527","278527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139886","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the rollout of new software at probate registries across England and Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278565","278565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139887","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to mitigate the potential effect of the rollout of new software at probate registries across England and Wales on the length of time it takes to obtain grants of probate and letters of administration.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278566","278566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139888","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken was to obtain grants of probate and letters of administration from probate registries across England and Wales in each month in 2018 and 2019.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278567","278567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139889","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 272771 on Heart Diseases: Health Services, if he will estimate the number of patients with structural heart diseases who have been unable to access transcatheter aortic valve implantation procedures by region in each year from 2015 to 2019; and if he will make an assessment of the effect of those levels of access on the mortality rates of those patients.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278569","278569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139890","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prevent garages from parking vehicles on streets that do not a display registration plate or a visible vehicle identification numbers; and if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the powers available to the (a) DVLA, (b) the Metropolitan police and (c) local authorities in tackling that problem.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278332","278332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139891","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Defence of 25 March 2019, Official Report, column 5, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the EU Commission has publicly questioned the legality of applying article 346 to the procurement of support ships by other member states.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278412","278412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139892","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of a national definition for rural crime.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278571","278571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139893","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many BAME young people were held in young offender institutions and secure units in (a) Wales, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) England and (d) Scotland in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278614","278614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139894","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275662, what provision her Department makes for claimants who do not have access to the internet and are unable to check how their award is calculated and a breakdown of what deductions are being made.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278343","278343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139895","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Leadership Magistrates there were by (a) gender, (b) age, (c) ethnicity, (d) socio-economic background and (e) who have declared a disability in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278554","278554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139896","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the advertisement seeking to recruit Leadership Magistrates; and in what locations that advert was made publicly available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278555","278555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139897","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether a diversity monitoring form was included for completion for people applying to be a Leadership Magistrate.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278556","278556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139898","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275665 on universal credit: fraud, what recourse is available to people who without their full knowledge have had their information used to make a fraudulent claim.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278344","278344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139899","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2019 Question 275136, when Herbert Smith Freehills was added to the list of law firms enlisted to provide legal support to Post Office Limited.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278413","278413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139900","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275665 on universal credit: fraud, what steps her Department is taking to close a loophole in the online application process which enables people to make an application and claim an advance using another person’s information.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278345","278345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139901","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking with commercial broadband providers to (a) help ensure delivery of service in a timely manner and (b) support communities where there are delays in delivering a service.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278572","278572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139902","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of including injuries or deaths of road rescue and recovery operators as part of its Stats19 review.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278573","278573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139903","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will include the safety road rescue and recovery operators in the Highway Code review.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278574","278574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139904","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a fixed penalty fine for drivers who put road rescue and recovery operators at risk.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278575","278575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139905","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what total Government expenditure on legal aid has been since 1989 in (a) nominal and (b) real terms.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278557","278557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139906","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of removing VAT from social care after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278576","278576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139907","2019-07-22","Church Commissioners","2019-07-17","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to tackle problem gambling.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278399","278399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139908","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2019 to Question 231895, whether prison governors have assessed all new prisoners for learning difficulties and/or disabilities on reception since April 2019; and what proportion of the new prison population has been identified as having learning difficulties or disabilities.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278346","278346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139909","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to improve her Department's support for people with haemochromatosis in (a) England and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278593","278593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139910","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to help increase the number of care leavers (a) accessing and (b) completing a higher education award.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278347","278347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139911","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to improve support for ex-military personnel with post-traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278594","278594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139912","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the attainment of children whose family receive universal credit with all school-aged children.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278348","278348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139913","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from pensioners on the challenges they have faced when renting a home from a private landlord.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278349","278349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139914","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2019 to Question 274454, whether his Department plans to collect data which would enable an assessment of the amount of apprenticeship levy money that was (a) paid by and (b) spent on apprenticeships by screen industry companies in financial year 2018-19.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278393","278393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139915","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assistance is available to parents of disabled children who need additional childcare during the school summer holidays.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278350","278350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139916","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Bangladeshi counterpart on the imprisonment of opposition leader Khaleda Zia.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278383","278383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139917","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to prevent insolvency; and what assessment he has made of the disparity in insolvency rates between (a) regions of England and Wales and (b) men and women.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278351","278351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139918","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to help support police officers who are experiencing mental health difficulties.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278352","278352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139919","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle the financial imbalance in donations received by state schools in affluent areas and those in poorer areas.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278353","278353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139920","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the jurisdiction of the (a) Information Commissioner’s Office and (b) Ofcom to the development of an age appropriate design code of practice for online services.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278394","278394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139921","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants of universal credit that have taken an advance payment have seen payments reduced by (a) up to 20 percent (b) between 21 and 30 per cent, (c) 31 to 40 per cent and (d) over 40 percent of the initial amount in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278385","278385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139922","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Ministers in his Department have held recent meetings with representatives of the Greater Manchester Fire and Rescue Service on proposals to reduce the number of fire stations and engines in the Manchester city region; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278384","278384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139923","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the proportion of ill-health related job losses that have been attributed to (a) mental ill and (b) physical ill health in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278386","278386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139924","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has made an assessment of the effect of trends in the level of poverty on the health of children and young people throughout the UK.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278519","278519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139925","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has allocated to further education colleges in Yorkshire and Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278595","278595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139926","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the conclusions in the report entitled, State of Child Health: Two years on, published by the Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278520","278520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139927","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the review of the definition of positions of trust in the Sexual Offences Act 2003 will conclude in the summer.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278517","278517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139928","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether positions of trust as defined in the Sexual Offences Act 2003 will be extended to cover all adults with power and authority over young people as defined in the Safeguarding Vulnerable Groups Act 2006.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278518","278518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139929","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will include a target to reduce childhood obesity inequality in the Green Paper on Prevention.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278521","278521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139930","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the amount of ethanol in petrol sold to reduce carbon emissions.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278404","278404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139931","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will introduce a children and young people's health strategy to link policies that affect child health and to tackle the social determinants of health outcomes.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278522","278522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139932","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of cricket pitches that have been sold for (a) housing development and (b) other commercial development since 2010.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278596","278596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139933","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NICE’s multiple technology appraisal process can be applied to treatments evaluated through NICE’s highly specialised technologies appraisal programme.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278512","278512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139934","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of victims of modern slavery in prison.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278558","278558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139935","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of child victims of modern slavery in custody.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278559","278559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139936","2019-07-22","Attorney General","2019-07-17","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate his Department made of the number of victims of modern slavery who have been charged with a criminal offence committed in connection to their being a victim of slavery.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278560","278560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139937","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women sentenced to prison for theft from shops received sentences of (a) less than one month, (b) less than three months, (c) less than six months, (d) less than 12 months and (e) 12 months or more.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278561","278561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139938","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what tendering process was followed prior to inclusion of Herbert Smith Freehills in the list of law firms able to provide legal services to Post Office Limited.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278414","278414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139939","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Clinical Commissioning Groups adhere to the guidance on patient needs to provide continued access to IVF treatment for patients.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278588","278588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139940","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on pupils using private tutors as scribes in (a) GCSE and (b) A level exams.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278513","278513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139941","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the equity of access to IVF treatment across (a) Clinical Commissioning Group and (b) post codes.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278589","278589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139942","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) children and (b) children eligible for free school meals reached a good level of development at age five in Norwich South in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278562","278562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139943","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many times he has met with the (a) Premier League and (b) Football Association to discuss improving (i) financial transparency and (ii) football regulation in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278488","278488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139944","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent diplomatic steps his Department has taken to help preserve rainforests.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278388","278388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139947","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the number of deaths and serious injuries per mile travelled experienced in (a) motor cars, (b) motor cycles and (c) motor scooters.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278389","278389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139948","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using drones to detect defects in roads.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278390","278390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139949","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what records his Department holds on cases of identity theft affecting company directors because their home addresses and dates of birth were disclosed through Companies House.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278466","278466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139950","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July to Question 273388 and with reference to the 2015 report of the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills entitled Research and development: relationship between public and private investment, whether his Department has conducted further analysis since the publication of that report on the finding that an extra £1 of public funding would give rise to an increase in private funding of between £1.13 and £1.60.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278489","278489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139951","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 273388, what (a) discussions he has had with and (b) advice he has received from UK Research and Innovation on the quantitative relationship between (i) public and (ii) private sector investment in science.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278490","278490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139952","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the rearing and sale of lamb and mutton of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278469","278469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139953","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingency plans his Department has made in relation to sheep that are not sold to the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278470","278470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139954","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure his Department will have adequate cold storage facilities available for the storage of sheep meat in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278471","278471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139955","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure adequate amounts of animal feed are available to feed sheep that are not sold to the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278472","278472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139956","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has in place to deal with sheep meat that is not sold into the EU as a result of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278473","278473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139957","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual budget was for the Royal Fleet Auxiliary in each financial year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 278613","278613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139188","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many UK companies have been issued with a licence to sell cannabis products for the NHS.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277762","277762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139189","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ring-fence a proportion of the revenue from Vehicle Excise Duty for projects to improve air quality.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277795","277795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139190","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the ProjectPolish schools project on Poland.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277694","277694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139191","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with his French counterpart on handling traffic from roll-on, roll-off ferry services originating from Dover and arriving at the Port of Calais in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277708","277708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139192","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with eating disorders receive treatment based on their mental state.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277857","277857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139193","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he is having with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on a long-term and sustainable funding package for the extension of PrEP trials.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277792","277792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139194","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on a small investment for public health budgets to increase the provision for PrEP trials.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277793","277793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139195","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much and what proportion of UK Guarantees Scheme guarantees issued to date have been allocated to road projects in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277663","277663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139196","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding was allocated to (a) Northern Ireland, (b) Scotland and (c) Wales from the National Productivity Investment Fund in (i) 2017-18, and (ii) 2018-19.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277664","277664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139197","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of delinking basic payments from the land as outlined in paragraphs 91 to 99 of the explanatory notes to the Environment Bill on patterns of land ownership in rural areas.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277626","277626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139198","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many planning applications on Green Belt land in (a) Walsall South constituency and (b) England have been referred to the National Planning Unit in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277719","277719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139199","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 170 of his Department's Annual Report 2018-19 on the increased NHS resource budget and to the Written Statement on NHS Workforce made on 21 March 2018, HCWS574, if he will clarify when the additional £4.2 billion was agreed by the Chancellor for the NHS Agenda for Change three year pay deal.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277749","277749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139200","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits to public health of stopping the advertising of high sugar milk and milk-replacement products on public transport.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277679","277679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139201","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department paid in overtime payments to (a) directly employed and (b) agency staff in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277786","277786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139202","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of prisoners being released on temporary licence on the supply of drugs into prisons.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277693","277693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139203","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase levels of IT literacy to help prevent the spread of malware and ransomware.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277667","277667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139204","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government remains on track to meet its target of ending rough sleeping in England by 2027.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277668","277668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139205","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when the tourism sector deal will be implemented; and if it will prioritise the regeneration of seaside towns.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277784","277784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139206","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to undertake a review of business rates and their effect on the sustainability of the retail sector.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277816","277816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139207","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis in receipt of disability living allowance who (a) underwent a reassessment and (b) made a new application for personal independence payments had their (i) application rejected and (ii) award reduced as a result of an informal observation made by the assessor in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277818","277818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139208","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis in receipt of disability living allowance in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Wales and (d) England appealed a decision at tribunal relating to a reassessment for personal independence payments and had that decision overturned (i) by her Department before the date of that tribunal and (ii) by that tribunal in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277819","277819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139209","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Wales and (d) England who made a new application for personal independence payments appealed the decision made by her Department at tribunal and had that decision overturned by (i) her Department before the date of the tribunal and (ii) the tribunal in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277820","277820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139210","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Battersea Cats and Dogs Home report on Pet friendly properties, if his Department will issue guidance for local authorities on pets in social housing.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277609","277609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139211","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Battersea Cats and Dogs Home report on Pet friendly properties, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits of pet ownership for social housing tenants.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277610","277610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139212","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding allocated to local councils for the provision of (a) support and (b) advice to families and young people in a financial crisis.","Biography information for Suella Braverman","Suella Braverman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277782","277782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139213","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps is he taking to reduce the number of emergency cancer diagnoses in County Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277701","277701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139214","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will commission a fully-funded long-term cancer workforce plan for the NHS to help ensure increased patient demand is met.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277702","277702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139215","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will introduce a 9pm watershed on advertising of junk food products on (a) TV and (b) on-demand services.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277703","277703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139216","2019-07-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress he has made on ensuring reciprocal mobility agreements between the UK and the EU for people in the music industry that require short-term visas after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277712","277712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139217","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure funding for Clinical Commissioning Groups is equitable and protects patient outcomes.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277858","277858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139218","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the stop and search powers available to Merseyside Police officers who suspect an individual of carrying a knife.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277650","277650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139219","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent representations he has received from the medical technology sector on the capacity of Notified Bodies to meet the demand for their services under the provisions of the Medical Devices Regulation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277763","277763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139220","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to seek an extension to the implementation period of the Medical Devices Regulation from the EU.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277764","277764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139221","2019-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of the Hong Kong Government's policing of the recent protests against the proposed extradition law with sections of the Sino-British Joint Declaration of 1984 on rights and freedoms related to (a) speech, (b) assembly, (c) the press, (d) movement, (e) correspondence, (f) travel, (g) to strike and (h) academic research.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277805","277805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139222","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the equity of the distribution of research and development spending for areas with poor health outcomes.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277765","277765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139223","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the Government's target of increasing research and development funding to 2.4 per cent of GDP benefits the areas with the poorest health outcomes, particularly parts of the north of England.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277766","277766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139224","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made against his Department’s commitment, as set out in the 2018 Loneliness Strategy, to test methods that will improve how a range of organisations, such as community pharmacies, social workers and community nurses, refer into existing social prescribing services and provision in 2019-20.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277685","277685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139225","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made against his Department’s commitment, as set out in the 2018 Loneliness Strategy, to improve knowledge sharing among social workers through the Chief Social Worker for Adults to develop social workers’ (a) ability to recognise people who may be experiencing loneliness and (b) their knowledge and services or support to refer people on to.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277686","277686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139226","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made against his Department’s commitment, as set out in the 2018 Loneliness Strategy, for Public Health England to reach one million members of the public with information on loneliness as a key risk factor for mental health problems.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277687","277687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139227","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the 2018 Loneliness Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to work with the Loneliness Action Group to share learning on loneliness and ensure effective implementation of the strategy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277688","277688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139228","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people with (a) sickle cell disease and (b) sickle cell disease and (i) stroke, (ii) chronic kidney disease, (iii) end-stage renal disease and (iv) pulmonary hypertension received social care support in the latest period for which figures are available; and what the annual cost is of providing that support to people in each of those groups.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277689","277689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139229","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce the burden of business rates on (a) retailers and (b) businesses in Blaydon constituency.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277817","277817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139230","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health and Social Care of 15 May 2018, Official Report, column 111WH, what progress has been made in discussions with NHS Digital on what data can be made accessible via the mental health dataset waiting times for attention deficit hyperactivity disorder assessments.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277852","277852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139231","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what account is taken of income from compensation payments under the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme in employment and support allowance calculations.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277751","277751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139232","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his South African counterpart in the (a) recent trends in the level of violence and murder in Cape Town and (b) the potential consequences for visitors from the UK of those matters.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277665","277665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139233","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's consultation on cleaner domestic burning of solid fuels and wood in England, what different types of PM2.5s released when burning (a) smokeless briquettes, (b) wet wood, (c) dried wood and (d) house coal on open domestic fires in England his Department is assessing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277779","277779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139234","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the use of alkaline hydrolysis as an alternative to traditional cremations.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277785","277785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139235","2019-07-22","Women and Equalities","2019-07-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to her Department's response to the Fifth Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Sexual harassment in the workplace, HC725,  what progress her Department has made on collating data on the (a) prevalence and (b) type of workplace sexual harassment.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277794","277794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139236","2019-07-22","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to paper (a) DEP2019-0710 and (b) DEP2019-0711 that were placed in the Library, what the expiry dates were for each of the extant Open Individual Export Licences under review.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277815","277815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139237","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many apprenticeship starts in England were funded by the NHS in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19 at each apprenticeship level.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277722","277722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139238","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of waiting time targets achieved by Queen Elizabeth Hospital Birmingham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277806","277806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139239","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with his Welsh counterpart on ensuring all UK ports are prepared for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277856","277856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139240","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential health benefits of adding an assessment of fire toxicity to fire safety tests for upholstered products and construction materials.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277634","277634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139241","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits to air quality of introducing fire toxicity assessments to fire safety tests of upholstered goods and construction materials.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277635","277635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139242","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the farming and agriculture industry in (a) the UK, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) Haltemprice and Howden constituency.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277642","277642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139243","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the shared ownership model for housing development.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277643","277643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139244","2019-07-18","Department for International Development","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to help eradicate polio in (a) Afghanistan and (b) Pakistan.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277648","277648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139245","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many workers employed by his Department are paid less than the Living Wage Foundation London living wage.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277710","277710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139246","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to gain Living Wage Foundation accreditation as a living wage employer.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277711","277711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139247","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to assist local authorities to increase the (a) provision and (b) affordability of childcare for disabled children in the school summer holidays.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277636","277636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139248","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to increase the (a) provision and (b) affordability of childcare for children of working parents in school summer holidays.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277637","277637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139249","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of schools that will obtain funding from his Department's £6 million fund for training on relationships and sex education; what assessment he has made of the adequacy of this fund to support primary and secondary school teachers to provide LGBT-inclusive teaching; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277695","277695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139250","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has made an estimate of the cost to his Department of making relationships education, sex and relationships education and health education a subject-specialism teacher training course; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277696","277696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139251","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that his Department's supplementary guidance on teaching relationships education in primary schools is inclusive of LGBT people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277697","277697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139252","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will discuss with the Chancellor of the Exchequer increasing funding for relationships and sex education in schools in the spending review.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277698","277698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139253","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will ensure that subject leads at every school receive in-person, inclusive training on relationships and sex education.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277699","277699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139254","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2019 to Question 243385 on Personal, Social, Health and Economic Education, whether the material and training for schools will include (a) testing for sexually transmitted infections (STIs), (b) the potential effects of STIs on those who contract them, (c) the treatment of STIs and (d) how STIs are transmitted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277700","277700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139255","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made on the cost effectiveness of installing three-phase electricity supplies in (a) new and (b) existing homes.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277717","277717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139256","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Energy and Clean Growth on 16 July 2019, what information his Department holds on the functions of those 400,000 green jobs.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277596","277596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139257","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made on the feasibility on subsidising the cost of upgrading single-phase electricity suppliers to three-phase electricity suppliers to support people to make their homes carbon neutral.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277718","277718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139258","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to improve accessibility at Luton station.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277706","277706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139259","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the value of tourism to Scotch whisky distilleries to the UK economy.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277769","277769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139260","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the contribution to UK tourism of the Scotch whisky industry’s investment in distilleries and visitor centres.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277770","277770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139261","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of the role of Scotch whisky as an export product in increasing UK access to high-value overseas markets.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277771","277771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139262","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has of the contribution of Scotch whisky to the UK's food and drink exports market.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277772","277772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139263","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of adopting land-use industrial policy measures to support specific clusters within the manufacturing industry.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277651","277651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139264","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many calls have been made to his Department's body fluid exposure and sharps Injury telephone helpline in each month since December 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277787","277787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139265","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many calls have been made to his Department's Body Fluid Exposure and Sharps Injury telephone helpline by each prison in each month since December 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277788","277788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139266","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions have prison staff calling the Body Fluid Exposure and Sharps Injury telephone helpline been advised to attend A&E in each month since December 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277789","277789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139267","2019-07-18","Cabinet Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of goods procured by the Government were manufactured in the UK in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277652","277652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139268","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pending the roll out of new rules on General Licences, what guidance his Department issues on permitted activities in (a) Special Areas of Conservation and (b) Special Protection Areas.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277603","277603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139269","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on salmon stocks in English rivers of seals.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277604","277604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139270","2019-07-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research programmes on the decline of salmon stocks in English rivers his Department is currently allocating funding to.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277605","277605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139271","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Energy and Clean Growth of 16 July 2019, Official Report, column 693 and his statement that there is no point in trying to impose green technology on local communities if they are not in support of that for the future, what recent assessment he has made of level of community support for onshore wind.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277597","277597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139272","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what transport infrastructure the Government is supporting to help the manufacturing industry grow.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277653","277653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139273","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what is the cost to the public purse is for the maintenance work on the Severn Beach line planned for July and August 2019; and what additional maintenance work is planned for that line.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277704","277704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139274","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate she has made of the number of women's refuges that have closed since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277638","277638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139275","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value was of credit guarantees provided by the Government to the manufacturing industry in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277654","277654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139276","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Energy and Clean Growth on 16 July 2019, what information his Department holds on the types of jobs that will be included in the two million additional green jobs that potentially will be available by 2030.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277598","277598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139277","2019-07-23","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has formally responded to the letter on the implementation of the recommendations of the Augar Review signed by 203 College Principals.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277649","277649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139278","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of (a) reducing and (b) simplifying the tax burden for independent retailers.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277669","277669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139280","2019-07-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the potential environmental effects of deep-sea mining.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277681","277681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139281","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 09 July 2019 to Question 275188 on Eating Disorders: Mental Health Services, on what date NHS England plans to begin testing four-week waiting times for adult and older adult community mental health teams.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277720","277720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139282","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Oxford to Cambridge Expressway road will be subject to a strategic environmental assessment.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277839","277839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139283","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 09 July 2019 to Question 275188 on Eating Disorders: Mental Health Services, if he will publish a list of the local areas in which NHS England plans to begin testing four-week waiting times for adult and older adult community mental health teams.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277721","277721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139284","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) major routes and (b) feeder roads are classified as (i) projects or (ii) programmes for the purposes of determining whether they require strategic environmental assessments.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277840","277840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139285","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the benefit to cost ratio of the Oxford to Cambridge expressway road is; and whether that ratio is comparable with other transport proposals under review.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277841","277841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139286","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the benefit to cost ratio of the Oxford to Cambridge Expressway road includes the (a) cost and (b) effect of (i) new feeder roads and (i) increases in road capacity.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277842","277842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139287","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Oxford to Cambridge Expressway project on the Government's greenhouse gas emissions targets.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277843","277843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139288","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of compulsory teaching of information technology until the age of 16.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277670","277670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139289","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of teaching coding in primary schools.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277671","277671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139290","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to reintroduce young apprenticeships.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277672","277672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139291","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what opportunities he has identified for further bilateral trade co-operation with Israel after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277705","277705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139292","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure the safety of those who serve on HMS Queen Elizabeth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277834","277834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139293","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of fixing the (a) propulsion problem and (b) leak on board HMS Queen Elizabeth.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277835","277835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139294","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment she has made of the ability of HMS Queen Elizabeth to protect UK military interests.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277836","277836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139295","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking with Calea UK Limited to ensure that (a) outpatients and (b) inpatients who are reliant on total parenteral nutrition are able to access the supplies and equipment they need.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277742","277742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139296","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Mansion House dinner speech on 20 June 2019, what his timeframe is for his Department to issue a second sovereign sukuk; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277780","277780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139297","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of using sukuk to finance infrastructure projects; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277781","277781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139298","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the closure of the Crown post office in Luton on the accessibility to biometric information services for visa or immigration applications.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277707","277707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139299","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number and proportion of prison staff who are signed-off from work with stress or other work-related illnesses.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277660","277660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139300","2019-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the evidence of torture in the Democratic Republic of the Congo submitted to his Department by the Freedom From Torture charity.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277753","277753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139301","2019-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of the use of torture against political activists by the Government of the Democratic Republic of the Congo.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277754","277754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139302","2019-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will make the eradication of torture in detention settings a priority for the Government's engagement with the Government of the Democratic Republic of the Congo.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277755","277755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139303","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the BBC on requiring people in care homes to purchase TV licences; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277633","277633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139304","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number and proportion of police officers who are signed-off from work with stress and work-related illness.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277661","277661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139305","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275643 on Railways: Surveys, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of updating the National Rail travel survey.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277594","277594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139306","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275643 on Railways: Surveys, if he publish the titles of the working documents his Department has developed that are based on information from National Rail Travel Survey December 2010.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277595","277595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139307","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the potential reduction in emissions from aviation as a result of reduced stacking in the event of the completion of a third runway at Heathrow airport.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277662","277662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139308","2019-07-18","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timeframe is for the (a) commencement of training on the use of PAVA spray and (b) roll-out of PAVA spray to staff in HMP Wakefield.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277743","277743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139309","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his has taken to implement the recommendations of the 2014 report entitled, National Review of Asthma Deaths.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277744","277744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139310","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken in response to the publication of three Regulation 28 (Prevention of Future Death) Reports on asthma deaths since 2015.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277745","277745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139311","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the publication of three regulation 28 (Prevention of Future Death) Reports on asthma deaths, what steps he is taking to ensure that severe asthma sufferers are referred to specialist services.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277746","277746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139312","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure compliance with NICE guidelines on Quality Statement 4 of Quality Standard 25 on Asthma in relation to the a person having a follow-up appointment with their GP within two working days of treatment in an emergency care setting for an asthma attack.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277747","277747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139313","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257660 on Asthma: Health Services, what processes he plans to put in place to ensure appropriate referrals of NHS patients to specialist centres for severe asthma services.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277748","277748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139314","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2019 to Question 276277 on Immigration: Windrush Generation, what the criteria of proportionality will be when applied to people applying to the Windrush compensation scheme.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277850","277850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139315","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2019 to Question 276276, whether the reasons for a decision sent to a claimant will include HMRC and DWP data checks on the claimant's employment or benefits history.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277851","277851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139316","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many responses his Department has received to the call for evidence on violence and abuse toward shop workers which closed on 28 June.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277825","277825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139317","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the cyber security implications of permitting DNS over HTTPS resolvers operating in the UK to reside outside of UK jurisdiction.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277853","277853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139318","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on online safety of the (a) DNS and (b) HTTPS protocol.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277854","277854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139319","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he as made on aligning the Cancer Alliances and Integrated Care Systems footprints as a result of the recommendations in the NHS Long-Term Plan.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277611","277611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139320","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Mansion House speech of 20 June 2019, when he plans to issue a second sovereign sukuk; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277615","277615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139321","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of using Islamic financial certificates, sukuk to finance infrastructure projects without adding to Government debt on the public sector balance sheet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277616","277616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139322","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 275205 on Shipping: Exhaust Emissions,  what estimate has he made of the capital expenditure required by a port to fund a berth for electric charging of vessels.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277752","277752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139323","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the liability for the whole rent of a property is reflected in the calculation of universal credit in cases where a claimant of universal credit in a joint tenancy remains after a partner leaves; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277617","277617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139324","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure people liable under the Child Maintenance Service's Direct Pay category pay (a) in full and (b) on time.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277773","277773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139325","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many members of staff worked (a) for the Child Maintenance Service and (b) in the financial investigations unit of that Service in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277774","277774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139326","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government has allocated to the Metropolitan Police Service in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277612","277612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139327","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what development outcomes his Department has set for the aid-funded Investment Promotion Programme.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277826","277826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139328","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what criteria were used to select India, the Philippines, South Africa and Nigeria as the main target countries for his Department's Investment Promotion Programme.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277827","277827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139329","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what analysis his Department conducted on the effectiveness of public private partnerships before it rolled out the Investment Promotion Programme.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277828","277828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139330","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether UK businesses are eligible to apply for funding from the Investment Promotion Programme.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277829","277829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139331","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the level of demand for participation in the PrEP Impact trial in London.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277796","277796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139332","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what consultation his Department conducted to inform the design of the Investment Promotion Programme.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277830","277830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139333","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what additional funding his Department will allocate to the NHS to fund the expansion of the PrEP Impact trial.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277797","277797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139334","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what additional funding his Department will allocate to local authorities to fund additional sexual health appointments as a result of the expansion of the PrEP Impact trial.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277798","277798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139335","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if it is his Department’s policy that there should be continuous delivery of PrEP for participants after the conclusion of the PrEP Impact trial.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277799","277799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139336","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of teachers of the deaf in teaching deaf children.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277613","277613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139337","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the number of teachers of the deaf to ensure deaf children are supported in financial year (a) 2019-20, (b) 2020-2021 and (c) 2021-2022.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277614","277614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139338","2019-07-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to limit job losses as a result of (a) further William Hill (b) other bookmakers branch closures.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277775","277775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139339","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the advice provided in the European Commission recommendations document EU 2019/1019, on reducing CO2 emissions, is distributed widely throughout the construction industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277627","277627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139340","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that all people entitled to radiotherapy in North Staffordshire are able to access that treatment.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277673","277673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139341","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on what date he plans to publish the consultation on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277846","277846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139342","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fixed penalty fines have been issued to electric scooter riders by police in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277623","277623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139343","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with (a) the Mayor of London, (b) the Metropolitan Police and (c) Transport for London on the enforcement of the regulations governing the use of electric scooters on roads, pavements and cycle highways.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277624","277624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139344","2019-07-22","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on (a) consumers and (b) businesses of the September 2019 deadline for the introduction of multi-factor authentication on electronic payments.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277802","277802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139345","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will ask the Office for Product Safety and Standards to (a) undertake an urgent review of and (b) support Electrical Safety First campaign to improve the regulation of electrical goods sales.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277803","277803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139346","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the funding allocated to the UK Shared Prosperity Fund will be equivalent in real terms to those EU funding streams it will replace.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277847","277847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139347","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Transport on the regulation of the use of electronic scooters.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277625","277625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139348","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of reinstating the employment and support allowance and universal credit work-related activity component.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277674","277674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139349","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing a disability element to universal credit to replace disability premiums.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277675","277675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139350","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of employment support projects that are funded by the European Social Fund.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277848","277848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139351","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that recalled products are not subsequently available to purchase online.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277804","277804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139352","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Clean Maritime Plan, published 11 July 2019, whether the zero-emission shipping target applies to international or domestic shipping.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277709","277709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139353","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which of the recommendations in the Report of the Task and Finish Group on Taxi and Private Hire Vehicle Licensing the Government plans to adopt.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277809","277809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139354","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timeframe is for the Government's implementation of the recommendations in the Report of the Task and Finish Group on Taxi and Private Hire Vehicle Licensing.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277810","277810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139355","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps his Department has taken to simplify the forms used to claim benefits.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277676","277676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139356","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information he holds on the number of UK households that have installed (a) additional and (b) replacement loft insulation in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277628","277628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139357","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what legislative proposals the Government plans to bring forward in relation to the recommendations in the Report of the Task and Finish Group on Taxi and Private Hire Vehicle Licensing.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277811","277811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139358","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2019 to Question 268953 on Employment: Taxation, which elements of the Check Employment Status for Tax (CEST) online guidance tool were tested; how were they tested; and who tested them.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277599","277599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139359","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which projects currently in receipt of EU funding will continue to receive the same level of funding under the UK Shared Prosperity Fund in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277849","277849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139360","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent steps her Department has taken to ensure that service members are directed to support services if required when leaving the armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277821","277821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139361","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding for special educational needs his Department has allocated from the public purse to schools in Barnsley in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277812","277812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139362","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding for special educational needs his Department has allocated from the public purse to schools in South Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277813","277813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139363","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will meet the Chancellor of the Exchequer to discuss increasing support for charities and other advice agencies to ensure that they are able to assist people in completing all disability benefit application forms.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277677","277677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139364","2019-07-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the delivery of the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277822","277822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139365","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on the joint scoping exercise carried out by NHS England and NHS Improvement on the review of non-emergency patient transport services.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277750","277750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139366","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to work with medical practitioners to improve the quality of medical evidence for benefits claimants.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277678","277678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139367","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 April 2019 to Questions 242132 and 242133 on Ophthalmic Services, what assessment he has made of the merits of having a tariff for combined trabecular bypass and cataract procedure that does not cover the cost of a combined procedure; and if his Department will publish the reference cost for the 2017-2019 national tariff for BZ91.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277723","277723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139368","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps he has taken to improve the health and safety of prison staff.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277823","277823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139369","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 2 April 2019 to Question 236381, what steps NHS England has taken to fill the gap left by the closure of the Commissioning Support Programme for those treatments that are awaiting review by the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277724","277724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139370","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the closure of the Commissioning Support Programme on treatments within NHS England’s Clinical Commissioning Policy programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277725","277725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139371","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to include women who are at risk of contracting HIV in the PrEP impact trial.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277726","277726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139372","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what response his Department has provided to the Prevention of Future Deaths report on the death of  Sophie Holman.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277727","277727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139373","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking in response to the death of Ella Kissi-Debrah to (a) improve asthma care and (b) monitor and reduce the effect of air pollution on asthma outcomes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277728","277728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139374","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans the UK's International Ambassador for Human Rights has to (a) promote to partner countries and (b) publicly reinforce the findings of the UN Special Rapporteur on the right to education on the provision of public education and regulation of private involvement in education presented to the UN Human Rights Council in July 2019.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277831","277831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139375","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will make an assessment of the implications for the Government's policies of the finding of the UN Special Rapporteur on Education presented to the UN Human Rights Council in July 2019 that public-private partnerships in education that focus on involving private actors for service delivery have empirically largely failed, in particular in fragile countries.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277832","277832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139376","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that asthma sufferers are referred for specialist treatment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277729","277729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139377","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257660 on Asthma: Health Services, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of NHS treatment for people with severe asthma.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277730","277730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139378","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase the number of severe asthma centres.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277731","277731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139379","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to monitor the safety of the prescription of short-acting beta agonists.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277732","277732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139380","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to monitor the safe prescription of oral corticosteroids to treat asthma.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277733","277733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139381","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to establish a medical consensus on the management of CIN2 cervical cell changes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277734","277734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139382","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he has taken in response to the April 2019 High Court judgment on the 45 day limit for support for victims of modern slavery; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277641","277641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139383","2019-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the recently announced £4 million programme for English language teaching in sub-Saharan Africa will be funded  from the Official Development Assistance budget.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277833","277833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139384","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to regulate the use of loot boxes in online games aimed at children.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277807","277807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139385","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions his Department has had with devolved Administrations in (a) Wales and (b) Scotland on policies to tackle loneliness.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277735","277735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139386","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 274432 on Waste Heat Recovery, in what ways the entries for certain flue gas heat recovery systems have not been calculated in full accordance with the standard BRE methodology.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277629","277629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139387","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many times the cross-government ministerial group on loneliness has met since the publication of the loneliness strategy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277736","277736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139388","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 274430 and with reference to paragraph two of the Building Research Establishment (BRE) document FGHRS Data Processing Changes Relating to Canetis GasSaver GS2 Data Record held in Products Characteristics Database, dated October 2018, if he will require the BRE to publish the method used to assess that technology.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277630","277630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139389","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has met the Loneliness Action Group to discuss the implementation of the loneliness strategy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277737","277737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139390","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 272120, if he will make an assessment of the compatibility of his statement that the BRE has not changed the assessment with the BRE's statement in its 7 February 2018 article that There is therefore an increased risk that boilers will in fact be non-compliant.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277631","277631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139391","2019-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has recently worked with the US Administration on tackling racism globally.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277767","277767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139392","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to set a quantitative target for reducing loneliness.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277738","277738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139393","2019-07-22","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether it is his Department's policy that food which meets the standards of the US Food and Drug Administration’s food defect levels handbook guidance will be saleable in the UK in the event of a free trade agreement with the US.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277768","277768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139394","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2019 to Question 258964, how the variable features of a household heating system described in that Answer affect the efficiency of the boiler rather than the heating system.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277632","277632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139395","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made on the commitment in the loneliness strategy to (a) include loneliness in the guidance for the family test and (b) embed consideration of loneliness and relationships throughout the policy-making process.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277739","277739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139396","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the use of the term non-physical to refer to people with hidden disabilities in the new Blue Badge guidance on the well-being of people with (a) myalgic encephalomyelitis and (b) Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277837","277837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139397","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on people with disabilities of the term non-physical to refer to people with hidden disabilities as part of the new Blue Badge guidance.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277838","277838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139398","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the criteria are for exclusion on medical grounds for police recruitment.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277801","277801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139399","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether community transport operators relying on the exclusively non-commercial exemption to holding a public service vehicle operators' licence will be able to continue to do so pending his Department’s publication of a final response to the consultation on Section 19 and Section 22 permits; and what criteria are used to define non-commercial for that purpose.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277808","277808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139400","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2019 to Question 271544, on what dates the Inter-Ministerial Group on Environment and Clean Growth (a) was created and (b) has met between that date and 16 April 2018.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277800","277800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139401","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to participate in the Horizon Europe programme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277740","277740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139402","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the adequacy of funding for medical R&D in advance of the Spending Review.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277741","277741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139403","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the loneliness strategy 2018, what progress has been made on his Department’s commitment to establish and grow a network of champions to encourage employers to support employees’ social wellbeing.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277655","277655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139404","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of personal independence payment reports completed by ATOS that were categorised as (a) unacceptable and (b) learning required in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277656","277656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139405","2019-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions the Inter-Ministerial Group on disability and society has met in each of the last two years; and which ministers attended each of those meetings.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277657","277657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139406","2019-07-23","Treasury","2019-07-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the merits of amending vehicle excise duty so that the duty applicable is based on the emissions recorded at MOT tests.","Biography information for Suella Braverman","Suella Braverman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277783","277783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139407","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions the rough sleeping advisory panel has met since its inception, (a) when and (b) where those meetings took place;and who attended each such meeting.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277658","277658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139408","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with AstraZeneca about the collapse of Avara Avlon and enhanced redundancy pay for employees.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277691","277691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139409","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress the Minister for Small Business, Consumers and Corporate Responsibility has made in strengthening the Department’s consideration of loneliness as a policy concern.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277659","277659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139410","2019-07-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with Avara about the collapse of Avara Avlon and the enhanced redundancy pay for employees.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277692","277692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139411","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on the commitment, in the loneliness strategy to encourage organisations across the transport sector to develop new initiatives to tackle loneliness.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277713","277713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139412","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on the commitment in the loneliness strategy to (a) create new partnerships with transport providers and community organisations who are developing ideas and initiatives for how transport can be used as a means to help tackle loneliness, and (b) use industry-wide forums to promote these.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277714","277714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139413","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on the commitment in the loneliness strategy to increase the numbers of drivers trained to support older and disabled passengers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277715","277715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139414","2019-07-22","Department for Transport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department’s has made on the commitment in the loneliness strategy to explore with seven mobility centres in England how the Government can help to identify signs of loneliness or lack of social connections.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277716","277716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139415","2019-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) average and (b) longest time taken is for his Department to process war pensions in the latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277790","277790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139416","2019-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of veterans with PTSD have been refused a war pension since 2010.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277791","277791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139417","2019-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the relationship between Hezbollah and the Islamic Resistance Support Organisation.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277639","277639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139418","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to tackle the domestic operations of Hezbollah since its full proscription.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277640","277640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139419","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment has he made of the adequacy of (a) funding for and (b) access to specialised services for (i) people and (ii) BAME people experiencing sexual violence.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277824","277824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139420","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding his Department has allocated from the public purse to wheelchair rugby in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277844","277844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139421","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to increase funding for hockey at grassroots level across the UK.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277845","277845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139422","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure UK residents deported to Romania, and subject to detention, are held in conditions that are of an acceptable standard.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277690","277690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139423","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2019 to Question 275828, what the timeframe is for the full withdrawal of the Windows XP operating system from across the NHS.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277855","277855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139424","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to add universal credit as an option on prescription exemption forms.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277776","277776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139425","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many penalty charge notices have been issued by the NHS Business Authority in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277777","277777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139426","2019-07-22","Department for Education","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2019 to Question 273502, whether primary legislation is required to place his Department's guidance on school uniforms onto a statutory footing.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277859","277859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139427","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many penalty charge notices issued by the NHS Business Authority have been overturned due to wrongly identified benefits on prescription forms in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277778","277778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139428","2019-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to (a) raise the maximum penalty for causing death by (i) dangerous driving and (ii) careless driving under the influence of drink or drugs to life imprisonment, (b) create a new offence of causing serious injury by careless driving and (c) increase the minimum period of disqualification for drivers convicted of causing death by any driving offence.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277860","277860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139429","2019-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to implement his Department’s response to the consultation on driving offences and penalties relating to causing death or serious injury, published on 17 October 2017, Cm 9518.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277861","277861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139430","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2018 to Question 122667 on Hezbollah, whether his policy on not collecting that data has changed since the Government's decision to proscribe Hezbollah in its entirety in February 2019.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277618","277618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139431","2019-07-18","Department for International Development","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that medical workers in Gaza can provide humanitarian assistance without the risk of attack.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277644","277644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139432","2019-07-18","Department for International Development","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that those responsible for attacks on humanitarian workers in developing countries are held to account.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277645","277645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139433","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the progress of the Global Polio Eradication Initiative in eradicating polio globally.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277682","277682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139434","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information he holds on the number of Al Qaeda (a) members and (b) supporters in the UK.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277619","277619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139435","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support people with post-polio syndrome.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277683","277683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139436","2019-07-18","Department for International Development","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to tackle impunity for attacks against health workers in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277646","277646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139437","2019-07-22","Home Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information he holds on the number of Daesh (a) members and (b) supporters in the UK.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277620","277620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139438","2019-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent to which Israel’s internal investigations into the killings of Palestinian health workers comply with international standards of (a) independence, (b) impartiality, (c) promptness, (d) thoroughness and (e) transparency.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277647","277647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139439","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on reports of a description on social media on 4 July 2019 by President Abbas's religious affairs adviser that Haj Amin Al-Husseini is a role model.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277621","277621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139440","2019-07-22","Department for International Development","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA) what discussions her Department has had with the PA on reports of the naming of a Palestinian youth summer camps after Dalal Mugrahbi and Omar Abu Laila.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277622","277622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139441","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to item 9 of NICE’s public board meeting agenda, 17 July 2019, how will membership of the (a) task and finish groups and (b) patient working group be decided; and what opportunities will exist for patient groups not invited to participate with the patient working group.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277756","277756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139442","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the 2019 Voluntary Scheme for Branded Medicines Pricing and Access, how many opportunities there have been for pharmaceutical industry trade bodies to input into NHS England’s commercial framework; and what steps the Government is taking to secure the participation of industry trade bodies.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277757","277757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139443","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his oral evidence at the Health and Social Care Committee on 9 July 2019, what the expiration date is for the options on the additional transport capacity for medicines; what the timescales are for exercising those options; and what the cost to the Department will be if those options are not exercised.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277758","277758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139444","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his oral evidence at the Health and Social Care Committee on 9 July 2019, if he will place in the Library his Department’s latest assessment of (a) the appropriate level of warehousing capacity required for stockpiling medicines and (b) the flow assumptions of importing medicines in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277759","277759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139445","2019-07-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the stockpiling of goods for sale at Christmas on warehouse capacity for medicines before the UK leaves the EU on 31 October.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277760","277760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139446","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the European Commission press release entitled EU-U.S. trade talks: milestone reached in mutual recognition on pharmaceuticals, dated 11 July 2019, whether the recently agreed mutual recognition agreement between the US and EU will continue to apply to manufacturers of pharmaceuticals in the UK in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277761","277761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139447","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce obesity related stigma; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277814","277814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139448","2019-07-22","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether she plans to table legislative proposals to implement payments to victims of historical and institutional abuse in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277666","277666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139449","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has in place to tackle the variation in the (a) quality of health visiting services and (b) delivery of the Health Child Programme among local authorities in England.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277600","277600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139450","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the deficit in trained health visitors.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277601","277601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139451","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to measure the adequacy of the health visitor workforce to implement the Healthy Child Programme.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277602","277602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139452","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has plans for a hardship fund to help people on the lowest incomes in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277684","277684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139453","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the company Big Ideas was appointed in a contested competitive process to work on the proposed UK Holocaust Memorial.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277606","277606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139454","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many views on the proposed UK Holocaust Memorial were submitted by the company Big Ideas to the Westminster City Council public comment website.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277607","277607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1139455","2019-07-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how the company Big Ideas described the alternatives to the proposed UK Holocaust Memorial project to the groups and individuals with which it interacted.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277608","277608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138793","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-15","What recent assessment he has made of the effect on asylum seekers of his Department's policy on the right to work.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911932","911932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138794","2019-07-16","Home Office","2019-07-15","What recent progress he has made on tackling knife crime.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911937","911937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138795","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-15","What recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of reported disability hate crime.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911940","911940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138797","2019-07-15","Home Office","2019-07-15","What progress he has made on his review of the treatment of overseas students accused of cheating in the Test of English for International Communication between 2011 and 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911936","911936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138804","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of reports of Uighur Muslim children in western Xinjiang being separated from their parents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277175","277175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138805","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage wildflower meadows throughout the country.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277176","277176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138806","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the contribution of wildflower meadows to the success of the various bee populations in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277177","277177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138807","2019-07-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to help farmers tackle the spread of bovine TB.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277178","277178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138808","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 270772 on Addiction Services, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of medically-staffed inpatient detoxification beds in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277157","277157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138809","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Office for National Statistics Public Sector Employment data, what assessment she has made of the effect on the performance of her Department of the loss of over 20,000 staff since 2013.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277229","277229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138810","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long-Term Plan implementation framework, what the timeframe is for local areas to produce system plans in relation to services for (a) autistic people and (b) people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277152","277152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138811","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 17 of the NHS Long-Term Plan implementation framework, what criteria will be used to calculate the local area share of the required further reduction of inpatient usage and beds for (a) autistic people and (b) people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277153","277153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138812","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 18 of the NHS Long Term Plan implementation framework, how much additional funding he plans to allocate to support the development of (a) new housing options and (b) suitable accommodation in the community for (i) autistic people and (ii) people with learning disabilities.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277154","277154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138813","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 27 of the NHS Long-Term Plan implementation framework, what proportion of patients with a long-term condition do not have access to a smartphone; and what funding he plans to allocate to increase digital connectivity among those people to enable them to access the NHS App.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277155","277155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138814","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page six of the NHS Long Term Plan implementation framework, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of digital connectivity among (a) older and (b) disabled people, and what steps he is taking to increase the number of those people that have access to new digital NHS services.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277156","277156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138815","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department had with the Chinese authorities prior to the state visit of President Xi in 2015 on the policing of public protests against the visit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277142","277142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138816","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Chinese authorities made any specific, (a) formal and (b) informal requests to his Department on the policing of protests prior and during the state visit of President Xi in 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277143","277143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138817","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patient organisations are involved in the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence’s review of health technology assessment methods and processes.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277170","277170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138818","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what opportunities patient organisations will have to make representations to the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence’s review of health technology assessment methods and processes.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277171","277171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138819","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he will take to ensure the broadest number of patient groups can participate in the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence’s review of health technology assessment methods and processes.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277172","277172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138820","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on meetings between the police and the Chinese authorities during the state visit of Chinese President Xi Jinping in October 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277144","277144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138821","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department made any specific requests to the (a) Metropolitan Police and (b) City of London Police on the handling of protests during the state visit of President Xi in 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277145","277145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138822","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Chinese authorities made any specific requests to his Department on the monitoring of specific individuals prior to the state visit of President Xi in 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277146","277146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138823","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department had with the previous Mayor of London on the policing of protests prior to the state visit of President Xi in 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277147","277147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138824","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his officials were party to any discussions between the previous Mayor of London and Chinese Government officials on the policing of protests prior to the state visit of President Xi in 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277148","277148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138825","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings were facilitated by his Department between the Chinese authorities and (a) other Departments, (b) the Mayor's Office for Policing and Crime and (c) the Metropolitan Police Service to discuss the policing of protests prior to the state visit of President Xi in 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277149","277149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138826","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any requests made to his Department by the Chinese authorities on the policing of protests against the state visit of President Xi in 2015 were passed onto (a) other Departments, (b) the Mayor’s Office for Policing and Crime, (c) the Metropolitan Police Service and (d) the City of London Police.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277150","277150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138827","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to ensure that the sexual harassment policies of universities are fit for purpose.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277109","277109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138828","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he will take to ensure that the Access for All accessibility programme includes improving access to public transport for autistic passengers and other people with invisible disabilities.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277116","277116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138829","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to improve support for people with neurodevelopmental conditions.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277125","277125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138830","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the new cross-departmental strategy for disability will reflect the needs of people with neurodevelopmental conditions.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277126","277126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138831","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 274615, on the Rough Sleeping Support Service (RSSS), how many cases have been referred to the RSSS from (a) the Home Office and (b) external bodies (i) in the last 12 months and (ii) since that programme's launch.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277279","277279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138832","2019-07-17","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will review the process for allocating a case to an investigator by the Financial Ombudsman Service to reduce the time taken for that process.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277299","277299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138833","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 274618, on Rough Sleeping Support Service (RSSS), from which teams in his Department were staff assigned to the RSSS.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277280","277280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138834","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 274618, on the Rough Sleeping Support Service (RSSS), how many status checks the RSSS team has conducted as part of its administrative duties since that programme's launch.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277281","277281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138835","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 274618 on the Rough Sleeping Support Service, how many cases the Rough Sleeping Support Service has identified for prioritisation since that programme's launch.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277282","277282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138836","2019-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment applications by people with multiple sclerosis have been returned by decision makers to assessment providers having been deemed to be of insufficient quality in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277269","277269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138837","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 274616 on the Rough Sleeping Support Service, how many (a) charities and (b) local authorities his Department has engaged with as part of the Rough Sleeping Support Service programme since that programme's launch.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277283","277283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138838","2019-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis have requested a copy of their personal independence payment assessment report following a face-to-face assessment in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277270","277270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138839","2019-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what data her Department holds on the number of applications for personal independence payments that were (a) refused and (b) reduced based on informal observations made of the applicant upon face to face assessment.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277271","277271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138840","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2019 to Question 274619 on the Rough Sleeping Support Service, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reassigning his Department's staff to the Rough Sleeping Support Service team on the day-to-day functioning of the teams from which those staff were reassigned.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277284","277284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138841","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to incentivise sustainable agricultural practices through the Environmental Land Management scheme.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277285","277285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138842","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has had recent discussions with the Department for Transport on the environmentally-friendly expansion of rural public transport; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277286","277286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138843","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to help the agricultural sector create new jobs in environmental land management.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277287","277287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138844","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that its Environmental Land Management scheme is developed as part of the Government's overall strategy to reach net-zero carbon emissions by 2050.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277288","277288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138845","2019-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the report entitled Capital grant required to meet social housing need in England 2021 – 2031, published by the National Housing Federation in June 2019, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings that (a) over the decade from 2021 it will be necessary to build 145,000 social homes each year and (b) on average a capital grant from Government of £12.8 billion per year will be required to provide these homes; and what action he is taking to increase the number of social homes in England.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277104","277104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138846","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2019 to Question 259358 on Medical Examinations: Sexual Offences,  how many Sexual Assault Referral Centres there are in England; and whether those centres offer a forensic medical examination to victims of sexual assault in cases where that victim does not wish to report that assault to the police.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277235","277235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138847","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of sexual harassment at universities on the prospects of the victims of that harassment.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277110","277110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138848","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of support provided to victims of sexual assault at universities.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277111","277111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138849","2019-07-18","House of Commons Commission","2019-07-15","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what plans the Commission has to improve the working conditions for Members' staff.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277112","277112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138850","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Homelessness Reduction Act 2017 on the (a) effectiveness of joint-working between criminal justice agencies and local authorities and (b) homelessness.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277248","277248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138851","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children under the age of 18 have been released from custody without accommodation in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277249","277249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138852","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many referrals have been made by (a) prison and (b) probation services to local authorities under the Homelessness Reduction Act 2017 duty to refer since October 2018.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277250","277250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138853","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department takes to (a) monitor, (b) investigate, (c) learn lessons for prevention from and (d) respond at a (i) local and (ii) national level to deaths of offenders in the community on post custody supervision.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277251","277251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138854","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the rise in deaths of people on post-custody supervision since 2010.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277252","277252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138855","2019-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people died whilst under post-release supervision in 2017-18; and what the (a) number of days between release from prison and date of death and (b) cause of death was in each of those cases.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277253","277253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138856","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent guidance he has published on the use of off-road all-terrain vehicles by people under the legal driving age.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277167","277167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138857","2019-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the environmental sustainability of residential properties smaller than 13 square metres constructed under permitted development rights.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277168","277168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138858","2019-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for residential properties of less than 13 square metres in the provisions of the Homes (Fitness for Human Habitation) Act 2018.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277169","277169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138859","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Clinical Advisory Group for Genomics, if he will set out (a) its terms of reference, (b) when it will first meet, (c) how patient voice will be incorporated into its work, (d) who it will report to and (e) when the (i) Commissioning Policy for Preimplantation Genetic Diagnosis review and (ii) other work of its predecessor, the Clinical Reference Group for Medical Genetics, will be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277243","277243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138860","2019-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether she plans to publish the results of the armed forces pay review before the 2019 summer recess.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277300","277300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138861","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of funding for the 30 hours' childcare policy for three- and four-year-olds.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277237","277237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138862","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of appropriateness of the level of business rates for private childcare providers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277238","277238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138863","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Department is taking to support local authorities to provide business rate relief to private childcare providers.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277239","277239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138864","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of enabling childcare costs to be paid directly to providers through universal credit.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277240","277240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138865","2019-07-17","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment he has made of the opening and closing rates of childcare settings in (a) wealthy areas and (b) disadvantaged areas.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277241","277241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138866","2019-07-17","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Early Years Alliance Minds Matter survey, published 2018; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce the stress and workload burden in the childcare sector.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277242","277242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138867","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department issues schools with guidance on reducing their carbon footprint; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277289","277289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138868","2019-07-17","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of teaching staff currently signed-off from work with a stress-related illness in (a) England, (b) the North East, and (c) Northumberland in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277195","277195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138869","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to implement the EU Single Use Plastics Directive 2019/904 which came into force on 3 July 2019.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277217","277217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138870","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding which will be allocated to local authorities for public health in 2020-21 in the event that the spending review is postponed.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277233","277233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138871","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will increase the funding allocated to sexual health services to tackle the incidence of syphilis and gonorrhoea in England.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277234","277234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138872","2019-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will meet the Chancellor to discuss the potential cost benefits of reducing VAT on the (a) building products and (b) low-carbon technologies used to retrofit homes to improve indoor air quality, energy efficiency and the health of occupants.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277276","277276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138873","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2019 to Question 223798 on International Convention for the Control and Management of Ships' Ballast Water and Sediments, what progress his Department has made on compliance with the Ballast Water Management Convention in order to accede to the Convention in Autumn 2019.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277151","277151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138874","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to promote the digital delivery of (a) structured education and (b) diabetes management services for people with (i) type 1 and (ii) type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277230","277230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138875","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of CCGs commission services to enable patients with (a) type 1 and (b) type 2 diabetes to access remote online consultations with healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277231","277231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138876","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to promote the use of coaching solutions to support patients with (a) type 1 diabetes and (b) type 2 diabetes manage their condition.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277232","277232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138877","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to encourage a modal shift to motorcycles and scooters.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277179","277179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138878","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the opportunities to improve (a) congestion, (b) the environment and (c) road safety through a modal shift to motorcycles and scooters.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277180","277180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138879","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer on 12 June 2019 to Question 260081, whether his Department will require Clinical Commissioning Groups to collect and publish data in a comparable form on (a) the amount spent on audiology services, (b) the number of hearing aids fitted and (c) outcomes of hearing aid fittings.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277193","277193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138880","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Sudanese counterpart on the reports of the killing of peaceful protesters in Sudan in June.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277196","277196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138881","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of the findings of the BBC Africa Eye investigation that the killing of protesters in Sudan on 3 June was ordered by that country’s senior military rulers.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277197","277197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138882","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Mali.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277198","277198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138883","2019-07-17","Department for International Development","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support his Department provides to Mali to tackle the increasing number of internally displaced persons.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277199","277199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138884","2019-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Kashmir.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277200","277200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138885","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many charging points for electric vehicles there are in England; and how many of those are located in each region.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277244","277244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138886","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the oil sector on introducing charging points for electric vehicles at  (a) service stations and (b) petrol forecourts.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277245","277245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138887","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to replace the plug-in car grant to encourage the manufacture and sale of low emission vehicles.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277246","277246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138888","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2019 to Question 256313 on Sickle Cell Diseases, which services (a) NHS England, (b) clinical commissioning groups and (c) other public bodies commission for people with sickle cell disease; and what the per capita annual cost is of providing each of those services.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277137","277137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138889","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2019 to Question 256313, which  services (a) NHS England, (b) clinical commissioning groups and (c) other public bodies commission for sickle cell disease patients with (i) stroke, (ii) chronic kidney disease, (iii) end-stage renal disease and (iv) pulmonary hypertension; and what the annual per capita cost is of providing each of those services.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277138","277138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138890","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with sickle cell disease were in receipt of (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment support allowance or their universal credit equivalents in the most recent period for which data are available; and what the annual cost to the public purse of providing that support in each of those groups is.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277139","277139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138891","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment support allowance and their universal credit equivalents have sickle cell disease with (i) stroke,(ii) sickle chronic kidney disease, (iii) end-stage renal disease and (iv) pulmonary hypertension in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what the annual cost to the public purse of providing that support in each of those groups is.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277140","277140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138892","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many carers of people with (a) sickle cell disease and (b) sickle cell disease and (i) stroke, (ii) chronic kidney disease, (iii) end-stage renal disease and (iv) pulmonary hypertension received carer’s allowance in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what the annual cost to the public purse of providing that support in each of those groups is.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277141","277141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138893","2019-07-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the oral evidence from the Permanent Secretary of the Department for Exiting the European Union to the Committee on Exiting the European Union of 4 September 2018, if he will list the 300 cross-government workstreams on the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277295","277295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138894","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the £7.7 million funding for the Back from the Brink programme is accessible to North Cornwall.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277227","277227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138895","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to commence negotiations with the First Group on the terms of an extension to the Great Western franchise after March 2020.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277158","277158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138896","2019-07-18","Cabinet Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons the rate of pay which requires approval for temporary staff was set at £750 per day in his Departments announcement of 4 July.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277113","277113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138897","2019-07-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the oral evidence from the Permanent Secretary of the Department for Exiting the European Union to the Committee on Exiting the European Union of 4 September 2018, at the point where they were last assessed, how many cross-departmental workstreams on the UK leaving the EU without a deal were rated as (a) red, (b) red/amber, (c) amber, (d) amber/green and (e) green.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277296","277296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138898","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the standard of catering services on the new Class 800 trains operated by First Group under the Great Western franchise.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277159","277159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138899","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on passengers of the decision by the First Group to discontinue its buffet car facilities and replace them with a more limited trolley service.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277160","277160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138900","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to make it a condition of any future extension of the Great Western franchise that an operator must provide full buffet car catering facilities.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277161","277161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138901","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of primary schools which had (a) fewer than 100, (b) 101 to 200, (c) 201 to 300, (d) 301 to 400, (e) 401 to 600 and (f) 601 or more pupils, were in deficit in each of the five most recent years for which data are available.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277297","277297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138902","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) doctors and (b) nurses are employed on a full-time basis for cancer care in Cornwall.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277228","277228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138903","2019-07-17","Cabinet Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the names of the firms his Department has hired contractors from in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277114","277114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138904","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate the Government has made of the increase in building and contents insurance premiums as a result of the increase in claims for flood damage; and what assessment he has made of the value for money to customers of those increases.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277165","277165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138905","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the insurance industry on the increase in building and contents insurance premiums due to the increase in claims for flood damage.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277166","277166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138906","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 273480 to Question 273480 on HIV Infection: Canterbury, what steps he is taking to ensure adequate funding for PrEP after September 2020.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277260","277260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138907","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 273480 on 273480, for what reason the Gate Clinic at Kent and Canterbury Hospital is not open to gay and bisexual men.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277261","277261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138908","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2019 to Question 273480 on HIV Infection: Canterbury, if he will take steps to ensure that gay and bisexual men in Canterbury have access to PrEP.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277262","277262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138909","2019-07-18","Treasury","2019-07-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet with (a) banks and (b) other financial institutions on recent reports of personal savings accounts with £170 billion and for which no interest is paid.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277117","277117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138910","2019-07-17","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the accessibility of the EU Exit: ID document check android app for applicants.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277254","277254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138911","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  what estimate he has made of changes in the number of children at school reporting domestic abuse since the launch of the operation encompass scheme.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277118","277118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138912","2019-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to increase access to statutory sick pay for low-paid workers.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277255","277255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138913","2019-07-17","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a national parking exemption badge to assist people (a) Thalidomide and (b) other disabilities that have difficulties in using the clock system on Blue Badges.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277218","277218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138914","2019-07-17","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the level of financial support available to university students.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277256","277256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138915","2019-07-17","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what role Ofstead will play in ensuring that primary schools comply with (a) relationships education, relationships and sex education and (b) religious education.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277201","277201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138916","2019-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of suitable homes for the elderly.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277257","277257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138917","2019-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of recorded workplace deaths in Scotland in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277258","277258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138918","2019-07-17","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions his Department has had with OFSTED on the teaching of (a) relationships and sex education and (b) religious education in primary schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277202","277202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138919","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2019 to Question HL16344, whether he plans to include the appointment of the Independent Reviewer of Prevent in the Schedule to the Public Appointments Order in Council 2016.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277293","277293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138920","2019-07-17","Scotland Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the supply of medicine to Scotland in the event that the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277259","277259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138921","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  what the timetable is for the advertisement for the role of independent reviewer of prevent; and where it will be published.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277294","277294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138922","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many European Health Insurance Cards in circulation are issued to people under 16 years of age.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277128","277128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138923","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his oral statement of 1 July 2019, Official Report, column 929, on the NHS Long Term Plan: Implementation, what steps his Department is taking to achieve the target to diagnose 75 per cent of cancers at stage 1 and 2 for less survivable cancers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277173","277173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138924","2019-07-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his oral statement of 1 July 2019, Official Report, column 929, on the NHS Long Term Plan: Implementation, if he will publish his plans to achieve the target to diagnose 75 per cent of cancers at stage 1 and 2 for less survivable cancers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277174","277174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138925","2019-07-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many claims were made for people under the age of 16 through the European Health Insurance Card scheme in the most 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277129","277129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138926","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have received under-occupancy penalty charges in each year since the introduction of those charges.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277204","277204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138927","2019-07-18","Department for Transport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the investigations undertaken by the Rail Accident Investigation Branch since 2010 have involved people working under a zero hours contract.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277205","277205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138928","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken was to process a claim for personal independence payment in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277206","277206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138929","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for support under the special rules for terminal illness have been received by her Department in each year since the introduction of those rules.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277207","277207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138930","2019-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the equity of the transition to environmental land management payments for farms of different sizes.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277105","277105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138931","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to (a) support the growth and (b) minimise the adverse environmental effects of the bioplastics industry.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277119","277119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138932","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Questions 264398, 264399, 264401 and 264402 of 13 June 2019 on the Disclosure and Barring Service, why those Questions remain unanswered; when he plans to provide Answers to those Questions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277194","277194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138933","2019-07-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of housing stock suitable for older people.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277120","277120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138934","2019-07-17","Department for International Trade","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the Defence and Security Organisation core markets are for 2018-19; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277162","277162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138935","2019-07-17","Department for International Trade","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the (a) premium income for defence transactions, (b) claims paid for defence sector contracts and (c) monies at risk for defence transactions in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277163","277163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138936","2019-07-17","Department for International Trade","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff worked for the Defence and Security Organisation (DSO) on 1 April 2019; how many of those staff worked in the Export Support Team; and what the DSO's budget is for 2019-20.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277164","277164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138937","2019-07-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what funding he has allocated to help tackle hate crime reported by the Sikh community in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277247","277247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138938","2019-07-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to reduce the number of (a) bogus and (b) nuisance phone calls.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277121","277121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138939","2019-07-18","Department for Education","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that school leavers are informed of degree apprenticeships.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277122","277122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138940","2019-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the heat strategy on the (a) upfront costs of installing new technologies and (b) the costs of energy efficiency upgrades for rural (i) homeowners, (ii) landlords and (iii) businesses.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277211","277211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138941","2019-07-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has plans to undertake a public consultation on changing the sequence by which deductions from benefits are ordered to ensure that child maintenance payments take priority over debts to private companies.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277210","277210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138942","2019-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government’s heat strategy will include proposals to remove the fuel cost element of the Energy Performance Certificate for rural (i) homeowners and (ii) landlords living off the gas grid.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277212","277212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138943","2019-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government’s heat strategy include a comparative assessment of the costs associated with improving an Energy Performance Certificate between (a) rural homeowners and landlords that are off the gas grid and (b) homeowners and landlords are on the gas grid.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277213","277213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138944","2019-07-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time enforcement case managers are employed by the child maintenance service.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277219","277219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138945","2019-07-18","Department for International Trade","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the UK's (a) automotive and (b) aerospace sectors is able to take advantage of global trading opportunities when the UK leaves the EU on 31 October 2019.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277189","277189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138946","2019-07-18","Home Office","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of adverse childhood experiences on (a) levels of criminality and (b) rates of youth offending.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277190","277190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1138947","2019-07-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the affordability of domestic energy costs as the UK transitions to a carbon neutral environment by 2050.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 277191","277191"
