"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851689","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received on changes to payments of housing benefit to women's refuges.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130452","130452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851690","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of students who have graduated with a degree in video game art and animation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130453","130453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851691","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of extending police pensions to life-long payments in the event of an officer's death.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130454","130454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851692","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the transfer of staff employed by HMRC at the Waterfront offices in Dudley.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130455","130455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851693","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the proposed transfer of staff employed by HMRC at the Waterfront offices in Dudley to the Department of Work and Pensions has been cancelled.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130456","130456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851694","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential roles that staff employed by HMRC at the Waterfront offices in Dudley could play in her Department, in particular with the work associated with the introduction and administration of universal credit.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130457","130457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851695","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether there are plans to reduce the amount of debt that a child maintenance paying parent owes before an application for a Liability Order can be made.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130458","130458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851696","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department takes to ensure that child maintenance payments are paid by non-resident parents; and what steps her Department takes to support the resident parent.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130459","130459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851697","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that refuge services that are in receipt of Government funding in (a) England and (b) Greater Manchester do not close at the end of the (i) 2017-18 and (ii) 2018-19 financial years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130460","130460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851698","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128880, how much further (a) funding and (b) FTE staffing her Department has deployed to the MPAM team.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130461","130461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851699","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of job centres make available accessibility software to assist blind and partially sighted people to claim universal credit; what assessment her Department has made of geographical variations in that provision; and what other support is made available to assist people with sensory impairments who cannot access the internet with applying for universal credit.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130462","130462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851700","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people diagnosed with Parkinson's disease are in the employment and support allowance work related activity group.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130463","130463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851701","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the NICE appraisal of Spinraza for the treatment of spinal muscular atrophy.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130464","130464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851702","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress NHS England and Biogenon have made in discussions on a managed access agreement for the use of Spinraza for the treatment of spinal muscular atrophy.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130465","130465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851703","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department provides to the NSPCC's Childline.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130466","130466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851704","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations his Department has received on funding for the NSPCC's Childline.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130467","130467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851705","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, by what year the Office for Nuclear Regulation is planning to deliver a Euratom-equivalent UK State System for Accountability for and Control of nuclear material.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130468","130468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851706","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many candidates have (a) applied, (b) been successful and (c) been rejected for positions in the new nuclear Safeguards Inspectorate in the Office for Nuclear Regulation.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130469","130469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851707","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the value is of the spending commitments that the Office for Nuclear Regulation has been authorised to make as part of the project to establish a UK State System for Accountability and Control of nuclear material.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130470","130470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851708","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease have been placed in the (a) support group and (b) work-related activity group with a prognosis statement of (i) three months, (ii) six months, (iii) 12 months, (iv) 18 months, (v) two years and (vi) more than two years at work capability assessments in each year since the introduction of employment and support allowance in 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130471","130471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851709","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether chlorine gas is prohibited as a weapon under the 1993 Convention on the Prohibition of the Development, Production, Stockpiling and Use of Chemical Weapons and on their Destruction.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130472","130472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851710","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that low-paid workers on zero-hours contracts are aware of their entitlement to universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130473","130473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851711","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what are the eligibility criteria is for a person to qualify for a bonus with a Help to Buy ISA.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130474","130474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851712","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to make a decision on the allocation of funding for the proposed Health and Wellbeing campus at the Halton hospital site.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130475","130475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851713","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to oral contribution of the Minister for Housing on 6 February 2018, Official Report, column 1461, whether a local authority with (a) no brownfield land to build on and (b) heavily contaminated land is classified as exceptional circumstances for enabling housebuilding on greenbelt land.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130476","130476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851714","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2018 to Question 128648 on Treasury: Tableware, which subcontractors supply his Department with its tableware.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130477","130477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851715","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to amend s1.3 of the Children Act 1989 to better define the classification of disability as incapacity to parent.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130478","130478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851716","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints the Independent Case Examiner is considering from Halton constituency relating to the equalisation of the state pension age; and how many such complaints from Halton constituency that examiner has resolved since 2 October 2017.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130479","130479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851717","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Housing on 6 February 2018, Official Report, column 1461, whether he has to empower local authorities to prevent developers from building on greenbelt when allocated brownfield sites have not been developed.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130480","130480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851718","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on how many disabled people have found work as a direct result of the Disability Confident campaign.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130481","130481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851719","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support his Department provides to women who engage with the criminal justice system as a result of domestic abuse in (a) Greater Manchester and (b) England.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130482","130482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851720","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what joint initiatives his Department has with the Department for Education on supporting a child whose parent enters a women's refuge.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130483","130483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851721","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support his Department provides for a child whose parent enters a women's refuge in (a) Greater Manchester and (b) England.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130484","130484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851722","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 63667 and the Answer of 22 February 2018 to Question, on what date NHS Protect's investigation into Phil Morley began.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130485","130485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851723","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the financial sustainability of Halton Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130486","130486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851724","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timescale is for appointing a new chief officer to Halton Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130487","130487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851725","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse was of the capital funding his Department provided for the Route 39 free school in North Devon.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130488","130488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851726","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the suitability of using desktop studies to assess the flammability of cladding on buildings.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130489","130489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851727","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of reducing Air Passenger Duty by 50 per cent on (a) the number of passenger journeys and (b) air routes.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130490","130490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851728","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse was of the capital funding provided for the Southwark Free School.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130491","130491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851729","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse was of the capital funding provided for the Royal Greenwich Trust School Academy.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130492","130492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851730","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse was of the capital funding provided for the Stockport Technical School .","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130493","130493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851731","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of key performance indicators were met by Amey in contracts that company held with his Department in each year since the first contract was signed.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130494","130494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851732","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have won an appeal against the withdrawal of their disability living allowance at a tribunal in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130495","130495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851733","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date his Department issued a request for information to industry in respect of a deployable long-range air defence radar for use overseas.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130496","130496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851734","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours of unpaid work have been handed down by the courts as part of community orders in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130497","130497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851735","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse was of the capital funding provided for the Durham Free School .","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130498","130498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851736","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether Care Quality Commission inspections of supported housing assess the extent to which providers (a) engage with wider communities living near supported housing, (b) encourage residents of supported housing to help their local community and (c) prevent drug use and alcohol abuse by supported housing residents.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130499","130499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851737","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many inspections of supported housing providers have been carried out by the Care Quality Commission in each year since 2009-10, and how many of those inspections resulted in an overall rating of (a) good, (b) inadequate and (c) requires improvement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130500","130500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851738","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many supported housing providers are registered with the Care Quality Commission; and how many of those providers have received an overall rating of (a) good, (b) inadequate and (c) requires improvement in their latest inspection.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130501","130501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851739","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many supported housing providers have de-registered from the Care Quality Commission (CQC) in each year since 2009-10, broken down by the latest overall CQC rating.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130502","130502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851740","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much National Lottery funding (a) North Cornwall and (b) Cornwall has received in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130503","130503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851741","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many supported housing providers were closed due to poor Care Quality Commission ratings in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130504","130504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851742","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of people undertaking paid apprenticeships in North Cornwall.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130505","130505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851743","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 42 of the Careers Strategy, whether his Department plans to widen the intention to improve the accessibility and transparency of data regarding gender disparities in STEM subject choices at age 16-19 to include other characteristics such as ethnicity, disability and socio-economic inequality.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130506","130506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851744","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the £60 million allocated in the Industrial Strategy White Paper to support apprenticeship take up by young people and poorer families from disadvantaged areas will be used.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130507","130507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851745","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the quantity of plastics washed up on UK beaches in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130508","130508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851746","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to update national design guidance on cycling and walking infrastructure.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130509","130509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851747","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many suspected benefit fraud reports from the public have been (a) received and (b) led to action by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130510","130510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851748","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken has been to process suspected benefit fraud reports from the public in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130511","130511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851749","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department holds records on the amount of money spent in (a) Cornwall, and (b) North Cornwall constituency on children’s mental health services.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130512","130512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851750","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of money spent on research into Rhabdomyosarcoma in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130513","130513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851751","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of money spent on research into childhood cancers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130514","130514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851752","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who have Rhabdomyosarcoma.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130515","130515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851753","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who are aged over 18 and have cancer in (a) North Cornwall constituency and (b) Cornwall.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130516","130516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851754","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether members of the public who submit reports to her Department on potential benefit fraud receive updates on the development of such cases.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130517","130517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851755","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to encourage local authorities to avoid raising council tax.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130518","130518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851756","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, Pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2018 to Question 128437, on High Rise Flats: Fire Prevention, for what reasons that Answer does not indicate whether (a) class 0 (national class) and (b) class B-s3, d2 must be composed only of materials that are of limited combustibility.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130519","130519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851757","2018-03-05","Department for Transport","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how funding has been allocated by his Department for repairing potholes in (a) North Cornwall, and (b) Cornwall.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130520","130520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851758","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in (a) North Cornwall, and (b) Cornwall, were living below the poverty line in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130521","130521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851759","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the total sleep­ in back pay liability is estimated to be for providers in (a) Hornchurch and Upminster constituency and (b) London Borough of Havering Council.","Biography information for Julia Lopez","Julia Lopez","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130522","130522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851760","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) merits and (b) costs of introducing a cap of £5,000 rather than £2,500 on landlord contributions to domestic private rented sector energy efficiency schemes.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130523","130523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851761","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what capital funding has been provided from the public purse for the Bolton Wanderers Free School.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130524","130524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851762","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of sexual assaults on NHS emergency workers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130525","130525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851763","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken since the broadcast of the C4 Dispatches investigation on 19 February 2018 to investigate whether any staff in mental health units have used violent restraint on patients in their care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130526","130526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851764","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what capital funding was provided from the public purse for the Dawes Lane Academy, North Lincolnshire.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130527","130527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851765","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to ensure all tyres for military vehicles are capable of being remanufactured.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130528","130528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851766","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what further steps he has taken since the broadcast of the C4 Dispatches programme of 19 February 2018 to ensure patient safety in all mental health units.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130529","130529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851767","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that (a) secure doors are fully functional, (b) access to areas containing pharmaceuticals are secure from patients and (c) staff have working personal alarms on their person at all times in (i) the Dene Hospital and (ii) other secure mental health hopsitals.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130530","130530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851768","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money his Department paid to the Priory Group for mental health services in each of the last seven years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130531","130531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851769","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has take to ensure that staff in acute situations with patients living with severe mental illness have (a) proper training and appropriate qualifications and (b) salaries commensurate with the specialist nature of the job.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130532","130532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851770","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has plans to begin collecting information on the proportion of children accessing 30 hours of free childcare from (a) single and (b) two parent households.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130533","130533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851771","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to include the performance management of teachers in the early years baseline assessment.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130534","130534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851772","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure continued funding for the South West Coastal Path national trail.","Biography information for Peter Heaton-Jones","Peter Heaton-Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130535","130535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851773","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the difference was in each of the last five years between the amount paid by his Department to Annington Homes and the amount of Service Family Accommodation personnel charges collected by his Department for (a) each property owned by Annington homes and (b) in total.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130536","130536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851774","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of equipping more police officers with Taser non-lethal weapons, and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130537","130537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851775","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she bring forward legislative proposals to enable medicines derived from cannabis to be available on prescription.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130538","130538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851776","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether services according to the rites of the Church of England are held at HMP Brixton; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130539","130539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851777","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence was produced by the Narey Review of Foster Care to support the recommendation to abolish the Independent Reviewing Office.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130540","130540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851778","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many places were available in secure children's homes in each of the last 10 years; and what the annual average occupancy rates have been in that same period.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130541","130541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851779","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many adoption placements were completed in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130542","130542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851780","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many adoptions have been disrupted in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130543","130543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851781","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish its formal response to the Narey review of fostering.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130544","130544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851782","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 26 February 2018 HCWS486 on Local Government Policy, what estimate he has made of the potential savings; and if he will place a copy of the cost-benefit analysis in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130545","130545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851783","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 26 February HCWS486 on Local Government Policy, if he will set out the planning and housing challenges in respect of which he is satisfied that a more strategic and holistic approach will be facilitated.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130546","130546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851784","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, by what means and on what date he was informed by (a) Poole Borough Council and (b) Bournemouth Borough Council that those councils did not consent to a new unitary authority comprising Poole and Bournemouth unless Christchurch Borough Council were included; and what reasons were given for the refusal to consent.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130547","130547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/847760","2018-02-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what intellectual property protections and enforcement measures counterfeiting authorities may use for counterfeiting and piracy of designs made by 3D printing.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129436","129436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850360","2018-02-27","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","What progress is being made on reducing the deficit.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904046","904046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850636","2018-03-01","Department for International Development","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, for what reason her Department has allocated to the Global Partnership for Education less than the £381 million over the next three years recommended in the First Report of the International Development Committee, DFID's work on education: Leaving no one behind?, HC 367, published on 21 November 2017.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129891","129891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850638","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support his Department provides to people who have received incorrect legal advice from a solicitor who subsequently absconds from the UK jurisdiction.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129892","129892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850639","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the collapse of Carillon on construction projects in the Hendon constituency.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129893","129893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850640","2018-03-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Minister for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of owners of holiday properties who have registered for the small business rates relief.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129894","129894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850641","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will make an assessment of the need for additional secondary schools in the London Borough of Barnet.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129895","129895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850643","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he will make representations to his Malaysian counterparts on the kidnapping of Pastor Raymond Koh in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129896","129896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850644","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will take steps to prevent one parent obtaining a passport for their children without the consent of the other.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129897","129897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850645","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with the BBC on the accuracy of its tax advice to employees establishing personal service companies and the implications of such companies on an employee's tax liability.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129898","129898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850646","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 127316 on High Rise Flats: Fire Prevention, what the Government's definition is of limited combustibility.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129899","129899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850647","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that the devolved administrations are able to share information on cases where (a) suicide, (b) self harm and (c) other mental health related issues.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129900","129900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850649","2018-03-01","Department for International Trade","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many Scottish based small and medium sized enterprises were invited to take part in the Prime Minister's trade visit to China in January 2018.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129901","129901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850650","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of school leavers have participated in further and technical education in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129902","129902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850651","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of school leavers have participated in higher education in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129903","129903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850652","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many social care deferred payments were agreed by local authorities in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129904","129904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850653","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people in full receipt of NHS continuing healthcare had their cases reviewed and then deemed ineligible for continuing healthcare in 2016-17.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129905","129905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850654","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to publish their planned refresh of the National Framework for NHS Continuing Healthcare.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129906","129906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850655","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, where people have experienced delays between assessment for NHS continuing healthcare and receiving a package of care (a) what was the average length of those delays and (b) what was the longest wait in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129907","129907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850656","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of referrals to community eating disorders services for children and young people being rejected solely on the grounds of weight or body mass index.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129908","129908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850658","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that information on the number of children and young people accessing specialist treatment for an eating disorder is transparent.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129909","129909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850659","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all community eating disorders services for children and young people are sufficiently staffed so that they are able to offer treatment in line with National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines to all young people with a clinical need.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129910","129910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850660","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to move budgetary responsibility for social care from the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government to the Department of Health and Social Care.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129911","129911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850661","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people experienced a delay between assessment for NHS continuing healthcare and receiving a package of care in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129912","129912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850662","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for Abbot-Diabetes monitors; and if his Department will extend the availability of free Abbot-Diabetes monitors.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129913","129913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850664","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the efficiency of ambulance services in rural areas.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129914","129914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850665","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will take steps to encourage increased trades union membership.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129915","129915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850667","2018-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government will take steps to ensure that the transposition into UK law of Article 7 of the Trade Secrets Directive includes strong language to penalise abusive litigation so as to prevent companies from using the threat of litigation to deter competitors or public interest scrutiny.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129917","129917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850668","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that non-commercial rooftop solar cells and storage installed on public buildings are not charged business rates.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129918","129918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850670","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the provision of mental health services in Portsmouth of the fall in the real terms income of Solent NHS Trust between 2011-12 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129919","129919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850671","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on the UK's refugee policies of (a) renewing and (b) ending inclusion in the Dublin III Regulation after 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129920","129920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850672","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the consultation arrangements on the Airspace Change Proposal around Brize Norton and London Oxford airports introduced in December 2017 include a more restricted number of consultees than previous consultations on similar topics.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129921","129921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850673","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effects of the new airspace arrangements around Brize Norton and London Oxford airports on general air traffic activity and safety.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129922","129922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850674","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether those NHS trusts which have created subsidiary companies have conducted an equalities impact assessment regarding that change.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129923","129923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850675","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to take steps independently of the United Nations to increase the number of Christians from Syria and Iraq receiving resettlement in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129924","129924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850677","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Oral Answer of the Minister of State for Europe and the Americas to the right hon. Member for Enfield North on 20 February 2018, whether any discussions have taken place between the UK Government and (a) the PYD and (b) the YPG following Turkey’s military operation in the Afrin region.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129925","129925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850678","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2018 to Question 128740, on Syria: Armed Conflict, when the Government last raised the issue of Eastern Ghouta (a) at the UN and (b) with Russia; and what response the Government received on each such occasion.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129926","129926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850679","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on healthcare provision in South Tyneside of the decision to move acute NHS services out of South Tyneside.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129927","129927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850680","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of local bus services in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East, and (d) the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129928","129928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850681","2018-03-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's explanatory memorandum to its Supplementary Estimate 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effect on house-building in London of surrendering £65m for the London settlement in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129929","129929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850682","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's explanatory memorandum to its Supplementary Estimate 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effect on affordable housing of surrendering £52m for build to rent in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129930","129930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850683","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's explanatory memorandum to its Supplementary Estimate 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effect on local regeneration programmes of surrendering £52m for estate regeneration in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129931","129931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850684","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's explanatory memorandum to its Supplementary Estimate 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effect on the building of affordable housing of surrendering £48m for affordable housing (National Productivity Investment Fund) in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129932","129932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850685","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's explanatory memorandum to its Supplementary Estimate 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effect on housebuilding of surrendering £166m for accelerated construction (National Productivity Investment Fund) in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129933","129933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850686","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's explanatory memorandum to its Supplementary Estimate 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effect on building of new starter homes of surrendering £329m for starter homes in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129934","129934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850688","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's explanatory memorandum to its Supplementary Estimate 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effect on the regeneration of the local area of surrendering £6m for Brent Cross in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129935","129935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850689","2018-03-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's explanatory memorandum on its Supplementary Estimate 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effect  the building of affordable housing of surrendering £24m for the Affordable Homes Programme in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129936","129936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850690","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's explanatory memorandum to its Supplementary Estimate 2017-18, what assessment he has made of the effect on devolved powers on housing of surrendering £75m for devolution deals in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129937","129937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850692","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of his Department’s cloud-hosting contracts have been awarded to (a) hyperscale cloud providers and (b) UK SMEs; and what the value of those contracts was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129938","129938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850693","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons the GP contract includes a postnatal check for babies but not for mothers.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129939","129939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850694","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will take steps to ensure that as part of the transitional arrangement EU students starting courses in English higher education institutions during any agreed implementation period will continue to be eligible for (a) home fee status and (b) student loans and grants.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129940","129940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850696","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the volume of UK citizens’ data held by companies (a) supplying cloud services to his Department and (b) contracted to deliver cloud services on behalf of his Department which is subject to information requests from US Government bodies.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129941","129941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850697","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the volume of UK citizens’ data held by companies (a) supplying cloud services to her Department and (b) contracted to deliver cloud services on behalf of her Department which is subject to information requests from US Government bodies.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129942","129942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850698","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the volume of UK citizens’ data held by companies (a) supplying cloud services to his Department and (b) contracted to deliver cloud services on behalf of his Department which is subject to information requests from US Government bodies.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129943","129943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850699","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who is acting as UK Ambassador to the UN prior to Karen Pierce taking up that post.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129944","129944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850701","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the rate of inflation for police forces is higher than that for the average household; and what estimate it has made of that rate for police forces over the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129945","129945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850702","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the monetary value of economic crime in the last year which the National Economic Crime centre will be tasked with reducing.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129946","129946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850703","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to make it easier for private companies to install charging infrastructure for Electric Vehicles on 3rd-party land.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129947","129947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850704","2018-03-05","Department for International Trade","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the change in the volume of UK trade with non-EU countries in each year between 2013 and 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129948","129948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850705","2018-03-01","Northern Ireland Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of applying the new technology developed to detect jihadi content online to the tackling of republican terrorism in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129949","129949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850707","2018-03-01","Department for International Trade","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to European Commission's recent decision to register imports of new and retreaded tyres imported from China, what guidance his Department is providing to UK companies importing such tyres from China.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129950","129950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850708","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of guaranteeing funding for UK Projects of Common Interest established under the Connecting Europe Facility for Energy.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129951","129951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850709","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the proposed energy price cap will extend to people who use (a) heating oil, (b) liquefied petroleum gas and (c) solid fuels.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129952","129952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850710","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's report of December 2017, Careers strategy: making the most of everyone’s skills and talents, if he will provide funding for all schools to appoint a named Careers Leader to lead a careers programme.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129953","129953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850711","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to promote STEM careers and pathways to (a) students, (b) parents, (c) teachers and (d) governors as part of the 2018 Year of Engineering.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129954","129954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850712","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to ensure that the National Careers Service website includes case studies of diverse STEM role models and career pathways.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129955","129955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850714","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for which policies the Implementation Unit has examined the effect in regard to the family in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129956","129956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850715","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many homes in Glasgow North East constituency have had works carried out under the Green Deal scheme.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129957","129957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850716","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children's residential care staff in England are not social work qualified; and what plans he has for Social Work England to register chilldren's residential care staff.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129958","129958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850717","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 125962, what the most up-to-date information is which his Department holds on (a) the number of secure accommodation places for children in England, (b) the capacity of those places and (c) the number of vacancies in those places.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129959","129959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850718","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children looked after by local authorities in England have been detained in secure accommodation in Scotland in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129960","129960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850719","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the first treatments and technologies chosen for the Accelerated Access Pathway will be available for the NHS to use.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129961","129961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850721","2018-03-05","Department for International Development","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the implementation of the Saint Sylvestre agreement in the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129962","129962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850722","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to implement any of the recommendations of the report, Joint Serious Case Review Concerning Sexual Exploitation of Children and Adults with Needs for Care and Support in Newcastle-upon-Tyne, published by the Newcastle Safeguarding Children Board and Newcastle Safeguarding Adults Board.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129963","129963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850723","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the period during which farmers are permitted to cut hedges; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129964","129964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850724","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether her Department plans to implement any of the recommendations of the report, Joint Serious Case Review Concerning Sexual Exploitation of Children and Adults with Needs for Care and Support in Newcastle-upon-Tyne, published by the Newcastle Safeguarding Children Board and Newcastle Safeguarding Adults Board.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129965","129965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850725","2018-03-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons the Environment Agency is proposing to increase variation fees; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129966","129966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850726","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to implement any of the recommendations of the report, Joint Serious Case Review Concerning Sexual Exploitation of Children and Adults with Needs for Care and Support in Newcastle-upon-Tyne, published by the Newcastle Safeguarding Children Board and Newcastle Safeguarding Adults Board.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129967","129967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850727","2018-03-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Seasonal Agricultural Workers' Scheme in providing specialised labour for farmers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129968","129968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850728","2018-03-05","Attorney General","2018-02-27","To ask the Attorney General, whether his Department plans to implement any of the recommendations of the report, Joint Serious Case Review Concerning Sexual Exploitation of Children and Adults with Needs for Care and Support in Newcastle-upon-Tyne, published by the Newcastle Safeguarding Children Board and Newcastle Safeguarding Adults Board.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129969","129969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850730","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to NHS dental care in (a) York, (b) North Yorkshire and (c) England.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129970","129970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850731","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure all children have access to NHS dental services.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129971","129971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850733","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is to issue amended guidance on discretionary leave to victims of modern slavery as a result of the judgement PK (Ghana) [2018] WLR(D) 94, [2018] EWCA Civ 98.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129972","129972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850734","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the judgment in the case of PK (Ghana) v Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether victims of modern slavery with a positive conclusive grounds decision will remain in receipt of National Referral Mechanism support until (a) her Department publishes its updated guidance on discretionary leave to remain and (b) a decision has been made on those cases in accordance with that updated guidance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129973","129973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850735","2018-03-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has set a target date for all council and housing association homes to meet the Decent Homes standard.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129974","129974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850736","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding has been allocated to the Decent Homes programme in each financial year since 2009-10; and what commitment he has made for future funding of that programme.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129975","129975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850738","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 124424, on Refugees, whether her Department plans to publish the findings of its pilot by UK Visas and Immigration in the North East and Yorkshire and Humberside; and what criteria her Department used to determine that that pilot was tested successfully.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129976","129976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850739","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 123573, if she will direct UK Visas and Immigration to introduce set standards for the judging of visa applications as complex by caseworkers.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129977","129977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850740","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of the Republic of Iraq on the opening to international passenger flights of the two airports in the Kurdistan Region of Iraq; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129978","129978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850741","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2018 to Question 123852, how much her Department has paid in reimbursement for costs relating to lost documents in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129979","129979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850743","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 124249, on Welfare in Detention of Vulnerable Persons Review, which bodies with an interest in immigration detention her Department plans to contact; what the timetable is for revising the guidance; and what assessment her Department has made of the recommendations or findings made by Stephen Shaw.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129980","129980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850744","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking encourage businesses to adopt (a) ethical business practices and (b) policies that protect workers from being abused and exploited in (i) the organisations and (ii) the global supply chains of such businesses.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129981","129981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850745","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that smart meters are on schedule to be installed in every household by 2020.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129982","129982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850746","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will he make an assessment of the potential contribution of 3D printing to UK GDP by 2020.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129983","129983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850748","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an estimate of the potential contribution of machine learning to UK GDP by 2020.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129984","129984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850749","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential contribution of graphene to UK GDP by 2020.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129985","129985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850750","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of RegTech's potential effect on reducing the administrative burden of regulation.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129986","129986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850751","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of young people in Telford started an apprenticeship after completing GCSEs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129987","129987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850752","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on enabling skilled technology entrepreneurs to enter and work in the UK.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129988","129988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850753","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps her Department has taken to tackle cyber crime.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129989","129989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850754","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the 200,000 new public sector apprenticeships announced by his Department on 20 January 2017 have been filled; and how many of those apprenticeships are based in (a) the Telford constituency, (b) Telford and Wrekin and (c) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129990","129990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850755","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of e-health technology in reducing patient waiting lists; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129991","129991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850756","2018-03-01","Cabinet Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of people in the (a) Telford constituency and (b) UK were employed by small and medium-sized enterprises in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129992","129992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850758","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential of machine learning to deliver efficiency savings in the NHS.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129993","129993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850759","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which artificial intelligence applications his Department uses; and what assessment his Department has made of the potential introduction of further such applications.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129994","129994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850760","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to help ensure parity of treatment for patients diagnosed with (a) mental health and (b) physical health conditions.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129995","129995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850761","2018-03-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to protect green belt and green open spaces in the Telford and Wrekin local authority area.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129996","129996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850762","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps are being taken by the Government to encourage businesses with a total annual turnover of under £36 million to produce a slavery and human trafficking statement for each financial year of that organisation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129997","129997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850763","2018-03-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Cyber Essentials scheme in reducing cyber fraud in the public sector.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129998","129998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850764","2018-03-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to support and spread awareness of cyber security insurance amongst businesses.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129999","129999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850765","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of (a) total and (b) per capita funding from his Department's budget on (i) health and (ii) mental health in England has been allocated to Telford and Wrekin CCG since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130000","130000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850766","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Office, what steps she is taking to improve awareness of cyber fraud amongst the public.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130001","130001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850767","2018-03-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the contribution of big data to GDP in the current financial year.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130002","130002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850768","2018-03-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the April 2017 reforms to the Horserace Betting Levy on (a) horse-racing and (b) the public purse.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130003","130003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850769","2018-03-01","Department for International Trade","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many businesses in (a) Shropshire and (b) the Telford constituency have received export support from his Department since it was set up.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130004","130004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850770","2018-03-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to reduce digital exclusion.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130005","130005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850772","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) number and (b) financial value of start-up loans was for small businesses in (i) Telford and Wrekin and (ii) the Telford constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130006","130006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850773","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to increase the level of access to credit for businesses in the Telford constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130007","130007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850774","2018-03-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much waste was recycled in (a) the Telford constituency (b) Shropshire and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130008","130008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850775","2018-03-01","Cabinet Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to ensure robust cyber security in the public sector.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130009","130009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850776","2018-03-01","Cabinet Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to make improve the use of digital technology in the public sector.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130010","130010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850777","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the average time taken to progress applicants for NHS Continuing Healthcare to (a) checklist stage and (b) a full decision in (i) England and (ii) Gloucestershire; how those figures compare with target times; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130011","130011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850778","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions the Defence Council has concluded that conduct by (a) a member of the armed forced engaged in active service and (b) a civilian subject to service discipline which would otherwise be deemed to be a relevant bribery offence, was necessary under Section 13 of the Bribery Act.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130012","130012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850779","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands will not receive the new state pension as a result of failing to meet the National Insurance Contributions threshold.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130013","130013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850780","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Cold Weather Payments have been issued to people in (a) Coventry South constituency, (b) Coventry and (c) the West Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130014","130014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850781","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of counselling services provided in schools in (a) England and (b) Gloucestershire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130015","130015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850783","2018-03-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of fuel poverty in (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130016","130016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850784","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households his Department has written to regarding the change in Support for Mortgage Interest from a benefit to a loan in Coventry South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130017","130017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850785","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people who live in Coventry South constituency are employed on zero-hour contracts.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130018","130018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850787","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge outpatients to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130019","130019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850788","2018-03-01","Scotland Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on staffing levels in the NHS in Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130020","130020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850789","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish his Department's contractual guidance on the (a) access and (b) use of big data collected by private companies contracted to the NHS.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130021","130021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850790","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge inpatients to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130022","130022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850792","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief benefit child dependency additions in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130023","130023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850793","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have committed suicide who had (a) visited their GP, (b) visited a general hospital, and (c) accessed NHS psychiatric services in the 3 months before their death in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130024","130024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850794","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief on severe disablement allowance in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130025","130025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850795","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief on rehabilitee allowances in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130026","130026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850796","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Victoria Cross and other gallantry awards holders received relief on pensions and annuities in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130027","130027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850797","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Forces’ widows received income tax relief on children’s allowance in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130028","130028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850798","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief on bereavement payments in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130029","130029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850800","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief on 15p luncheon vouchers in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130030","130030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850801","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received Stamp Duty Land Tax relief for relocation of employment in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130031","130031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850802","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief on Stamp Duty Land Tax for transfers involving public bodies in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130032","130032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850803","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy that UK embassies in EU 27 countries collect information British citizens living within those countries to ensure that information on the UK leaving the EU can be provided to those people.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130033","130033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850804","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief on Stamp Duty Land Tax for zero carbon homes in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130034","130034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850805","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many bodies established for national purposes received relief on acquisition in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130035","130035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850806","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge patients with long term medical conditions to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130036","130036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850807","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief for incorporation of limited liability partnership in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130037","130037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850809","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge dialysis patients to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130038","130038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850810","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge cancer patients to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130039","130039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850811","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief on payments to relevant scientific research associations in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130040","130040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850812","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has put in place to ensure that UK embassies in EU 27 countries provide adequate assistance to British citizens during the process of the UK leaving the EU; and whether he plans to allocate additional resources to those embassies for that purpose.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130041","130041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850813","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge new parents to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130042","130042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850815","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge new parents with a baby in the neonatal unit to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130043","130043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850816","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS hospitals in England charge brain injury patients to park.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130044","130044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850817","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were admitted to an NHS hospital in England with a brain injury or related condition in 2017.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130045","130045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850818","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients stayed at an NHS hospital in England for seven days or longer in 2017.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130046","130046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850819","2018-03-01","Attorney General","2018-02-27","To ask the Attorney General, how many proven fraudulent personal injury claims were made by (a) horse-riders, (b) pedestrians, (c) cyclists and (d) other vulnerable road users in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130047","130047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850820","2018-03-01","Attorney General","2018-02-27","To ask the Attorney General, how many successful prosecutions there have been for personal injury insurance fraud in the UK court system in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130048","130048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850821","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many businesses have failed to comply with the requirement under the Modern Slavery Act 2015 that every organisation carrying on a business in the UK with a total annual turnover of £36m produce a slavery and human trafficking statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130049","130049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850822","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many litigants in person pursued personal injury cases in the courts in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130050","130050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850823","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment his Department has made of the level of proven fraud or exaggeration in non-road traffic accident injury claims.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130051","130051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850825","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal injury claims were submitted to the Compensation Recovery Unit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130052","130052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850826","2018-03-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the amount spent by local authorities in the UK on Smoke Control Area enforcement in each year since 1992 up to the latest year for which data is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130053","130053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850827","2018-03-01","Department for International Development","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to encourage businesses to comply with the Ethical Trading Initiative Base Code.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130054","130054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850828","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on staffing levels in the NHS.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130055","130055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850829","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether UK embassies in EU 27 countries are making preparations to engage with British citizens overseas in the event that the Overseas Electors Bill is passed into law.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130056","130056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850831","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last visited the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130057","130057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850832","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money NHS hospitals have been fined for not reaching targets in the last five financial years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130058","130058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850833","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on the implementation of a ceasefire in the Afrin region as a result of UN Resolution 2401.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130059","130059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850834","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money NHS hospitals have been fined for not reaching the target of 95% of people being seen in A&E in four hours in the last five financial years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130060","130060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850835","2018-03-06","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money NHS hospitals have been fined for failing to treat a patient on the non-urgent referral-to-treatment waiting list within 18 weeks in the last five financial years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130061","130061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850836","2018-03-05","Cabinet Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the year-on-year changes to average weekly incomes in each constituency in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130062","130062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850837","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2018 to Question 128081, for what reason complaints from women born in the 1950s who are affected by changes in state pension age have not yet been allocated to an investigation case manager; what steps his Department is taking to ensure that those complaints are (a) allocated to an investigation case manager and (b) resolved in a timely manner; and how long the Department estimates it will take to (i) allocate, (ii) investigate and (iii) resolve those complaints.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130063","130063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850839","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money was spent by (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in employing supply teachers in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130064","130064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850840","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the use of (a) higher level teacher assistants and (b) cover supervisors to cover teaching absences.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130065","130065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850841","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the names of all supply teacher agencies registered with his Department in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130066","130066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850842","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many defence contracts his Department has awarded to Boeing since December 2017; and what the value of each of those contracts was.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130067","130067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850843","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of people who left their undergraduate degree course for mental health reasons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130068","130068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850844","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) lesbian, (b) gay, (c) bisexual and (d) transgender asylum seekers have been granted refugee status in the United Kingdom in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130069","130069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850846","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) musicians and (b) artists have been refused entry into the UK due to them being deemed not conducive to the public good.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130070","130070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850847","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of employers in Wales who paid national minimum wage arrears in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130071","130071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850848","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the independent review by David Anderson QC entitled Attacks in London and Manchester, published in December 2017, whether the Joint Terrorism Analysis Centre is now responsible for producing national threat assessments of terrorist threats arising from domestic extremism.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130072","130072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850849","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the independent review by David Anderson QC entitled Attacks in London and Manchester, published in December 2017, whether (a) MI5 (b) and the Joint Terrorism Analysis Centre will take on an increased role in domestic extremism work; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130073","130073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850851","2018-03-01","Cabinet Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants have been (a) disciplined, (b) subject to criminal charges, and (c) dismissed for offences under the Official Secrets Act 1989 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130074","130074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850852","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports have been reported lost or mislaid by her Department and its agencies during immigration applications in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130075","130075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850853","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the policy of UK Immigration and Visas is on returning passports to immigration applicants by (a) recorded delivery, (b) first class post, (c) second class post and (d) other means.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130076","130076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850854","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans HM Revenue and Customs has for the future of its staff working at Abbey House and Parkside Court in Telford.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130077","130077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850855","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what revenue has been raised by the Dart Charge in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130078","130078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850856","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications of Israel’s plans to hold local elections in the Golan Heights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130079","130079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850858","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of deferring the upcoming increase in the contributions holiday for SAYE schemes from six to 12 months to allow more time for the share plan industry to undertake (a) system development and (b) regression testing.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130080","130080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850859","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps are being taken to protect forensic evidence following the collapse of Key Forensic Services; and if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of reopening the Forensic Science Service to ensure forensic work is not lost in the event of a contractor's closure.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130081","130081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850860","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his planned increase to contributions holidays for SAYE schemes will apply to those (a) on maternity leave, (b) on shared parental leave, (c) on adoption leave and (d) who miss payment contributions.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130082","130082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850861","2018-03-01","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the planned increase to the contributions holiday for SAYE schemes will apply to new SAYE contracts only or also cover pre-existing SAYE contracts.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130083","130083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850862","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) British citizens, (b) EEA nationals and (c) individuals with leave to remain or indefinite leave to remain have been wrongfully detained in immigration detention centres in each of the last five years; and will she make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130084","130084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850863","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the selection process is for members of the Children's Commissioner's Advisory Board.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130085","130085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850864","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department took to inform recipients of Support for Mortgage Interest of the changes from benefit to loan occurring on 5 April 2018.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130086","130086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850866","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any recipients of Support for Mortgage Interest did not receive notice of the impending changes to the benefit scheduled for 5 April 2018.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130087","130087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850867","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much time his Department deemed adequate to provide sufficient notice to those in receipt of Support for Mortgage Interest of the impending changes scheduled for 5 April 2018.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130088","130088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850868","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the latest date was by which recipients of Support for Mortgage Interest were made aware of the changes to the benefit scheduled for 5 April 2018.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130089","130089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850869","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of police forces' capacity to tackle rural crime; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130090","130090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850870","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made on the effects of rural crime on (a) residents and (b) business in Barnsley East constituency.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130091","130091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850871","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken was for a decision on settlement or indefinite leave to remain applications from submission to response in (a) Barnsley and (b) England in each of the last 3 years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130092","130092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850873","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the target time is for her Department to reach a decision on indefinite leave to remain applications; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130093","130093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850874","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of universal credit recipients in receipt of disability benefit with non-dependents living at their home receiving housing cost contribution deductions for non-dependents.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130094","130094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850875","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what percentage of initial decisions to award a housing cost contribution deduction for non-dependents to those in receipt of universal credit was overturned in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130095","130095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850876","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to use community pharmacies to help support people with long term conditions to manage their conditions.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130096","130096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850877","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has for greater use of community pharmacies to support (a) A&E departments and (b) general practices.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130097","130097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850878","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the contribution of community pharmacies to the NHS.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130098","130098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850879","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons her Department’s public guidance on applying for, extending or switching a family visa states that the earliest an application can be made is 28 days before current permission to stay in the UK expires; and for what reasons that guidance states that a decision will be made within 12 weeks if the application is from outside the UK and 8 weeks if the application is from within the UK.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130099","130099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850880","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for further leave to remain in the UK were received before an applicant’s current visa expiry date but completed by her Department after this date in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130100","130100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850882","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 128396, on Schools: Admissions, for what reason the Department exceeded the 12-week guideline on responding to consultations in the case of the Schools that work for everyone consultation; whether the Government plans to update that 12-week guideline; and for what reason the Department did not provide complete answers to the questions on (a) when the Department plans to respond to that consultation and (b) for what reason the Department has not yet responded to that consultation.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130101","130101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850883","2018-03-01","Northern Ireland Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Irish Government on preventing a hard border in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130102","130102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850884","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2017 to Question 118701, on children’s centres, what role he plans for children’s centres to have in delivering his Department’s social mobility action plan.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130103","130103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850885","2018-03-05","Northern Ireland Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her policy is on proposals to reduce the pay of Members of the Northern Ireland Assembly while that Assembly is not sitting; and what assessment she has made of the potential effect of such a reduction on Members of the Northern Ireland Assembly's (a) staff and (b) wider office costs.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130104","130104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850887","2018-03-01","Scotland Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on improving digital connectivity; and what recent discussions he has had with that Government on improving broadband (a) connections and (b) speeds to new housing developments.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130105","130105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850888","2018-03-05","Scotland Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 125135, on Housing: Broadband, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Government’s brokered agreement to connect new build developments in Scotland; and what recent representations he has received from (a) Scottish Government Ministers and (b) local authorities on that agreement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130106","130106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850889","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the HMRC offices at the Waterfront in Dudley are owned or leased by his Department; and what assessment has been made of the costs to the public purse of closing those office.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130107","130107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850890","2018-03-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 125135, on Housing: Broadband, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of that brokered agreement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130108","130108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850892","2018-03-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 125135, on Housing: Broadband, if she will make initial reports on the effectiveness of the Government's brokered agreement available to (a) the Housing, Communities and Local Government Select Committee and (b) the Scottish Affairs Select Committee inquiry into digital connectivity in Scotland.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130109","130109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850893","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the REACH chemical framework on the defence supply chain.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130110","130110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850894","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has undertaken an impact assessment on the consequences of the UK changing its regulatory standard away from the REACH chemical use and transport regulations for chemicals produced or imported into the UK once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130111","130111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850895","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Government has to adopt the REACH chemical use and transport regulations for chemicals produced and imported into the UK after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130112","130112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850897","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will assess the health and economic benefits of legalising cannabis for medical use.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130113","130113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850898","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to introduce a new CONTEST strategy.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130114","130114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850899","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what report he has received on whether all 80 of the detainees included in the Government of Sudan’s announcement of 18 February 2018 have been released.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130115","130115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850900","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on whether the Government of Sudan has released political detainees on the condition that they do not organise protests in the future.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130116","130116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850901","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assistance the Government plans to provide to staff made redundant by HMRC at the Waterfront offices in Dudley in terms of advice, financial support, retraining and job search to help them obtain alternative employment in the event of the proposed closure of that office.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130117","130117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850902","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs what information he holds on the arrest and detention of Salih Mahmoud, vice chair of the Darfur Bar Association.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130118","130118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850903","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on whether the journalist Amal Habani was hospitalised after being beaten by Sudanese security officials.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130119","130119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850905","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will establish a task force comprised of his Department, the Department for Work and Pensions, Dudley Metropolitan Borough Council, advice agencies and training organisations to support staff who lose their job in the event of the proposed closure of the HMRC Waterfront offices in Dudley.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130120","130120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850906","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the proposed transfer of staff employed by HMRC at the Waterfront offices in Dudley to the Department of Work and Pensions has been cancelled.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130121","130121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850907","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the removal of Robert Mugabe as President of Zimbabwe on the safe return of failed asylum seekers to Zimbabwe who are active members of the Movement for Democratic Party.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130122","130122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850908","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of EU health workers who have left the NHS since the EU referendum on 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130123","130123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850909","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money the police service has received from charging for special police services in relation to football matches in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130124","130124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850910","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the police are sharing biometric data of migrant children with Immigration Enforcement; and whether such sharing is for purposes other than safeguarding.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130125","130125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850911","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the persecution of the Rohingya in Myanmar.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130126","130126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850912","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) applications for leave to remain and (b) written communications from Members of Parliament on behalf of their constituents have been received by UK Visas and Immigration in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130127","130127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850915","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 2 (General) Certificate of Sponsorship have been submitted in each month since November 2017; how many of those applications were granted, and how many of those applications were refused as a result of the annual cap having been reached.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130128","130128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850916","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Tier 2 (General) Certificates of Sponsorship have been refused since November 2017 as a result of the annual cap having been reached; which Standard Occupational Classification codes have been affected by that cap; and how many applications have been refused for each of those codes.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130129","130129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850917","2018-03-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with the road haulier industry on access to EU member states after 2019.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130130","130130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850918","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 17 January 2017 to Question 59048 and pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 122503 on Speed Limits, for what reasons (a) the research commissioned by his Department into the effects of 20 mph speed zones and (b) his Department's report have yet to be published.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130131","130131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850919","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his counterpart in the Government of Sudan on the recent demolition of places of worship in North Khartoum.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130132","130132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850921","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of support for pupils who experience mental health problems.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130133","130133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850922","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment the Government has made of the effectiveness of the National Maritime Single Window pilot exercise.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130134","130134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850923","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to stimulate demand for recycled material.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130135","130135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850924","2018-03-01","Department for International Trade","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many mutual recognition agreements he plans to negotiation with third countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130136","130136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850925","2018-03-01","Northern Ireland Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which (a) stakeholders and (b) representatives of victims and survivors of terrorism she has met since taking office.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130137","130137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850927","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what monitoring arrangements there are for the contracts given to (a) the NESTA consortium and (b) Cardiff University in relation to the What Works Centre.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130138","130138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850928","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to Answer of 6 February 2018 to Question 126173, on Department for Education: Telephone Services, what funding his Department has allocated to each helpline mentioned in that Answer for the next 12 months; and whether his Department plans to cease funding any of those helplines.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130139","130139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850929","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of LINK's decision on interchange fees on the ability of UK consumers to freely access cash.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130140","130140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850930","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve early diagnosis rates for pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130141","130141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850931","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations his Department has made to LINK on its decision to change the interchange fee mechanisms paid by banks to ATM operators.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130142","130142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850933","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to seek a Defence Sector Deal.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130143","130143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850934","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding the Government plans to provide to support care providers in funding the (a) historical capital costs and (b) ongoing revenue costs of complying with the recent tribunal ruling on sleep-in payments and the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130144","130144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850935","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions officials of his Department have had with BAE Systems on that company's ongoing redundancy programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130145","130145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850936","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 8 January 2018 to Questions 121064, 121066 and 121067, what information his Department has provided to people claiming welfare support to confirm that they are eligible for a loan.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130146","130146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850937","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions have been imposed on universal credit claimants who are (a) disabled and (b) experiencing mental health problems in the most recent 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130147","130147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850939","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued to general practitioners on charging to provide medical evidence to support benefit claims.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130148","130148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850940","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, on what date he expects Wave 3 of the Local Full Fibre Network Challenge Fund to open for applications.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130149","130149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850941","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Universal Credit easements from conditionality have been applied to (a) claimants experiencing a period of sickness, (b) claimants suffering a bereavement following the death of a partner, child or qualifying young person, (c) claimants receiving treatment for drug and alcohol dependency and (d) claimants who are main carers of a Child in Considerable Distress.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130150","130150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850942","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has conducted an evaluation into Work Coaches' tailoring of the Universal Credit Claimant Commitment for people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130151","130151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850943","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has assessed the potential merits of reimbursing general practitioners for providing medical evidence to support benefit claims; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130152","130152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850945","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when her Department most recently revised its guidance to jobcentre staff on managing customer declarations of intention to attempt suicide or self-harm.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130153","130153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850946","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the estimated cost is of the Royal Free and North London Breast Screening Service for 2018-19.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130154","130154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850947","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether jobcentre staff are required to undertake a safeguarding visit before imposing a sanction on a vulnerable customer.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130155","130155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850949","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Government of Turkey on military operations against the Democratic Federation of Northern Syria.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130156","130156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850950","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many mammographers are planned for employment under the Royal Free and North London Breast Screening Service in 2018-19.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130157","130157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850951","2018-03-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 17 January 2018 to Question HL4467 on Syria: Kurds, whether the Government plans to provide (a) diplomatic, (b) military, and (c) humanitarian support to the Democratic Federation of Northern Syria.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130158","130158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850952","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the (a) detail and (b) quality of Ofcom’s quarterly telecoms complaints data on the ability of consumers to make informed decisions.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130159","130159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850954","2018-03-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of including data from Alternative Dispute Resolution schemes in Ofcom’s quarterly telecoms complaints data to enable consumers to make better informed decisions.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130160","130160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850955","2018-03-01","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February to Question 125796, on vulnerable children, which professionals, schools and other experts have been consulted as part of the Government's scoping exercise; and what evidence has assessed during that work.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130161","130161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850956","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to respond to the joint serious case review into sexual exploitation in Newcastle.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130162","130162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850957","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 125923 on Army: Recruitment, how many people (a) applied and (b) enlisted in the regular army in October to December 2017.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130163","130163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850958","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Highways England designated fund for cycling, safety and integration; and how much of that fund was spent in 2016/17.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130164","130164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850960","2018-03-01","Department for International Trade","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which non-EU countries his Department has identified as best for future trade deals in the automotive sector.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130165","130165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850961","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport,  whether his Department has allocated funding for Network Rail's Hope Valley Capacity Order.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130166","130166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850962","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when construction work is planned to start on Network Rail's Hope Valley Capacity Order.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130167","130167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850963","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for train operating companies to operate increased services on Network Rail's Hope Valley Capacity Order.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130168","130168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850965","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his counterpart in the Government of Poland on their Holocaust law.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130169","130169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850966","2018-03-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many local government employees were suspended on full pay in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130170","130170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850967","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Deptartment, what the Government's policy is on the destruction of security service files on the political activities of private individuals.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130171","130171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850968","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, What guidance his Department has been issued on drivers using satellite navigational apps on mobile phones whilst driving vehicles.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130172","130172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850970","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies have been prosecuted by HMRC under the Money Laundering Regulations 2017 in the last year.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130173","130173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850971","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies have been prosecuted under the Money Laundering Regulations 2017 by the Financial Conduct Authority in the past 12 months.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130174","130174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850972","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding was allocated to the Prevent strand of the counter-terrorism strategy in 2016-17.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130175","130175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850974","2018-03-05","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been allocated to the Prevent strand of the counter-terrorism strategy in 2017-18.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130176","130176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850975","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the level of debt accrued by SMEs as a result of late payments.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130177","130177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850976","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the number of businesses that have been wound up as a result of late payments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130178","130178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850977","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate the his Department has made of the number of SMEs that have been forced to take legal action to recover late payments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130179","130179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850978","2018-03-01","Department for International Trade","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with which countries he and his officials have held discussions with about future trading options after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130180","130180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850980","2018-03-01","Department for International Trade","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to promote UK automotive exports to the international market.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130181","130181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850981","2018-03-05","HM Treasury","2018-02-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of credit union legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130182","130182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850982","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she plans to take to encourage the Post Office to allow people on universal credit to access credit union services; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130183","130183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850983","2018-03-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fly tipping prosecutions there were in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017; and how much was raised in fines from such prosecutions in each of those years.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130184","130184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850985","2018-03-05","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason observational assessment is not part of the assessment criteria for the incoming early years baseline assessment.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130185","130185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850986","2018-03-05","Department for International Development","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Department requires agencies delivering its programmes to ensure their staff have access to counselling for (a) post traumatic stress disorder and (b) other mental health needs.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130186","130186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850987","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to support the development of a new ballistic missile defence radar demonstrator.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130187","130187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850989","2018-03-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many species of plants the UK has provided for the Svalbard Global Seed Vault in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130188","130188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850990","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, whether the Government plans to attend the UN High-Level Conference on Nuclear Disarmament in May.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130189","130189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850991","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, what steps the Government is taking to support gradual multilateral nuclear disarmament.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130190","130190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850993","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to (a) raise awareness and (b) reduce the prevalence of prostate cancer.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130191","130191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850994","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the potential number of cases of prostate cancer which could be identified earlier by a national prostate cancer screening programme and (b) the potential effect such a programme on survival rates.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130192","130192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850995","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve pancreatic cancer survival rates.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130193","130193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850997","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the devolved Administrations on the future treatment and care of people with cancer.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130194","130194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850998","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment he has made of the speed with which (a) GPs in the UK and (b) their equivalents in other countries refer patients who might have cancer; and what steps he is taking to improve the speed of cancer referrals.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130195","130195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/850999","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to encourage energy companies to improve the accessibility and clarity of energy bills and statements to help customers better understand their charges.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130196","130196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851000","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to increase cancer survival rates in the next five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130197","130197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851002","2018-03-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the reliability and accuracy of smart meter energy readings.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130198","130198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851003","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was for cancer test results in each hospital trust in England in 2009-10 and each subsequent year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130199","130199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851004","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have received medicine funded by the Cancer Drugs Fund by medicine since 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130200","130200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851006","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Northern Ireland Government on the availability of drugs to treat cancer.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130201","130201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851007","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many young people aged 17 and under were sectioned under the Mental Health Act 1983 by age in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130202","130202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851008","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve access to mental health services for care leavers who are between 18 and 25 years old.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130203","130203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851009","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many young people of what age under 18 were treated in adult mental health wards in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130204","130204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851010","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the longest period of time was that a patient has had to wait for access to mental health services in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130205","130205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851011","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many young people were registered with Child and Mental Health services in (a) England, (b) London, (c) each London borough and (d) each London health trust on 1 January of each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130206","130206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851012","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to improve the support available to mental health professionals to manage their own mental health.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130207","130207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851013","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to improve access to mental health services for children who have (a) been the victims of abuse and (b) experienced other trauma.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130208","130208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851015","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much interest has been paid by NHS trusts and Foundation Trusts on bailout loans from his Department in (a) this year and (b) each of the past five years; where such interest is paid to; and for what purposes such interest payments were subsequently used.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130209","130209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851016","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment has he made of the effect of planned reductions in his Department’s total budget on (a) reoffending levels and  (b) access to justice.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130210","130210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851017","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when in 2018 his Department plans to choose a replacement for the British Army's BR90 bridge system as part of Project TYRO.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130211","130211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851018","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment has he made of the effectiveness of outsourcing maintenance works in prisons.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130212","130212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851019","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of prison conditions.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130213","130213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851021","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to increase the number of private prisons.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130214","130214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851022","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of violence and self-harm in prisons.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130215","130215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851023","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of mental health services provision in prisons.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130216","130216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851024","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce overcrowding in prisons.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130217","130217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851025","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of the number of (a) prisoners and (b) staff on levels of violence in prisons.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130218","130218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851026","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of sentences below three months in reducing reoffending.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130219","130219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851028","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of privatised probation companies.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130220","130220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851029","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment has he made of reoffending levels since the part-privatisation of probation.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130221","130221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851030","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that private probation companies have adequate staffing levels.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130222","130222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851031","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to make additional extra payments to privatised probation companies following the £342 revision in 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130223","130223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851032","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, What steps his Department is taking to ensure that the review of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 receives input from a wide range of stakeholders.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130224","130224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851033","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department has undertaken into the cost effectiveness of legal aid for early legal help.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130225","130225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851034","2018-03-05","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel he plans to deploy to Mali in support of the three RAF CH-47 Chinook heavy lift helicopters providing logistical support to French operations in the Sahel region.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130226","130226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851036","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department has commissioned on the potential effects of virtual court hearings on vulnerable defendants.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130227","130227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851037","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) bridges, (b) vehicles, (c) trestle sets and (d) pontoon sets his Department is planned to continue to operate as part of the Project TYRO plan to upgrade the British Army's BR90 bridging system.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130228","130228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851038","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the next annual update of the Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130229","130229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851040","2018-03-01","Department for Transport","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the health effects of achieving the aims of the Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130230","130230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851041","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the number of (a) Close Support Bridges, (b) General Support Bridges and (c) Launch and Support vehicles in the British Army is planned to be reduced following the completion of Project TYRO.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130231","130231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851042","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the overall cost of Project TYRO to replace and upgrade the British Army's BR90 bridging system.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130232","130232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851043","2018-03-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on average ambulance waiting times in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130233","130233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851044","2018-03-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been affected by the under-occupancy penalty in North West Durham constituency.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130234","130234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851045","2018-03-05","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the attrition rate was for students on midwifery courses in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130235","130235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851047","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many councils have (a) requested and (b) received funding help for urgent fire safety work following the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130236","130236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851048","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which (a) regular and (b) reserve units within the Corps of Royal Engineers operate the BR90 bridging system.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130237","130237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851049","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the longest length of time a prison officer spent on detached duty was in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130238","130238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851051","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of days of detached duty served by a prison officer was in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130239","130239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851052","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage investment in The Gambia.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130240","130240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851053","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2018 to Question 125714, what his Department's estimated cost is for determining on how many occasions wings of publicly-owned prisons were closed due to insufficient staff levels in December 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130241","130241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851055","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2018 to Question 125736, what was the value was of each of those subcontracted contract; how performance was measured under each of those subcontracts; and by what mechanism his Department had oversight of each of those subcontracts.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130242","130242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851056","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2018 to Question 126481, on Prisons: Repairs and Maintenance, and with reference to the contracts to outsource facilities management in prisons signed in 2014, what the most recent five charges were for which his Department has information on the cost of (a) replacing a broken window, (b) replacing a lock, (c) cleaning up a spillage, (d) fixing a toilet seat and (e) screening a shower.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130243","130243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851057","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2018 to Question 126482, what estimate his Department made of the cost of providing the information sought.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130244","130244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851058","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2018 to Question 126526, if he will publish the report into the riot at HMP Birmingham in December 2016 with the sections which could compromise security arrangements redacted.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130245","130245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851059","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of Question 8 February 2018 to Question 125878, on Community Rehabilitation Companies, whether the monitoring of expenditure referred to in that Answer includes monitoring decisions on executive pay and the payment of dividends.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130246","130246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851060","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the weight of British Army Challenger 2 tanks will be that have gone through the CR2 Life Extension Programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130247","130247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851061","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126465, what estimate his Department made of the cost of providing the information sought.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130248","130248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851062","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126466, on Capita, on how many occasions his predecessor met Capita to discuss the issues raised by the Public Accounts Committee report on outsourced electronic monitoring.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130249","130249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851063","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) building and (b) refurbishment projects his Department plans in the (i) current, (ii) next and (iii) subsequent financial year; and what the cost will be of each such project.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130250","130250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851065","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost has been of employing civil servants to undertake procurement in his Department in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130251","130251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851066","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many legal aid matter starts there were in each matter start category in each constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130252","130252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851068","2018-03-05","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incarcerated (a) children (b) 18-21 year olds and (c) 22- 25 year olds were recorded as having speech, language and communication needs in the last year for which the information is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130253","130253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851069","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours people in each Young Offenders Institution spent in (a) work and (b) education on average in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130254","130254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851070","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Office, how many cases were referred to the Trafficking Victim Support Scheme in each year since 2010; and which organisation made each such referral.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130255","130255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851071","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claims for compensation were rejected by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority in each year since 2010-11; and for what reasons each of those claims was rejected.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130256","130256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851072","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether plans to re-timetable or re-profile the Project TYRO replacement and upgrade of the British Army's BR90 bridging system are under consideration as part his Department's Modernising Defence Programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130257","130257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851074","2018-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for compensation rejected by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority were referred to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Appeals Panel in each year since 2010; and how many such applications were successful.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130258","130258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851075","2018-03-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of tapering state benefits when an employee retires and has an auto-enrolment pension.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130259","130259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851076","2018-03-01","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which elements of the British Army's bridging capability fall under the remit of Project TYRO.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130260","130260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851077","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on future of the Minsk II agreement; what assessment he has made of the implications for UK foreign policy of the entry into force of the Ukrainian law on reintegration of the temporarily occupied territories; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130261","130261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851078","2018-03-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking in support of the Minsk II agreement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130262","130262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851080","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of  26 February 2018 HCWS486 on Local Government Policy, if he will place in the library a copy of the evidence which satisfied him that local government and service delivery will be improved in Christchurch as a result of his decision.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130263","130263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851081","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of  26 February 2018 HCWS486 on Local Government Policy, how many (a) written and (b) oral representations he received between 7 November 2017 and 8 January 2018 on Local Government reorganisation in Dorset; and how many of those representations were (a) against the abolition of Christchurch Borough Council and (b) in favour of the abolition of Christchurch Borough Council.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130264","130264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851082","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of  26 February 2018 HCWS486 on Local Government Policy, what the steps were that were taken after 7 November 2017 to secure local consent; and to the extent to which local consent was secured.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130265","130265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851084","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of  26 February 2018 HCWS486 on Local Government Policy, if he will place in the library a copy of the evidential basis which satisfied him that across Dorset as a whole there is a good deal of local support for the new Council.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130266","130266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851085","2018-03-05","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of  26 February 2018 HCWS486 on Local Government Policy, if the drafts of the necessary secondary legislation will include a requirement that the same level of Council tax will be payable by all households on Band D in the unitary authority proposal for Christchurch, Poole and Bournemouth.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130267","130267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/851186","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with her counterpart in the French Government on unaccompanied children in Calais vulnerable to (a) human trafficking and (b) modern slavery; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130268","130268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/968090","2018-09-10","Department for Education","2018-02-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the level of student debt of universities charging administration fees for courses.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 170759","170759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849286","2018-02-27","Home Office","2018-02-26","What recent assessment she has made of the effect of alcohol abuse on levels of crime and costs of policing.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904008","904008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849288","2018-02-26","Home Office","2018-02-26","What discussions she has had with Police and Crime Commissioners on the level of the police precept for 2018-19.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904009","904009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849289","2018-02-26","Home Office","2018-02-26","How many times the Tier 2 (General) Certificate of Sponsorship cap has been reached in each of the last three months.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904010","904010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849290","2018-02-26","Home Office","2018-02-26","What steps she is taking to tackle cyber crime.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904012","904012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849291","2018-02-26","Home Office","2018-02-26","What steps she is taking to confiscate money from criminals; and how she plans to further strengthen the asset recovery regime.","Biography information for Huw Merriman","Huw Merriman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904013","904013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849292","2018-02-26","Home Office","2018-02-26","What steps her Department is taking to encourage greater collaboration between police and fire services.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904014","904014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849293","2018-02-26","Home Office","2018-02-26","What discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the resourcing of the Economic Crime Unit.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904015","904015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849294","2018-02-26","Home Office","2018-02-26","What recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the protective equipment available to police forces.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904016","904016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849945","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 123234, whether the certificates of past performance for the HS2 contracts awarded to Carillion in July 2017, the HESTIA contracts awarded to Carillion in July 2017 and the London to Corby electrification contract awarded in November 2017 were self-certificates.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129513","129513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849946","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many incidents of malware being used to illegally mine cryptocurrency have been reported by the Government since 2015.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129514","129514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849947","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information the Government holds on the amount of personal data which was stolen from government websites in the recent BrowseAloud hack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129515","129515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849948","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments has taken to monitor compliance by the right hon. Member for Sevenoaks of conditions it gave with regard to his appointment at Avanton Ltd.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129516","129516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849949","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments has taken to monitor compliance by Robert Hannigan of conditions it gave with regard to his commissions under the independent consultancy announced in October 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129517","129517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849950","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will require the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments to collate and publish advice collected by Departments which is given to SCS1 and SCS2 civil servants on appointments after public service.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129518","129518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849951","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether consultants and temporary workers are subject to the business appointment rules regulated by the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129519","129519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849952","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to revise the Civil Service Management Code; and if he will take steps to strengthen references in that code to real or perceived conflicts of interest.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129520","129520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849953","2018-02-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of ECMO beds this winter.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129521","129521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849954","2018-02-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether any patients have been unable to access an ECMO bed after its use had been clinically recommended in each of the (a) last 12 months and (b) last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129522","129522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849955","2018-03-01","Home Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made whether all medical professionals should be included on the shortage occupation list; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129523","129523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849956","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of departmental variations in finance, human resources and procurement processes on the development of shared services across government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129524","129524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849957","2018-02-28","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment is Department has made of the potential effect of reducing data duplication across government on access to public services for people who are (a) precariously housed, (b) students and (c) experiencing relationship or family separation and (d) leaving abusive relationships; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129525","129525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849958","2018-02-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the process will be for upholding the High Court judgment on Personal Independence Payments.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129526","129526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849959","2018-03-01","Cabinet Office","2018-02-26","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much of the funding from his Department to underwrite the costs of Carillion’s receiver has been spent to date; and what costs have been covered by that funding.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129527","129527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/849960","2018-02-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an estimate of the amount of time spent on managing existing contracts by clinical commissioning group commissioners.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129528","129528"
