"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772132","2017-10-20","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Written Statement of 9 October 2017, on Student finance update, HCWS 145, what estimate her Department has made of the long-term annual cost to the taxpayer of those policy changes in that statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108349","108349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772133","2017-10-20","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Early Years Workforce Strategy published in March 2017, when her Department plans to publish the feasibility study on the development of a programme to grow the graduate workforce in disadvantaged areas.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108341","108341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772135","2017-10-20","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are in receipt of the service pupil premium; and what the amount received by Plymouth schools was of that premium in financial years (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108342","108342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772136","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to prioritise approval of standard for Maritime Caterer Apprenticeship between her Department and the Maritime Trailblazer Working Group.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108308","108308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772137","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times the standard for Maritime Caterer Apprenticeship submitted to her Department by the Maritime Trailblazer Working Group has been rejected since her Department assumed responsibility for apprenticeships policy.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108309","108309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772138","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answers of 18 September 2017 to Questions 10212 and 10213 on Erasmus+, whether the Government will underwrite successful bids submitted for Erasmus+ for those students with a mandatory year abroad in 2019-20, including the bids that are signed after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108312","108312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772139","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the change in attainment levels at Key Stage 4 for (a) white, (b) BAME and (c) all pupils  who are (i) eligible and (ii) not eligible for free school meals in the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108351","108351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772141","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the number of apprentices in the maritime industry.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108307","108307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772142","2017-10-20","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the local authority of Warwickshire County Council has requested to disapply the high pass-through requirement.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108156","108156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772143","2017-10-20","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's response to Freedom of Information request 45757, for what reason her Department does not hold information on family income in relation to validation of 30 hours of free childcare codes.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108171","108171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772145","2017-10-20","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether there is a deadline on using childcare eligibility codes issued by HM Revenue and Customs to secure 30 hours of free childcare from childcare providers.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108106","108106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772148","2017-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to increase food production in the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU in March 2019 with no agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108147","108147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772150","2017-10-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of leaving the EU on the level of the UK's self sufficiency in food; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108129","108129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772151","2017-10-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on domestic food prices across the UK in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108130","108130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772152","2017-10-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent of the spread of sudden oak death; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108185","108185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772153","2017-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the export of ivory from the UK.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108202","108202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772155","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps at his Department's next meeting with the Government of Pakistan to ensure that the Government of Pakistan works to improve trust between NGOs and that Government and to improve consultation with NGOs on polices that affect their daily operations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108196","108196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772156","2017-10-19","Department for International Development","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government plans to take to use its aid to Pakistan as a mechanism to discourage the overregulation of NGOs and to reduce violations of the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108198","108198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772157","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps at his Department's next meeting with the Government of Pakistan to emphasise the contribution of NGOs to countering violent extremism and promoting development and human rights.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108199","108199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772158","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to facilitate dialogue between the Government of Pakistan and NGOs in line with the concluding observations of the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights and the Universal Periodic Review of Pakistan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108197","108197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772160","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department last had discussions with the Government of Pakistan on space for civil society in Pakistan; what was on the agenda at that meeting; what the outcome of that meeting was; and when the next such meeting is planned to take place.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108195","108195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772161","2017-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of implementation of the 2016 peace agreement in Colombia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108163","108163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772162","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made recent representations to the Government of Israel on the adequacy of the water supply and sanitation infrastructure in the West Bank.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108133","108133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772163","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Israel and Palestinian officials on water permits in the (a) Jordan Valley area and (b) wider Palestinian West Bank.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108132","108132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772165","2017-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his priorities are for the Antarctic region for the next 12 months.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108168","108168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772166","2017-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department will represent the UK at the meeting of the Commission for the Conservation of Antarctic Marine Living Resources between 16 and 27 October 2017.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108169","108169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772168","2017-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received legal opinions on the status and contravention of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe's rights under (a) international human rights law and (b) Iranian law.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108108","108108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772169","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many people with dual Palestinian and British citizenship have been (a) refused entry to, (b) detained by and (c) deported from Israel in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108313","108313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772170","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in the US to reconsider the alleged practice of officials not medically monitoring hunger striking in Guantanamo Bay detainees.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108280","108280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772172","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK citizens have been deported by Israel for reasons related to pro-Palestinian activity after initially being granted entry to Israel in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108292","108292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772173","2017-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received from (a) members of the public, (b) non-governmental organisations and (c) parliamentarians on the detention of the Chinese human rights lawyer, Gao Zhisheng.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108343","108343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772174","2017-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Chinese counterpart on  the detention of the Chinese human rights lawyer, Gao Zhisheng.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108344","108344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772175","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US on the UK's support for the closure of the detention facility at Guantanamo Bay.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108281","108281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772177","2017-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Joint Press Statement from the Permanent Representatives to the UN of the US, France and UK on 7 July 2017, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the global stockpile of nuclear weapons.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108345","108345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772178","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK citizens held in Israel's airport detention facilities have been provided with consular assistance by the UK embassy in Tel Aviv in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108293","108293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772179","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK citizens have been (a) detained and (b) delayed when entering Israel in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108294","108294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772180","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Russian counterpart on the number of troops committed to the Zapad 17 military exercise.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108299","108299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772181","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK citizens have complained of poor treatment by Israeli authorities at border crossings and entry points; and of those people how many have raised such issues with the (a) Government, (b) embassy in Tel Aviv and (c) consulates in Jerusalem and Ramallah in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108290","108290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772183","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK citizens have been detained, interrogated and subsequently denied entry to Israel in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108291","108291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772185","2017-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) his counterpart in Somalia and (b) representatives of Somalia in the UK on support for counter-terrorism and security issues in that country since the recent terrorist attack in Mogadishu.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108339","108339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772187","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote Israeli-Palestinian cooperation relating to the water sector.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108333","108333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772189","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support improved access to portable, affordable and clean water for the domestic and livestock needs of the Bedouin communities in the Palestinian West Bank.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108332","108332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772190","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many companies supplying goods and services to his Department, or contracted to deliver services on behalf of his Department, have been identified as avoiding their tax liabilities in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108263","108263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772192","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on repression in Tibet.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108246","108246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772194","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of UK citizens who have been refused entry and deported by the Israeli Government as a direct result of amendment 27 of the Entry into Israel Law during the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108261","108261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772195","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Foreign Secretary meets representatives of Guantanamo detainee, of 1 March 2012, whether it is the Government's policy that indefinite detention in Guantanamo Bay is wrong; and that the UK will continue to call for Guantanamo Bay to be closed.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108323","108323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772196","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the comparative capacity and caseload weight of special community mental health services in 2012-13 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108205","108205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772198","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to bring forward legislation to make all dermal fillers prescription-only products.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108240","108240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772199","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that maternity units deliver full cover and staff at weekends.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108219","108219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772200","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure improved treatment in cases of sepsis in hospitals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108220","108220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772201","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with clinical bodies on the potential connection between e-cigarette use and heart disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108221","108221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772203","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with Alzheimer's disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108222","108222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772204","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with leg ulcers in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108223","108223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772205","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when laser treatment for people with leg ulcers will be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108224","108224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772206","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with clinical bodies on the potential connection between quinine and heart risk.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108225","108225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772207","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with Group B strep in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108226","108226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772209","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with clinical bodies on assistance with stem-cell therapy for people with MS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108227","108227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772210","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many companies supplying goods and services to his Department, or contracted to deliver services on behalf of his Department, have been identified as avoiding their tax liabilities in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108264","108264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772211","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what body has taken responsibility for the security functions previously undertaken by NHS Protect.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108270","108270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772212","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 21 November 2016 to Question 52567, on prescription drugs, what further steps have been taken to reduce the amount of unused prescription medication; and what the cost to the public purse was of those steps.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108352","108352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772214","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of medication being administered when required for patients rather than automatically dispensing repeat prescriptions.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108353","108353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772216","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with NHS England undertaking an urgent review into the commissioning of post-stem cell transplant services.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108148","108148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772217","2017-10-20","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to assist those affected by complications relating to transvaginal mesh implants.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108174","108174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772219","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to assess the (a) clinical benefit and (b) value for money of Endaravone in extending the lifespan of people with motor neurone disease.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108151","108151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772221","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK citizens have been extradited from Bangladesh to the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108152","108152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772222","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many European arrest warrants for UK citizens were outstanding at 1 September 2017.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108175","108175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772224","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions her Department has in place to help support sponsored foreign nationals at risk of homelessness if their sponsor is no longer available.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108137","108137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772225","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 105522, how much was paid to the Behavioural Insights Team for services relating to each of those policy areas.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108145","108145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772226","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from Ethiopia submitted applications for asylum in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2016-17.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108134","108134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772228","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for asylum submitted by (a) Iranian and (b) Ethiopian nationals between 2010 and the latest date for which figures are available (i) are pending and (ii) have been (A) approved and (B) refused.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108135","108135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772229","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from Iran have submitted applications for asylum in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2016-17.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108136","108136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772230","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum and immigration cases were delayed as a result of misplaced documents in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108155","108155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772231","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK citizens have been extradited from India to the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108176","108176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772233","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time for extradition proceedings was for UK citizens extradited from India to the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108177","108177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772235","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time for extradition proceedings was for UK citizens extradited from Pakistan to the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108178","108178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772236","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK citizens have been extradited from Pakistan to the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108179","108179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772237","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time of extradition proceedings was for UK citizens extradited from Bangladesh to the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108153","108153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772239","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) longest waiting time was for non-straightforward Tier 5 visa applications in each quarter of the last five years.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108188","108188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772240","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on the introduction of a register for people found guilty of stalking or domestic violence offences.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108200","108200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772241","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will communicate guidance to the Director-General of the National Crime Agency on the use of the powers under section 241A of the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002, as amended by Criminal Finances Act 2017.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108203","108203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772243","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether people who purchase knives for work-related purposes will be made exempt from the proposed ban on online knife sales.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108102","108102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772246","2017-10-25","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions she has put in place for people who grew up in care and are unable to provide a birth certificate when applying for a passport.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108350","108350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772248","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of police officers in the Metropolitan Police Service worked in the London Borough of Newham in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108252","108252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772249","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied migrant children in the UK have been moved to at least two different local authorities since their arrival.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108253","108253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772250","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the adequacy of the level of financial reserves held by fire authorities.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108234","108234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772251","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of closing the refugee camp in Calais on the availability of data on unaccompanied child refugees; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108251","108251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772253","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) longest waiting time was for non-straightforward Tier 4 visa applications in each quarter of each of the last five years.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108208","108208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772255","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) longest waiting time was for non-straightforward spousal visa applications in each quarter of each of the last five years.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108209","108209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772256","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time was at immigration control at the 10 busiest airports in the summer months of each of the last five years.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108210","108210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772258","2017-10-20","Home Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting times are at immigration control at the 10 busiest airports in the UK in peak morning and evening arrivals.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108211","108211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772259","2017-10-19","Department for International Development","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funds her Department has committed to the Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria programme in the financial years (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108242","108242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772260","2017-10-19","Department for International Development","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department provided for bilateral programmes on tuberculosis in the financial years (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108243","108243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772261","2017-10-19","Department for International Development","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on ensuring that expenditure from the Prosperity Fund prioritises international development over UK industrial and political interests.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108245","108245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772263","2017-10-19","Department for International Development","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many companies supplying goods and services to her Department, or contracted to deliver services on behalf of her Department, have been identified as avoiding their tax liabilities in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108265","108265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772264","2017-10-20","Department for International Development","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make representations to the Bangladeshi Government on ensuring that Islamic Relief is able to operate in that country; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108340","108340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772265","2017-10-19","Department for International Development","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of arms sales to Saudi Arabia on development and humanitarian outcomes in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108139","108139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772266","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what resources have been allocated to the Central London County Court in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108149","108149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772268","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how staffing resources are allocated within the Central London County Court.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108150","108150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772269","2017-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to commence its review of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108159","108159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772270","2017-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for exceptional case funding were (a) made and (b) granted for clinical negligence where the case relates to vaginal mesh implants in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108187","108187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772271","2017-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which options the Government plans to assess on reducing the number of litigants in person as part of its review into the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108161","108161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772273","2017-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which provisions of the Legal Aid Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 the Government's plans to scrutinise in its post-implementation review.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108162","108162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772274","2017-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many clinical negligence proceedings involving the death of a child were granted legal aid in (a) 2008, (b) 2009, (c) 2010, (d) 2011, (e) 2012 and (f) 2013.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108186","108186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772275","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for jobseeker's allowance tribunals in Glasgow East constituency was in each of the last four years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108087","108087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772276","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for tax credits tribunals in Glasgow East constituency was in each of the last four years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108088","108088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772278","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment tribunal claimants there were in Glasgow East constituency in the 12 months (a) before and (b) after the introduction of tribunal fees.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108089","108089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772279","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for income support tribunals in Glasgow East constituency was in each of the last four years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108090","108090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772280","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for employment and support allowance tribunals in Glasgow East constituency was in each of the last four years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108091","108091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772281","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for personal independence payment tribunals in Glasgow East constituency was in each of the last four years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108092","108092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772283","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans the Justice in Wales Working Group have to discuss its work with the Commission on Justice in Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108318","108318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772285","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Justice in Wales Working Group consulted the (a) Police Commissioners, (b) Police Chiefs and (c) Police Federation in Wales prior to the publication of its report on devolution.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108319","108319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772286","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the list of organisations and individuals consulted by the Justice in Wales Working Group relating to its report on devolution.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108320","108320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772288","2017-10-19","Attorney General","2017-10-17","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to ensure greater collaboration between the Crown Prosecution Service and the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108331","108331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772289","2017-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many domestic abuse cases included the use of Level 1 restorative justice in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108212","108212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772290","2017-10-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of family law proceedings in England and Wales involved domestic violence or child abuse in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108207","108207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772291","2017-10-19","Scotland Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate the Government has made of the number of new trains planned to operate on the East Coast mainline between Edinburgh and London as a result of High Speed 2.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108143","108143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772294","2017-10-20","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress is being made on finalising the East Midlands rail franchise.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108170","108170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772297","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what changes he is making to the national airspace strategy which will result in Leeds Bradford Airport changing flight paths planes use after take-off.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108104","108104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772298","2017-10-20","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Road Investment Strategy: for the 2015-16 to 2019-20 Road Period, which of the projects announced have (a) been completed, (b) been cancelled, (c) faced changes to their completion date and (d) experienced increases in their costs; which of the projects (i) will be completed by 2020, (ii) will have started before 2020 and (iii) will neither have started nor be completed before or by 2020, broken down by region; and in which regions those projects have been conducted.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108214","108214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772299","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 7 July 2016 to Question 42206 on roads: suicide, how many suicides or attempted suicides were recorded on the strategic road network from 1 July to 31 December 2016.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108247","108247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772301","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the potential future level of overcrowding on London's transport network.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108239","108239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772303","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to double the number of apprentices in the UK maritime sector; and what discussions he has had with employers on such an increase since London International Shipping Week 2017.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108260","108260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772304","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many companies supplying goods and services to his Department, or contracted to deliver services on behalf of his Department, have been identified as avoiding their tax liabilities in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108266","108266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772306","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to double the number of officer cadets in the UK shipping industry; and what engagement he has had with employers on that issue since London International Shipping Week 2017.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108306","108306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772307","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on the time taken in agreeing the standard for a Maritime Caterer Apprenticeship between his Department and the Maritime Trailblazer Working Group.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108311","108311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772308","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many merchant seafarer (a) ratings and (b) officer cadets were trained by employers in the commercial ferry sector in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108310","108310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772310","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to double the number of rating apprentices in the UK shipping industry; and what engagement he has had with employers on that issue since London Shipping Week 2017.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108279","108279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772311","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to double the number of apprentices in the UK ports sector; and what engagement he has had with employers on that issue since London Shipping Week 2017.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108278","108278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772313","2017-10-19","Wales Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate his Department has made of the number of journeys by (a) people and (b) freight between ports in Wales and the Republic of Ireland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108154","108154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772314","2017-10-20","Wales Office","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether the power to legislate to make parking on the pavement an offence in Wales is a reserved or devolved matter.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108183","108183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772315","2017-10-19","Women and Equalities","2017-10-17","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to meet the Government's target of women making up 33 per cent of FTSE 350 boards by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108146","108146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772316","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what additional support is being offered to single parent families applying for universal credit whose children are at risk of falling into poverty.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108138","108138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772318","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the status is of his Department's proposal to move the Galashiels Jobcentre.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108142","108142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772320","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent progress his Department has made on the roll-out of the Youth Obligation.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108131","108131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772321","2017-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2017 to Question 105496, on universal credit: internet, how many new claimants log into their online journal after submitting a claim for universal credit within (a) 24 hours, (b) one week and (c) one month.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108172","108172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772322","2017-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what additional support is being offered to people applying for universal credit who (a) have lost identification documents during a period of homelessness and (b) are unable to provide a permanent address.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108189","108189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772324","2017-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average level of debt held by a household on universal credit.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108190","108190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772326","2017-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the six-week wait on universal credit payments on levels of (a) household poverty, (b) household debt and (c) rent arrears.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108182","108182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772327","2017-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of further advanced payment loans on financial security in cases were the universal credit recipients roll-out has caused financial hardship.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108191","108191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772329","2017-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to revise the criteria for determining applications for personal independence payments and employment and support allowance for people with Crohn's disease.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108160","108160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772331","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the longest length of time in days is that a universal credit applicant has waited for their initial payment in Glasgow East constituency to date.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108094","108094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772333","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of how many people in Glasgow East constituency are eligible to receive pension credit.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108096","108096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772334","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to adapt Shettleston Jobcentre to accommodate extra staff and customers as a result of the closure of Parkhead, Easterhouse and Bridgeton Jobcentres in February 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108097","108097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772335","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of how many full-time equivalent staff will be employed by his Department at Shettleston Jobcentre in Glasgow after the closure of Parkhead, Easterhouse and Bridgeton Jobcentres in February 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108098","108098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772337","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent staff his Department employs at Bridgeton Jobcentre in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108099","108099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772339","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of the number of full-time equivalent work coaches who will be based at Shettleston Jobcentre when universal credit is rolled out in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108100","108100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772340","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to change the opening hours of Shettleston Jobcentre; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108101","108101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772341","2017-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who in those areas where universal credit is being rolled out is receiving the payment by sex in each household.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108347","108347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772343","2017-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2017 to Question 106562, on PAYE: disclosure of information, in what circumstances the abbreviation, LMI referred to is used to stand for Late, Missing and Incorrect.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108336","108336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772346","2017-10-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 106034, on universal credit, for what reason that data is not available; and whether his Department has plans to make that data available.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108338","108338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772347","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claimants have had their tribunal appointment rescheduled due to insufficient time on the day in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108314","108314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772348","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the current average waiting time is for an employment and support allowance tribunal appointment.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108316","108316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772349","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the current average waiting time is for rescheduled tribunal appointments.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108317","108317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772350","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many companies supplying goods and services to his Department, or contracted to deliver services on behalf of his Department, have been identified as avoiding their tax liabilities in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108267","108267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772351","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has conducted a cost-benefit analysis of the closure of Eastern Avenue jobcentre.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108248","108248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772352","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 105923 on UK Trade with EU; if he will publish those plans for contingency scenarios; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108235","108235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772353","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 105923 on UK Trade with EU; what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on planning to meet those contingency scenarios.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108236","108236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772354","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 105923 on UK Trade with EU; what cost to the public purse was incurred by developing those plans to meet those contingency scenarios.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108237","108237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772355","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the extent of offshore ownership of UK land freeholds.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108268","108268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772356","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the number of graduates in non-graduate jobs.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108269","108269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772357","2017-10-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an impact assessment of the (a) implementation of a domestic safeguards regime and (b) undertaking other roles fulfilled by UK membership of Eurtatom by the Office for Nuclear Regulation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108256","108256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772358","2017-10-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the workforce capacity of the Office for Nuclear Regulation to undertake the safeguarding programmes currently undertaken by Eurtatom.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108258","108258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772359","2017-10-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what funding his Department plans to make available to the Office for Nuclear Regulation to enable it to take responsibility for the nuclear safeguarding role currently undertaken by Eurtatom.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108257","108257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772360","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information the Government holds on how many households have been on British Gas, E.on, EDF, Npower, Scottish Power and SSE's standard variable tariffs for (a) five years or more and (b) 10 years or more.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108315","108315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772361","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 70 of the Women and Equalities Committee's report of Session 2016-17, Pregnancy and maternity discrimination, HC90, whether he plans to implement a system similar to that used in Germany under which pregnant women and new mothers can be made redundant only in specified circumstances.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108335","108335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772362","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of coal required to manufacture the (a) cement and (b) iron and steel required to construct (i) Hinckley Point power station, (ii) the third runway at Heathrow and (iii) Crossrail 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108105","108105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772363","2017-10-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government response to the First Report of the Women and Equalities Committee of Session 2016-17, Pregnancy and maternity discrimination, published on 26 January 2017, Cm 9401, when he plans to implement the Government's commitment to bring forward proposals to ensure that those protections in place for women who are pregnant or returning from maternity leave are sufficient.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108107","108107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772364","2017-10-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure that his decision on hydraulic fracturing consent applications, and the assessments made to support it, are published.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108109","108109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772365","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for the Government's review of redundancy protection for pregnant women and new mothers.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108120","108120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772366","2017-10-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department holds information on the proportion of energy customers on standard variable tariffs who are also in receipt of the winter fuel payment for each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108127","108127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772367","2017-10-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the level of personal debt associated with unpaid energy bills; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108128","108128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772368","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of households in Glasgow East constituency which spend more than 10 per cent of their income on fuel bills.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108093","108093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772369","2017-10-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to tackle incidents of late payments to small and medium-sized enterprises by larger businesses.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108181","108181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772370","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 155 of his Department's Clean Growth Strategy, published on 12 October 2017, what the energy intensity level was of the UK economy measures by final energy demand of MWh of energy per million pounds of GDP in real 2016 prices in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108204","108204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772371","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether an estimate has been made of the number of energy customers in Berwickshire, Roxburgh and Selkirk constituency who are on (a) standard variable tariffs or (b) a default tariff.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108140","108140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772372","2017-10-19","Department for International Trade","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the number of small and medium-sized enterprises who export goods to other EU countries but have no experience of customs documentation or procedures for trading with countries outside the customs union.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108325","108325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772373","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 106966, on Fracking: Ryedale, on what day that application was received; what the timetable is for a decision to be made; whether he plans to publish an assessment of that application; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108327","108327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772374","2017-10-19","Department for International Trade","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how he plans to ensure bilateral cumulation in rules of origin exist as part of plans to replicate existing EU third-party trade agreements.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108326","108326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772375","2017-10-20","Department for International Trade","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations he has made to his Slovak counterpart on that country's procurement of a replacement for the L39 aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108217","108217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772376","2017-10-19","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the European Court of Justice has any remit in relation to the activities of the European Aviation Safety Agency.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108329","108329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/772377","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support the Government is planning to provide to small and medium-sized enterprises who face additional customs procedures after the UK has left the Customs Union.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108324","108324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/775466","2017-10-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Operation Ruman in providing humanitarian aid to Caribbean islands affected by hurricane Irma.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901319","901319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/775467","2017-10-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to encourage innovation in the defence industry.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901323","901323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/775468","2017-10-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to encourage innovation in the defence industry.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901322","901322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/775469","2017-10-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on defence spending.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901320","901320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771326","2017-10-18","Attorney General","2017-10-16","To ask the Attorney General, if he will consider overturning the decision to classify documents about the death of Dr David Kelly; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107770","107770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771327","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any action has been taken to date following and as a result of the meetings of the Borders Planning Group.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107763","107763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771328","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 7789, on day care, what proportion of parents who have successfully applied for tax-free childcare are self-employed.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107743","107743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771329","2017-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) high-rise residential buildings over 30 metres in England and (b) flats in those buildings.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107753","107753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771330","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what records his Department keeps on the delivery of projects of a value in excess of 10,000.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107742","107742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771331","2017-10-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when the Tourism Industry Emergency Response Group met over the last year.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107752","107752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771332","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the Hawk TMk1 training aircraft to be taken out of service for the (a) Royal Air Force Aerobatics Team and (b) rest of the Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107758","107758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771333","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on suitability tests of Advanced Hawk 128 T2 Jet Trainers; and whether he plans to procure further Advanced Hawks for the (a) Royal Air Force Aerobatics Team and (b) rest of the Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107748","107748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771334","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the annual (a) maintenance, (b) spares, (c) fuel, (d) provision and (e) other running costs of a (i) Type 45 Destroyer, (ii) Type 26 Destroyer, (iii) Landing Platform Helicopter, (iv) Landing Platform Dock, (v) Hunt Class Minehunter and (vi) Astute Class Submarine.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107740","107740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771335","2017-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK personnel were embedded in the National Security Agency Cryptologic Centre in Georgia USA, in each month between 1 October 2016 and 1 October 2017.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107756","107756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771336","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Hawk T1 Aircraft and (b) Advanced Hawk 128 T2 Jet Trainers are in use by the Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107757","107757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771337","2017-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date his Department plans to publish its response to the Better Compensation consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107769","107769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771338","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the new funding formula for schools includes funding for students with high needs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107760","107760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771339","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the use of finger printing of school children for identification purposes.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107761","107761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771340","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the 30 hours free childcare entitlement on childcare providers' ability to (a) employ and (b) support (i) qualified early years teachers and (ii) other staff with suitable qualifications.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107754","107754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771341","2017-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to support apple growers as part of any post-Common Agricultural Policy arrangements after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107764","107764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771342","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's policy is on the findings of the UN Working Group on Arbitrary Detention Opinion No. 28/2016 on Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107759","107759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771343","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps have been taken to secure consular access to Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe since recent new charges have been brought against her.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107751","107751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771344","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to implement the recommendations of the Accelerated Access Review, published on 24 October 2016.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107744","107744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771345","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to launch a scheme to help GPs with indemnity payments; whether that scheme will be targeted at new entrants to the profession; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107780","107780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771346","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of delayed transfer of care to avoid bed shortages at hospitals in winter 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107800","107800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771347","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many licences have been issued under the Animal (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 for research involving (a) deer and (b) registered stag hunts in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107781","107781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771348","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Turkish citizens were granted a Turkish Businessperson visa to the UK under the terms of the Ankara Agreement in each year between 2007 and 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107765","107765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771349","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has had discussions with her counterpart in Turkey on the future of the Turkish Businessperson visa established under the terms of the Ankara Agreement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107766","107766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771350","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to continue to offer the Turkish Businessperson visa established under the terms of the Ankara Agreement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107767","107767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771351","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the most recent review her Department has conducted on the reintroduction of the Seasonal Agricultural Workers Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107747","107747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771352","2017-10-19","Department for International Trade","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to DIT Ministerial Quarterly Transparency Returns, published on 13 October 2017, on which international journeys undertaken by (a) him, (b) the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Investment, (c) the Minister of State for Trade and Export Promotion and (d) the Minister of State for Trade Policy were (i) economy, (ii) business, (iii) first and (iv) any other class were used.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107745","107745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771353","2017-10-18","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of Transport for London's dispute with Uber on taxi operators and drivers in other parts of the UK.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107762","107762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771354","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Sefton Central of 12 October 2017 to the Leader of the House, Official Report, column 469, if he will remove the charge for telephone calls to his Department on universal credit.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107750","107750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771355","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the level of incidences of collusion in the insurance industry between providers of home and contents insurance.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107741","107741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771356","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of competition conditions for domestic supply contracts within the retail energy market; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107746","107746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771357","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support the Government is offering to the employees affected by the closure of some Homebase stores.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107755","107755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771358","2017-10-19","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to appoint a permanent Government Chief Scientific Advisor.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107768","107768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771359","2017-10-19","Department for International Trade","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which members of the US Senate he has met to discuss the trade dispute between Boeing and Bombardier.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107749","107749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771360","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to establish an online service to enable people to check if they are registered to vote.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107941","107941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771361","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent comparable assessment the Government has made in the volume of guidance produced by the Electoral Commission for the registration of UK citizens overseas and the registration of homeless people; and whether his Department plans to review such guidance.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107935","107935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771362","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding was allocated by the Government to support (a) the registration of UK electors overseas and (b) residents without a fixed address in advance of the (i) 2017 General Election, (ii) EU referendum and (iii) 2015 General Election.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107936","107936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771363","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to ensure consistency in Unique Property Reference Numbers for the database used by councils and the gov.uk/register-to-vote website.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107937","107937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771364","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what safeguards are in place to ensure that people registered to vote outside of the UK do not register in more than one parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107938","107938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771365","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many cases of impersonation took place in each parliamentary constituency and local authority in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107940","107940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771366","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that homeless people are (a) registered to vote and (b) participate in elections; and what assessment he has made of the effect on registration levels of the requirement for electors without a fixed address to print a local connection form to register to vote.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107939","107939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771367","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the working population of Bolton West constituency is employed in the (a) public and (b) private sector.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108071","108071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771368","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people in Bolton took part in National Citizen Service in 2016; and where that borough ranks in numbers of children taking part in the scheme nationally.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108073","108073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771369","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which local authorities have expressed interest to his Department in conducting a voter ID pilot in polling stations for the May 2018 local elections.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108068","108068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771370","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government has taken to implement the recommendations of Sir Eric Pickles' review of electoral fraud entitled Securing the ballot, not including the voter ID pilots planned for the May 2018 local elections.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108084","108084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771371","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list the Government departments that his Department does not anticipate needing discrete funding to prepare for UK negotiations on the EU resulting in no deal in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108053","108053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771372","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department plans to make of the contribution of European Structural and Investment Funds to UK universities; and if he will takes steps to ensure that there will not be a funding gap for universities.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108069","108069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771373","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total amount of discrete funding his Department estimates each Government Department will receive to aid preparations for UK negotiations on the EU resulting in no deal in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108054","108054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771374","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will allocate a proportion of the funds collected from the Apprenticeship Levy funding to the College of Printing for police training in Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108066","108066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771375","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many kinship carers have been denied child tax credit, for a baby to whom they or their partner have given birth, as a result of the restriction of child tax credit to two children in a household since 6 April 2017.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107976","107976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771376","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the potential fiscal effect is of reducing the maximum stake on fixed odds betting terminals to (a) 2, (b) 10, (c) 20, (d) 30 and (e) 100.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107989","107989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771377","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the contribution of the Prime Minister of 11 October 2017, Official Report, column 328, how much of the funding to Departments for work on the UK leaving the EU each Department will receive.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107932","107932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771378","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential additional bureaucratic requirements that will be imposed on British businesses in the event that the UK leaves the Customs Union.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107952","107952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771379","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of social care employers found to be non-compliant with the national minimum wage have had arrears identified by self-correction since January 2016.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107910","107910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771380","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the analyses the Government has undertaken on the effect of leaving the Customs Union on various sectors of the UK economy.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107891","107891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771381","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 11 September 2015 to Question 8179 on children: day care, what recent assessment he has made of the link between the introduction of tax-free childcare and (a) the cost and (b) demand for childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107892","107892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771382","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 46 of HM Revenue and Customs Annual Report and Accounts 2016-17, whether HM Revenue and Customs took account of the minority status of the Cornish under the Framework Convention for the Protection of National Minorities when it made location decisions under the Building our Future Programme.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107911","107911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771383","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding HM Revenue and Customs has (a) set aside and (b) paid out to parents in compensation for not being able to access their tax-free childcare accounts.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107874","107874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771384","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made on the effect on the wine and spirit industry of the 3.9 per cent increase in duty paid.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107904","107904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771385","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that performers contracted to work in shows under the management of a director employed as workers and are remunerated as such.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107898","107898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771386","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps his Department is taking to support the wine and spirits industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107905","107905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771387","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to support public country by country reporting.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107885","107885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771388","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to halt the planned increases in wine and spirits duty.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107906","107906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771389","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will review the planned increases to the duty applied to wines and spirits in the November budget.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107907","107907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771390","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in other EU countries on public country by country reporting.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107886","107886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771391","2017-10-19","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 6005, what plans HM Revenue and Customs has to conduct compliance work nationally from a reduced number of tax offices.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107832","107832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771392","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to extend the April 2018 deadline for childcare vouchers if the Childcare Service IT system is not fully operational.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107860","107860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771393","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the suitability of the IT system run by ATOS that operates tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107861","107861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771394","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many childcare providers have registered for the provision of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107862","107862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771395","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the technical performance of the Childcare Choices portal and the effect of that performance on access to (a) 30 free hours and (b) tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107873","107873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771396","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential connection between (a) street and (b) ambient lighting and the incidence of burglaries.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107850","107850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771397","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many housing starts there were in (a) May, (b) June, (c) July and (d) August 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107856","107856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771398","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people on a waiting list for an allotment in England in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107851","107851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771399","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what grants his Department has made to which (a) Muslim, (b) Jewish, (c) Christian and (d) inter-faith organisations for the purposes of integration and community cohesion in each year since May 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107852","107852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771400","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) published since May 2010 on citizenship and public attitudes towards extremism.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107853","107853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771401","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department has provided directly to the public to help it understand the threat from extremism and to promote integration; and whether such information has been made available in languages other than English.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107854","107854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771402","2017-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to review the effect on households of the 2014 changes to enforcement agents.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107883","107883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771403","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to establish the role of letting agents in ensuring that landlords comply with their obligation to protect tenants' monies in tenancy deposit schemes.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107887","107887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771404","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many requests his Department has received from (a) local authorities, (b) housing associations and (c) other social housing providers for financial support to fit sprinkler systems in high-rise tower blocks since the Grenfell Tower fire; and what his Department's response was to each of those requests.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107921","107921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771405","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people aged (a) 0 to 10, (b) 11 to 20, (c) 21 to 30, (d) 31 to 40, (e) 41 to 50, (f) 51 to 60, (g) 61 to 70, (h) 71 to 80, (i) 81 to 90 and (j) over 91 years who (i) died and (ii) were injured as a result of fire in private rented sector housing in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107771","107771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771406","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's (a) catering and (b) hospitality budget was in (i) 2015, (ii) 2016 and (iii) 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107801","107801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771407","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of (a) privately-rented, (b) social and (c) owner-occupied homes in England which had at least one working smoke alarm in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107772","107772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771408","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of his Department's staff excluding non-departmental public bodies were (a) women in top management posts, (b) women, (c) black and minority ethnic and (d) disabled in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107802","107802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771409","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many hectares of land in England have been (a) declassified and (b) classified as greenbelt in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107803","107803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771410","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of housing development has taken place on (a) greenbelt and (b) brownfield land in each of the last 20 years in England; how many housing units have been built in (i) greenbelt and (ii) brownfield land in each such year; and how many hectares of (A) greenbelt and (B) brownfield land have been consumed by housing in each such year.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107804","107804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771411","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on training delivered by the Fire Service College in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017 to date; how much she expects to be spent on such training in (i) 2017-18, (ii) 2018-19 and (iii) 2019-20; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107775","107775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771412","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effects on the number of (a) households and (b) children living in poverty of changes to council tax in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107805","107805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771413","2017-10-18","Cabinet Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Green Paper and consultation on the long-term funding for social care will include proposals for working age adults with disabilities.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107806","107806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771414","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many officials in his Department are currently working on matters relating to the UK exiting the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107777","107777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771415","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on software licences in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107778","107778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771416","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities in England have not increased levels of council tax in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107779","107779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771417","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the average cost to the owner of a domestic dwelling of damage caused by fire in a property that (a) has and (b) does not have a smoke alarm.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107796","107796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771418","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number and proportion of domestic fires in the private rented sector in England that have occurred as a result of (a) smoking and (b) electrical faults since 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107797","107797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771419","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) fatalities and (b) injuries there were in England as a result of fire in (i) privately rented, (ii) social and (iii) owner-occupied homes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107798","107798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771420","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with cabinet colleagues on the planning of the Stay Well This Winter 2017 campaign.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107799","107799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771421","2017-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish a supported housing green paper.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107812","107812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771422","2017-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) published on anti-Semitism since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107835","107835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771423","2017-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reductions in social care funding on the delayed transfer of care.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107962","107962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771424","2017-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress is being made on the roll-out of voluntary right to buy.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107978","107978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771425","2017-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of the Sheffield City Region mayoral election.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107979","107979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771426","2017-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to make a decision on the application from the London Borough of Newham to continue its private rented sector licensing scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107992","107992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771427","2017-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to make a decision on the London Borough of Newham's application to continue its private rented sector licensing scheme.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108022","108022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771428","2017-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the cost to the public purse was of converting the London Stadium to and from an athletics venue for the 2017 IAAF World Championships.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108013","108013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771429","2017-10-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2017 to Question 106052, when the complete figures for the numbers of library closures for the last 12 months will be available; and if she will publish the data her Department holds on the numbers of libraries in each constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107956","107956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771430","2017-10-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what financial assistance is available to cultural institutions which have incurred extra security costs resulting from recent acts of terrorism in London.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107960","107960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771431","2017-10-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the independent review of S4C announced on 7 August 2017, whether information on (a) the deadline for submitting evidence, (b) the questions on which the review is gathering evidence and (c) the contact to whom evidence should be submitted has been made publicly available online.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107920","107920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771432","2017-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what percentage of UK premises experience broadband download speeds of less than (a) 1MB/s, (b) 2MB/s, (c) 5MB/s and (d) 10 MB/s.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107944","107944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771433","2017-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what financial assistance the Government has given to cultural and artistic venues to assist with extra security costs incurred as a result of recent terrorist attacks in London.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107945","107945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771434","2017-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the equity of regional and national trends in the award of National Lottery grants over the last three years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107899","107899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771435","2017-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, on what the 740 million 5G research and infrastructure fund announced in the 2016 Autumn Statement has been spent.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107884","107884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771436","2017-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish the recommendations on fixed-odds betting terminals of the Responsible Gambling Strategy Board and the Gambling Commission.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107900","107900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771437","2017-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 105517, on Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport: redundancy pay, what the total amount was that was paid to (a) men and (b) women.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107894","107894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771438","2017-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Government's publication Ministerial hospitality, 1 April to 30 June 2017, published on 13 October 2017, whether (a) representatives or employees of the firm which offered that hospitality and (b) lobbyists or contractors of those firms were present at those events.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107871","107871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771439","2017-10-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on providing finance for the establishment of a Cultural Development Fund.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108027","108027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771440","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the financial implications of re-deploying military units from Strensall to Gamecock Barracks, Nuneaton.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107880","107880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771441","2017-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department does not record the postcode of new recruits to HM Armed Forces.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107912","107912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771442","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of acacia clearances in the UK Sovereign Base Area in Cyprus on the illegal trapping of songbirds on the base.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107794","107794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771443","2017-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the ambassadorial use of HMS Duncan by Belfast City Council or Invest NI.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107811","107811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771444","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that the planned refresh of the Government's defence industrial policy ensures that the flow of work from prime contractors to UK-based sub-contractors is measured in order to compare and evaluate the relative merits of competing proposals to meet his Department's requirements.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107849","107849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771445","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will ensure that the Royal Air Force Aeronautics Team always flies in aircraft manufactured in the UK.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107787","107787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771446","2017-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on defence and aerospace manufacturing capability in the North West of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107966","107966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771447","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which defence systems and equipment his Department regards as critical for retaining sovereign defence capability.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107999","107999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771448","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the Norwich Area Programme targets do not recognise vocational trade-related qualifications as a measure of progress for disadvantaged young people.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108014","108014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771449","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of eligible three and four year-olds in England are not claiming the early years pupil premium.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107967","107967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771450","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Children and Families of 12 October 2017, Official Report, column 212WH, in how many instances parents are using 30 hours of free childcare with (a) one provider, (b) two providers and (c) more that two providers.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107955","107955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771451","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the revenue raised by the Apprenticeship Levy will be allocated to fund apprenticeships with non-levy employers.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107963","107963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771452","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the total money raised by the Apprenticeship Levy will be allocated to levy-paying companies for their own apprenticeship training schemes.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107964","107964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771453","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment she has made of registered training providers in receipt of (a) less, (b) the same, (c) more funding in real terms per apprenticeship start in the period (i) May to December 2017 and (ii) August 2016 to April 2017.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107965","107965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771454","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's budget is for apprenticeships for 16 to 18 year olds in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19; and what proportion of that budget is generated by the Apprenticeship Levy.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107917","107917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771455","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Children and Families of 12 October 2017, Official Report, column 210WH, how many times a validation code has been generated on the basis of a job offer.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107954","107954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771456","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish a list of the funding allocated to each training provider for apprenticeship starts for the periods (a) August 2016 to April 2017 and (b) May to December 2017.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107918","107918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771457","2017-10-23","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of those eligible for free school meals in (a) Enfield North constituency, (b) London and (c) the UK took up free school meals in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108046","108046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771458","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils have studied humanities at GCSE level in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108035","108035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771459","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils have studied (a) double and (b) triple science in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108036","108036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771460","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils have studied a modern foreign language at GCSE level in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108034","108034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771461","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she had made of the number of children in each local authority in Greater Manchester who will benefit from the Government's policy of 30 hours of free childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107980","107980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771462","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she intends to take to address the shortage of applications for secondary teacher training places in subjects not expected to reach the targets set by the teacher supply model for September 2017.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108025","108025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771463","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils' data has been (a) requested by and (b) given to the Home Office under the data sharing agreement with her Department for purposes including immigration enforcement in each month in 2017; and when those numbers will be published.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108061","108061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771464","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish the data sharing agreement with the Home Office, used in monthly transfer of national pupil data, for purposes including immigration enforcement.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108062","108062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771465","2017-10-23","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children in (a) Enfield North constituency, (b) London and (c) the UK were eligible for free school meals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108047","108047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771466","2017-10-23","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average class size was in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (i) Enfield North constituency, (ii) London and (iii) the UK in each of then last seven years.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108049","108049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771467","2017-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish the Government's youth policy statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108072","108072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771468","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the most recent estimate is of the funding required to establish a free school in Bolton.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108074","108074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771469","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools in Bolton West constituency have received funding from the pupil premium; and how many pupils in each such school have attracted such payments.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108075","108075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771470","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools are currently meeting the Gatsby benchmarks of good practice in careers education, information, advice and guidance.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107822","107822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771471","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many registered (a) childminders, (b) nurseries and (c) maintained nurseries rated as good or outstanding by Ofsted have closed in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107819","107819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771472","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to continue the National Careers Service Prime Contractor Area Groups from 1 April 2018.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107823","107823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771473","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship starts there were in May to July 2017 for each industry sector.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107824","107824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771474","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to achieve the objectives on broadening the early years workforce set out in the Early Years Workforce Strategy.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107814","107814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771475","2017-10-19","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to monitor the level of additional charges placed on parents by childcare providers accessing government-funded free childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107915","107915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771476","2017-10-18","Department for Education","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will assess the potential merits of increasing the number of non-pupil days for special needs schools to allow teachers to train to meet pupils' health needs.","Biography information for Lucy Frazer","Lucy Frazer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108052","108052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771477","2017-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the levels of domestic and business insurance held by those at risk of flooding in each local authority area.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107931","107931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771478","2017-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is his policy to maintain the contents of the EU Timber Regulation after it is transposed into UK law.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107913","107913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771479","2017-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the use of single use plastics.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107863","107863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771480","2017-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to increase the level of recycling of single use drinks containers.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107864","107864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771481","2017-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to examine the effectiveness of the Phage and PCR tests for the testing of cattle for bovine TB.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107782","107782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771482","2017-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people in Bolton were found guilty of animal cruelty in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108077","108077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771483","2017-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment on the benefits for Great Britain and Northern Ireland's coastal communities of the marine resources in the UK's Exclusive Economic Zone being used solely for the benefit of the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108048","108048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771484","2017-10-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the entirety of the Fisheries acquis will be transferred into domestic legislation in the EU (Withdrawal) Bill.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108021","108021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771485","2017-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how his Department allocates funds to each region to protect dwellings and businesses from surface water flooding.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107923","107923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771486","2017-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many properties and businesses have been flooded in Norwich in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107922","107922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771487","2017-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2017 to Question 68600, whether he has had sight of the bilateral treaty between Ethiopia and Yemen on Andy Tsege's removal to Ethiopia.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107927","107927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771488","2017-10-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Iranian Government on the new charges being brought against Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe; and what steps the Government has taken to secure her release.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107988","107988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771489","2017-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has requested that consular visits with Andy Tsege be conducted in private.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107994","107994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771490","2017-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to visit Tunisia following the lifting of the travel ban.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107774","107774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771491","2017-10-18","Department for International Development","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to include tackling global health threats such as malaria as part of its ongoing dialogue with other Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107809","107809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771492","2017-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contribution the UK is making to degrading Al Qaeda in the Arabian Peninsula in the Gulf.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107836","107836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771493","2017-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will support EU sanctions against Myanmar's military leaders in response to their role in the Rohingya crisis.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107795","107795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771494","2017-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart in bilateral co-operation on foreign and security policy.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107841","107841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771495","2017-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Saudi Government on lifting the blockade of Yemeni ports and airports.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107846","107846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771496","2017-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Emirati counterpart on that country's use of regulatory gaps in UK shell companies to facilitate the export of arms to the South Sudanese Government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107882","107882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771497","2017-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to end the violence against Rohingya people in Myanmar; and what support the Government is providing to Bangladesh to support displaced Rohingya refugees.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108085","108085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771498","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people aged over 65 have adequate transport to and from routine hospital appointments.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107872","107872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771499","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the removal of the nursing bursary on the number of people entering mental health nurse training in the last 12 months; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of that removal in the next five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107869","107869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771500","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the proposed requirement for clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) to go through an individual funding request before each patient is able to access bariatric surgery on (a) patient health and (b) capacity of CCGs to respond to that requirement.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107834","107834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771501","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many admissions were made to acute psychiatric in-patient beds in England for each year from 2012-13 to 2016-17.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107870","107870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771502","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) couple therapists, (b) interpersonal therapists, (c) brief psychodynamic therapists and (d) counsellors for depression have been employed by NHS England in the Adult Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107829","107829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771503","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS England has spent on specialised inpatient eating disorder services (a) in total and (b) using services provided by private sector organisations in Scotland in each if the last six (i) financial and (ii) calendar years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107833","107833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771504","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of admissions to acute psychiatric inpatient units were made under the Mental Health Act 1983 in England in each year from 2012-13 to 2016-17.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107876","107876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771505","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of a junior doctor's training.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107865","107865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771506","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average occupancy rate was for acute psychiatric inpatient beds in England in each year from 2012-13 to 2016-17.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107877","107877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771507","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been detained in locked rehabilitation wards in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107867","107867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771508","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of (a) total and (b) per capita spending on (i) health and (ii) mental health in England in spent in York; and where York is ranked in England for such spending.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107879","107879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771509","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been detained in locked rehabilitation wards outside their local area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107868","107868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771510","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to monitor progress on achieving the target of increasing the size of the mental health workforce by 2020-21.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107896","107896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771511","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the start of the Meningitis B teenage carriage study; and when he plans for the results of that study to be published.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107909","107909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771512","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what extra resources the Government has given to CAMHS in Lancashire since the Manchester area attack of 22 May 2017.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107847","107847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771513","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on how many (a) couple therapists, (b) interpersonal therapists, (c) brief psychodynamic therapists and (d) counsellors for depression have been employed in the Adult Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme by clinical commissioning group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107830","107830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771514","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on how many cognitive behavioural therapists have been employed by NHS England in the Adult Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme by clinical commission group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107828","107828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771515","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects of budgetary changes to the funding of drug treatment programmes on mortality rates among heroin and crack cocaine users in England between 2013 and 2017.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107820","107820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771516","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding from the public health grant his Department allocated to Blackpool for drug treatment budgets in the years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15, (d) 2015-16 and (e) 2016-17.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107821","107821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771517","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the (a) number of children having a delayed discharge from in-patient mental health treatment and (b) total number of delayed days for each (i) NHS region and (ii) mental health trust provider in England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107825","107825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771518","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff were employed by NHS England in the Adult Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107826","107826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771519","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on how many staff were employed in the Adult Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme by clinical commission group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107827","107827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771520","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the GP to patient ratio for (a) Enfield Clinical Commissioning Group and (b) other clinical commissioning groups in London; and if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of those GP to patient ratios.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107810","107810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771521","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time for a GP appointment was in Denton and Reddish constituency in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107776","107776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771522","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department is giving to promote further negotiations between NICE, NHS England and the drug manufacturer Vertex on access to Orkambi for people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107793","107793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771523","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the care needs of stem cell transplant patients beyond the first 100 days of recovery.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108063","108063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771524","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information is available on support and self-help groups for patients recovering from a stem cell transplant.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108064","108064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771525","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of care and support that stem cell transplant patients are able to access after leaving hospital.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108065","108065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771526","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the Cost-Effectiveness Methodology for Immunisation Programmes and Procurements working group's report into vaccine cost effectiveness has not been published.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108067","108067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771527","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many over-65s in (a) Southampton, (b) Portsmouth and (c) England have a long-term mental health condition.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108038","108038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771528","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many over-65s in (a) Southampton, (b) Portsmouth and (c) England have a long-term physical health condition.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108039","108039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771529","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the number of children dropping out of (a) child and adult mental health services treatment and (b) eating disorder treatment in each month of the past year for each (i) clinical commissioning group and (ii) trust in England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108042","108042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771530","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department defines a long-term health condition.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108040","108040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771531","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many over-65s in (a) Southampton, (b) Portsmouth and (c) England have a long-term health condition.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108037","108037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771532","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate NHS England has made of the baseline level of investment clinical commissioning groups need to commit to children's mental health services in order to provide an acceptable level of service.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108020","108020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771533","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the number of children entering in-patient treatment for eating disorders for each NHS region in England for each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108045","108045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771534","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children started eating disorder treatment in each (a) clinical commissioning group area and (b) trust in each of the last 36 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107981","107981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771535","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the number of children entering child and adult mental health services treatment within (a) six weeks and (b) 18 weeks from the date of referral for each (i) clinical commissioning group area and (ii) Trust area for each month of the past year.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108044","108044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771536","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the number of children completing (a) child and adult mental health services treatment and (b) eating disorders treatment in each month of the past year for each (i) clinical commissioning group and (ii) Trust in England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108043","108043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771537","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the local authority spending on children's mental health by area for the last two years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108019","108019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771538","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were (a) referred to a CAMHS service and (b) accepted by a CAMHS services for each (i) clinical commissioning group area and (ii) trust in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107982","107982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771539","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children had a delayed discharge from in-patient eating disorder treatment and how many days of delayed discharge there were in each (a) NHS region and (b) mental health trust provider in England for each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107983","107983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771540","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children started mental health treatment in each (a) clinical commissioning group area and (b) trust in each month of the last three years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108016","108016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771541","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the level of spending on universal and targeted (non specialist) child and adolescent mental health services in each clinical commissioning group area in England in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108017","108017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771542","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish clinical commissioning group spending on children's mental health by area for the last two years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108018","108018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771543","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the number of children entering in-patient treatment for mental health conditions in each NHS region in England for each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108041","108041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771544","2017-10-19","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of emergency calls which have been put on hold in East Sussex in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107969","107969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771545","2017-10-18","Department of Health","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to meet the Government's commitment to provide funding for the Samaritans' helpline until the end of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Esther McVey","Esther McVey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107934","107934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771546","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has secured reciprocity in the criteria for entitlement to Irish nationality for spouses of Irish citizens resident in the UK.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107928","107928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771547","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to the Answer of 12 October 2017 to Question 9570, how many unsuccessful bids were made to the Police Transformation Fund; and what the amount was of each unsuccessful bid made to that fund.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107961","107961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771548","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what is the average waiting time to speak to an adviser from her Department's Further Submissions Unit by telephone in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108009","108009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771549","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there is a limit on the number of appointments that can be made each day by her Department's Further Submissions Unit.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108007","108007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771550","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many daily appointments were made on average by her Department's Further Submissions Unit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108008","108008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771551","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the hon. Member for Warley can expect to receive a reply regarding the case of Ms Kajal Verman and her letter of 14 June 2017.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107998","107998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771552","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the hon. Member for Warley can expect to receive a reply regarding the case of Mr Asad Joyn and his letter of 24 August 2017.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107996","107996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771553","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants living in Scotland have been granted permission to submit their application to her Department's Further Submissions Unit via post in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108006","108006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771554","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the hon. Member for Warley can expect to receive a reply regarding the case of M Waqas and his letter of 21 August 2017.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107997","107997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771555","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance or service standards are in place to ensure that asylum seekers are able to add (a) dependents and (b) new born children to their asylum support.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108002","108002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771556","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been employed as telephone advisers at her Department's Further Submissions Unit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108011","108011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771557","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been employed by her Department's Further Submissions Unit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108012","108012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771558","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many daily telephone calls on average her Department's Further Submissions Unit has received in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108010","108010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771559","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures are in place to ensure that pregnant asylum seekers and refugees receive access to maternity grants.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108003","108003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771560","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures are in place to ensure that her Department's Further Submissions Unit telephone helpline has sufficient capacity to answer calls.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108004","108004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771561","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants living in Scotland have been refused permission to submit their applications to her Department's Further Submissions Unit via post in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108005","108005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771562","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will introduce a central database of unaccompanied children entering the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107991","107991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771563","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time was between initial telephone contact being made with the Further Submissions Unit of her Department and an appointment being scheduled for the most recent period for which information is available.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108000","108000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771564","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how her Department's policy on unaccompanied child refugees is informed by the principle of putting children's best interests at the centre of all decision-making, as set out in the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107990","107990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771565","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the number is of fire-related deaths by fire authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108070","108070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771566","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what proportion of occasions when a fire engine was despatched in response to a 999 call (a) a police vehicle and (b) an ambulance was also sent to the same incident in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107773","107773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771567","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the effects of placing both parents names on a child's passport in the interests of helping border staff fulfil their duty to safeguard children; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107791","107791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771568","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were detained by the Border Force in the latest period for which figures are available; what information her Department holds about those who have been so detained; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107790","107790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771569","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many alcohol licences have been revoked from shops which have participated in the sale of (a) non-duty paid alcohol and (b) illicit tobacco in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107838","107838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771570","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the equipment available to police forces to deal with an extended period of a critical terror threat.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107839","107839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771571","2017-10-18","HM Treasury","2017-10-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HM Revenue and Customs is taking to encourage local authorities to remove alcohol licences from premises which have participated in the sale of (a) non-duty paid alcohol and (b) illicit tobacco.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107848","107848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771572","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of a change in the level of neighbourhood policing on police counter-terrorism operations.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107844","107844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771573","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of people detained for immigration purposes.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107888","107888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771574","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who is responsible for paying the international skills charge for NHS psychiatrists who do not have a PhD and are on a tier 2 visa.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107878","107878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771575","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to prevent people who have been victims of torture being held in detention centres.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107903","107903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771576","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that children of asylum-seeking families are accommodated appropriately while their parents await a decision on their application for asylum support.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107889","107889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771577","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to pay compensation to victims of torture who have been held in detention centres.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107901","107901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771578","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people identified as victims of torture are still being held in detention centres; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107902","107902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771579","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has provided to local authorities (a) to help them understand the threat from extremism and (b) relating to statutory powers available to them to challenge extremist speakers.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107855","107855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771580","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 9459, on passports: children, what criteria her Department uses for certain circumstances under which the Border Force can stop a parent and ask them to produce documentation explaining the relationship between the parent and the child.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107875","107875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771581","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to communicate guidance to the National Crime Agency to recommend freezing the assets of people implicated in the Magnitsky case.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108032","108032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771582","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether a taskforce has been set up to implement Section 13 of the Criminal Finances Act 2017.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108030","108030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771583","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has communicated guidance to the Director General of the National Crime Agency on the implementation of section 13 of the Criminal Finances Act 2017.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108031","108031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771584","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been made available to implement section 13 of the Criminal Finances Act 2017.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108028","108028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771585","2017-10-19","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many National Crime Agency personnel have been assigned to investigate people whose conduct constitutes, or is connected with, the commission of a gross human rights abuse or violation and to enforce the asset-freezing provisions in Part 5 of the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108029","108029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771586","2017-10-18","Department for International Development","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on economic growth in countries where malaria is endemic.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108055","108055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771587","2017-10-18","Department for International Development","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has made a recent assessment of the effect of arms sales to Saudi Arabia on development and humanitarian outcomes in Yemen; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107843","107843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771588","2017-10-18","Department for International Development","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans the Government has to improve coordination between her Department and the Foreign and Commonwealth Office.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107845","107845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771589","2017-10-18","Department for International Development","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that aid to Yemen reaches those people who need it most; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107785","107785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771590","2017-10-18","Women and Equalities","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what plans her Department has to help the UK make progress towards meeting UN Sustainable Development Goal 5.5.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107924","107924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771591","2017-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has made an assessment of the recommendations in the report produced by Lord Bach on access to justice.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107929","107929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771592","2017-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what arrangements are in place with HM Prisons and Probation Service to hold funds on behalf of prisoners during periods in custody.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108033","108033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771593","2017-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many additional prison officers have been recruited since June 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107842","107842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771594","2017-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce levels of radicalisation in prisons.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107837","107837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771595","2017-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many legal aid applications for civil cases of domestic violence have been made in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107908","107908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771596","2017-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for personal independence payments tribunals in Alyn and Deeside constituency was in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108057","108057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771597","2017-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons waiting times for personal independent payment tribunals have increased over the last four years.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108058","108058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771598","2017-10-18","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the number of vehicle accidents in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016 that involved vehicles with tyres over 10 years old.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108059","108059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771599","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will review the decision to increase security requirements on passengers flying between Ercan International Airport and UK airports.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107831","107831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771600","2017-10-18","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will provide funding for the installation of an electric vehicle rapid-charging point in Peterlee.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107857","107857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771601","2017-10-18","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the number of electric vehicle charging points in the Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107858","107858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771602","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many station upgrades are due to start before April 2019 under the Network Rail Access for All scheme.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107813","107813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771603","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on improving the accessibility of train stations for disabled people under Network Rail's Access for All scheme since 2014 in each region.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107818","107818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771604","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many planned station upgrades under Network Rail's Access for All scheme have been (a) cancelled during rail control period 5 and (b) deferred to rail control period in each region.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107817","107817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771605","2017-10-18","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make representations to representatives of the airline sector on the withdrawal of the Zika list for cabin crew who are pregnant or trying to conceive when travelling to countries with that virus.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107807","107807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771606","2017-10-18","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to restrict lorries to the inside lane of motorways only; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107783","107783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771607","2017-10-18","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to ensure that new rail freight terminals are appropriately sited to benefit the national economy.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107792","107792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771608","2017-10-23","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's response to its consultation on proposed changes to the laws governing powered mobility scooters, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing compulsory third-party insurance cover; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108081","108081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771609","2017-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of funding to protect domestic dwellings and business from surface water flooding has been awarded to Norfolk.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107930","107930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771610","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish the detailed legislative guidance on the franchising powers made available to combined authorities with elected mayors under the provisions of the Bus Services Act 2017.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107957","107957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771611","2017-10-19","Department for Transport","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made on the effect of shared-space schemes on disabled people.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107968","107968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771612","2017-10-19","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2017 to Question 105962, what the timetable is for the establishment of the Shared Property Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107953","107953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771613","2017-10-19","Wales Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many meetings he has had with organisations and campaigners from Wales since June 2016 on European Structural Investment Funds after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108026","108026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771614","2017-10-18","Wales Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of total Welsh exports in (a) goods and (b) services went to the Middle East in 2016.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108060","108060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771615","2017-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2017 to Question 105109, when he plans for (a) the light infantry unit to move to St Athan and (b) No. 4 School of Technical Training at St Athan to leave; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107893","107893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771616","2017-10-18","Women and Equalities","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2017 to Question 901069, whether the Government has plans to develop and implement best practice guidelines to ensure local providers account for sexual-gender identity within service provision.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Gerard Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107895","107895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771617","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to adopt a strategy on prostitution which emphasises preventing women and girls entering prostitution and support women wishing to exit prostitution; what steps she plans to take to ensure that women are not penalised by the implementation of such a strategy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107788","107788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771618","2017-10-18","Home Office","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to fund specialist services to prevent women entering prostitution.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107789","107789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771619","2017-10-18","Women and Equalities","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when the consultation on changes to the Gender Recognition Act 2004 will begin.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107933","107933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771620","2017-10-19","Women and Equalities","2017-10-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of female hon. Members; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107977","107977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771621","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will meet the hon. Member for Glasgow East and a delegation from WASPI Glasgow and Lanarkshire to discuss changes to the state pension age for women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108001","108001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771622","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, from what acceptance date the Independent Case Examiner's Office is allocating complaints to an investigation case manager.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108015","108015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771623","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of February 2016 to Question 25760, what advice he gives to applicants needing to make a telephone call to discuss their Universal Credit claim but not able to afford to use his Department's helpline.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107919","107919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771624","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent staff are currently employed at Shettleston jobcentre in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108051","108051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771625","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent staff are currently employed at Parkhead jobcentre in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108050","108050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771626","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases were awaiting allocation to an investigation case manager at the Independent Case Examiner's Office on 30 September 2017.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107993","107993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771627","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many people above state pension age will no longer have their full rent covered by support for housing costs from 1 April 2019.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107995","107995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771628","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what budget has been assigned to the dedicated team to address complaints by women adversely affected by an increase in the state pension age.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108023","108023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771629","2017-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent staff work in the dedicated team to address complaints by women adversely affected by an increase in the state pension age.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108024","108024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771630","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to tackle youth unemployment in Angus constituency.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107808","107808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771631","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff are employed in his Department's Rapid Response Team set up to assist BAE Systems employees affected by recent job losses; in which regions those staff are based; and how many BAE Systems staff potentially affected by job losses have been contacted by a member of that Rapid Response team.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107786","107786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771632","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward proposals for additional powers of enforcement to ensure that employers comply with deductions of earnings issued by the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107897","107897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771633","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of levels of co-operation between employers and the Child Maintenance Service to process deductions of earnings in a timely manner.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107859","107859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771634","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide hon. Members with a direct telephone contact number for benefit centres in their and neighbouring constituencies.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107881","107881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771635","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review the employment and support allowance assessment criteria to tackle the difficulties faced by applicants suffering with mental health problems including anxiety and depression.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107866","107866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771636","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the number of (a) job centres and (b) full-time permanent job centre employees there were in Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108083","108083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771637","2017-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent staff are currently employed at Easterhouse jobcentre in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108056","108056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771638","2017-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of removing the parental support inequality that exists for self-employed fathers who wish to take parental leave to care for a new-born child.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107784","107784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771639","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment that (a) the relevant criteria for hydraulic fracturing consent have been met for the KM8 wellsite in Ryedale, North Yorkshire and (b) it is appropriate to grant hydraulic fracturing consent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107816","107816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/771640","2017-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment that the relevant criteria for hydraulic fracturing consent have been met for the KM8 wellsite in Ryedale, North Yorkshire.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107815","107815"
