"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676030","2017-01-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the number of properties that have been built in high flood-risk areas in (a) Hull and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber after 1 January 2009.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61074","61074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676031","2017-01-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many properties in (a) Hull and (b) each nomenclature of territorial units for statistic region 1 of England are on the Environment Agency's register of properties at higher risk of flooding; and what estimate she has made of the proportion of such properties in each of those areas that have been insured through the Flood Re scheme.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61075","61075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676032","2017-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to table its resolution on Yemen at the UN Security Council meeting on 25 January 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61036","61036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676033","2017-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Omani government on the crisis in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61032","61032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676034","2017-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the increasing influence of Al-Qaeda in the Arabian Peninsula in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61033","61033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676035","2017-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department provides bilateral funding or other resources for the office of the UN Special Envoy to Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61030","61030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676036","2017-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last discussed with the Libyan Government of National Accord the matter of compensation for victims of IRA terrorism where Semtex and weapons were supplied by Libya; and what plans he has for further such discussions.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60996","60996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676037","2017-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Bangladeshi government on the case of Mr Ahmad Bin Quasem.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61020","61020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676038","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vehicles operated by the NHS have been found to be fitted with emissions defeat devices; and how many of those devices have been removed from such vehicles.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61013","61013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676039","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the (a) set-up and (b) training costs of the Selective Internal Radiation Therapy procedure.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61023","61023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676040","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to train NHS staff on the use and availability of Naloxone.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61024","61024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676041","2017-01-25","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has plans to ring-fence mental health funding to clinical commissioning groups; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60991","60991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676042","2017-01-25","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on patient access to new medical treatments of the European Medicines Agency relocating outside the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60978","60978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676043","2017-01-25","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulances based in Camberwell and Peckham have responded outside the (a) Category A and (b) Category C response-time target in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60989","60989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676044","2017-01-25","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people attending A&E in Guy's and St Thomas' hospitals waited longer than four hours to receive treatment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60992","60992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676045","2017-01-25","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many admissions were made to medical facilities operated by Guy's and St Thomas' Trust in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60988","60988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676046","2017-01-25","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of the potential effect of the proposed dispersal of Royal Brompton's congenital heart disease research team on the quality of care provision.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60967","60967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676047","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Tobacco Control Plan will be replaced.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61045","61045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676048","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides on the use of (a) paediatric speech and language therapy, (b) paediatric physiotherapy and (c) paediatric occupational therapy for children and young people with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61046","61046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676049","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reduction in the number of his Department's officials has been in each year since 2009-10; and what planned reduction in the number of his Department's officials there is in each year to 2019-20 by nomenclature of territorial units for statistics region 1.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61078","61078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676050","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to provide funding to ensure that patient treatment is not affected during the assessment period for Selective Internal Radiation Therapy in the Commissioning through Evaluation process.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61052","61052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676051","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how much funding has been allocated to and (b) how many staff have been employed by (i) Healthwatch England, (ii) Healthwatch Hull and (iii) each other local Healthwatch in England and Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61059","61059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676052","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what analysis the Department has undertaken to assess the reasons for the time taken between a patient being cleared to be discharged from hospital and that discharge taking place.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61053","61053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676053","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much in legal and other costs his Department has spent on (a) high court and (b) court of appeal cases related to the commissioning of pre-exposure prophylaxis for HIV prevention.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61076","61076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676054","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria NHS England uses to reach a decision on whether a procedure is included in the Commissioning through Evaluation process.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61051","61051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676055","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the length of her Department's contract with the Refugee Council was for the provision of independent advice to asylum seekers; what the cost of the contract was to the public purse; and how many staff the Refugee Council employed to fulfil that contract.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61073","61073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676056","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers received independent advice from the Refugee Council over the course of the duration of its contract with her Department; and what the average length of time was between opening and closing those cases.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61060","61060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676057","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs on British authorities investigating incidents of honour-based violence committed against British Nationals abroad.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61029","61029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676058","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have received independent advice from Migrant Help in each year since that contract was signed with her Department; and what the average length of time has been between opening and closing those cases through that organisation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61079","61079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676059","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the length of her Department's contract is with Migrant Help for the provision of independent advice to asylum seekers; what the cost of the contract has been to the public purse to date; and how many staff Migrant Help has employed to fulfil that contract since that contract was signed.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61080","61080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676060","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 31 October 2016 to Question 49716, what further progress has been made by her Department in processing refugee family reunion applications for unaccompanied children in France with family ties in the UK; and how many family reunion applications (a) are still outstanding and (b) were closed without a decision being made because the applicant went missing.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61055","61055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676061","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of Migrant Help's contract with her Department.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61057","61057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676062","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fire service vehicles have been found to be fitted with emissions defeat devices; and how many of those devices have been removed from such vehicles.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61049","61049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676063","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her oral contribution of 10 October 2016, Official Report, column 25, whether her Department transferred all the minors from the Calais camp within days of the demolition of that facility.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61056","61056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676064","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police vehicles have been found to be fitted with emissions defeat devices; and how many of those devices have been removed from such vehicles.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61050","61050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676065","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to simplify the process for UK-resident EEA nationals and their families to apply for permanent residence status.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61027","61027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676066","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department takes to promote the welfare of dogs and horses used by the police.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60955","60955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676067","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to convene the ministerial seminar on hate on the internet referred to in Action Against Hate: The UK Government's plan for tackling hate crime, published in July 2016; and which Government Departments will be consulted prior to that seminar on which victims' groups, stakeholders and industry representatives will be invited to attend.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60965","60965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676068","2017-01-25","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government's Drug Strategy is to be published; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60969","60969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676069","2017-01-25","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to minimise barriers for EU-resident staff and students who plan to come to Scottish universities after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60971","60971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676070","2017-01-25","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of racism in football were recorded or reported during 2016.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60970","60970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676071","2017-01-25","Department for International Development","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which (a) projects, (b) tenders and (c) contracts have been suspended or cancelled by Ministers of her Department in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61003","61003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676072","2017-01-24","Department for International Development","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has received on Zambia's diversification of its energy mix.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61005","61005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676073","2017-01-24","Department for International Development","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the provision of reliable base-load electricity in delivering Sustainable Development Goals other than goal seven.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61006","61006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676074","2017-01-24","Department for International Development","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the relative costs of (a) coal, (b) gas, (c) oil, (d) nuclear, (e) offshore wind, (f) onshore wind, (g) large-scale hydro and (h) solar PV in the delivery of utility scale electrification in developing countries.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61007","61007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676075","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to provide support for the use of carbon capture technology in the developing world additional to the £60 million committed to the International Climate Fund in 2012.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61008","61008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676076","2017-01-24","Department for International Development","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage investment in renewable energy in the least-developed countries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61028","61028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676077","2017-01-24","Department for International Development","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the £100 million pledged by her Department to the conflict in Yemen has been spent; and on what those monies have been spent.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61034","61034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676078","2017-01-24","Department for International Development","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on the humanitarian surge in Yemen proposed by the US Permanent Representative to the UN, Samantha Power, at the UN Security Council session on 31 October 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61035","61035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676079","2017-01-24","Department for International Development","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's spending in relation to the conflict in Yemen is dedicated to programmes for Yemeni refugees in Djibouti.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61031","61031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676080","2017-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information her Department has received to date from its pilot on restorative justice approaches in prisons; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61009","61009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676081","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions fire service vehicles have been called out to prisons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61010","61010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676082","2017-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the effect of not ring-fencing funding for Police and Crime Commissioner spending on restorative justice on the availability of such justice for victims of crime; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61011","61011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676083","2017-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she plans to extend the use of restorative justice measures for victims in domestic violence cases.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61012","61012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676084","2017-01-25","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on the other EU member states requesting an extension to the two-year negotiating period following the triggering of Article 50 in the event that a deal is not secured within that timeframe.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60981","60981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676085","2017-01-25","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on seeking an alternative deal with the EU in the event that Parliament rejects the deal brokered by the Government.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60982","60982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676086","2017-01-25","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether it remains his policy to trigger Article 50 by the end of March 2017.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60980","60980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676087","2017-01-25","Department for Transport","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make available increased support for rural bus services in Hemsworth constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61004","61004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676088","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of electric vehicle charging points and devices; and how information is made available to the public.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60997","60997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676089","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the geographical extent of the compulsory helicopter route under the London City control zone.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60995","60995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676090","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will announce increased support for rural bus services in Hemsworth constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61022","61022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676091","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicles in the Government Car Service have been found to be fitted with emissions defeat devices; and how many of those devices have been removed from such vehicles.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61014","61014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676092","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on reimbursing rail operators for costs incurred by industrial action by Northern Rail; and whether the Government has set aside a contingency fund in the event that such reimbursement is needed.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61054","61054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676093","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of contracts with train operating companies have contained clauses which allow those companies to claim back any revenue lost as a result of industrial action in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61058","61058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676094","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will provide support and extra funding to people affected by the closure of the number 30 bus route in Hemsworth constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61071","61071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676095","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have received hardship payments in the last three years are classified by the Government as vulnerable.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61072","61072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676096","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of the primary beneficiaries who receive non-discretionary support for (a) HIV, (b) Stage 1 hepatitis C and (c) Stage 2 hepatitis C as a result of the contaminated blood scandal are also recipients of employment support allowance.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61061","61061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676097","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of universal credit claimants have required assistance to complete their online account in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61062","61062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676098","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of universal credit have been subject to higher-level sanctions in the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61063","61063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676099","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of universal credit are defined as being self-employed.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61066","61066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676100","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes in the event that people claiming personal independence payments say that they have not received correspondence sent from the Department relating to personal independence payment (a) assessments and (b) awards.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61047","61047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676101","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of universal credit have not declared paid work.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61065","61065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676102","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 57149, whether people in the Work-Related Activity Group (WRAG) of Employment Support Allowance (a) will continue to receive £102.15 a week or (b) will receive the lower rate of £73.10 in the event that they are re-assessed and placed again in the WRAG after April 2017.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61026","61026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676103","2017-01-31","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many funerals were conducted by each unitary and district council in England under section 46 of the Public Health (Control of Disease) Act 1984 in 2016; and what the cost to each local authority was for conducting such funerals.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61039","61039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676104","2017-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on older people of the changes made to the Support for Mortgage Interest scheme in the Welfare and Reform Work Act 2016.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61040","61040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676105","2017-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disability employment advisers are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61041","61041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676106","2017-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on halving the disability employment gap by 2020.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61042","61042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676107","2017-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Improving Lives green paper, published in October 2016, what recent progress his Department has made in undertaking (a) research and (b) a trial to provide support to help individuals in the employment and support allowance support group to move closer to the labour market.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61043","61043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676108","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been sanctioned for not attending their jobseeker's allowance appointment within five minutes of the appointed time in (a) Glasgow Central, (b) Glasgow South, (c) Glasgow North East, (d) Glasgow East, (e) Glasgow South West, (f) Glasgow North and (g) Glasgow North West constituencies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61044","61044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676109","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 16-17 year-olds are in receipt of universal credit; and how many of those recipients are (a) lone parents, (b) disabled and (c) without parental support.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61064","61064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676110","2017-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what circumstances work-related activities will be required from a claimant of universal credit who has been signed off work by a GP but has not yet undertaken a work capability assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60979","60979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676111","2017-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the funding will be for each of the employment support programmes set out in Improving Lives: The Work, Health and Disability Green Paper, Cm9342, published in October 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60973","60973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676112","2017-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Government plans to spend on employment support services for disabled people by 2020.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60974","60974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676113","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to extend the grace period for final decisions to be made on an appeal or mandatory reconsideration of a personal independence payment award for a Motability user in order to reduce the incidence of those claimants losing access to their vehicles.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60993","60993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676114","2017-01-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to protect UK R&D investment that has been made in Scottish universities after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60972","60972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676115","2017-01-25","Department for International Trade","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, for what reasons his Department provided financial assistance to companies attending the consumer electronics show in Las Vegas on 5 to 8 January 2017; and what criteria were used in allocating funds to each such company.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60968","60968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676116","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, for what reasons his Department decided not to provide funding for the Drinktec trade fair in Munich on 11-15 September 2017.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61067","61067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676117","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of recent changes in the government funding provided to promote British businesses at trade shows on SME export growth in the brewing industry.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61070","61070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676118","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to (a) support bespoke business matching and (b) help UK businesses maximise their market presence overseas.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61068","61068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676119","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of potential merits of increasing funding for stands in trade shows; and for what reasons his Department did not support such a stand at the Eureka Park start-up zone at the Consumer Electronics Show in Las Vegas in January 2017.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61069","61069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676120","2017-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with (a) the Prime Minister and (b) the Foreign Secretary on the future of the Ireland-UK border after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60962","60962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676121","2017-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has met his Irish counterpart to discuss the future of the Ireland-UK border after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60961","60961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676122","2017-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has received representations on the UK leaving the EU from the governments of (a) France, (b) Germany, (c) Italy and (d) Spain.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60956","60956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676123","2017-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil service fast stream staff his Department employs.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60957","60957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676124","2017-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has met the Chief Minister of Gibraltar to discuss priorities for Gibraltar in the UK's negotiations on leaving the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60958","60958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676125","2017-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the Chief Minister of Gibraltar on the future of the border between Gibraltar and Spain after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60959","60959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676126","2017-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with (a) members of the Northern Ireland Executive and (b) members of the Northern Ireland Assembly on the future of the Ireland-UK border after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60960","60960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/676127","2017-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the Irish government on the future of the Ireland-UK border after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 61021","61021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675426","2017-01-23","Attorney General","2017-01-19","To ask the Attorney General, how many senior civil servants in the Law Officers' Departments were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Departments' creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60793","60793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675427","2017-01-23","Attorney General","2017-01-19","To ask the Attorney General, how many officials of his Department are working full-time on preparations for the UK leaving the EU; and what proportion of his Department's staff that number represents.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60886","60886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675428","2017-01-23","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials of his Department are working full-time on preparations for the UK leaving the EU; and what proportion of his Department's staff that number represents.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60880","60880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675429","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Minister in which Department has principal responsibility for (a) refugees outside and (b) asylum seekers inside the UK.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60854","60854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675430","2017-01-23","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60794","60794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675431","2017-01-24","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of full-time equivalent employees are women in the gross salary bands (a) £150,000 to £155,000, (b) £155,000 to £160,000, (c) £160,000 to £165,000, (d) £165,000 to £170,000, (e) £170,000 to £175,000, (f) £175,000 to £180,000, (g) £180,000 to £185,000, (h) £185,000 to £190,000, (i) £190,000 to £195,000, (j) £195,000 to £200,000 and (k) £200,000 and above for each government Department and Office.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60786","60786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675432","2017-02-01","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people died from the effects of (a) tobacco, (b) alcohol and (c) cannabis in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60737","60737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675433","2017-01-23","HM Treasury","2017-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60777","60777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675434","2017-01-23","HM Treasury","2017-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times deductions have been made from a person's child tax credit payment to service outstanding arrears from working tax credits in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60739","60739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675435","2017-01-23","HM Treasury","2017-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials of his Department are working full-time on preparations for the UK leaving the EU; and what proportion of his Department's staff that number represents.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60875","60875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675436","2017-01-23","Church Commissioners","2017-01-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to support the police in dealing with vulnerable people.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60948","60948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675437","2017-01-23","Church Commissioners","2017-01-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to increase provision of spiritual guidance in prisons.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60949","60949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675438","2017-01-23","Church Commissioners","2017-01-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, if the Church of England will take steps to ensure efforts to tackle theft of lead from church buildings do not lead to reduced accessibility to those buildings.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60950","60950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675439","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 September 2016 to Question 46112, in what proportion of those planning permissions where building has not yet commenced (a) a developer has an option to build or is otherwise working in partnership with the landowner, (b) a developer owns the land and (c) no developer is in place.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60927","60927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675440","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much Government funding has been made available for lessons in English for speakers of other languages in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60891","60891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675441","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will list each of the councils receiving the New Home Bonus where there has been an increase in the number of new homes built in those areas by (a) 0.4 per cent or below and (b) above 0.4 per cent in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60931","60931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675442","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many officials of his Department are working full-time on preparations for the UK leaving the EU; and what proportion of his Department's staff that number represents.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60879","60879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675443","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to enable regulation of short-term holiday lets in line with the regulation of bed and breakfast properties.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60815","60815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675444","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the effect of the Government's proposal to allow local government to retain 100 per cent of the business rates they raise locally on Bedford Borough and Central Bedfordshire local authority budgets.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60816","60816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675445","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice and support his Department provides to trading standards officers on the enforcement of the Infant Formula and Follow-on Formula (England) Regulations 2007.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60743","60743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675446","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Government made of how much each local authority spent on physical activity services per capita in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60766","60766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675447","2017-01-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the level of participation of people from (a) ABC1 and (b) C2DE families in programmes funded by the Youth Social Action Fund in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60767","60767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675448","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since its creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60795","60795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675449","2017-01-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many senior civil servants in her Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60796","60796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675450","2017-01-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to meet representatives of (a) local authorities, (b) the gambling industry, (c) charities and (d) other relevant bodies ahead of the publication of the formal recommendations of the Review of Gaming Machines and Social Responsibility Measures.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60760","60760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675451","2017-01-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many submissions to the consultation on the Leveson Inquiry and its implementation (a) supported and (b) opposed Part 2 of that Inquiry.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60749","60749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675452","2017-01-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on tackling online hate crime.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60863","60863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675453","2017-01-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials of her Department are working full-time on preparations for the UK leaving the EU; and what proportion of her Department's staff that number represents.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60878","60878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675454","2017-01-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish the report her Department received from the Gambling Commission on updating the regulations governing society lotteries.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60937","60937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675455","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the country of origin is of each piece of personal protective equipment issued to personnel deployed on operations overseas in the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60908","60908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675456","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the country of origin is of each product within the 24-hour ration packs issued by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60909","60909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675457","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what EU regulations apply to medicines and medical equipment used by (a) medics and (b) medical officers in the (i) Royal Navy, (ii) Army and (iii) Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60910","60910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675458","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2016 to Question 47540, how the process to collect feedback from the victims of crime operates; what plans he has to monitor the performance of that process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60905","60905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675459","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much compensation his Department has paid as a result of low flying incidents in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60906","60906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675460","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the country of origin is of each garment in each of the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) Royal Air Force categories by order of uniform.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60907","60907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675461","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officials of his Department are working full-time on preparations for the UK leaving the EU; and what proportion of his Department's staff that number represents.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60876","60876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675462","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many low flying incidents involved livestock in each of the last five years; and what the cost was of compensation paid in relation to each of those incidents.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60911","60911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675463","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people his Department employed in each of the last five years who were subsequently found to be illegal immigrants.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60912","60912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675464","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that defence personnel with essential nuclear skills are retained by the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60913","60913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675465","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects a permanent Chief Executive Officer of the new Submarine Delivery Body to be appointed.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60914","60914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675466","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much compensation his Department has paid to armed forces personnel as a result of road traffic accidents in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60916","60916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675467","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that the defence industry maintains the people with nuclear skills required for his Department's nuclear-based programmes.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60917","60917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675468","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many bearskins are (a) in use and (b) unaccounted for; and whether he is taking steps to procure additional bearskins.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60918","60918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675469","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what budget has been allocated to the new Submarine Delivery Body.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60919","60919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675470","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent industrial action by Atomic Weapons Establishment staff on the delivery of his Department's nuclear weapons programme.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60871","60871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675471","2017-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many works of art his Department owns and where they are located.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60832","60832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675472","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many foreign military aircraft have made unapproved landings at UK airports and airfields since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60833","60833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675473","2017-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Air Force aircraft have made unapproved landings at overseas airports since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60834","60834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675474","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60797","60797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675475","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many senior civil servants in her Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60798","60798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675476","2017-01-24","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Home Secretary on universities in (a) England and (b) Scotland being able to recruit academic staff who are EU nationals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60787","60787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675477","2017-01-24","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with Ministers on the academic funding for Scottish universities after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60837","60837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675478","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support is being provided for schools identified under phase 2 of the Priority Schools Building Programme which are awaiting urgent repairs.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60817","60817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675479","2017-01-24","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students achieved three or more A grade or higher A-levels in each national statistical social economic classification for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60867","60867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675480","2017-01-24","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start children's centres have been opened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60922","60922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675481","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the value of feasibility studies to ascertain how to prioritise delayed work in schools identified in phase 2 of the Priority School Building Programme.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60814","60814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675482","2017-01-24","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start children's centres closed in England in 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60923","60923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675483","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will detail the funding for flood defences set out in the National Infrastructure Delivery Plan by NUTS 1 region.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60933","60933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675484","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment has been made of including the permeable ammonia-recycling crust within the Farming Ammonia Reduction Grant.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60899","60899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675485","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will continue to implement the provisions of the European school milk scheme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60828","60828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675486","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2017 to Question 59331, how many applications for import permits relating to hunting trophies were (a) received, (b) approved and (c) refused by the Joint Nature Conservation Committee in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60831","60831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675487","2017-01-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on implementing the revised European School Milk scheme.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60847","60847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675488","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to encourage greater uptake of free milk in schools and nurseries.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60827","60827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675489","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that air quality standards are improved across the UK by the planting of trees.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60947","60947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675490","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many senior civil servants in her Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60799","60799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675491","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of a reduction in local government funding on litter and fly tipping.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60761","60761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675492","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce litter and fly tipping.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60762","60762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675493","2017-01-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on proposed changes to cost protections for environmental claims; and what assessment she has made of the effect of those changes on environmental (a) justice and the UK's compliance with the Aarhus Convention and (b) standards.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60768","60768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675494","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what post-legislative assessment her Department has carried out on the Flood and Water Management Act 2010 since it was brought into force; if she will place in the Library a copy of that assessment; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60713","60713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675495","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Nigerian counterpart after the bombing of a displaced persons camp in Rann, North Eastern Nigeria.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60747","60747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675496","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the risks associated with the links between al-Qaeda and Jabhat Fatah al-Sham in Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60750","60750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675497","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the strength of al-Qaeda in Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60751","60751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675498","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of the Democratic Republic of the Congo on its commitment not to hold a referendum on further constitutional change in 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60752","60752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675499","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on further lifting of the restrictions on the number of visitor visas for Iranian nationals to visit the UK.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60745","60745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675500","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in the Gambia; and what recent representations he has made to his Gambian counterpart on the current state of emergency in that country.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60753","60753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675501","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Matthew Rycroft, Permanent representative of the UK to the UN on the political situation in the Gambia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60748","60748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675502","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60801","60801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675503","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2017 to Question 58596, how many contracts the Government placed with UK-based public relations companies between 2010 and 2015 that include work in or on Somalia; and with which companies those contracts were placed.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60780","60780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675504","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Australian government on administrative and constitutional changes to the arrangement of government of Norfolk Island.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60765","60765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675505","2017-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funding has been provided through the Conflict Stabilisation and Security Fund to projects in Russia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60807","60807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675506","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the oral evidence of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs to the Northern Ireland Affairs Committee of 22 March 2016, Question 397, what progress has been made by the Libyan Government of National Accord in establishing a committee to study the case of victims of IRA terrorism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60888","60888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675507","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials of his Department are working full-time on preparations for the UK leaving the EU; and what proportion of his Department's staff that number represents.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60877","60877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675508","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to assist victims of IRA terrorist attacks where Semtex and weapons were supplied by Libya in securing compensation from the Libyan government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60894","60894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675509","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Libya Reconciliation Unit last discussed with the Libyan Government of National Accord the matter of compensation for victims of IRA terrorism where Semtex and weapons were supplied by Libya.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60893","60893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675510","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications for bereaved persons' lump sum payments related to the contaminated blood scandal have been received to date; how many of those applications have been (a) accepted and (b) rejected; and whether applications received after the 20 January 2017 deadline will be permissible.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60941","60941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675511","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients used Type (a) 1, (b) 2 and (c) 3 accident and emergency units in each English region in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60852","60852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675512","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60776","60776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675513","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's definition is of an NHS walk-in centre.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60848","60848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675514","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department issues guidance to local NHS commissioners on the effectiveness of the use of walk-in centres.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60849","60849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675515","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the potential causal link between the availability of NHS walk-in centres and levels of Type 1 accident and emergency attendance in the vicinity of such centres.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60850","60850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675516","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Type (a) 1, (b) 2 and (c) 3 accident and emergency units there were in each English region in (i) 2010-11 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60851","60851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675517","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the suicide rate in England was in 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60842","60842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675518","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged between 15 and 19 were hospitalised for self-harm in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60843","60843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675519","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2016 to Question 55609, on health professions: training, if he will provide the same figures relating to each other provider in England.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60829","60829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675520","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on incorporating current discretionary support payments into the new scheme for victims of contaminated blood; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60813","60813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675521","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mothers died by suicide within a year after the birth of their child in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60839","60839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675522","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have died by suicide who had lost a member of their immediate family to suicide in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60840","60840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675523","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how many people in England have lost a member of their immediate family to suicide in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60841","60841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675524","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cancer patients have had their operation cancelled due to a shortage of beds in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60846","60846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675525","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) have received funding under the NHS Diabetes Prevention Programme; and how much funding each of those CCGs received.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60779","60779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675526","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60802","60802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675527","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been tested for diabetes under the NHS Diabetes Prevention Programme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60810","60810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675528","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the budget for Leicester City Clinical Commissioning Group (a) was in 2014-15, (b) was in 2015-2016 and (c) is for the current financial year.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60811","60811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675529","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what projects by (a) name and (b) value his Department funded from the Conflict Stabilisation and Security Fund; and which of those projects were categorised as contributing towards Overseas Development Aid.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60806","60806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675530","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what Health Education England is required to deliver in March 2017 to satisfy the mandate for a strategic review of the cancer workforce.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60759","60759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675531","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Ministers of his Department have had with Health Education England on the strategic review of the cancer workforce in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60764","60764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675532","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings of the report from the Care Quality Commission on Marie Stopes International, published in December 2016, what steps his Department plans to put in place to ensure that fetal remains are disposed of by private abortion clinics respectfully and in accordance with the wishes of patients who have undergone abortions.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60714","60714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675533","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times and on which dates (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met with representatives of Unicef Baby Friendly.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60720","60720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675534","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times and on which dates (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met with representatives of First Steps Nutrition Trust.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60721","60721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675535","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times and on which dates (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met with representatives of Baby Milk Action.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60722","60722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675536","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times and on which dates (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met with representatives of Live Nation.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60723","60723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675537","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times and on which dates (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met with representatives of MG Alba.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60724","60724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675538","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the internationally recognised adult congenital heart disease research team at the Royal Brompton Hospital as a result of the proposed closure of congenital heart disease services at that hospital.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60727","60727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675539","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the cost-benefit analysis on the extent of the (a) improvements in clinical outcomes and (b) unit cost reductions anticipated to result from the proposed closure of congenital heart disease services at the Royal Brompton Hospital.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60725","60725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675540","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of the effect of the proposed dispersal of the Royal Brompton Hospital's congenital heart disease research team on care quality.","Biography information for Sarah Olney","Sarah Olney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60728","60728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675541","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the initial findings of the NHS England paediatric critical care and specialised surgery in children service review are still expected to be published in winter 2016-17.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60726","60726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675542","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made an assessment of the implications of the findings of the Care Quality Commission's report of 20 December 2016 on Marie Stopes International for (a) patient safety and (b) public confidence in private abortion clinics; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60716","60716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675543","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of treatment of people affected by air pollution and poor air quality.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60718","60718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675544","2017-02-01","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS has been of purchasing opioid painkillers in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60736","60736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675545","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times and on which dates (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have met with representatives of the British Specialist Nutrition Association.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60719","60719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675546","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been diagnosed with chronic urinary tract infections over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60731","60731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675547","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to respond to the letters from the hon. Member for Hornsey and Wood Green of (a) 7 November and (b) 14 December 2016 on scheduling a meeting to discuss his Department's policy on the treatment of chronic urinary tract infections.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60732","60732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675548","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to develop anti-bot technology to prohibit bulk booking of appointments in respect of VFS Global visa applications in the Republic of Iran.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60755","60755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675549","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish data on the levels of non-compliance of visa conditions granted to Iranian nationals visiting the UK in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60744","60744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675550","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training and advice is available to immigration officers carrying out asylum interviews where a claimant has been a victim of sexual violence.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60741","60741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675551","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for naturalisation as a British citizen were (a) lodged, (b) granted and (c) refused in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60742","60742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675552","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications that included medical evidence of torture her Department received in each of the last five years; and how many of those applications that were rejected were subsequently overturned on appeal.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60735","60735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675553","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many senior civil servants in her Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60775","60775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675554","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects the report of the Daniel Morgan Independent Panel to be released.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60845","60845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675555","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) standard, (b) enhanced and (c) enhanced with barred list checks applications have been submitted to the Disclosure and Barring Service in each year since 2009-10; and how many of those applications were (i) accepted and (ii) rejected.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60820","60820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675556","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether someone with leave to remain in the UK as a stateless person has (a) a right to work in the UK and (b) recourse to public funds.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60819","60819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675557","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were employed in regulated activity sectors of the workforce in each employment sector in the Disclosure and Barring Service's database in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60821","60821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675558","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how (a) much funding was allocated to and (b) many staff were employed by the (i) Independent Safeguarding Authority, (ii) Criminal Records Bureau in each year till December 2012 and (iii) Disclosure and Barring Service in each year since December 2012.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60944","60944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675559","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff have left the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse in each month since it was established.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60945","60945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675560","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20698, on vetting, if she will provide the same information for (a) 2010, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60830","60830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675561","2017-01-24","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the Government's response to the report by the Advisory Council on the misuse of drugs, reducing opioid-related deaths in the UK, published in December 2016.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60861","60861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675562","2017-01-30","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much UK Visas and Immigration paid out in costs in respect of judicial reviews of (a) deportation orders and (b) other immigration decisions in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60869","60869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675563","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what projects by (a) name and (b) value her Department funded from the Conflict Stabilisation and Security Fund; and which of those projects were categorised as contributing towards Overseas Development Aid.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60808","60808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675564","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Salva Kiir Mayardit, President of South Sudan, holds (a) British citizenship and (b) a current UK passort.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60809","60809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675565","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for stateless person travel documents have been made in each year since 2009-10; and how many of those applications were (a) accepted and (b) rejected.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60942","60942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675566","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for Tier 1 (Investor) visas have been refused in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60883","60883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675567","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions police forces have provided additional information for criminal records checks in each financial year (a) before and (b) since the passage of the Protection of Freedoms Act 2012; and what proportion of total applications that number represents.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60940","60940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675568","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have worked for the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse since that inquiry was established; and how many such people have received (a) standard, (b) enhanced and (c) enhanced with barred list checks by the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60935","60935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675569","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to renew the right to stay in the UK as a stateless person were made by people who previously had the right to remain as a stateless person in each year since 2009-10; and how many of those applications were (a) accepted and (b) rejected.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60936","60936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675570","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 7 August 2014 to Question 205989, on vetting and the Disclosure and Barring Service, if she will provide those statistics for (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60904","60904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675571","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken was for police to visit a burglary scene following a reported burglary in each police force area in England and Wales in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60925","60925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675572","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of resources to attend to reported burglaries in (a) London and (b) West Ham constituency on 28 December 2016.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60924","60924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675573","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people made representations to the (a) Disclosure and Barring Service and (b) Independent Safeguarding Authority to remove their names from the (i) children's and (ii) adult's barred list in each year since 2009-10; and what proportion of those representations were (A) successful and (B) unsuccessful.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60934","60934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675574","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to stay in the UK as a stateless person were made in each year since 2009-10; and how many of those applications were (a) accepted and (b) rejected.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60943","60943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675575","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of people who arrive in the UK on Tier 1 (Investor) visas later apply to settle; and what proportion of those later applications is successful.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60884","60884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675576","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many barred list checks were made for people in the controlled activity category in each year until that category was repealed by the Protection of Freedoms Act 2012; and how many of those checks (a) found and (b) did not find matches with the barred list. in each of those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60932","60932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675577","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people arrived in the UK on Tier 1 (Investor) visas in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60882","60882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675578","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are in the UK having arrived on a Tier 1 (Investor) visa.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60885","60885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675579","2017-01-24","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in what year the Crime Survey for England and Wales first asked questions on (a) any form of cyber-enabled and (b) credit card fraud.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60953","60953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675580","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the utility of the Joint Precision Aerial Delivery System for delivering humanitarian aid; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60826","60826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675581","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment the Government has made of using the Joint Precision Airdrop System to provide aid to besieged Syrian civilians.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60818","60818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675582","2017-01-23","Department for International Development","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many senior civil servants in her Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60803","60803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675583","2017-01-23","Department for International Development","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to provide additional resources to the dispatched persons camp in Rann, North Eastern Nigeria as a result of the airstrike on that camp.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60746","60746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675584","2017-01-24","Department for International Development","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much was paid from the public purse to Marie Stopes International in 2016; and how much of that total came from the international aid budget for expenditure overseas in 2016.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60715","60715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675585","2017-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many senior civil servants in her Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60774","60774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675586","2017-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff currently employed by Community Rehabilitation Companies in (a) Wales and (b) West England will be expected to join the Voluntary Severance Scheme by the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60901","60901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675587","2017-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have left the employment of the Community Rehabilitation Company in Wales (a) voluntarily and (b) through redundancy since 1 January 2016.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60902","60902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675588","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidences of online (a) hate crime, (b) anti-Semitism and (c) Islamophobia have resulted in convictions in the last (i) 12, (ii) 24 and (iii) 36 months.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60862","60862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675589","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential financial implications of redistributing funds recovered under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 regionally rather than locally.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60864","60864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675590","2017-01-24","Home Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy that all funds recovered under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 are not diverted to organisations which are not empowered to conduct investigations.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60865","60865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675591","2017-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the names of the (a) people and (b) organisations are who submitted written responses to her Department's consultation, Reforming the soft tissue injury (whiplash) claims process, published on 17 November 2016.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60856","60856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675592","2017-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many responses were received from (a) people and (b) organisations to her Department's consultation, Reforming the soft tissue injury (whiplash) claims process, published on 17 November 2016.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60857","60857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675593","2017-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans to publish her Department's response to its consultation, Reforming the soft tissue injury (whiplash) claims process, published on 17 November 2016.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60853","60853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675594","2017-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have applied for the Voluntary Severance scheme offered by the Community Rehabilitation Company in Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60900","60900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675595","2017-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will assess the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to amend the Employment Rights Act 1996 to include paralegals in the statutory list of relevant advisers in respect of compromise agreements.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60929","60929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675596","2017-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the monetary value was of drugs seized from each prison in each quarter of 2016.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60930","60930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675597","2017-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to increase diversity in (a) the legal sector and (b) among paralegals.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60928","60928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675598","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to put (a) prisoner health care and (b) individual prisoner health care services out to competitive tender.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60915","60915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675599","2017-01-23","Leader of the House","2017-01-19","To ask the Leader of the House, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central of 18 December 2016 on his promise to draw the Ministry of Justice's attention to three constituency cases affected by Tier 1 immigration tribunal delays.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60738","60738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675600","2017-01-24","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what his policy is on the promotion of the Irish language; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60783","60783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675601","2017-01-23","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since its creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60804","60804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675602","2017-01-23","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many senior civil servants in the Office of the Prime Minister were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60773","60773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675603","2017-01-23","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the Government has made on its planned anti-corruption strategy.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60892","60892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675604","2017-01-23","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the communique form the Anti-Corruption Summit held in London in May 2016, whether he asked the Financial Action Task Force, the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development and the Global Forum on Transparency and Exchange of Information for Tax Purposes to develop initial proposals on ways to improve the implementation of the international standards on transparency, including on the availability of beneficial ownership information and its international exchange.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60874","60874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675605","2017-01-23","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to follow up on the outcome of the Anti-Corruption Summit held in London in May 2016; and whether he plans to convene another such summit.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60887","60887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675606","2017-01-23","Cabinet Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 2 of the communique of the Anti-Corruption Summit in London in May 2016, what progress has been made on uncovering corruption wherever it exists and pursuing and punishing those who perpetrate, facilitate or are complicit in it.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60903","60903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675607","2017-01-23","Scotland Office","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60772","60772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675608","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since its creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60805","60805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675609","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Fiat Crysler on the review of that company's emissions by Market Surveillance Unit; and what the (a) timetable and (b) process is for that review.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60920","60920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675610","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish details of the monthly monitoring reports provided to him by the working group created to implement the Action Plan for Information on Rail Fares and Ticketing, published on 13 December 2016.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60866","60866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675611","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been made of the effect of pedicab drivers on traffic congestion in Central London.","Biography information for Victoria Borwick","Victoria Borwick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60859","60859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675612","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to bring forward legislative proposals for the operation of pedicabs in London.","Biography information for Victoria Borwick","Victoria Borwick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60860","60860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675613","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many electrical vehicle charging (a) points and (b) devices are avaiable to the public in England and Wales.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60812","60812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675614","2017-01-24","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for introducing legislative proposals on the operation of pedicabs in London.","Biography information for Victoria Borwick","Victoria Borwick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60858","60858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675615","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Transport of 12 January 2017, Official Report, column 451, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of any group litigation action by owners of Volkswagan vehicles.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60872","60872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675616","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to improve the flexibility of electric vehicle charging points to ensure such points operate across networks and connector types.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60898","60898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675617","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his most recent estimate is of the number of electric vehicle charging points in full working order in England and Wales.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60890","60890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675618","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his target is for the proportion of electric vehicle charging points that are fully functioning.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60895","60895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675619","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to allocate the £80 million expenditure announced for electric vehicle charging points in the Autumn Statement 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60896","60896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675620","2017-01-23","Women and Equalities","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many legal cases the Equality and Human Rights Commission has (a) opened, (b) continued and (c) concluded in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60825","60825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675621","2017-01-23","Women and Equalities","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much funding has been allocated to the Equality and Human Rights Commission to tackle hate crime since the EU referendum.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60824","60824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675622","2017-01-23","Women and Equalities","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Equality and Human Rights Commission is taking to support staff who are facing compulsory redundancy to seek new roles within the civil service.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60822","60822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675623","2017-01-23","Women and Equalities","2017-01-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much funding has been allocated to the Equality and Human Rights Commission (EHRC) for each year until 2020; and how much of that funding will be allocated to advertising the advisory services of the EHRC.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60823","60823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675624","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of whether child poverty rates will (a) increase, (b) remain the same or (c) decrease during the current Parliament.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60836","60836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675625","2017-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what further measures the Government plans to introduce to assist employers in supporting employees' return to work after a heath-related absence.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60926","60926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675626","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants in Scotland received carer premiums for (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support and (d) pension credit in in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60952","60952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675627","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment the Government has made of the total value of carer premiums paid to claimants in Scotland in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60951","60951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675628","2017-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the offsetting of personal pension payments against child maintenance payments on families in receipt of such maintenance payments.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60873","60873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675629","2017-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the personal independence payment appeal process on disabled people who use mobility vehicles.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60889","60889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675630","2017-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2016 to Question 51325, whether the introduction of fees and ongoing collection charges referred to in that Answer apply to victims of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60712","60712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675631","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to meet local community groups in Glasgow South constituency to discuss the effect of proposed jobcentre closures in Glasgow.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60733","60733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675632","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to extend the public consultation on proposed jobcentre closures in Glasgow to all of the eight sites that are earmarked for closure.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60734","60734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675633","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to publish its response to the findings of the consultation, Exceptions to the limiting of the individual child element of tax credits and the child element of universal credit to a maximum of two children, published in October 2016, before 31 January 2017.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60791","60791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675634","2017-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Walsall North of 20 December 2016 on housing benefit policy and student loans on behalf of a constituent.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60769","60769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675635","2017-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Minister for Employment visited any jobcentres in Scotland during his ministerial visit in January 2017.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60740","60740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675636","2017-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Glasgow Central constituency have had their benefit payments reduced after transferring from disability living allowance to personal independence payments in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60754","60754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675637","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the role that carbon capture and (a) storage and (b) utilisation will play in meeting the developing world's growing demand for energy.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60757","60757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675638","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the contribution that new (a) coal-fuelled, (b) gas-fuelled, (c) hydro, (d) solar and (e) wind electricity generating capacity will play in alleviating energy poverty in each of its priority countries.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60758","60758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675639","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Walsall North of 20 December 2016 on broadband on behalf of a constituent.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60770","60770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675640","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department plans to (a) monitor, (b) enforce and (c) impose appropriate sanctions arising from the investor agreement between his Department and nine nuclear investment companies for the Hinkley C nuclear power plant.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60784","60784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675641","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on households' access to low-cost and off-peak rates of Ofgem recommendations on the future installation of smart meters.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60785","60785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675642","2017-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60792","60792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675643","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) post offices and (b) sub post offices have closed in each year since 2010 in (i) York Central constituency, (ii) the York Local Authority area, (iii) North Yorkshire and the Humber and (iv) England.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60717","60717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675644","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with relevant stakeholders on the potential effect on the UK's insolvency and restructuring regime of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60729","60729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675645","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the UK's insolvency and restructuring regime of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60730","60730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675646","2017-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many officials of his Department are working full-time on preparations for the UK leaving the EU; and what proportion of his Department's staff that number represents.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60881","60881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675647","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Horizon 2020-funded research projects are underway in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK; and what steps he is taking to ensure that those projects will continue to have access to that funding after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60838","60838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675648","2017-02-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to bring forward proposals to amend existing legislation as a result of the European Court of Justice judgment of 2006 on rolled-up holiday pay.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60870","60870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675649","2017-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the most cost-effective way of providing utility scale baseload power in its priority countries.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60844","60844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675650","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which Minister approved the arms export licence given to CAS Global in July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60855","60855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675651","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the value of UK exports secured through the US Department of Defense Foreign Comparative Testing Program since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60835","60835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675652","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase awareness of the UK tech and innovation industry abroad; and what assistance his Department is providing to businesses to build their brands abroad.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60946","60946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675653","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help companies engage with the US Department of Defense Foreign Comparative Testing Program.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60921","60921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675654","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will take steps to ensure that the agendas and minutes of all meetings held by the (a) Australia-UK trade working group, (b) UK-New Zealand trade policy dialogue and (c) Norway-UK trade dialogue are published.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60938","60938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675655","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with the UK's prospective trading partners on the UK's trading relationship with the EU after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60939","60939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675656","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department's decision to offer financial support to companies wishing to attend a trade show is determined by the location of that trade show.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60954","60954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675657","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to his Department's news story of 9 January 2017, what criteria his Department used to determine which countries were included in the priority markets for growing UK trade.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60897","60897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675658","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many non-EU countries he has had discussions with on potential negotiations for a trade deal after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60711","60711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675659","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60778","60778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675660","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government has undertaken an investor state dispute settlement risk assessment of UK legislation relating to (a) health, (b) the environment, (c) waste management and (d) fisheries.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60789","60789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675661","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government has undertaken an audit of the compliance with World Trade Organisation rules of UK legislation relating to (a) health, (b) the environment, (c) waste management and (d) fisheries.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60788","60788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675662","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if his Department will make funding available to help businesses attend the Craft Brewers Conference and BrewExpo in Washington DC on 13 April 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60781","60781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675663","2017-01-24","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what financial support his Department provided to (a) start-up and (b) other companies that attended the consumer electronics show in Las Vegas on 5 to 8 January 2017.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60790","60790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675664","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Written Statement of 5 December 2016, HCWS316 on the UK's commitments at the World Trade Organisation (WTO), what assessment he has made of the effect of the draft WTO schedules on the cost efficiency of the UK toy manufacturing industry.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60782","60782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675665","2017-01-23","Department for International Trade","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will publish the agendas and minutes of meetings (a) he and (b) officials of his Department have held with representatives of non-EU governments on trade matters since July 2016.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60763","60763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675666","2017-01-23","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what advice his Department has received from trade unions on the Government's forthcoming negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60756","60756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675667","2017-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will include the Mayor of London and Assembly Members from the Greater London Authority in future meetings of the devolved administrations forum.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60771","60771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/675668","2017-01-23","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many senior civil servants in his Department were on a leave of absence from work due to mental illness in each month of each year since the Department's creation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60800","60800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674748","2017-01-23","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the public interest in pursuing prosecutions against former members of the armed forces for activities in Northern Ireland which occurred prior to the Good Friday Agreement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60651","60651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674749","2017-01-20","Cabinet Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) mean and (b) median gender pay gap is for (i) part-time and (ii) full-time staff at the Office for National Statistics.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60545","60545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674750","2017-01-27","HM Treasury","2017-01-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, (a) how many people other than parents (i) applied for and (ii) were granted specified adult childcare credits to obtain national insurance credits as an adult carer, caring for a child under 12, in each month since 6 April 2011 and (b) how much those national insurance credits have cost in each full tax year for which that scheme has been in place.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60604","60604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674751","2017-01-23","HM Treasury","2017-01-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions officials of his Department have had with officials of the Northern Ireland Executive on (a) the Autumn Statement 2015 and (b) the settlement letter referring to the costs of Northern Ireland's non-domestic renewable heat incentive scheme.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60597","60597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674752","2017-01-23","HM Treasury","2017-01-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether discussions that officials of his Department had with officials of the Northern Ireland Executive included (a) budgetary challenges facing the Executive during 2015 and (b) the escalated spending exposure under the Northern Ireland non-domestic renewable heat incentive scheme.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60598","60598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674753","2017-01-23","HM Treasury","2017-01-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to fund the commitments the UK has made to the EU after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60692","60692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674754","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 17 January 2017, HCWS 418, if he will publish the evidential basis for the estimate that savings made by local authorities as a result of the Homelessness Reduction Bill will fully offset any additional costs to local authorities by 2019-20.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60647","60647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674755","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Ministerial Statement of 17 January 2017, HCWS 418, if he will publish the evidential basis used to determine the level of funding to local government to meet the new burden costs associated with the Homelessness Reduction Bill.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60648","60648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674756","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the level of (a) council tax arrears and (b) non-domestic rate arrears was on 31 March 2016 in (i) Purbeck District Council, (ii) North Dorset District Council, (iii) West Dorset District Council and (iv) Weymouth and Portland Borough Council.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60671","60671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674757","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households were living in temporary accommodation paid for by (a) Bournemouth Borough Council, (b) Poole Borough Council and (c) Christchurch Council on (i) 31 March 2016 and (ii) the most recent date for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60672","60672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674758","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) minimum and (b) maximum number of years will be for which council tax spending will be assessed for the purpose of regulations setting a threshold to trigger a local referendum under the Local Government Finance Bill.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60673","60673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674759","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the maximum size of area will be as measured by population in which pooling of non-domestic sites will be permitted under provisions of the Local Government Finance Bill.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60674","60674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674760","2017-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals on subletting through companies, such as Airbnb, to mandate the owner's permission before that accommodation is sublet.","Biography information for Victoria Borwick","Victoria Borwick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60637","60637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674761","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the full impact assessment used to determine funding for the Homelessness Reduction Bill.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60582","60582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674762","2017-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with local authorities on ensuring that there is more flexibility in the criteria for disabled people to be included on the housing register for an accessible home.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60612","60612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674763","2017-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of amounts raised from the social care precept for local authorities with disproportionate requirements for funding on social care.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60503","60503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674764","2017-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average length of stay in temporary accommodation was for households in the London Borough of Southwark in (a) 2010, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60535","60535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674765","2017-01-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when her Department plans to respond to the technical proposals produced by Ofcom on the designation of the universal service obligation for broadband.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60581","60581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674766","2017-01-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to visit Coventry following the launch of the UK City of Culture 2021 competition; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60587","60587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674767","2017-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Steering Committee of the Defence Growth Partnership last met; and when that committee next plans to meet.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60622","60622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674768","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2017 to Question 59887, what measures will be included in the refresh of defence industrial policy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60628","60628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674769","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle, the effective strength and the basing locations of the Royal Marines are.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60539","60539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674770","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on meeting Army annual recruiting targets this year.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60554","60554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674771","2017-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on meeting Future Reserves 2020 recruiting targets in each of the three services.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60556","60556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674772","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons the Director of Fair Access can issue fines to universities.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60557","60557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674773","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of nurseries in the private, voluntary and independent sector in each local authority employ at least one member of staff with early years practitioner or qualified-teacher status.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60537","60537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674774","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 51314, what the Ofsted categories of assessment are for each (a) academy school and (b) free school sponsored by a (i) grammar school or (ii) multi-academy trust run by a grammar school.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60529","60529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674775","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to work with the devolved administrations to combat anti-Semitism and holocaust denial in schools, colleges and on university campuses.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60505","60505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674776","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the wastage rates school support staff in each of the last 10 years (a) in total and (b) for each type of support staff.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60621","60621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674777","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the (a) amount and (b) proportion of government funding for early years provision that each local authority has retained in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60626","60626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674778","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of school-based counselling services in Wales and Northern Ireland in improving young people's educational attainment and attendance in schools; and what her policy is on whether such services should be established in England.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60620","60620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674779","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many universities did not meet widening participation targets agreed with the Office for Fair Access in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60577","60577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674780","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies on school-based mental health services of the findings of the Children's Society's Good Childhood report, published in August 2016.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60600","60600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674781","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many fines the Director of Fair Access has issued to universities that have not met widening participation targets in each year since the establishment of that office.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60578","60578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674782","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of school-based mental health services in reducing levels of pupil exclusions.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60596","60596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674783","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of academic posts at higher education institutions in the UK which are directly funded from EU sources; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60574","60574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674785","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will list the approved apprenticeship Trailblazer Standards which do not include recognised qualifications.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60559","60559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674786","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Trailblazer groups developing new apprenticeship standards have had their draft Trailblazer Standard rejected because it includes a qualification which does not meet her Department's rules.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60560","60560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674787","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Trailblazer groups developing new apprenticeship standards have been advised that their draft Trailblazer Standard should not include a qualification because it does not meet her Department's rules.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60561","60561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674788","2017-01-20","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to evaluate the effectiveness of her Department's policy on the value of reorganised qualifications in apprenticeship standards.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60562","60562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674789","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to respond to the email of 22 November 2016 from Tim Fuller, the Director of Reality Business, on the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60670","60670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674790","2017-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether fishing policy will be national or regional after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60652","60652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674791","2017-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the Scottish Government on Common Agricultural Policy payments.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60563","60563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674793","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2016 to Question 54404, if she will estimate when the outcome of the Planning Inspectorate inquiry into the former Willenhall Gas Works will permit her to provide a substantive reply to that Question.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60602","60602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674794","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the potential change in cost required to deliver her Department's agricultural objectives after the UK has left the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60624","60624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674795","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the proportion of income of farmers and growers which was directly provided by EU sources of funding in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60585","60585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674796","2017-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on the future of Common Agricultural Policy payments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60500","60500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674797","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that Thames Water customers affected by water outages and burst water pipes receive full compensation.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60532","60532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674798","2017-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the Environment Agency plans to proceed with the pilot projects to investigate transferring the management of some stretches of main rivers and associated assets to other risk management authorities or communities where there is local support.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60540","60540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674799","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of Israel on the demolition of the Bedouin village of Umm al-Hiran in southern Israel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60551","60551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674800","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2017 to Question 58505, whether the meeting on 15 December 2016 was his only one with the Russian ambassador on the humanitarian situation in Aleppo in 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60555","60555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674801","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many rebel groups are fighting President Assad in Syria; and what the names of those rebel groups are.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60567","60567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674802","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of the Democratic Republic of the Congo on President Joseph Kabila's commitment not to seek re-election in 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60524","60524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674803","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2017 to Question 58877, which Ministers were made aware of the text of the UN Security Council Resolution 2334 (2016) before the vote on that resolution took place.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60521","60521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674804","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of migrants who have died crossing the Mediterranean from Libya to Europe.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60568","60568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674805","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the cost of intervention in Libya since 2011.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60569","60569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674806","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assist the Nigerian government recover children kidnapped by Boko Haram.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60610","60610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674807","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help bring about a ceasefire and peace talks in Yemen.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60616","60616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674808","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to report to the House the outcome of the Paris Peace Conference on 15 January 2017.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60645","60645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674809","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of North Korea's nuclear programme.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60635","60635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674810","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to discuss the political and human rights situation in North Korea with the incoming US administration.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60636","60636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674811","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what report he has received on alleged human rights abuses and violations of international humanitarian law against residents of Benghazi and other Libyan cites by forces allied to Khalifa Haftar.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60656","60656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674812","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the threat posed to the international community by North Korea's nuclear programme.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60630","60630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674813","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Japan, (b) South Korea and (c) China on the political and human rights situation in North Korea.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60631","60631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674814","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has (a) received and (b) made to the government of Pakistan on reports of persecution and mistreatment of the Ahmadi community in Pakistan.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60700","60700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674815","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with the Home Secretary on former British-Hong Kong armed forces personnel seeking UK (a) residency and (b) citizenship.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60706","60706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674816","2017-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he and officials of his Department have made to the government of Cameroon on reports of violence against anglophone Cameroonians; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60699","60699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674817","2017-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the security situation in Umm al-Hiran since the car-ramming attack in that village in January 2017.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60710","60710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674818","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the wastage rates among (a) medical staff not including doctors or nurses and (b) non-medical staff in the NHS over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60677","60677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674819","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking through the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency to ensure that all women of child-bearing age who are prescribed Valproate have received the new guidance on the use of that treatment.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60689","60689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674820","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether GPs are required to (a) record and (b) report each instance when they have warned a female patient of the dangers of prescribed Valproate.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60690","60690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674821","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how (a) his Department and (b) the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency will be alerted when all concerned women have been warned of the dangers of prescribed Valproate.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60691","60691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674822","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to support Cervical Cancer Prevention Week.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60693","60693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674823","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing HPV self-sampling as part of the cervical screening programme.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60694","60694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674824","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with Public Health England on increasing cervical screening  uptake among women from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60695","60695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674825","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the decline in cervical screening uptake among women in the age groups (a) 25 to 29 and (b) 60 to 64.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60696","60696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674826","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2017 to Question 59597, on hospital beds, how many patients' discharge was delayed because there was no care package in their own home or place in a care home in November 2016.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60661","60661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674827","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department paid to each other EU member state for costs related to the medical treatment for UK nationals in each of the last five years; and how many cases of (a) emergency medical care under the European Health Insurance Card system and (b) other treatment those costs relate to.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60662","60662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674828","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS of NHS mental health patients being treated in non-NHS institutions has been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60665","60665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674829","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Specialist Training 4 psychiatry posts were filled in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60666","60666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674830","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) mental health and (b) other health services he has visited since he took office; and what the date was of each such visit.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60667","60667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674831","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of in-patients have been sectioned under the Mental Health Act 1983 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60668","60668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674832","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children were admitted to adult in-patient mental health wards in 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60669","60669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674833","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to changes in reported levels of children's self-harm set out in the Good Childhood Report 2016, published by the Children's Society in August 2016, what steps his Department is taking to strengthen collaboration with the Department for Education on improving the availability of school-based mental health services.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60644","60644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674834","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2017 to Question 59597, on hospital beds, when data for December 2016 will be published.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60650","60650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674835","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of management of adult atopic dermatitis across the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60609","60609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674837","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints have been made against Primary Care Support England regarding the transfer of patient records in West Yorkshire, in each month since 1 September 2015.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60615","60615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674838","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of members of health trust boards are women.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60571","60571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674839","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to prevent nuisance calls to 999.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60611","60611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674840","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce geographic variation in access to dermatology services for patients with (a) skin diseases and (b) adult atopic dermatitis.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60608","60608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674841","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of adults with atopic dermatitis in (a) Strangford and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60605","60605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674842","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of (a) atopic dermatitis and (b) other skin diseases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60606","60606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674843","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there are plans for the development of NICE guidelines on the management of atopic dermatitis in adults.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60607","60607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674844","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of NHS physiotherapists in Shropshire.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60617","60617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674845","2017-01-23","Department for Education","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of school-based mental health services for young people aged between 10 and 17.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60603","60603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674846","2017-01-23","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential for (a) flexible pricing and (b) indication-specific pricing for drug purchase by the NHS.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60583","60583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674847","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the potential effect of the implementation of the Sustainability and Transformation Plan for North West London on the provision of health services in that area.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60576","60576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674848","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what policy proposals the Clinical Priority Advisory Group assigned priority level (a) 1, (b) 2, (c) 3, (d) 4 and (e) 5 to the specialised commissioning re-prioritisation process for 2016-17, announced on 4 December 2016.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60527","60527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674849","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts offer faecal occult blood testing for suspected bowel cancer.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60525","60525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674850","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the NHS England 2018-19 specialised commissioning annual prioritisation process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60526","60526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674851","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NICE-approved medicines evaluated through the Highly Specialised Technology programme have had a quality adjusted life year measure of £100,000 or less since the programme was established.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60514","60514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674852","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of how the introduction of the proposed fast-track NICE technology appraisal process for promising new technologies that fall below an incremental cost-effectiveness ratio of £10,000 per quality adjusted life year will affect the review timings for products that are not fast-tracked.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60515","60515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674853","2017-01-20","Department of Health","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the appropriateness of introducing the £100,000 quality adjusted life year threshold for evaluating highly specialised technologies.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60516","60516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674854","2017-01-20","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2017 to Question 59330, for what reasons her Department does not hold information on the number of persons examined under Schedule 7 to the Terrorism Act 2000 at individual UK airports; in what format data is supplied to her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60520","60520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674855","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK have paid the immigration health surcharge in each year for which records exist.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60528","60528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674856","2017-01-20","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the level of gender-based and sexual violence experienced by women and girls held in transit on journeys to seek asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60513","60513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674857","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the change in the number of EU citizens in the UK that will be (a) engaged in agricultural work, (b) engaged in construction work, (c) employed in the NHS and (d) employed in the UK after April 2017.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60534","60534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674858","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made on the new ICT gateway into the National Offender Management System.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60522","60522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674859","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) women and (b) men were killed by a current or former partner in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60533","60533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674860","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department has allocated to Border Force; and how many people have been employed by that agency in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60627","60627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674861","2017-01-20","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to assist unaccompanied refugee children in (a) France and (b) other European countries.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60619","60619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674862","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many drunk tanks have been established since 2013.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60640","60640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674863","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to monitor whether EEA nationals residing in the UK who are out of work or not actively seeking work for a period longer than three months have been asked to provide evidence (a) of identity and nationality of an EEA member state and (b) that they are exercising a free movement right in the UK.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60595","60595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674864","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with (a) the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, (b) the Department for Exiting the European Union and (c) farming representatives on seasonal agricultural workers from other EU member states.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60646","60646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674865","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for permanent residence by EU nationals living in the UK there have been in each of the last five years; and what proportion of those applications were refused.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60675","60675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674866","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what average length of time is taken for her Department to process applications for permanent residency from EU nationals.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60676","60676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674867","2017-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to mark Holocaust Memorial Day on 27 January 2017.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60633","60633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674868","2017-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent steps he has taken to tackle anti-Semitism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60634","60634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674869","2017-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to bring forward legislative proposals on subletting through companies, such as Airbnb, to mandate the owner's permission before that accommodation is sublet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Victoria Borwick","Victoria Borwick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60638","60638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674870","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many appeals there have been against refusal of an application for permanent residence by EU nationals in each of the last five years; and what proportion of those appeals have been successful.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60664","60664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674871","2017-01-23","Home Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has had discussions with the HKOR Benevolent Association on UK (a) residency and (b) citizenship for former British-Hong Kong servicemen and women.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60707","60707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674872","2017-01-20","Department for International Development","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding from the UK's contribution to the Iraq humanitarian pooled fund is provided to projects in the Kurdistan region; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60508","60508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674873","2017-01-20","Department for International Development","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has provided to the Kurdistan regional government for support of internally displaced people in the Kurdistan region since 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60509","60509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674874","2017-01-20","Department for International Development","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has had discussions with (a) the Yemen Executive Mine Action Centre and (b) other national de-mining institutions in Yemen on the provision of funding for clearing UK-produced cluster munitions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60523","60523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674875","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of sentences for each category of offence are suspended sentences.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60546","60546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674876","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effect of the eligibility criteria for family legal aid funding on the number of litigants in person in domestic violence cases.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60547","60547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674877","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will publish a progress report on the Ministry of Justice Action Plan on Restorative Justice.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60548","60548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674878","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to ensure that restorative justice is offered to victims of crime.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60549","60549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674880","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that victims of crime are informed of mechanisms available for restorative justice before an offender has been sentenced.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60550","60550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674881","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many legal cases related to rendition her Department has defended since 1997.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60510","60510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674882","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that there is more than one housing legal aid provider in each legal aid procurement area in (a) England and (b) Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60511","60511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674883","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that there is more than one housing legal aid provider in each provider area in Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60512","60512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674884","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much her Department has paid to claimants in (a) cases and (b) settlements of cases relating to rendition since 1997.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60507","60507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674885","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who the housing legal and providers are in (a) the Dwyfor Meirionydd constituency and (b) each provider area in Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60517","60517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674886","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with the Welsh Government on the provision of housing legal aid advice in Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60518","60518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674887","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations her Department has received on the adequacy of funding for community rehabilitation companies (CRCs) after 1 April 2017; and what recent estimate her Department has made of the level of future funding for CRCs.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60501","60501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674888","2017-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the effect of the proposed changes to cost protections in environmental claims on (a) the number of environmental judicial review applications, (b) the proportion of successful environmental claims and (c) the UK's compliance with the Aarhus Convention and EU law.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60594","60594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674889","2017-01-20","Attorney General","2017-01-18","To ask the Attorney General, what guidance his Department provides to ensure the consistent prosecution and assessment of hate crime by the regional Crown Prosecution Service offices.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60575","60575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674890","2017-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the evidential basis was for the Government's finding in its consultation on Costs Protection in Environmental Cases of September 2015 that the existing environmental costs regime results in meritless applications which cause delay and frustrate proper decision making.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60599","60599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674891","2017-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure environmental claims are not prohibitively expensive under its proposals to remove the fixed-cost cap.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60601","60601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674892","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what dates the Government plans to (a) start and (b) end the review of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60702","60702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674893","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many family court users represented themselves as litigants in person in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60698","60698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674894","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding she plans to allocate from the victim services budget for 2020-21 to police and crime commissioners for restorative justice capacity building.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60697","60697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674895","2017-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to support the prison service on reporting problems and sharing best practice on preventing the misuse of drones around prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60657","60657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674896","2017-01-23","Northern Ireland Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the peace process in Northern Ireland of pursuing prosecutions against former members of the armed forces for activities in Northern Ireland which occurred prior to the Good Friday Agreement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60649","60649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674897","2017-01-23","Prime Minister","2017-01-18","To ask the Prime Minister, how many parliamentary private secretaries she has authorised to travel overseas with or on behalf of their Ministers since she became Prime Minister.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60641","60641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674898","2017-01-20","Prime Minister","2017-01-18","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she discussed the role and place of the devolved administrations in forthcoming EU negotiations during her conversations on 17 January 2017 with EU Council President Tusk, EU Commission President Juncker, German Chancellor Merkel and French President Hollande.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60618","60618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674899","2017-01-20","Scotland Office","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what plans he has to visit a food bank in February 2017.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60506","60506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674900","2017-01-20","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on improving surface access to each airport in the South East of England since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60519","60519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674901","2017-01-20","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the legal basis for the proposed sale by National Express of the c2c franchise to Trenitalia; what discussions he has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) external stakeholders on that proposed sale; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60543","60543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674902","2017-01-20","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what role he has in granting authorisation for one rail franchisee to sell its potential franchise to another commercial organisation; if he will set out the process and procedures for any such sale; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60544","60544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674903","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if, in the light of the deaths of Sam Boulton, Robert Hamilton and Sam Harding, his Department will review the maximum penalties for the offence of opening the door of a vehicle into the path of another road user.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60531","60531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674904","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what level of aircraft noise has been recorded in Camberwell and Peckham constituency in each of the last five years; and what assessment he has made of the effect of the addition of a third runway at Heathrow Airport on noise levels in that constituency in each of the five years after the expansion of that airport.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60536","60536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674905","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to respond to the Law Commission's report into taxi and private hire regulation, published in May 2014.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60623","60623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674906","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of his Department's staff work on cycling policy.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60642","60642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674907","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2017 to Question 59977, on motor vehicle exhaust emissions, where the 12 hydrogen refuelling stations are; and what plans he has to support the expansion of that network.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60579","60579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674908","2017-01-20","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure compliance with requirements set out in the Supreme Court judgment on FirstGroup Plc v Paulley, issued on 18 January 2017.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60614","60614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674909","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to work with the rail regulator to ensure that each train operating company is complying with its obligations under the Consumer Rights Act 2016.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60591","60591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/674910","2017-01-23","Department for Transport","2017-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that independent alternative dispute resolution is provided in the rail sector that adequately supports passenger complaints.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 60592","60592"
