"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519021","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total size was of the Government's fleet of M3 Amphibious Rig bridging vehicles in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37341","37341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519022","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had about the future of the Knightsbridge Barracks.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37330","37330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519023","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport about moving the Knightsbridge Barracks to an alternative location in the Royal Parks.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37331","37331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519024","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle is of the Royal Military Police.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37237","37237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519025","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Section 104 Order covering fatal accident inquiry military deaths will come into force.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37271","37271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519026","2016-05-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the original planned date was for cutting steel to begin for the first Type 26 Global Combat Ship; to what date this planned date has been moved; whether the cause of that change was (a) limited capacity of BAE Systems and its sub-contractors to meet the original schedule or (b) a decision to remove a significant sum from the annual T26 budget; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37138","37138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519027","2016-05-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of by how much the cost of the Type 26 programme is expected to increase for every year that the in-service date for each ship is delayed.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37140","37140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519028","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprentices there are (a) at each level and (b) by age of apprentice in each of the armed forces.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37222","37222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519029","2016-05-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the original projected in-service date was for the first Type 26 Global Combat Ship; and what the current projected in-service date is for first such ship.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37139","37139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519030","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what Armed Forces Day events in Northern Ireland during June 2016 his Department plans to support.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37224","37224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519031","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 25 April 2016 to Question 34910, what qualifications are required by his Department for English and mathematics tutors who teach functional skills in numeracy and literacy.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37111","37111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519032","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what opportunities his Department offers to trainee soldiers aged under 18 to resit GCSEs as part of their elective personal development.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37109","37109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519033","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which of his Department's contracts in the last five years used the largest proportion of British steel.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37176","37176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519034","2016-05-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's definition is of a cyber act of war.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37120","37120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519035","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to encourage the establishment of co-operative schools.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37158","37158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519036","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) timescale and (b) terms of reference are of the review referred to in paragraph 6.69 of the Educational excellence everywhere White Paper, Cm 9230, of what is happening in practice for children with special educational needs and disabilities.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37119","37119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519037","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Key Stage 1 children in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley local authority area and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber were in classes of more than 35 children in the academic year beginning September (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2013, (iv) 2014 and (v) 2015.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37096","37096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519038","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Key Stage 1 children in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley and (c) Yorkshire and the Humber were in classes of more than 30 children in the academic year beginning September (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2013, (iv) 2014 and (v) 2015.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37097","37097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519039","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase entrepreneurship and business education in schools.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37151","37151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519040","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding is available for learners formerly on the Youth Contract after the closure of that programme on 31 March 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37152","37152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519041","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy that parents will retain the right to remain anonymous from the school in question when they object to a schools admission arrangements under the School Admissions Code after the forthcoming review of that code.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37020","37020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519042","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools founded since 2015 are compliant with section 5 of the Education (Independent School Standards) (England) Regulations 2010.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37188","37188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519043","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many enforcement actions have been initiated by her Department for contravention of the Education (Independent School Standards) (England) Regulations 2010 section 5 since 2015.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37189","37189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519044","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the trial of Active Movement in schools in Newbury; and if she will roll out Active Movement to other parts of the country.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37254","37254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519045","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which bodies are responsible for maintaining food hygiene standards in state funded primary and secondary schools; and what steps he is taking to support those schools which are found to be in need of improvement in that area.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37236","37236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519046","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report of Ofsted on its inspection of Audenshaw School Academy Trust which took place on 23 and 24 February 2016, if she will make an assessment of the effect on the students for whom pupil premium funding was intended of that funding being saved for a capital project.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37375","37375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519047","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools were closed in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37380","37380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519048","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what rules govern the use of pupil premium funding (a) for capital projects and (b) in a different year to that for which the funding was allocated.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37376","37376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519049","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was spent on free school projects that did not result in the establishment of a school in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37381","37381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519050","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools are in temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37382","37382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519051","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what monitoring her Department undertakes of the (a) allocation, (b) spending and (c) outcomes of pupil premium funding at (i) maintained schools and (ii) academy trust schools.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37374","37374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519052","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what response her Department has made to the findings of Ofsted in its report of the inspection of Audenshaw School Academy Trust which took place on 23 and 24 February 2016 that approximately £120,000 of pupil premium funding has not been spent on pupils for whom that funding was intended.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37377","37377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519053","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will order an investigation to be undertaken into (a) financial management and (b) governance relating to the use of pupil premium funding at Audenshaw School Academy Trust.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37378","37378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519054","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on trends in the number of vacancies for science teachers in secondary schools in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) nationally in the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37383","37383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519055","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools spent more than one year in temporary accommodation in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37379","37379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519056","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) physics and (b) chemistry trainee teachers undertook a pre-initial teacher training subject knowledge enhancement course, broken down by subject and length of course, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37394","37394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519057","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) local authority-run and (b) private or voluntary sector children's homes there were in each local authority area in 31 March 2015.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37346","37346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519058","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many cases of sexual assault have been recorded in schools in Cumbria in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37395","37395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519059","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been spent on supply teacher pay by state-funded schools in England in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37396","37396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519060","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much capital spending was committed to university technical colleges in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37335","37335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519061","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was spent on (a) local authority and (b) non-local authority residential care provision per week and per child in each local authority in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37347","37347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519062","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 28 April 2016 to Question 35059, how many requests to meet with hon. Members she has received from each of the political parties represented in the House since 1 February 2016.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37292","37292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519063","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were placed in regulated children's homes within each local authority boundary in the year ending 31 March 2015; and how many and what proportion of children in regulated children's homes within each local authority boundary were the responsibility of that local authority in that year.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37345","37345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519064","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which university technical colleges closed in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37333","37333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519065","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students were on the roll of university technical colleges in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015 and (d) 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37334","37334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519066","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many successful applicants to the Schools Direct scheme there were in each of the last five years; and what the cost of that scheme was to her Department in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37433","37433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519067","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase recruitment of teachers of priority subjects in secondary schools.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37411","37411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519068","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department gives to schools which are converting to academy status on whether that school should adopt a new uniform; and what information she holds on the number of schools which have adopted a new uniform when converting to academy status.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37369","37369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519069","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish Alan Wood's report on local safeguarding children's boards' roles and functions.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37460","37460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519070","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether additional funding will be provided to support further education students who have to travel further to access education as a result of colleges merging.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37449","37449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519071","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33136, on how many occasions has a child's admission been directed by (a) the Schools Adjudicator after it was sought by a local authority and (b) the Education Funding Agency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37487","37487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519072","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applicants there were for the Northern fund for academy sponsors by the deadline of 22 February 2016; and if she will list the trusts which were approved for funding.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37442","37442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519073","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information she holds on trends in recruitment of teachers of priority subjects in secondary schools across the UK in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37432","37432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519074","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33136, whether her Department provides guidance to academies on the consultation of local people on admission policies.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37443","37443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519075","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the effect of a vote to leave the EU on the cost of school trips abroad.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37529","37529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519076","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications she has received from academy trusts wishing to use land for purposes other than education in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37530","37530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519077","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she made of the effect of a vote to leave the EU on school language exchange programmes.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37531","37531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519078","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information she holds on the number of science graduates hired by secondary schools as teachers across the UK in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37532","37532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519079","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications from academy trusts to use land for purposes other than education have been (a) approved and (b) refused in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37528","37528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519080","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36326, what representations she has received from (a) schools and (b) union representatives about the provision for academy trusts to charge teachers for car parking services on school grounds; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37479","37479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519081","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what procedures she will follow in consideration of applications for the disposal for development of the former Two Trees High School in Denton.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37464","37464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519082","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what account she will take of the loss of playing fields in consideration of applications for the disposal for development of the former Two Trees High School site in Denton.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37465","37465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519083","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to consult (a) alternative educational providers, (b) the public and (c) the hon. Member for Denton and Reddish over applications for the disposal for development of the former Two Trees High School site in Denton.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37466","37466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519084","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment of need for (a) additional school places, (b) a new academy or (c) a new free school she plans to carry out in connection with applications to dispose for development of the former Two Trees High School site in Denton.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37467","37467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519085","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has received an application from Tameside Metropolitan Borough Council to release the former Two Trees High School site in Denton for development.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37468","37468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519086","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many funding agreements have been terminated by each regional schools commissioner.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37527","37527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519087","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what consideration she has given to the retention of Article 10(a) paragraph 16(a) of the EU Emissions Trading System, Directive 2003/87/EC, to take account of the carbon leakage vulnerability of activities with a high proportion of raw material-related process emissions under the next phase of the EU Emissions Trading System; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37505","37505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519088","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much domestic solar PV by MWp was deployed in Quarter 1 of the new FIT scheme; and what the cap was for that quarter.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37503","37503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519089","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make it her policy to support French proposals for an EU-wide carbon floor price.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37483","37483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519090","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will join the Carbon Pricing Leadership Coalition; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37482","37482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519091","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reasons it has not been practicable for her Department to lay the Committee on Climate Change report on Compatibility of Onshore Petroleum with meeting UK carbon budgets before Parliament.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37533","37533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519092","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much domestic solar PV by MWp has been deployed in quarter 2 of the new FIT scheme; and what the cap is for this quarter.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37502","37502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519093","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's policy is on restricting the import of cheap, inferior-quality coal to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37519","37519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519094","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when her Department plans to lay the Committee on Climate Change report on Compatibility of Onshore Petroleum with meeting UK carbon budgets and its response before Parliament.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37534","37534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519095","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the number of job losses in the UK solar SME sector arising from the closure of the feed-in tariff scheme and its replacement with a capped scheme.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37501","37501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519096","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of how many UK solar companies have gone out of business or stopped installing solar PV as a result of policy changes made since May 2015.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37500","37500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519097","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 14 April 2016 to Question 33418, what progress her Department has made on options for taking account of process emissions in a tiering system for the allocation of free allowances under Phase IV of the EU Emissions Trading System; and what those options are.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37463","37463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519098","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to her Answer of 12 May 2016, Official Report, column 707, what the evidential basis is for the statement that take up of domestic solar PV systems is strong.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37504","37504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519099","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will publish the findings of the Ricardo Energy and Environment report into benchmarking for the Phase IV of the EU Emissions Trading System; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37507","37507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519100","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 14 April 2016 to Question 33419, what the next steps are and when she expects to come to a final position on the UK and French tiering proposal for Phase IV of the EU Emissions Trading System.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37508","37508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519101","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department will implement the recommendations made by the Committee on Climate Change in its report of November 2015, The fifth carbon budget - The next step towards a low-carbon economy.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37461","37461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519102","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if her Department will maintain the 2014 commitment to ring-fence spending through the Contracts for Difference (CfD) for 100MW of marine energy in the UK and make the full 100MW available to developers during the 2016 CfD auction process.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37477","37477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519103","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will set the emissions target recommended by the Independent Committee on Climate Change in the Fifth Carbon Budget.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37405","37405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519104","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with (a) Ofgem and (b) the National Grid on steps to encourage coal plants to stay open.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37398","37398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519105","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how the reforms to the Capacity Market announced on 6 May 2016 will provide investment incentives for new gas plants to be built in the UK.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37353","37353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519106","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how the reforms to the Capacity Market announced on 6 May 2016 will ensure a secure electricity supply that is consistent with the decarbonisation objectives set out in her Department's single departmental plan.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37352","37352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519107","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total length is of tunnels for each specific diameter being constructed by the London Power Tunnels Project; and what length of each such type of tunnel has been constructed to date.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37258","37258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519108","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent estimate she has made of the cost to the National Grid of the London Power Tunnels project; and how much of that cost is related to (a) civil engineering, (b) electrical engineering and (c) equipment.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37259","37259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519109","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the London Power Tunnels Project is (a) on schedule for completion in 2018 and (b) within budget.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37257","37257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519110","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions her Department has had with other government departments on the potential for the construction of new nuclear reactors in Somerset independent of the proposals by EDF at Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37290","37290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519111","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress her Department has made on rolling-out smart meters as standard by the end of 2020; and what estimate she has made of the number of homes that will have a smart meter installed by the end of each year to 2020.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37190","37190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519112","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of extra reserve capacity in the National Grid in 2016 and 2017.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37191","37191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519113","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to ensure the data security of smart meters.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37098","37098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519114","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total gross expenditure on the London Power Tunnels Project is to date.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37100","37100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519115","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the expansion of new electricity interconnectors on (a) the capacity market auction price and (b) long-term investment in gas-fired electricity generation.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37038","37038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519116","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to work with other departments to formulate the Government's response to the recommendation of the Energy and Climate Change Committee in its Fifth Report of Session 2015-16, on Setting the fifth carbon budget, HC 659, that effective drivers need to be put in place by Government to encourage innovation and investment for transport, buildings and agriculture.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37037","37037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519117","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which Combined-Cycle Gas Turbine plants have closed in the last two years; and what the (a) generation size and (b) location was of each of those plants.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37060","37060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519118","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations she has received from (a) industry bodies and (b) the public on reviewing the treatment of electricity interconnectors under the reformed capacity market; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37048","37048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519119","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, by what mechanisms the National Grid can procure electricity supplies outside of the capacity market.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37049","37049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519120","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the level of megawatts of new Combined-Cycle Gas Turbine (CCGT) capacity unit that will be commissioned by 2022; and what estimate her Department has made of the total available CCGT capacity by 2022.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37061","37061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519121","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with the European Commission on the application of EU state aid rules related to the provision of (a) Supplementary Balancing Reserve and (b) other Black Start ancillary support contracts provided by the National Grid to Eggborough, Fiddler's Ferry and Drax power plants; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37050","37050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519122","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on the (a) costs and (b) margins of combined cycle gas turbine plants of (i) Supplementary Balancing Reserve and (ii) other Black Start ancillary support subsidy contracts to coal plants.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37051","37051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519123","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost is of (a) the supplementary balancing reserve and (b) other black start ancillary support contracts provided by the National Grid to (i) Eggborough, (ii) Fiddler's Ferry and (iii) Drax power plant.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37062","37062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519124","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the National Grid's (a) Supplementary Balancing Reserve and (b) other Black Start  ancillary support contracts to coal plants on the capacity market auction price.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37052","37052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519125","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with (a) Big Six and (b) other electricity generators on the effect on the electricity market of (i) existing and (ii) new combined cycle gas turbine generation.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37053","37053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519126","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with (a) Big Six and (b) other combined cycle gas turbine generators on the potential effect of an expansion of electricity interconnectors on (i) the capacity market and (ii) long-term investment in gas-fired electricity generation.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37039","37039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519127","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effects of retention of Eggborough and Fiddler's Ferry coal plants on investment in new combined cycle gas turbine plants.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37040","37040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519128","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with (a) OFGEM and (b) the National Grid on encouraging the construction of new combined cycle gas turbine power stations.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37041","37041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519129","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what measures she is taking to reassure existing electricity generators that the capacity market is fair and stable.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37042","37042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519130","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost of maintaining Black Start plans for coal-fired power stations has been to date.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37043","37043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519131","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with (a) Big Six and (b) other combined cycle gas turbine generators on the effect on the electricity market of Black Start payments to coal-fired power stations.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37044","37044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519132","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent progress has been made on the gas generation strategy.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37058","37058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519133","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many terawatt hours of electricity have been imported into the UK by individual interconnectors since 2013.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37065","37065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519134","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with UK electricity generators on the effect on the electricity market of market imported electricity by interconnectors not subject to the carbon price floor.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37066","37066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519135","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many megawatts of Combined-Cycle Gas Turbine construction is taking place in the UK; and what the (a) size and (b) location is of each of those constructions.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37059","37059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519136","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with the European Commission on EU state aid related to UK interconnector operations.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37064","37064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519137","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will publish the information her Department holds on the (a) process, (b) criteria and (c) guidance followed by the National Grid to deliver (i) supplementary balancing reserve and (ii) black start ancillary services contracts for the next 12 months; and what analysis was taken in advance to inform that delivery.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37063","37063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519138","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that (a) there is a strategy for decommissioning offshore oil and gas rigs around the UK and (b) that decommissioning work is carried out in UK yards.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37118","37118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519139","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 11 May 2016 to Question 36451, if she will make it her policy to publish dates of meetings held between the Inter-Ministerial Group on Oil and Gas and representatives from that industry since May 2015.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37082","37082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519140","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 11 May 2016 to Question 36450, what consultation meetings she (a) has had and (b) plans to have with trades unions for UK oil and gas workers on the development of the Inter-Ministerial Group on Oil and Gas plan for the UK oil and gas workforce.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37083","37083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519141","2016-05-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 27 April 2016 to Question 34978, what resources his Department plans to allocate to local authorities in Northamptonshire to develop their capacity to deal with flash floods in the next three years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37084","37084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519142","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taken to encourage the use of solar power in new building developments in England.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37142","37142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519143","2016-05-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations the Government has received from (a) the Chinese government and (b) Chinese energy companies on the use of alternative nuclear technology to that proposed by EDF at Hinkley Point.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37126","37126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519144","2016-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to speed up the process enabling UK pig producers to export trotters to China.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37085","37085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519145","2016-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons the Tobacco Manufacturers' Association has not been invited to meetings of the litter strategy advisory group.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37153","37153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519146","2016-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans that the national litter strategy will include beach and aquatic litter.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37071","37071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519147","2016-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will direct the Rural Payments Agency not to make any bonus payments to its Chief Executive until payments to eligible farmers have been completed.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37217","37217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519148","2016-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of microplastics entering the sea on protected species in UK waters.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37205","37205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519149","2016-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which flood insurance providers have joined the Flood Re re-insurance scheme; and what proportion of the domestic flood insurance market is now able to access the Flood Re scheme.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37204","37204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519150","2016-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has responded to the WHO Ambient Air Pollution Database Update 2016; what assessment she has made of the findings of that update; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37454","37454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519151","2016-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the proportion of farmers who have received (a) a payment and (b) full payment from the Rural Payments Agency under the Basic Payment Scheme in 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37414","37414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519152","2016-05-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will respond to the findings of the report entitled Oilseed rape and neonicotinoids, by 38 Degrees, published in September 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37494","37494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519153","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to Israeli authorities about reports of further demolitions of EU-funded structures in Jabal al Baba.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37484","37484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519154","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Egyptian government on the disconnection of power lines providing electricity to Southern Gaza; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37481","37481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519155","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 34085, whether any UK discussions with the Saudi Arabian authorities regarding the alleged use of cluster munitions in Yemen have led to confirmation that such munitions have been used by Saudi Arabian armed forces on any occasion.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37524","37524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519156","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Egyptian government on the death penalty imposed on Ibrahim Mohammed Helal and other journalists in that country.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37436","37436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519157","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the detention of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37435","37435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519158","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that Syrian children given asylum in the UK will be able to enter in time for the start of the school year in September.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37475","37475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519159","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on whether the Assad government's military is targeting medical facilities in opposition-held territory in Syria.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37437","37437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519160","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what resources his Department allocates to promoting and upholding freedom of religion or belief within the countries with which it works.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37363","37363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519161","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Ethiopia on the (a) imprisonment of the journalist Eskinder Nega and (b) protection of freedom of speech in that country.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37362","37362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519162","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of violations of freedom of religion or belief on women; and what his Department is doing to tackle such violations.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37367","37367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519163","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on alleged violations of freedom of religion or belief in Crimea by the Russian authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37365","37365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519164","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department takes to ensure that its policies do not encourage discrimination of religion or belief.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37364","37364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519165","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in other EU countries and the EU Commission on the demolition of EU-funded structures by Israeli authorities in Jabal al Baba on 16 May 2016; and what steps he plans to take (a) independently and (b) with those counterparts to ensure that any further such planned demolitions are halted.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37391","37391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519166","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made representations to the Iranian government on the continued detention of seven Bahá'í leaders.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37291","37291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519167","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he made and received during his visit to Mexico in May 2016 on upholding the right to freedom of religion or belief in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37310","37310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519168","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he intends to reply to the letter of 8 April 2016 on the death of Claire Martin in Italy from the hon. Member for Ashfield.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37229","37229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519169","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the demolition of Bedouin homes at Jabal Al-Baba in East Jerusalem.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37230","37230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519170","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Turkish counterpart to (a) re-open Turkey's borders to Syrian asylum seekers and (b) conduct independent investigations on alleged attacks on Syrian asylum seekers by Turkish border guards.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37099","37099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519171","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the President of Sri Lanka on (a) the implementation of UN Human Rights Council resolution 30/1 and (b) the involvement of foreign judges and prosecutors in the investigation and prosecution of war crimes during the Sri Lankan civil war since the last ministerial visit to Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37289","37289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519172","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the Government permits the 35 people named under the US Sergei Magnitsky Rule of Law Accountability Act of 2012 to (a) hold assets in the UK and (b) be issued with UK visas.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37317","37317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519173","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the health condition of Kamal Foroughi in Iran; and what assessment he has made of the level of Mr Foroughi's access to appropriate medical care.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37277","37277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519174","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made representations to the Iranian government on the imprisonment of seven Bahá'í leaders.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37315","37315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519175","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Ethiopian government on the cases of Tibebu Mekuria, Dawit Jemberu and Belete Tilahun.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37023","37023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519176","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Iranian government on the imprisonment of Ebrahim Firouzi and other Christians in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37156","37156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519177","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of China on the case of the disabled rights lawyer Ni Yulan who has recently been placed under house arrest in that country.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37116","37116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519178","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from the Libyan government on UK military training and mentoring for Libyan authorities; and what offers of such training and mentoring the UK has made to Libyan authorities.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37106","37106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519179","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals were employed by the European Parliament in each year since 2010; and how many such people were employed at administrator grade.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37107","37107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519180","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals were employed by the European Commission in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37108","37108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519181","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to engage with international partners to tackle the persecution of secularists or of people with no faith in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37160","37160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519182","2016-05-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Ministers of his Department have raised human rights issues in an official capacity, and with whom, in the last four weeks.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37161","37161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519183","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that non-medical scientists and technicians working in the health sector are registered with the Science Council or other relevant professional bodies.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37121","37121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519184","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many students studying (a) nursing and (b) psychiatric nursing at the University of Hull received NHS bursaries in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37137","37137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519185","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce geographic variation in access to surgical and transcatheter interventions for heart valve disease.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37122","37122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519186","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on ensuring that all science-related government contracts and outsourced activities are awarded to organisations that demonstrate a commitment to high professional standards and invest in the professional development of their scientific workforce; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37123","37123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519187","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on the number of people in the UK with undiagnosed heart valve disease; and if he will estimate the potential cost to the NHS of treating such people.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37124","37124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519188","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nursing students who enrolled on pre-registration nurse education courses in each region held a prior degree-level qualification in any subject in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37125","37125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519189","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's news story of 13 September 2015, From 2020 people with suspected cancer will be diagnosed faster, when his Department plans to make tailored recovery packages available for cancer patients, including those with rarer cancers.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37113","37113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519190","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department ensures that the delivery of drug and alcohol treatment by local authorities conforms to the NHS constitution.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37104","37104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519191","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals in England are equipped to deliver thrombectomy to stroke patients.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37148","37148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519192","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness and adequacy of mental health support available to stroke survivors.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37149","37149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519193","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the current scheme of discretionary top-up payments provided by the Macfarlane Trust to its beneficiaries will be removed as a result of the Government's proposed changes to its scheme of support for people affected by contaminated blood.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37036","37036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519194","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he intends to answer the letter to him dated 23 March 2016 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regards to Mr C Costigan.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37035","37035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519195","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the recent decision of the US and Indian governments, announced in the press release of the government of India on AYUSH of 3 March 2016, to review and cooperate on whether to reduce morbidity from cancer using ayurveda, yoga, naturopathy, unani, siddha and homeopathy interventions.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37034","37034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519196","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the maximum distance recommended by NHS England is for people with severe asthma to travel to receive day-case treatment.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37090","37090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519197","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many specialist centres for asthma are recognised by NHS England.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37091","37091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519198","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what treatments are commissioned by specialist centres for severe asthma.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37092","37092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519199","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to incentivise purchase of defibrillator equipment; and if he will discuss with the Chancellor of the Exchequer reviewing the VAT regulations that apply to such equipment.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37055","37055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519200","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what obligations private hospitals and NHS foundation trusts have to share the medical records of patients who have used both services (a) in general and (b) when such trusts have referred patients to private hospitals.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37056","37056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519202","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to raise awareness of World AIDS Day before 1 December 2016.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37075","37075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519203","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what specialist support is provided by his Department to vulnerable adults without family support.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37305","37305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519204","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS plans to make minoxidil available to women who have lost their hair.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37306","37306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519205","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with clinical bodies on the risks associated with continued use of steroids.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37308","37308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519206","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with clinical bodies on potential links between moderate alcohol consumption and levels of (a) heart disease and (b) breast cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37309","37309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519207","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been referred to the NHS for remedial treatments for scarring and pain after laser hair treatment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37304","37304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519208","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total expenditure by the NHS on HIV drugs was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37303","37303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519209","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many men have been diagnosed with psoriasis in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37307","37307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519210","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS uses hypnosis to improve dietary and exercise habits in children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37295","37295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519211","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of people with high blood pressure.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37296","37296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519212","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to encourage people to reduce the symptoms of diabetes using exercise and diet.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37294","37294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519213","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS plans to offer keyhole surgery for liver and colon cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37297","37297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519214","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Royal College of Midwives and the British Pregnancy Advisory Service on time limits for abortion.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37300","37300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519215","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in the UK in each age group were diagnosed with ADHD in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37301","37301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519216","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Ministers of his Department plan to attend the World Health Organisation Framework Convention on Tobacco Control in India in 2016.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37256","37256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519217","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which organisations will be represented in the UK delegation to the World Health Organisation Framework Convention on Tobacco Control in India in 2016.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37255","37255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519218","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to clinical commissioning groups on the storage and disposal of embryonic waste following IVF treatment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37267","37267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519219","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued to hospital trusts on the discharge of frail elderly patients.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37238","37238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519220","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adults on GP registers had been diagnosed with diabetes in (a) 2000 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37227","37227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519221","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many never events have been recorded in (a) Furness General Hospital and (b) Westmorland General Hospital in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37216","37216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519222","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to ask NHS England to publish the initial Sustainability and Transformation plans submitted on 15 April 2016 to permit scrutiny of those plans.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37280","37280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519223","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to assess the extent to which Sustainability and Transformation plans address (a) mental health provision in a locality and (b) the case for the integration of mental and physical health.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37278","37278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519224","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that engagement and consultation with key stakeholders, communities and local voluntary sector organisations is undertaken within each Sustainability and Transformation plan footprint prior to finalisation of those plans.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37279","37279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519225","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support innovation in assistive technology for use by people with dementia.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37186","37186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519226","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to (a) improve the provision of care for patients with lung disease and (b) increase funding for research into lung diseases.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37187","37187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519227","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's news story of 13 September 2015, entitled From 2020, people with suspected cancer will be diagnosed faster, by what date he expects tailored recovery packages to be available for (a) all cancer patients and (b) patients with rarer cancers.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37293","37293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519228","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a human rights charter for care homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37322","37322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519229","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what statutory reasons (a) a resident of a care home may be evicted and (b) a relative of a person in a care home may be banned from visiting; and what evidence must be provided in each such case.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37323","37323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519230","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many relatives have been banned from visiting family members resident in local authority-funded care homes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37324","37324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519231","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on forced evictions from care homes.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37327","37327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519232","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure uniformity of data available from different mental health service providers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37372","37372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519233","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the Mental Capacity Act 2005 has been found to have been wrongly applied to exclude a relative of a resident from visiting a care home.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37326","37326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519234","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of clinical commissioning groups increased their spending on children and young people's mental health as a proportion of their overall budget in 2015-16; and how many are forecast to increase such spending in 2016-17.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37373","37373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519235","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there is a team within his Department with specific responsibility for children and young people's mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37371","37371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519236","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 1 February 2016 to Question 24630, for what reasons the thematic review of how the mental health needs of children and young people in vulnerable groups have been addressed as part of the Local Transformation Plan analysis has not been published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37370","37370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519237","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department and its agencies and non-departmental public bodies spent on staff away days in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37423","37423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519238","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to extend the 28-day eviction notice period for care home residents.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37329","37329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519239","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures are in place to ensure that alternative accommodation is found for people evicted from a care home.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37328","37328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519240","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to publish a new tobacco control strategy in the next two months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37407","37407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519241","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the letter to him of 22 March 2016 from the hon. Member for Tottenham, whether he plans to meet with the hon. Member to discuss North Middlesex Hospital.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37438","37438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519242","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the provision of A&E services at North Middlesex Hospital.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37439","37439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519243","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the criteria is for which hospitals are listed as being supported by the Emergency Care Intensive Support Team.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37440","37440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519244","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals are listed as being supported by the Emergency Care Intensive Support Team.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37441","37441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519245","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the annual cost to the NHS of high-risk pregnancies caused by patients going abroad for IVF treatment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37486","37486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519246","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to consult on levels of bursaries and salary support for trainee clinical psychologists for the 2017-18 cohort.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37445","37445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519247","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure levels of bursaries and salary support for trainee clinical psychologists for the 2017-18 cohort are adequate to ensure a diverse future workforce.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37446","37446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519248","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the changes to junior doctors' contracts and NHS working patterns on hospices and other institutions providing end of life care.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37476","37476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519249","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the extent of the practice among clinical commissioning groups in England of offering only one fresh cycle of IVF treatment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37489","37489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519250","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that the workforce requirements for the delivery of the NHS England transformation plan can be met with qualified clinical psychologists within the five-year timescale of the plan.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37447","37447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519251","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to clinical commissioning groups on the storage and disposal of embryonic waste following IVF treatment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37488","37488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519252","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33135, on employment and support allowance: inflammatory bowel disease, how many new claimants there have been in this Parliament.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37490","37490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519253","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS bodies will authorise Sustainability and Transformation Plan footprints; what role NHS Improvement will play; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37450","37450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519254","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of agency costs as a proportion of the total nursing costs in each NHS (a) trust and (b) foundation trust in 2015-16.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37434","37434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519255","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has for a National Stroke Strategy after the end of the ten year strategy plan in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37404","37404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519256","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what legal costs (a) his Department and (b) NHS England have incurred to date in relation to decisions on access to (i) narcolepsy drugs, (ii) hepatitis C drugs and (iii) pre-exposure prophylaxis for HIV.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37421","37421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519257","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each NHS trust spent on cleaning services in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37425","37425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519258","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had with NICE on changes to its current methodology for evaluating new drugs.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37422","37422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519259","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS hospital trusts in England spent on cleaning services in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37426","37426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519260","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of childhood obesity on the development of musculoskeletal conditions.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37360","37360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519261","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government plans to take to address musculoskeletal conditions in its childhood obesity strategy.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37361","37361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519262","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rate of smoking is in England among people over the age of 18.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37408","37408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519263","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rate of smoking is in England for 15 year olds.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37409","37409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519264","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the prevalence of smoking among pregnant women.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37418","37418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519265","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent by the Cancer Drugs Fund in 2015-16; and how much that fund is estimated to spend in 2016-17.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37420","37420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519266","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each (a) NHS trust and (b) foundation trust has paid to his Department in repayment of public dividend capital of £25,000 or more provided by his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37526","37526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519267","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33537 on Sustainability and Transformation Plan footprints, how his Department defines a system control total; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37495","37495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519268","2016-05-23","Department for Education","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of variations in levels of provision of fertility treatment on (a) adoption uptake and (b) fostering services; and whether such variations are being considered by the Child Protection Taskforce.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37471","37471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519269","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has conducted on the level of compliance with NICE guidelines on fertility treatment by each clinical commissioning group in England in the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37472","37472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519270","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Royal College of General Practitioner's report entitled A blueprint for building the new deal for general practice in England, published in May 2015, if his Department will respond to the recommendations of that report on (a) necessary increases in the GP workforce and (b) the proportion of the NHS budget that should be invested in general practice.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37493","37493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519271","2016-05-23","Department of Health","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each (a) NHS trust and (b) foundation trust has paid to his Department in repayment of loans of £25,000 or more issued by his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37525","37525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519272","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff are employed in the Higher Education Audit Team; and what plans she has to change that number.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37513","37513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519273","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many take charge requests under the family unity provision of the Dublin III Regulation the UK has received for transfer from Greece in the last six months; how many such requests were accepted; and how many people so accepted have arrived in the UK.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37451","37451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519274","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's Written Statement of 21 April 2016, HCWS687, on refugees and resettlement, what (a) additional steps she has taken and (b) further steps she plans to take to implement and streamline the Dublin III Regulation process and to quickly identify children who qualify for family reunion across Europe.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37499","37499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519275","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether data gathered from border exit checks will enable her Department to distinguish between short and longer-term overstaying of visas.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37514","37514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519276","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to use data from border exit checks to estimate emigration from the UK.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37511","37511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519277","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what analysis she plans to undertake of the data gathered from border exit checks; and whether those checks will provide accurate data on emigration disaggregated by route.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37512","37512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519278","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish data gathered from border exit checks.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37509","37509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519279","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how her Department plans to publish data gathered from border exit checks.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37510","37510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519280","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK would lose access to the Prüm Convention in the event of a vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37455","37455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519281","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 20 April 2016 to Question 32851, on Asylum housing, how many and what proportion of properties were deemed compliant with contractual obligations following an inspection by (a) her Department and (b) providers in each (i) COMPASS region and (ii) contractual pay period in (A) 2014-15 and (B) 2015-16; and how many people were affected by faults identified from COMPASS inspections not being repaired within the contract timescales in each of those regions in each of those periods.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37350","37350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519282","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children have been reunited with their families in the UK in (a) the last five years and (b) the last year under (i) the EU Dublin III Regulation; (ii) part 11 of the UK immigration rules, (iii) any other parts of the UK immigration rules and (iv) under exceptional circumstances.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37351","37351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519283","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to accelerate the process of identifying and processing people who are eligible for family reunification transfers from Greece to other EU countries under the Dublin III Regulation in addition to the two UK experts already sent to Greece to support Greek immigration officials dealing with applications under Dublin III Regulation and a further one to be deployed in May.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37355","37355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519284","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of (a) trafficking in human beings and (b) forced labour were recorded by Humberside Police in each year from 2010 to 2015; in how many such cases prosecutions were brought; and what the outcomes were of those prosecutions.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37201","37201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519285","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that when a girl is identified as being at risk of female genital mutilation (FGM), frontline professionals are taking the steps outlined in the multi-agency statutory guidance on FGM.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37282","37282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519286","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish all of her Department's statistics on the incidents of (a) domestic violence and (b) dowry related abuse in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37200","37200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519287","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the UK Football Policing Unit has requested information from other EU member states on football banning orders and other data relevant to the safe policing of football matches in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37209","37209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519288","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police, emergency responders and other security and military personnel have been deployed from other EU member states to respond to emergencies and other security threats in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37208","37208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519289","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that all frontline professionals receive adequate training to pursue the steps outlined in multi-agency statutory guidance on female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37281","37281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519290","2016-05-25","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police raids in England, Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland resulted in potential victims of human trafficking being taken by the police to reception centres in each of the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37239","37239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519291","2016-05-25","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many potential victims of human trafficking were taken by the police to reception centres following police raids in the last year; what proportion of such potential victims volunteered to enter the National Referral Mechanism; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37240","37240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519292","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police staff have been deployed to (a) each region of the UK from other EU member states and (b) other EU member states from each region of the UK to police (i) football matches and (ii) other sporting events in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37235","37235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519293","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of her Department's officials are working on processing Dublin III asylum transfer requests; and what plans her Department has to increase the number of such staff.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37248","37248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519294","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to increase the resources available for the processing of Dublin III asylum transfer requests.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37249","37249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519295","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of her Department's full-time equivalent officials are seconded to (a) France, (b) Italy, (c) Greece and (d) any other EU country in order to identify and support Dublin III asylum transfer requests; and what plans her Department has to second further staff to identify and support such requests.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37247","37247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519296","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visas have been issued to Latvians who are categorised as non-citizens in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37269","37269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519297","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to simplify application and processing systems to expedite the processing of Dublin III asylum transfer requests.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37250","37250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519298","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the level of trends in (a) online and (b) telephone fraud in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37302","37302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519299","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many European Arrest Warrant surrenders (a) to and (b) from each UK law enforcement agency there have been in each year since 2010; and what type of offence each of those surrenders related to.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37288","37288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519300","2016-05-23","Home Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether all children in Calais with valid family reunion claims and the first 300 of those children identified as most at risk will be re-located to the UK in time for the start of the new school year in September 2016.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37021","37021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519301","2016-05-23","House of Commons Commission","2016-05-18","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will take steps to ensure that the Union flag is regularly flown from the existing flag pole on the premises at 14 Tothill Street.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37030","37030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519302","2016-05-23","House of Commons Commission","2016-05-18","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, when the Commission plans to reopen the main doors at St Stephen's Entrance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37105","37105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519303","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to encourage the promotion of LGBT rights through its work with recipients of UK aid.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37154","37154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519304","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes her Department provides to counter the use of rape and sexual violence as a weapon of war and subjugation.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37157","37157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519305","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if the Government will make a multi-year commitment which increases in real terms funding for education in humanitarian situations.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37033","37033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519306","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 15 April 2016 to Question 32928, what issues of prisoner payments were raised with the Palestinian Authority Finance Minister Bishara in September 2015; which prisoners were discussed with that Minister; and what representations she has received on reported payments made to Kifah and Ibrahim Ghanimat.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37018","37018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519307","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that the Education Cannot Wait fund for education in emergencies is monitored to ensure that (a) the funds are used for the purposes for which they are allocated and (b) those funds achieve the expected outcomes.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37029","37029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519308","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent representations her Department has made to the Israeli government on the demolition of Palestinian homes and property funded by the UK.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37231","37231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519309","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government plans to become a founding donor of the Education Cannot Wait fund for education in emergencies when it is launched at the World Humanitarian Summit 2016.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37286","37286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519310","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department plans to take to help ensure that the Education Cannot Wait fund for education in emergencies focuses on (a) girls, (b) children with disabilities and (c) other marginalised children.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37287","37287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519311","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure the Education Cannot Wait fund for education in emergencies focuses on the most marginalised children including girls and children with disabilities.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37348","37348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519312","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans the Government has to become a founding donor to the Education Cannot Wait fund for education in emergencies.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37349","37349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519313","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government plans to become a founding donor of the Education cannot wait fund for education in emergencies, at its launch at the World Humanitarian Summit.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37332","37332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519314","2016-05-23","Department for International Development","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with (a) Egyptian authorities and (b) other stakeholders on the implications for UK aid projects in Gaza of disconnection of power lines providing electricity into South Gaza by Egypt.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37480","37480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519315","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 11 May 2016 to Question 36152, which religious festivals prisoners were released on temporary licence to attend in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37515","37515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519316","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases relating to the (a) eviction of residents and (b) banning of guests in care homes have reached the High Court in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37325","37325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519317","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish the report evaluating the pilots of section 28 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37400","37400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519318","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to increase employment opportunities for people (a) on community sentences and (b) released from prison.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37199","37199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519319","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's consultation on fee proposals for grants of probate, whether the proposed fees will reflect the (a) actual cost of administration of the Probate Registries and (b) amount of time expended by staff in the Probate Registries.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37182","37182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519320","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's consultation on fee proposals for grants of probate, what safeguards his Department plans to provide to enable applications to be filed for grants of probate in respect of estates which do not have sufficient liquid funds to enable payment of the fee before a grant has been issued.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37183","37183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519321","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's consultation on fee proposals for grants of probate, how fee income in excess of the costs of providing the Probate Registries service will be used.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37270","37270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519322","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the guardianship of the property and affairs of missing people.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37272","37272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519323","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of (a) men and (b) women who were remanded in custody (i) before conviction and (ii) after conviction did not go on to receive a custodial sentence for each offence type in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37253","37253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519324","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) fast and (b) standard delivery pre-sentence reports were prepared for offenders with each band number of previous convictions in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37251","37251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519325","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders were (a) remanded in custody and (b) released on court bail after being charged with an offence of (i) common assault, (ii) actual bodily harm, (iii) grievous bodily harm and (iv) assault in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37252","37252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519326","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the petition entitled Introduce Helen's Law, published on the change.org website, what steps his Department is taking to encourage prisoners to reveal information about the crimes they have committed.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37031","37031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519327","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding has been received from the European Social Fund via the National Offender Management Service Co-Financing Organisation to help employer roadshows at HM Prison (a) Sudbury, (b) Drake Hall and (c) Wayland.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37067","37067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519328","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding has been received from the European Social Fund via the National Offender Management Service Co-Financing Organisation to help set up and finance The Employers' Forum for Reducing Re-offending.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37068","37068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519329","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding HM Young Offender Institution (a) Werrington, (b) Feltham and (c) Cookham Wood has received from the European Social Fund via the National Offender Management Service Co-Financing Organisation in each year since January 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37069","37069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519330","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding his Department has received from the European Social Fund to fund the National Offender Management Service Co-Financing Organisation in each year since January 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37070","37070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519331","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the total spend by the National Offender Management Service (NOMS) on projects to improve the employability of ex-offenders came from the European Social Fund via the NOMS Co-Financing Organisation in each year since January 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37057","37057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519332","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 13 January 2016 to Question 20908, on prisons: discipline, how many days were added in each prison establishment as a result of adjudications in 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37078","37078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519333","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answers of 25 January 2016 to Question 22862 and of 26 June 2015 to Question 2890, for what reasons additional days were added as a result of adjudications to sentences served by children under the age of 18 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37079","37079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519334","2016-05-23","Northern Ireland Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on the Common Travel Area of the UK voting to leave the EU.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37027","37027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519335","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the taper arrangements will be for the proposed phasing in of EU migrants' entitlement to in-work benefits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37077","37077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519336","2016-05-23","Prime Minister","2016-05-18","To ask the Prime Minister, how many of the leaflets entitled Why the Government believes that voting to remain in the European Union is the best decision for the UK, have been returned to (a) 10 Downing Street and (b) other Government departments; and what the postage cost to the Government has been of such returns.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37198","37198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519337","2016-05-23","Prime Minister","2016-05-18","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will visit Northern Ireland before 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37402","37402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519338","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many motorists were fined as a result of motorway average speed cameras in each year since 1985 for which figures are available; and how much was collected in fines in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37410","37410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519339","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have had with the Rail North Board.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37428","37428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519340","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how frequent the partnership meetings between his Department and Rail North are; and who represents his Department at those meetings.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37429","37429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519341","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who funds arrangements for the DFT Rail North Board meetings.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37430","37430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519342","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding the Government provides to Rail North.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37431","37431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519343","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made a decision on the proposed conversion of Class 801 Intercity Express Programme units to bi-mode diesel operation.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37456","37456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519344","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what account he plans to take of the construction of C-Series planes by Bombardier in Northern Ireland in any decision on London City Airport accommodating  C-Series or similar planes on its proposed new taxiway.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37444","37444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519345","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on bringing Crossrail 2 through Harrow and Wealdstone station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37485","37485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519346","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 12 May to Question 36842, on railways: franchises, whether the partnership referred to in that Answer has provided his Department with advice on mobilisation plans for franchises other than the Cross Country franchise since 1 November 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37535","37535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519347","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36052, on diesel vehicles: exhaust emissions, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of a pre-Euro 4 diesel scrappage scheme; how many vehicles in the UK were estimated to have been potentially eligible for a claim under such a scheme; and whether a benefit-cost ratio was calculated for that proposal.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37537","37537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519348","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what changes his Department has made to Govia Thameslink Railway Ltd's performance benchmarks under Schedule 7.1 of the Thameslink Southern and Great Northern franchise agreement since that agreement was signed.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37536","37536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519349","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether revenue risk on the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern franchise will be borne by the franchisee or the public purse in the event of industrial action.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37520","37520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519350","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 27 October 2015 to Question 13105, on cycling, if he will (a) update the table provided in that Answer to include the year 2015-16 and (b) provide a version of that table that excludes Cycle Ambition Cities funding from the regional breakdown of per capita spend.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37538","37538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519351","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding is allocated to motorcycling safety in his Department's budget for the current year.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37521","37521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519352","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of tunnelling between Darenth and South Ockenden as an option for the Lower Thames Crossing.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37232","37232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519353","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the performance of those train companies that scored low marks in the Office of Rail and Road's mystery shopping exercise on delay compensation, reported on in March 2016.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37076","37076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519354","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent by the Government on transport infrastructure projects nationally in 2011-12.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37163","37163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519355","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent by the Government on transport infrastructure projects nationally in 2013-14.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37164","37164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519356","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent by the Government on transport infrastructure projects nationally in 2012-13.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37165","37165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519357","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent by the Government on transport infrastructure projects nationally in 2014-15.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37166","37166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519358","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent by the Government on transport infrastructure projects nationally in 2015-16.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37167","37167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519359","2016-05-23","Department for Transport","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent by the Government on transport infrastructure projects nationally in 2010-11.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37162","37162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519360","2016-05-23","Women and Equalities","2016-05-18","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent steps she has taken to increase the number of women represented on the executive boards of FTSE 100 companies.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37143","37143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519361","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36333, on employment schemes, how much was spent on each of the programmes referred to in that Answer in the most recent financial year for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37112","37112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519362","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with the Canadian government on the uprating of pensions for UK citizens living in that country.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37086","37086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519363","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many ex-offenders have been helped into employment in each year since January 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37087","37087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519364","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 26 April 2016 to Question 35188, if he will estimate the cost of collecting information on the number of personal independence payment assessment appointments which are cancelled.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37155","37155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519365","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to reply to the letter of 15 March 2016 on wage insurance from the hon. Member for Birkenhead.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37135","37135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519366","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease who leased a Motability vehicle under disability living allowance were assessed as being ineligible for that vehicle under personal independence payment prior to any subsequent appeal.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37127","37127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519367","2016-05-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost is of a personal independence payment tribunal hearing.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37128","37128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519368","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease have been transferred from long-term disability living allowance to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37129","37129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519369","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons 60 per cent of appeals made in personal independence payment cases have resulted in the initial decision being overturned.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37130","37130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519370","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that the quality of service is consistent at jobcentres around the country.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37072","37072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519371","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the rate of take-up of carer's allowance; and what steps he is taking to improve that rate.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37081","37081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519372","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what consultations the Joint Work and Health Unit has undertaken with external groups on its work since its creation.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37093","37093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519373","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what workstreams have been established by the Joint Work and Health Unit; and when each such workstream is expected to report.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37094","37094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519374","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress the Joint Work and Health Unit has made on its priority of (a) productivity and growth in the economy, (b) halving the disability employment gap and (c) reducing health inequalities relating to gender, age and geographies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37095","37095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519375","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36280, how many people are waiting for a rearranged work capability assessment having had their initial appointment cancelled.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37213","37213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519376","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36280, for what reasons work capability assessments have been cancelled.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37214","37214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519377","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects to reply to the letter of 1 March 2016 from the Rt hon. Member for Birkenhead on the recommendations made by the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Hunger.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37215","37215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519378","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pieces of recording equipment are available in each region of the UK for the purposes of recording work capability assessments.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37212","37212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519379","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on potential mitigation measures for women that have witnessed an increase in their pensionable aged.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37192","37192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519380","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on potential mitigation measures for women that have witnessed an increase in their pensionable age.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37193","37193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519381","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number of people having to travel more than one hour to attend a jobcentre plus office in order to obtain a National Insurance number in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37202","37202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519382","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobcentre plus offices have been able to issue National Insurance numbers to new arrivals into the UK in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37203","37203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519383","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease who were assessed as being ineligible under personal independence payment for a Motability vehicle to which they were entitled under disability living allowance have had that decision overturned at (a) mandatory reconsideration and (b) appeal.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37206","37206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519384","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with which other EU countries the UK has a bilateral arrangement for the payment of annual uprating of pensions that would remain in force in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37274","37274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519385","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on what other OECD member states do not uprate the pensions of its pensioners living abroad; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37312","37312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519386","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what account his Department is taking of future levels of healthy life expectancy in making decisions on future levels of pension age.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37321","37321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519387","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will (a) review and (b) slow down the rate of increase in pensionable age for women.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37311","37311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519388","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants there were in Blackpool South constituency in (a) June 2015, (b) December 2015 and (c) the latest month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37492","37492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519389","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the progress that has been made in the rollout of universal credit in Northampton.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37415","37415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519390","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 8 December 2015 to Question 17583, on child maintenance, for what reason there is a difference between the estimated costs of (a) caseworker activity to review and update Child Support Agency (CSA) arrears and (b) establishing arrears on the CMS system set out in paragraph 93 of the Department's final impact assessment on CSA case closure, dated 10 April 2013, and those supplied in that Answer.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37474","37474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519391","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 13 April 2016 to Question 32812, whether the figures provided for sums to be spent annually and in total are additional to each other; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37473","37473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519392","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions has the personal independence payment (PIP) telephone has been unobtainable to the public in 2016; and how many people calling to enquire about PIP have been affected by those incidents.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37506","37506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519393","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of (a) disability living allowance and (b) personal independence payments have (i) lost or (ii) gained the higher rate mobility allowance since 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ronnie Campbell","Mr Ronnie Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37496","37496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519394","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many safety inspections the Health and Safety Executive carried out in the last year for which figures are available; and what estimate he has made of the number of such inspections the Executive will be able to make with the planned budget for 2019-20.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37427","37427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/519395","2016-05-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment the Health and Safety Executive has made of the effect of an ageing workforce on safety at work in the UK.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 37424","37424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/520960","2016-05-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the UK's influence in the world of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905061","905061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/520961","2016-05-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on peace and stability in Europe and around the world of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905058","905058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/520962","2016-05-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the strength of diplomatic and economic relations between India and the UK.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905056","905056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/520963","2016-05-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the UK's international and diplomatic relations.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905054","905054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/520964","2016-05-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, If he will make it his policy that the Scottish Government Minister with responsibility for fisheries will chair meetings of the Agriculture and Fisheries Council when the UK holds the presidency of the Council of the EU in 2017.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905060","905060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/520965","2016-05-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the UK's influence in the world of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905057","905057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521418","2016-05-25","Wales Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on the Swansea Bay tidal lagoon project.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905024","905024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/521419","2016-05-25","Wales Office","2016-05-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on the potential effect on Wales of plans to repeal the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905022","905022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518530","2016-05-12","Prime Minister","2016-05-11","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will clarify his recent remarks concerning Suliman Gani.","Biography information for Mr Keith Simpson","Mr Keith Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37017","37017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518374","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government made of the effectiveness of the insolvency system after the collapse of Comet in 2012; and what steps he has taken to improve that system.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36951","36951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518375","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the oral contribution of the then Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on 20 December 2012, Official Report, column 989, whether he plans to keep the opposition front bench updated on the Insolvency Service's investigation into BHS.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36970","36970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518376","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the oral contribution of the then Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on 20 December 2012, Official Report, column 989, for what reasons the Insolvency Service's investigation into Comet was not shared with the opposition front bench.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36971","36971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518377","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the oral contribution of the then Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on 20 December 2012, Official Report, column 989, if he will share the findings of the Insolvency Service's investigation into Comet with the opposition front bench.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36972","36972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518378","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Small Business, Industry and Enterprise on 9 May 2016, Official Report, column 442, what the addresses are of the 14 locations across which his Department's policy teams are spread.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36974","36974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518379","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many students studying social work in Lancashire are in receipt of a bursary.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36995","36995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518381","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the role of his Department is planned to be in implementing the recommendations of the Independent Review on Antimicrobial Resistance.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36988","36988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518382","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which British Overseas Territories and Crown dependencies have been invited to the UK Anti-Corruption Summit on 12 May 2016.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36986","36986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518383","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for (a) Health and (b) International Development on implementation of the Independent Review on Antimicrobial Resistance.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36987","36987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518384","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of Civil Service Fast Stream employees based in London complete a placement outside London.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36956","36956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518385","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Civil Contingencies Unit has made an assessment of the current levels of radioactive contamination existing in upland areas across the UK as a result of radioactive fallout in May 1986 following the Chernobyl nuclear accident in April 1986.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36950","36950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518386","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to ensure that private sector companies are responsible for their off-payroll workers who use personal service companies paying the correct amount of tax.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36952","36952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518387","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when Lifetime ISAs will be available to the public.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36953","36953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518388","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to offer public financial advice on Lifetime ISAs.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36954","36954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518389","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff at HM Revenue and Customs work on insolvency procedures.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37006","37006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518390","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs has received related to insolvency procedures in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37007","37007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518391","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his Department's policy that employees should be offered the choice of either auto-enrolment or paying into a Lifetime ISA as a means for saving for their pension, or that employees who wish to invest in a Lifetime ISA must do so in addition to auto-enrolment.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37003","37003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518392","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost was to HM Revenue and Customs related to insolvency procedures in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37008","37008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518393","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times HM Revenue and Customs has been a creditor in the last five years.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37009","37009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518394","2016-05-12","Department for Education","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much of the Dedicated Schools Grant allocated to Lancashire County Council was spent on Special Educational Needs support for children under five years old in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37002","37002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518395","2016-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33117, which programmes the reprioritisation of £100 million in capital funding to deliver low-cost second stage accommodation for rough sleepers will affect.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36975","36975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518396","2016-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which (a) communities and (b) projects will receive funding from the English Language scheme.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36983","36983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518397","2016-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the Housing and Planning Bill on housing associations that manage properties on behalf of councils.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36944","36944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518398","2016-05-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of the £1.7 billion funding for the Superfast Broadband Programme is from (a) central government (b) local government and (c) the EU.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36984","36984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518399","2016-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the purpose is of the training provided by the UK armed forces to the security and armed forces personnel of Burundi, Rwanda and the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36967","36967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518400","2016-05-12","Department for Education","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36326, what representations she has received from (a) schools and (b) trades union representatives on the ability of academy trusts to charge teachers for car parking services on school grounds; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36990","36990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518401","2016-05-12","Department for Education","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the total amount awarded to schools in pre-opening support grants in each month of the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36991","36991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518402","2016-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Children's Act 1989 to protect children from the effects of Parental Alienation syndrome and implacable hostility.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36978","36978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518403","2016-05-12","Department for Education","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Burnley and (b) Lancashire have an Education, Health and Care 0-25 years Special Educational Needs plan.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37005","37005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518404","2016-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policy on the building of a nuclear power plant at Hinkley Point C of the finding of the UN Economic and Social Council in the Report of the Implementation Committee on its thirty-fifth session, page 21, that the UK is in non-compliance with its obligations to examine the potential adverse transboundary impacts of an accident at any new nuclear plant constructed in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36948","36948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518405","2016-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the comparative particulate pollution created by (a) diesel and (b) electric cars.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36949","36949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518406","2016-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on British farming of the Plan for Public Procurement, published in July 2014.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36943","36943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518407","2016-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the financial value of pollinators to the economy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36981","36981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518408","2016-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the total (a) cost of monitoring and (b) number of full-time equivalent officials of her Department supporting the emergency authorisation period for neonicotinoid pesticides which expired on 20 November 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36980","36980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518409","2016-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to prevent atrocities, such as the Gatumba massacre, from taking place in Burundi.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36968","36968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518410","2016-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to formally encourage the Burundian government to play a greater role in the truth and reconciliation process in that country.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36969","36969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518412","2016-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the enactment of UN Security Council Resolution 2248 on Burundi, passed on 12 November 2015.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36957","36957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518413","2016-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the imposition of sanctions on the Burundian government.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36958","36958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518414","2016-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on progress in the Eastern African mediation process in relation to the crisis in Burundi; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36959","36959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518415","2016-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that Burundi implements the recommendations of the Arusha Accords.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36963","36963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518416","2016-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the change in constitution in Rwanda; and what assessment he has made of whether that change will effect the continued provision of UK diplomatic support to the Rwandan government.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36961","36961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518417","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of replacing the NHS bursary with student loans on the number of healthcare students; and what steps he is taking to (a) maintain and (b) increase the number of such students.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36985","36985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518418","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the NHS England consultation on a proposed method to support investment decisions in specialised commissioning launched on 12 April 2016 does not disadvantage potential treatments for rare diseases.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36977","36977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518419","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on reducing medical indemnity costs for GPs.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36992","36992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518420","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to increase the level of funding allocated  for staffing in GP practices.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36993","36993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518421","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vacancies the London Ambulance Service has for paramedics.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37013","37013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518422","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current average response times are for ambulances responding to C1 and C2 incidents.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37014","37014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518423","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulances are currently in service in London; and how many ambulances were in service in London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37012","37012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518424","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many allied health professionals are working in Lancashire.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36999","36999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518425","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many students in (a) the UK, (b) the North West and (c) Lancashire are studying for a clinical pharmacy diploma.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37000","37000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518426","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many students in Lancashire studying a clinical pharmacy diploma are in receipt of a bursary.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37001","37001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518427","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many social workers are working in Lancashire.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36996","36996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518428","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many students studying allied health professions in Lancashire are in receipt of an NHS bursary.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36997","36997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518429","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on NHS bursaries for (a) doctors, (b) nurses and midwives and (c) allied health professionals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36998","36998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518430","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many paramedics were employed by the London Ambulance Service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37016","37016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518431","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the target response times are for ambulances responding to C1 and C2 incidents.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37015","37015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518432","2016-05-12","Department of Health","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of pharmacies in the UK in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36982","36982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518433","2016-05-12","Home Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to extend the cross-government definition of domestic violence and abuse to include people under 16 years old.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36955","36955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518434","2016-05-12","Home Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect Rwandans residing in the UK from assassination.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36962","36962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518435","2016-05-12","Home Office","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36224, on proceeds of crime, how many reporters received no reply within seven working days following the first working day after the report was submitted; and by what statutory authority appropriate consent is given to reporters who do not receive a reply from the National Crime Agency within the seven day limit.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36973","36973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518436","2016-05-12","Department for International Development","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what conditionality in relation to governance and human rights is applied to aid to Rwanda.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36960","36960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518437","2016-05-12","Department for International Development","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support issuances of land titles and registration of land in Rwanda.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36965","36965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518438","2016-05-12","Department for International Development","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to encourage other nations to contribute bilateral donations to the Great Lakes regional appeal.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36966","36966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518439","2016-05-12","Department for International Development","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to support widows of genocide and conflict in Rwanda, Burundi and the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36964","36964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518440","2016-05-12","Department for International Development","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to develop a bilateral programme of aid for Burundi similar to programmes for Rwanda and the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36979","36979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518441","2016-05-12","Department for International Development","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure that the Education cannot wait: the fund for education in emergencies focuses on (a) girls, (b) children with disabilities and (c) other marginalised children.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37011","37011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518442","2016-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance is issued to family court judges on Parental Alienation syndrome and implacable hostility.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36976","36976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518443","2016-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the current total balance is of outstanding financial penalties imposed by courts.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36945","36945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518444","2016-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many financial penalties imposed by courts are currently outstanding.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36946","36946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518445","2016-05-12","Department for Transport","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fatalities have occurred on the railway network in Great Britain since 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ronnie Campbell","Mr Ronnie Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36947","36947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518446","2016-05-12","Department for Transport","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with Fred Olson cruise lines and his US counterparts on the welfare of passengers aboard MV Balmoral who have contracted norovirus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36942","36942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518447","2016-05-12","Department for Transport","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36423, whether the package of measures to mitigate the impact of Heathrow Airport expansion on local communities will relate to new as well as existing schools and hospitals.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36989","36989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518449","2016-05-12","Department for Transport","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many additional electric motorcycles his Department expects to register as a result of the introduction of the motorcycle plug-in scheme.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37010","37010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518450","2016-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much in supplementary payments he estimates will be paid to disability living allowance claimants in Northern Ireland refused personal independence payments on reassessment who successfully appeal that refusal in the next three years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37004","37004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518451","2016-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have decreased their working hours in order to remain eligible for the carers allowance since the introduction of the National Living Wage.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36994","36994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518138","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 4 May 2016 to Question 36124, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the apprenticeship levy on apprenticeship completion rates.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36793","36793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518139","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when officials of his Department last met with representatives of the devolved administrations to discuss (a) how the apprenticeship levy will operate and (b) the proportion of the apprenticeship levy that each of the devolved administrations will receive.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36819","36819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518140","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the Government's policy is on whether an employer with an annual pay bill of under £3 million will be liable to pay the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36820","36820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518141","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with higher education institutions about the potential effect of changes in the level of university teaching staff on casual employment contracts on the quality of teaching.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36885","36885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518142","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff were employed on (a) fixed-term and (b) atypical contracts at UK universities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36886","36886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518143","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answers of 16 February 2016 to Question 26010 and 11 April 2016 to Question 32109, when he now plans to establish a reading room for hon. Members to access Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership documents.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36887","36887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518144","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what measures the Government has (a) planned and (b) implemented to monitor the effects of abolishing student maintenance grants on students that the equality impact analysis identified would be disproportionately affected by that policy.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36932","36932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518145","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, from which academic year the Government plans that a Sharia-compliant student loan will be available for Muslim students.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36933","36933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518146","2016-05-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to increase British trade with Mexico.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36924","36924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518147","2016-05-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to reduce the reliance of universities on state funding.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36925","36925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518148","2016-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Government plans to introduce a Sharia-compliant Takaful alternative finance product for students unable to access 24+ Advanced Learning Loans as well as for students undertaking higher education courses.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36934","36934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518149","2016-05-12","Department for Education","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures she plans to take to support further education students with additional travel costs arising from mergers of institutions as a result of area reviews of post-16 education.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36936","36936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518150","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 May 2016 to Question 35770, what technical and practical barriers will prevent the Electoral Commission implementing a registration look-up tool before the EU referendum.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36913","36913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518151","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a list of people who attended the Anti-Corruption Summit on 12 May 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36906","36906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518152","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to ensure that the commitments made at the Anti-Corruption Summit (a) are ambitious, (b) are specific, (c) include a timeframe for implementation and (d) are enforceable.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36904","36904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518153","2016-05-11","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a list of the commitments negotiated at the Anti-Corruption Summit of 12 May 2016 after that summit has taken place.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36878","36878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518154","2016-05-11","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, who sits on the Inter-Ministerial Group on Corruption.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36880","36880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518155","2016-05-11","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the budget is for the Inter-Ministerial Group on Corruption.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36881","36881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518156","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36373, which overseas territories and Crown dependencies have declined the invitation to attend the Anti-Corruption Summit on 12 May 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36902","36902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518157","2016-05-11","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many 16 and 17 year olds from (a) West Midlands and (b) Birmingham Yardley have participated in the National Citizen Service in each year since it was piloted in 2011.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36805","36805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518158","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many homicides were recorded by police in (a) Merseyside and (b) St Helens in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013, (v) 2014 and (vi) 2015.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36816","36816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518159","2016-05-11","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many public procurement contracts were won by small and medium-sized businesses in North West Norfolk in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36849","36849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518160","2016-05-11","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many small and medium-sized businesses in North West Norfolk placed a bid on a public contract in the last two years.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36850","36850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518161","2016-05-12","Cabinet Office","2016-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) the cost to the public purse has been of and (b) advice he has sought or received from the Electoral Commission on Government plans to promote public awareness of the (i) forthcoming EU referendum and (ii) need for timely registration in order to participate in that referendum.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36782","36782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518162","2016-05-11","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department last conducted a review of the Alternative Fuels Framework.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36851","36851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518163","2016-05-11","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which transport emissions are factored into the assessment of fuels within the Alternative Fuels Framework.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36852","36852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518164","2016-05-11","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the latest assessment of liquefied petroleum gas within the Alternative Fuels Framework.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36853","36853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518165","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the tax gap was for (a) income tax, (b) national insurance contributions and (c) capital gains tax in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36833","36833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518166","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to set target levels of reformulation for soft drinks manufacturers under the soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36826","36826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518167","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will include a time limit in the terms of the soft drinks industry levy such that that levy would cease to apply if reformulation targets are met by soft drinks manufacturers.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36827","36827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518168","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what timeline he has set for all multinational companies operating in the UK to publish country-by-country reporting; and how that requirement will be enforced.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36903","36903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518169","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the proportion of gross income of the top one per cent income bracket which people in that bracket paid in (a) direct and (b) indirect tax in the most recent financial year for which data is available; and what proportion those sums are of gross national income in that same period.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36884","36884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518170","2016-05-12","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that UK corporate tax rules do not incentivise companies to avoid tax in developing countries.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36905","36905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518171","2016-05-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects Louise Casey's review of opportunity and integration in isolated and deprived communities to be (a) completed and (b) published.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36808","36808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518172","2016-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 May 2016 to Question 36169, how many taxi journeys his Department paid for in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36789","36789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518173","2016-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of what the likely change in the level of social housing stock will be if the proposed extension of right-to-buy to housing association properties is agreed in (a) Tottenham, (b) Enfield, (c) Haringey, (d) Barnet, (e) Islington and (f) London in (i) 2016 and (ii) each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36790","36790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518174","2016-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of affordable starter homes that will be built in (a) Tottenham, (b) Islington, (c) Barnet, (d) Haringey, (e) Enfield and (f) London in (i) 2016 and (ii) each of the next four years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36791","36791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518175","2016-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the average price of affordable starter homes that will be built in (a) Tottenham, (b) Islington, (c) Barnet, (d) Haringey, (e) Enfield and (f) London in (i) 2016 and (ii) each of the next four years.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36792","36792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518176","2016-05-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of (a) regional development funds and (b) structural funds that the UK is due to receive in each year to 2020 under the current EU Multi-Annual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36753","36753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518177","2016-05-11","HM Treasury","2016-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding the UK is due to receive in each year to 2030 of (a) regional development funds and (b) structural funds under future EU multi-annual financial frameworks.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36754","36754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518178","2016-05-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish responses to the Broadband Universal Service Obligation consultation.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36781","36781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/518179","2016-05-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many and what proportion of named day written parliamentary questions have been answered after the specified date by each Minister in his Department since May 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 36809","36809"
