"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903902","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of expanding the family reunion scheme for Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143618","143618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903903","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of female councillors in England.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143818","143818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903905","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative estimate he has made of the apprenticeship uptake in Greater Manchester in (a) the last twelve months and (b) the previous three years.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143819","143819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903906","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department plans to provide to Jobcentre Plus employees affected by the closure of Shop Direct centres in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143820","143820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903907","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a breakdown by local authority of the £50 million brownfield land fund for Greater Manchester announced at the end of March 2018.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143821","143821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903908","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for UK policy of the recent attacks by the Government of Sudan in the Jebel Marra region of Darfur.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143755","143755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903909","2018-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which EU (a) networks, (b) information systems and (c) databases his Department expects to  (i) lose access to and (ii) pay to be part of and (iii) replicate after the UK has left the EU; and what assessment his Department has made of the cost of (A) paying for access and (B) replicating those systems.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143619","143619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903910","2018-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the number of people who had work that they consider defective completed by the Mark Group under the Green Deal.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143810","143810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903911","2018-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people who had work that they consider defective undertaken in their homes by the Mark Group under the Green Deal are (a) compensated and (b) able to remedy the resulting problems.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143811","143811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903912","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many drivers have had their licences revoked as a result of having failed an eye test in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143803","143803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903914","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that all women (a) aged up to 72, and (b) who missed their final screening appointment will be able to access mammogram services within six months.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143620","143620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903915","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of people working as private tutors for (a) primary and (b) secondary school aged children.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143804","143804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903916","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the revocation of the Director of Human Rights Watch Israel and Palestine, Omar Shakir’s work permit.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143731","143731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903918","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish a response to each question in the Schools that work for everyone consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143790","143790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903919","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the Government selecting a non-UK based supplier for a deployable long range air-defence radar on the commercial viability of UK based companies seeking to export the commander radar.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143866","143866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903920","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans are in place to encourage the uptake of diagnostics in diabetes.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143789","143789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903922","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2018 to Question 123474, what the timetable is for the publication of the mental health pathways for crisis care, perinatal mental health, children and young people's mental health and acute mental health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143690","143690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903923","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Bangladesh Government to ensure the fair and equal treatment of political parties in that country's forthcoming elections.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143663","143663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903924","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Bangladeshi counterpart on the imprisonment of the leader of the main opposition party in that country.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143664","143664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903925","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the assessment he has made of the potential effect of discussions at the April 2018 Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in London on the forthcoming elections in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143665","143665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903927","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the efficient and timely transfer of prisoners to hospitals under the Mental Health Act 1983; and how many prisoners have waited for more than 14 days for such a transfer in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143749","143749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903928","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of in-patients in mental health units have been sectioned under the Mental Health Act 1983 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143750","143750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903929","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of staffing levels at places of safety under the Mental Health Act 1983 in England in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143751","143751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903930","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have had their housing support terminated as a result of a failed asylum claim in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) Liverpool City Region, (d) Merseyside and (e) England in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143752","143752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903932","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people that used self-employed status to avoid paying child maintenance payments in 2017.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143850","143850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903933","2018-05-17","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-14","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how much the House of Commons spent on (a) disposable cups, (b) disposable food containers and (c) disposable cutlery in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143830","143830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903934","2018-05-17","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-14","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what proportion of disposable (a) cups, (b) food containers and (c) cutlery used on the parliamentary estate is recycled.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143831","143831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903935","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Written Ministerial Statement of 11 May 2018 on Good School Places, HCWS676, what criteria his Department will use to assess (a) demand for places and (b) the requirement to raise school standards.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143826","143826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903937","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Written Ministerial Statement of 11 May 2018 on Good School Places, HCWS676, what proportion of schools approved in Wave 13 are located in the Government’s Opportunity Areas.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143827","143827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903938","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to answer Questions 136372, 136373, 136374 and 136376 tabled on 18 April 2018 by the hon. Member for Tottenham.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143636","143636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903939","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people that declared themselves as self-employed were found to be have employee status in 2017.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143851","143851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903940","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Academy Trusts reported a severe financial deficit to the Education and Skills Funding Agency in financial year 2018-19.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143828","143828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903941","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many motorcyclists were (a) injured and (b) killed on roads in 2017.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143852","143852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903942","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Academy Trusts have received emergency funding from the Education and Skills Funding Agency in the current financial year; and the total amount of emergency funding that was allocated.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143829","143829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903944","2018-05-16","Scotland Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much match-funding allocated by the Government the Scottish government has not received as a result of that government not meeting its 5 core economic targets.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143853","143853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903945","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to reply to the letter of Wednesday 18 April 2018 from the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle on the tier 4 CAHMS inpatient unit in Hull.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143864","143864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903946","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to encourage people to transition from conventionally fuelled to electric cars.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143740","143740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903947","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 May 2018 to Question 140051 on Cycling: Rural Areas, how much of the £1.2 billion of funding available for cycling and walking has been allocated to Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143741","143741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903948","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of non-EU nationals who are in the UK having entered on a false EU (a) passport or (b) identity document.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143710","143710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903949","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 May 2018 to Question 140051 on Cycling: Rural Areas, how much of the £1.2 billion of funding available for cycling and walking has been allocated.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143742","143742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903951","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2018 to Question 140056 on Universal Credit: Easington, what data his Department collects on individual claims for (a) Universal Credit and (b) Mandatory Reconsiderations.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143743","143743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903952","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for (a) personal independence payment, b) employment and support allowance and c) universal credit (limited capability for work related activity element) were determined by paper assessment only in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143744","143744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903953","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the timetable for the introduction of the additional qualified informants for Death Certification provided for in the Coroners and Justice Act 2009.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143745","143745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903954","2018-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to establish a statutory period of parental leave for bereaved parents whose children have experienced birth complications or post-natal incidents.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143854","143854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903955","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will make an assessment of the adequacy of the level of local authority early years funding rates in advance of the start of the next school year.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143666","143666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903956","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to provide business rates relief to childcare providers.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143667","143667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903957","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what support his Department provides to micro businesses to manage their business rates.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143668","143668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903959","2018-05-16","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a rent recognition database to be regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143855","143855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903960","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the help-to-buy to scheme to people purchasing house boats as their main residence.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143856","143856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903961","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings he has had with small business owners in the childcare sector in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143669","143669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903962","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which NHS Trusts met their A&E winter pressure targets over the last winter period.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143857","143857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903963","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will made an assessment of the potential merits of deploying canine detection units at Post Office depots to detect the shipment of drugs from online vendors.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143858","143858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903965","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed  Guangzhou-Shenzhen-Hong Kong Express Rail Link Bill on (a) British citizens residing in Hong Kong, (b) Hong Kong civil society and (c) the principle of one country two systems.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143649","143649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903966","2018-05-16","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will publish the guidance on protocol for members of the Irish Government visiting in an official capacity (a) Northern Ireland and (b) other parts of the UK .","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143859","143859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903967","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 136295 on Children’s Centres: Closures, what assessment has been made of the potential merits of requiring local authorities to report children’s centre closures in real time.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143822","143822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903968","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of removing British citizenship from people convicted of serious crimes who obtained British citizenship as a second nationality.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143860","143860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903969","2018-05-16","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the HM Revenue and Customs press release of 9 May 2018, 200,000 receive back pay as HMRC enforces National Minimum Wage, how much of the £15.6 million of minimum wage arrears identified in 2017-18 was identified through self-correction by employers; and how many of those 200,000 people those arrears self-corrected by employers relate to.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143732","143732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903970","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of children in families with the legal right to remain in the UK with an attached no recourse to public funds condition on their leave to remain who are unable to access free school meals; and what plans the Government has to review the policy and practice in those circumstances.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143733","143733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903971","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools have closed in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143670","143670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903972","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ban landlords with convictions for serious offences from renting out their property.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143861","143861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903974","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve the support provided to children in need.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143759","143759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903975","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve the outcomes of children in need.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143760","143760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903976","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing transition support for children in need.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143761","143761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903977","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to encourage the establishment of Combined Cadet Force units in state schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143824","143824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903979","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress is being made in tackling county lines criminal activity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143825","143825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903980","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what time timetable for the agenda of the next meeting of the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation to be published is.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143696","143696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903981","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Sudan economic factsheet published by his Department on 26 April 2018, what proportion of the budget of the Government of Sudan has been allocated to the military in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143643","143643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903982","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Sudan economic factsheet published by his Department on 26 April 2018, what estimate he has made of the level of military spending in Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143644","143644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903983","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made representations to Sudanese Government on the death sentence of Noura Hussein.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143645","143645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903985","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government raised during the latest round of the UK-Sudan Strategic Dialogue in Khartoum the attack of 22 April 2018 made by the Government of Sudan in the Jebel Marra region in Darfur.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143646","143646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903986","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is her policy that EU citizens who have indefinite leave to remain will have to apply for settled status.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143621","143621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903987","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of trains that were supposed to stop at Plumpton but did not do so between 1 January and May 1 2018.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143806","143806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903988","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement of 10 May 2018, HCWS674 on Immigration, if he will make is his policy that information in response to the call for evidence to inform design of the compensation scheme will not (a) be used for the purposes of immigration enforcement and (b) affect access to welfare benefits.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143734","143734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903989","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if his Department will publish an immigration white paper before the Migration Advisory Committee's final report on the effect on the UK labour market of the UK’s exit from the European Union is published.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143763","143763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903990","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged between 16 and 24 in Wales have been in receipt of Job Seeker’s Allowance in each of the last five years; and if she will provide that same data by region.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143812","143812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903991","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, by what methods a prisoner who is either serving a sentence or on remand in a private sector jail in (a) England and (b) Wales can complain about their health treatment.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143813","143813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903992","2018-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the prison population in England and Wales was for the most recent date for which information is available; and how many of those prisoners were formerly members of the armed forces.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143814","143814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903993","2018-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prisoners who are serving a sentence or on remand in England and Wales who had previously served in (a) the British Army, (b) the Royal Navy and (c) the Royal Air Force for the most recent date for which information is available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143815","143815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903994","2018-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prisoners  who had joined the armed forces aged 17 years or under for the most recent period for which information is available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143816","143816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903995","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 May 2018 to Question 141912 on Pupils: Hyperactivity, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the (a) approach and (b) guidelines in place to assist and support pupils who have ADHD.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143877","143877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903997","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with the Government of Nigeria the case of Bridget Agbahime who was murdered by on 2 June 2016 to seek to ensure the perpetrators are prosecuted.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143766","143766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903998","2018-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to improve the habitats of curlew birds.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143767","143767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/903999","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of women in the UK have had a mental illness during pregnancy in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143768","143768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904001","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many account managers there are in his Department.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143660","143660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904002","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had and with whom on connections between old age depression and memory loss.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143769","143769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904003","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British Embassy sites the Government has sold since 2009.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143661","143661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904005","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to improve UK relations with the Islamic Republic of Iran.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143652","143652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904006","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the new Malaysian Prime Minister.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143770","143770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904007","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Government of Saudi Arabia on the rights of lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender people in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143653","143653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904009","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of Myanmar on recent attacks on Christians in Kachin in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143689","143689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904010","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to enable women's frozen eggs to be kept for longer periods of time.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143771","143771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904011","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much has accrued to the public purse from the sale of British Embassy premises since 2010.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143662","143662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904012","2018-05-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for the Financial Reporting Council to (a) complete its review and (b) publish an updated version of the UK Corporate Governance Code.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143650","143650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904013","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the World Health Organisation on Taiwan’s non-participation in the World Health Assembly later this month.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143672","143672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904014","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Director-General of the World Health Organisation on facilitating Taiwan being an observer at the 2018 World Health Assembly.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143673","143673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904016","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with shingles in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143772","143772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904017","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people diagnosed with shingles have developed eyesight problems in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143773","143773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904018","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to help restore democracy to Libya.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143774","143774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904019","2018-05-16","Department for International Development","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is giving Libya in terms of medical and food aid.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143775","143775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904021","2018-05-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much money raised from the tampon tax has been allocated to BAME women's organisations since 2016.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143654","143654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904022","2018-05-17","Department for International Development","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that the United Nations Relief and Works Agency for Palestine Refugees in the Near East has adequate funding for the 2018 annual Children's Summer Camp in Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143655","143655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904023","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to shorten the approval process time for treatments that are not selected for the accelerated access pathway.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143872","143872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904024","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to make an assessment of the effectiveness of the accelerated access pathway to enable access to new, innovative medicines.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143873","143873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904026","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to Clinical Commissioning Groups of providing salary support for Improving Access to Psychological Therapies trainees in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20 and (c) 2020-21.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143715","143715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904027","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Five Year Forward View, published in October 2014, what steps he is taking to ensure Clinical Commissioning Groups meet the expansion plans for national Improving Access to Psychological Therapies.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143716","143716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904028","2018-05-16","Department for International Development","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment has made of the humanitarian situation in South Sudan, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143656","143656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904030","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to allocate funding for the training of (a) clinical psychologists and (b) child and adolescent psychotherapists after September 2019.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143717","143717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904031","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the targets set in the Five Year Forward View, published in October 2014, and Health Education England’s Stepping forward to 2020-21: The mental health workforce plan for England, published in July 2017, how many additional psychological therapists are working in Improving Access to Psychological Therapies services as of May 2018 compared to September 2016.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143718","143718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904032","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of (a) fees, (b) facilitation costs and (c) enabling works for High Speed 2 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143657","143657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904033","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) his Department and (b) NHS England plans to undertake a review of the outcomes of decision support tool assessments to ensure that eligibility decisions made are lawful and in line with the provisions of the Care Act 2014 and the Coughlan and Grogan court judgments.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143691","143691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904035","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the pupil to teacher ratio is in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in (A) the West Midlands and (B) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143658","143658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904036","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page six of the Thirty-Ninth report of the Public Accounts Committee, the Equipment Plan 2017- 27, HC880, what steps he is taking to improve his Department’s accountability to Parliament.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143697","143697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904037","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to publish its response to the Modernising Defence Programme consultation before it publishes the Modernising Defence Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143698","143698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904038","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many university places were awarded to people with refugee status in the UK in each year between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143659","143659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904039","2018-05-16","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households in (a) UK, (b) Wales, and (c) Aberavon constituency are subject to the high income child benefit tax charge.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143795","143795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904040","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much responsibility a Government Local Plan Inspector has for identifying the soundness of a Local Plan.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143713","143713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904041","2018-05-16","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the high income child benefit tax charge.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143796","143796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904042","2018-05-16","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue has accrued to the public purse under the child benefit tax charge.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143797","143797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904044","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the (a) mechanisms for challenging and (b) processes for appealing against the decisions of a Government Local Plan Inspector are; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143714","143714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904045","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on the provision of statutory services for children by local authorities.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143746","143746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904046","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness with which local authorities are discharging their statutory duties to children.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143747","143747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904047","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will assess the effectiveness of the way in which local authorities are funded to provide statutory services to children.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143748","143748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904048","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to stimulate and facilitate high-quality research into chronic fatigue syndrome.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143805","143805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904049","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to extend the remit of the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority to social care.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143622","143622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904051","2018-05-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to improve the advice for care workers on gov.uk to help them check employers' compliance with minimum wage obligations.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143623","143623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904052","2018-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of young people sentenced in each sentencing court of (a) the Crown Court and (b) magistrates' courts for (i) less than 6 months and (ii) more than 6 months of custody in the North Wales Police Force Area in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143679","143679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904053","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to improve the advice provided for care workers on tax relief for travel expenses.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143624","143624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904054","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to ensure that universal credit claimants are aware that they are entitled to deduct expenses when stating their income.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143625","143625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904056","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to ensure care workers whose income is too low to trigger auto-enrolment know the advantages of opting in to pension saving.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143626","143626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904057","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who had an earnings deduction order for child maintenance subsequently lost their jobs and claimed job seeker's allowance in 2016 -17.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143692","143692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904059","2018-05-16","Women and Equalities","2018-05-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to ensure people who have autism are given equal opportunities in employment.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143720","143720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904060","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has any plans to increase the time pupils participate in physical education.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143721","143721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904061","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to prevent cheating in examinations.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143722","143722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904062","2018-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require all animal owners to hold a licence to own an animal.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143723","143723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904063","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department provides on safety measures on farms.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143724","143724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904065","2018-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on home nation sports events being televised on free-to-air television.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143725","143725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904066","2018-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to encourage sports clubs to have disability teams.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143726","143726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904067","2018-05-16","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings has she had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on the customs union since that Department's establishment.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143727","143727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904068","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to recruit new soldiers into the armed forces.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143728","143728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904069","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officers from the Territorial Army were deployed on a tour of duty in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143729","143729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904070","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work coaches have been allocated within her department to assist universal credit claimants in each month of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143674","143674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904071","2018-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities to roll out recycling bins on streets.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143758","143758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904073","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will take steps to help taxi drivers who have been affected by the bankruptcy of Alpha Insurance to seek (a) reimbursement and (b) alternative insurance providers.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143627","143627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904074","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many additional school places have been created in (a) North Swindon constituency and (b) Swindon Borough Council in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143762","143762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904075","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 14th May 2018 to Question 141013 on Official Cars, how many times the Chief Medical Officer has used an official car and driver in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143711","143711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904076","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Bahraini counterpart on the continued use of the death penalty in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143802","143802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904078","2018-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the levels of crowd violence at horse racing meetings in 2018.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143737","143737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904079","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests have been made at each Horse Racing racecourse in 2018; and for what offences those arrests were made.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143738","143738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904080","2018-05-17","Department for International Trade","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that UK businesses trading with Iran are protected from the imposition of US extraterritorial sanctions in relation to that country.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143840","143840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904081","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members there have been of the Joint Cyber Reserve in each year since it was launched; and how people have expressed an interest in joining the Joint Cyber Reserve in that same period.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143699","143699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904082","2018-05-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the implementation of the General Data Protection Regulation on (a) nuisance calls and (b) the ability of nuisance callers to retain and share personal data.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143875","143875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904084","2018-05-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the implementation of the General Data Protection Regulation on the level of cold calling from (a) inside and (b) outside the EU.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143876","143876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904085","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Summary Report for the Commission on Gangs and Violence: Uniting to Improve Safety by Reverend Dr Carver Anderson, published in November 2017, what steps he is taking to implement the recommendations in that report.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143687","143687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904086","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an estimate of the financial effect of the proposed NHS pay increases on voluntary sector hospices.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143688","143688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904088","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role the Armed Forces played in response to the (a) Parliament and (b) Wannacry cyber attacks in 2017.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143700","143700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904089","2018-05-16","Department for International Development","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce income and wealth inequality in partner countries.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143832","143832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904090","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that personal independence payment assessments are undertaken fairly and efficiently.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143833","143833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904092","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of recent trends in the average levels of household debt of people in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143834","143834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904093","2018-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the inter-ministerial group on healthy living has held its first meeting.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143776","143776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904094","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of recent trends in the number of in-work households living in poverty.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143835","143835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904096","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the proposed closures of jobcentres on local communities in Scotland.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143836","143836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904097","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to bring forward legislative proposals to strengthen maternity protections for women with (a) casual and (b) zero hours employment contracts.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143837","143837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904098","2018-05-17","Cabinet Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Ministers are members of the National Security Council ministerial sub-committee on matters relating to cyber programmes and policy development.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143701","143701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904099","2018-05-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when the Government plans to publish its funding scheme to compensate owners of equipment affected by the clearing of the 700 MHz band of radio spectrum for mobile network operators.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143799","143799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904100","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Department has made an assessment of the effect of the NHS surcharge for non-EEA migrants on the recruitment and retention of non-EEA NHS staff.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143800","143800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904101","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department will make an estimate the cost of a waiver on the NHS surcharge for non-EEA citizens working in the NHS.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143801","143801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904103","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason additional resources have not been provided to the Independent Case Examiner to ensure that complaints made by WASPI women and all others are allocated and processed in a timely manner; and if the Government will provide such resources.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143651","143651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904104","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to provide for the treatment of children and young people who are already (a) overweight, (b) obese and (c) severely obese.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143874","143874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904105","2018-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on the inclusion of support for the aerospace sector in the Tay Cities Deal.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143842","143842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904107","2018-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's policy is on the establishment of UK-wide frameworks for agriculture after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143843","143843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904109","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to prepare for the merger of the Scottish Division of British Transport Police with Police Scotland.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143844","143844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904110","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has determined whether Northern rail have breached the terms of their contract for the Lakes line in Cumbria.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143719","143719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904112","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish his Department’s (a) guidance and (b) charging policy for the provision of Hormone Replacement Therapy by NHS Trusts.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143647","143647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904113","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of accidental fires in England and Wales were caused by faulty appliances and leads in each of the last last ten years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143680","143680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904114","2018-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) powered rescue boats, (b) non-powered rescue boats, (c) wading teams, (d) water incident managers, and (e) high volume pumps have been purchased by fire services in England through Government grants in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143681","143681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904115","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made on the amount spent by each local authority on temporary accommodation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143682","143682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904117","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average length of stay for people placed in temporary accommodation in each local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143683","143683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904118","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the interpretation by NHS England of NICE guidance on the level of provision of Ibrutinib for patients with chronic lymphocytic leukaemia.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143739","143739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904119","2018-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) legislation and (b) regulations govern the UK government’s ability to provide match funding for European Maritime and Fisheries Fund projects; and  whether those rules apply to his Department's executive agencies in the same way as his Department.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143756","143756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904121","2018-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the rules governing match funding contributions by the UK Government and the Devolved Administrations to European Maritime and Fisheries Fund projects are required to be applied in the same way in (a) England, (b) Scotland and (c) Wales.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143757","143757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904122","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train journeys have been delayed because of fallen trees or leaves on the line by train operating company in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143648","143648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904123","2018-05-16","Department for International Trade","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he had at the most recent Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting on the effect of Economic Partnership Agreements on developing countries in the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143838","143838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904124","2018-05-16","Cabinet Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that appointments to the Grenfell Tower inquiry panel have the confidence of survivors and bereaved families.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143839","143839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904125","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC has undertaken an investigation into the company agent that formed (a) Augela Systems LLP, (b) PR-Vert system Ltd and (c) Ronida Invest Ltd, all of which  have a registered office at Cornwall Buildings, 45-51 Newhall Street, Office 330, Birmingham, B3 3QR, in relation to allegations of money laundering as a result of records obtained by the Organised Crime and Corruption Reporting Project.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143868","143868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904127","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC has undertaken an investigation into the company agent that formed Griden Developments Ltd, which had, a registered office at 22 Brondesbury Park, London, England, NW6 7DL, in relation to accusations of money laundering as a result of records obtained by the Organised Crime and Corruption Reporting Project.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143869","143869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904128","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC has undertaken an investigation of the company agent that formed Valemont Properties Ltd, which had a registered office at International House 221 Bow Road, London, E3 2SJ, in relation to allegations of money laundering as a result of records obtained by the Organised Crime and Corruption Reporting Project.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143870","143870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904129","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HMRC has undertaken an investigation into the company agent that formed Tenby Services Ltd which had a registered office at International 145-157 St. John Street, London, EC1V 4PW, in relation to allegations of money laundering as a result of records obtained by the Organised Crime and Corruption Reporting Project.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143871","143871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904130","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in response to the Answer of 14 May 2018 to Question 141018 on Bangladesh: Politics and Government, what representations his Department has made to the Government of Bangladesh oh ensuring protections are put in place for voter safety during the upcoming election to encourage participation.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143712","143712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904132","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the implementation of the Homelessness Reduction Act 2017 on the prevention of homelessness.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143675","143675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904133","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Airbus (a) H135 and (b) H145 helicopters his Department has purchased for use as training aircraft.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143693","143693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904134","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the maximum number of trainees is that can be accommodated in an Airbus (a) H135 and (b) H145 helicopter.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143694","143694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904135","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many training flights his Department has purchased from Ascent Flight Training.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143695","143695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904136","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on consumers in England of (a) recent and (b) forthcoming RBS bank branch closures.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143764","143764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904138","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 May 2018 to Question 138993 on Schools: Finance, if he will publish the 19 local authorities that submitted disapplication notices to transfer more than 0.5 per cent of their block funding for schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143791","143791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904139","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer 10 May 2018 to Question 138993 on Schools: Finance, in how many of those nineteen cases he has made a decision; and what the decision was in each case.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143792","143792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904140","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 May 2018 to Question 138993 on Schools: Finance, how much each local authority has asked permission to transfer (a) in cash terms and (b) as a proportion of their block funding for schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143793","143793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904141","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 May 2018 to Question 138993 on Schools: Finance, if he will to publish the decisions made by his Department on applications from local authorities to transfer more than 0.5 per cent of their schools'block funding.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143794","143794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904142","2018-05-17","Department for International Trade","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many staff in his Department were posted to each country for the purposes of promoting trade with the UK since his Department was established; and  what estimate he has made of the number of staff in his Department that will be posted to each country in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143765","143765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904144","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pieces of correspondence her Department has received from honourable Members on waiting times for personal independence payment appeals tribunals in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143684","143684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904145","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the longest waiting time recorded from the lodging of a personal independence payment appeal to the confirmation of a date for the appeal tribunal, in each region of the UK in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143685","143685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904146","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 10 paragraph 1.10 of the National Cyber Security Strategy 2016-2021, what assessment he has made of the Armed Forces' ability to assist in the event of a significant national cyber-attack.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143702","143702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904147","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 5.28 on page 51 of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review, what steps his Department has taken with Poland on cyber security.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143703","143703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904149","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 5.38 on page 52 of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review, what steps his Department has taken with Germany on cyber security.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143704","143704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904150","2018-05-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 8402 on Personal Independence Payment: Appeals, what the average waiting time was for a personal independence payment appeal to be heard for the 2017-18 reporting period.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143686","143686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904151","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 5.42 on page 53 of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review, what steps his Department has taken with the European Union on cyber security.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143705","143705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904152","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department has made on the roll-out of the breathing space policy in relation to problem debt.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143676","143676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904153","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 5.73 on page 58 of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review, what steps his Department has been taken with the Republic of Korea on cyber security.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143706","143706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904154","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 5.74 on page 58 of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review, what steps his Department has taken with China on cyber security.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143707","143707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904155","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 5.76 on page 58  of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review, what steps his Department has taken with India on cyber security.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143708","143708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904156","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 59 paragraph 5.83 of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review, what work has been undertaken with Latin American states on cyber security.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143709","143709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904157","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2018 to Question 142304 on Sustainability and Transformation Partnerships: South East, what sanctions are available to him for late delivery in the Sustainability and Transformation Partnership.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143616","143616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904159","2018-05-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of Hitachi on the funding of any new nuclear power projects in the UK.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143841","143841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904160","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of each branch of the armed services work at the National Cyber Security Centre.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143807","143807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904161","2018-05-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of each branch of the services are employed in the national offensive cyber programme.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143808","143808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904162","2018-05-17","Cabinet Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much and to which companies his Department has allocated funding from the Cyber Innovation Fund.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143809","143809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904164","2018-05-16","Cabinet Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government has taken steps to prepare for holding the 2019 European Elections.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143730","143730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904165","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many claimants of universal credit who ticked  the box income-based JSA on their free prescription forms were subsequently accused of attempting to defraud the National Health Service.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143677","143677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904166","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 9 May 2018 to Questions 140753 and 140754 on Network Rail: Standards, when he plans to publish the (a) targets and (b) benchmarks the Office for Rail and Road will bring forward as part of its regulatory approach to ensure improvements to Network Rail’s (i) unit costs and (ii) productivity in Control Period 6.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143786","143786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904167","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 9 May 2018 to Questions 140753 and 140754 provided on May 9th on Network Rail: Standards, whether the Office for Rail and Road will be able to levy financial penalties on Network Rail in the event that it does not deliver improvements to (a) unit costs and (b) productivity in Control Period 6.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143787","143787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904168","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to Parliamentary answers of 9 May to Questions 140753 and 140754 on Network Rail: Standards, whether the Office for Rail and Road’s regulatory approach to Network Rail in Control Period 6 will (a) benchmark and (b) measure route level (i) unit costs and (ii) productivity.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143788","143788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904169","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason Hull College's fresh start formula funding included was a cap on its staffing costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143865","143865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904171","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers of the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the effect of migrants working in the UK on Tier 2 skilled worker visas being subject to a 20-day annual limit on unpaid leave from work on those workers' right to strike; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143867","143867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904172","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has conducted an economic impact study on the effects of clean air zones and associated air quality measures on businesses in Nottingham.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143862","143862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904173","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers and (c) officials of his Department have had with small and medium businesses in Nottingham on the financial effect of proposed clean air zones and associated air quality measures.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143863","143863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904175","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from representatives of the Welsh Government on the development of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143845","143845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904176","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations he has made to the Welsh Government on the development of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143846","143846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904177","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the correspondence between his Department and the Welsh Government on the creation of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143847","143847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904178","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with representatives of local authorities in England on the development of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143848","143848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904180","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proposed value of the future UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143849","143849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904181","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to promote the consumption of UK (a) fruit and (b) vegetables.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143817","143817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904182","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to take steps to simplify the application process for a Blue Badge for organisations that are required to prove that a service user is entitled to a Blue Badge.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143777","143777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904183","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the quality of social care provision is not being affected by increase in demand.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143778","143778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904184","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to change the social care budget in line with changing levels of demand for services.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143779","143779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904185","2018-05-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employees of her Department have applied for redeployment after medical evidence was produced that use of display screen equipment and on-line computer work was damaging their health since 2012; and how many of those employees were (a) given alternative work in her Department, (b) made redundant on medical grounds and (c) were not given alternative work but are still employed in her Department.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143671","143671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904187","2018-05-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has had discussions with its Israeli counterpart on the use by the Israeli military of expanding bullets in the Gaza Strip between February 2018 and May 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143735","143735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904188","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed ‘Bradley’ open-cast coal mine in Pont Valley, County Durham on the UK meeting its carbon reduction targets in the Climate Change Act 2008.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143736","143736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904189","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to Local Authorities on the procurement of IT systems to deliver 30 free hours of childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143823","143823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904190","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government’s decision to remove the ordering restriction on exceptions to the two-child limit for the child element of Child Tax Credit and Universal Credit for children in kinship care and adopted children, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of that two-child limit on women who have conceived a child through non-consensual sexual intercourse and who then subsequently choose to have two further children with a new partner.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143798","143798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904191","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department allocated to schools in Harborough constituency in each financial year since 2010-11; and what estimate he has made of the funding that will be allocated to schools in Harborough constituency under the National Funding Formula in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143878","143878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904193","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils were being educated in the state sector in (a) Harborough constituency, (b) Leicestershire, (c) Leicester and (d) England in each financial year since 2010-11; and what estimate he has made of the number of pupils there will be in each of these areas in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143879","143879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904194","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on whether (a) people can be on the membership of more than one multi academy trust board and (b) the chair of a multi academy trust board should be allowed to chair more than one trust.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143780","143780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904195","2018-05-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of households receiving universal credit are repaying debts incurred on (a) the social fund, (b)crisis loans, (c) tax credit overpayments, (d) housing benefit overpayments and (e) other forms of social security debt, inherited before claimants began drawing universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143678","143678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904196","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many victims of crime have been reported to his Department in each of the last five years; and how many of those people were victims of domestic violence.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143637","143637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904197","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many diagnoses of (a) hypothyroidism and (b) hyperthyroidism were made in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143638","143638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904198","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many medical exemption certificates were issued under regulation 10 of the National Health Service (Charges for Drugs and Appliances) Regulations 2015 in each of the last three years in relation to (a) myxoedema and (b) other conditions.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143639","143639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904199","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS has spent on (a) T4 and (b) T3 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143640","143640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904200","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential to reduce the cost to the NHS of treating hypothyroidism by procuring relevant medicines from (a) from licensed providers other than Concordia and (b) appropriately accredited overseas providers.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143641","143641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904202","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what damages his Department has sought against companies which have breached competition law in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143642","143642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904203","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many properties have been disposed of by housing associations in each English region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143628","143628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904205","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports were wrongly issued  and subsequently cancelled or suspended in the last year.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143781","143781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904206","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many properties have been disposed of by each housing association in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143629","143629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904207","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many properties have disposed of by housing associations in each local authority in London since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143630","143630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904208","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many properties have been disposed of by each housing association in England since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143631","143631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904209","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many additional (a) Border Force personnel and (b) customs officials the Government plans to assign to Welsh ports of entry in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019 and (iii) 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143782","143782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904210","2018-05-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many properties of each number of bedrooms have been disposed of by each housing association in England since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143632","143632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904211","2018-05-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what has been the (a) cash and (b) real terms allocation to each English clinical commissioning group for (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14, (iii) 2014-15, (iv) 2015-16, (v) 2016-17 and (vi) 2018-19.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143633","143633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904212","2018-05-17","Home Office","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people born outside of the UK to active UK armed forces personnel from 1970 to 2016 were (a) issued British passports and (b) denied British passports at first application in (i) 2016, (ii) 2017 and (iii) 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143783","143783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904213","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will rank English clinical commissioning groups by the proportion difference between their actual and target allocations.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143634","143634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904215","2018-05-17","Department for Transport","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what testing period was agreed with Hitachi for the new rolling stock for Great Western Railway.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143784","143784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904216","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will rank English clinical commissioning groups by the porportion change in the real term allocation per capita since 2012-13.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143635","143635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904217","2018-05-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether (a) he, (b) Ministers and (c) officials of his Department have discussed the relocation of sediment from the Hinkley C project site to Cardiff Grounds with (a) the Welsh Government, (b) EDF and (c) Natural Resources Wales.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143785","143785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904218","2018-05-17","Department for Education","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason he did not implement grant funding for Year Seven catch-up proposals.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143614","143614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/904220","2018-05-17","Treasury","2018-05-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many IT faults with the 30 hours childcare system have been outstanding since November 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143615","143615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/909346","2018-06-04","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimates he has made of the number of survivors of the Harrods bombing in 1983 who (a) are entitled to compensation and (b) have received compensation.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 146864","146864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902110","2018-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many Housing Ombudsman decisions were sent for judicial review between March 2016 and March 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143227","143227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902111","2018-05-15","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle the attainment gap among BAME students.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143228","143228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902112","2018-05-15","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the attainment gap between students from the North and South of England.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143229","143229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902113","2018-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy that the statutory enforcement of the identification of horses be compiled by the Central Equine Database once that database is fully launched.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143230","143230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902114","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the EU on triggering Article 7 of the Lisbon Treaty against the Government of Hungary on freedom of the press and the judiciary in that country.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143231","143231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902115","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to amend the law on abortion to make it easier for women with complex medical conditions to access abortion services.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143232","143232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902116","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for social security benefit fraud was for an individual convicted of a further social security benefit fraud in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most such recent offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143128","143128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902117","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for breaching an antisocial behaviour order was for an individual convicted of a further breach of an antisocial behaviour order in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most such recent offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143129","143129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902118","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for taking, permitting to be taken, distributing or publishing indecent photographs of children was for an individual convicted of a further taking, permitting to be taken, distributing or publishing indecent photographs of children offence in each of the last 3 years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most such recent offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143130","143130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902119","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for fraud was for an individual convicted of a further fraud offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most such recent offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143131","143131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902120","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for failing to surrender was for an individual convicted of a further failing to surrender offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most such recent offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143132","143132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902121","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for common assault was for an individual convicted of a further common assault offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most such recent offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143133","143133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902122","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for actual bodily harm was for an individual convicted of a further actual bodily harm offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most such recent offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143134","143134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902123","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to put the UK in the top quartile of comparator countries for the speed of adoption of innovative new medicines.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143105","143105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902124","2018-05-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the options for an agreement on the terms for the UK's financial services industry after the end of the transition period are.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143118","143118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902125","2018-05-15","Treasury","2018-05-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) short-term and (b) long-term risks to  financial services in each region of the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143119","143119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902126","2018-05-15","Treasury","2018-05-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many UK financial services firms have attained a presence in Europe since the EU referendum.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143120","143120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902127","2018-05-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the agreement between the Forestry Commission and Forest Holidays to develop holiday chalets and infrastructure across the forestry estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143125","143125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902128","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the HM Prison and Probation Service is taking to respond to the findings in the 2016-17 National Offender Management Service Annual Staff Equalities Report to tackle inequalities for (a) BAME staff and (b) staff with disabilities relating its performance management system.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143217","143217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902129","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what comparative assessment his Department has made of standards for fire safety and building regulations in other countries.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143212","143212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902131","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of how many (a) accidents and (b) casualties have been caused by drivers who have (i) failed eye tests or (ii) been found to have insufficient eyesight in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143198","143198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902132","2018-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the US withdrawal from the Iran nuclear deal on stability in the Middle East.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143236","143236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902133","2018-05-16","Treasury","2018-05-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Questions 245 to 259 of his evidence to the Treasury Committee on 25 April 2018 on local authorities, how he defines the term at risk.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143143","143143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902134","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many courts have been closed and replaced with remote video technology since 2015.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143201","143201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902135","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken to schedule a court date in cases of unpaid penalty notices for non-attendance at school in each year since 2015 is.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143202","143202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902136","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of incidents of victims and suspects travelling on the same bus or train to court in areas where the local court has closed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143203","143203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902137","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the potential additional financial costs on police forces in areas where the local court has recently closed.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143204","143204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902138","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has received representations on the availability of independent domestic violence advisers to attend court in areas where the local court has recently closed.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143205","143205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902139","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases were summonsed in (a) 2018, (b) 2016, (c) 2010 in West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143206","143206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902140","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many tier 2 visas were awarded to NHS Trusts or other bodies which are registered sponsors in each month from December 2016 until April 2018.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143189","143189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902141","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many tier 2 visas were declined or deferred to NHS Trusts or other bodies which are licensed sponsors in each month from December 2016 until April 2018.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143190","143190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902142","2018-05-15","Treasury","2018-05-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of Stamp Duty Land Tax repayments claimed were repaid within the 15 days target in the last financial year; and what the total sum outstanding beyond 15 days at the end of the previous fiscal year was.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143215","143215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902143","2018-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant the Answer of 9 May 2018 to Question 139479, what rehabilitation strategies his Department has put in place to prepare Gypsies and Travellers for release from prison.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143142","143142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902144","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the cost of policing rural areas compared to urban areas.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143216","143216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902145","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will support the bid by Scarborough to host Armed Forces Day in 2019.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143153","143153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902146","2018-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for bids to be received for the UK City of Culture 2025.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143154","143154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902147","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on the allocation of the top-up component of high needs funding.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143155","143155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902148","2018-05-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason the time limit to apply for compensation from the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority is two years after the incident.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143156","143156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902149","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Strategic Review of the Undercover Policing Inquiry, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of appointing a panel of advisers prior to the commencement of Module 1 hearings.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143209","143209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902150","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to Question 130114, on counter-terrorism, tabled by the Hon. Member for Sheffield, Heeley, on 27 February 2018.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143210","143210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902151","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to Questions 135961 and 135962, on Crimes of Violence: Disclosure of Information, tabled by the hon. Member for Sheffield, Heeley, on 16 April 2018.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143211","143211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902152","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what perinatal services his Department makes available to families in Birkenhead constituency; and whether he has made an estimate of the take-up of those services.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143117","143117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902153","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy to guarantee state subsidy of rent for tenants of service family accommodation after 2021.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143233","143233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902154","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to put extra protection measures in place for England fans travelling to the 2018 FIFA World Cup in Russia.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143234","143234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902155","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to issue guidance for LGBT fans travelling to Russia for the 2018 FIFA World Cup.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143235","143235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902156","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had any recent discussions with the Government of Bangladesh with the objective of either (a) promoting the human rights of female migrant workers and (b) promoting the need for more safeguarding for female migrant workers against exploitation and trafficking; and if he will list the outcomes of recent discussions he has had with that Government.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143144","143144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902157","2018-05-16","Department for International Development","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has had any recent discussions with the Government of Bangladesh with the objective of either (a) promoting the human rights of female migrant workers and (b) promoting the need for more safeguarding for female migrant workers against exploitation and trafficking; and if she will list the outcomes of recent discussions she has had with that Government.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143145","143145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902158","2018-05-16","Department for International Development","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is taking steps to support judicial officials in Bangladesh to promote awareness of their justice system to female migrant workers in that country.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143146","143146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902159","2018-05-15","Treasury","2018-05-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Royal Bank of Scotland on branch closures throughout England and Wales.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143237","143237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902160","2018-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to seek to end cosmetic animal testing throughout the world.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143238","143238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902161","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to provide additional funding to support nursery schools beyond April 2020.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143141","143141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902162","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve the uptake of innovative new medicines in the UK.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143106","143106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902163","2018-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Office for Product and Safety and Standards has taken steps in response to the Which? investigation which claimed some retailers are providing incorrect and unsafe advice on fire-risk tumble dryers.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143218","143218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902164","2018-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for the publication of​ the strategy for the Office of Product Safety and Standards.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143219","143219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902165","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Consultation on the use of section 19 and section 22 permits for road passenger transport in Great Britain, published by his Department on 8 January 2018, whether the exemptions in that consultation are intended to (a) not compel Scout groups to purchase public service vehicle licences and (b) allow them to continue using Section 19 licences when delivering services.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143168","143168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902166","2018-05-15","Cabinet Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on Clause 11 of the EU (Withdrawal) Bill.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143220","143220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902167","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the framework for bids for further devolution from areas that do not have a devolution agreement.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143240","143240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902168","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the causes of changes in the number of cases of (a) brain and (b) glioblastoma multiforme tumours since 1995.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143213","143213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902169","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department first implemented a policy for imposing targets for deportation of illegal immigrants; and whether the Home Secretary had discussions with Cabinet colleagues on that policy at that time.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143223","143223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902170","2018-05-16","Cabinet Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with whom he would plan to co-ordinate the delivery of Government objectives in the event that the Prime Minister was temporarily or permanently incapacitated.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143136","143136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902171","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of whether there is a link between mobile phone usage and the increase in number of cases of glioblastoma multiforme tumours since 1995.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143214","143214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902172","2018-05-16","Attorney General","2018-05-11","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on his Department's responsibilities.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143137","143137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902173","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on the responsibilities of his Department of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143138","143138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902174","2018-05-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the potential sale of Wembley Stadium on participation rates in (a) association football and (b) American football.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143139","143139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902175","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on the transparency of the process in the event that one academy replaces another as the provider of education at a school.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143140","143140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902176","2018-05-16","Cabinet Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how his Department plans to use the evaluation of the voter ID pilots to inform (a) further pilots taking place in 2019 and (b) the implementation of voter ID requirements at the next general election.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143115","143115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902177","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the effect of the public sector pay cap on the level of (a) recruitment and (b) retention of staff in schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143116","143116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902178","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to item 13 in table 2.1 of the Spring Budget 2017, whether it is still his policy to provide free travel to selective schools at the cost of £5 million per year.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143180","143180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902179","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s news story Drive to create more good school places for families published on 11 May 2018, how many additional school places the Selective Schools Expansion Fund is forecast to create in each of the next four years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143181","143181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902180","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s news story Drive to create more good school places for families published on 11 May 2018, whether the £50 million a year Selective Schools Expansion Fund is in addition to the £50 million of funding to allow selective schools to expand announced in paragraph 5.13 of the Autumn Statement 2016.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143182","143182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902181","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s news story Drive to create more good school places for families published on 11 May 2018, whether there are any specific steps which will need to be outlined in a grammar school’s Fair Access and Participation Plan for them to be eligible for funding from the Selective Schools Expansion Fund.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143183","143183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902182","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to make the practice of up-skirting a sexual offence; and what recent discussions and with whom he has had on that matter.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143147","143147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902183","2018-05-15","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that local authority children’s services receive sufficient funding to support vulnerable young people.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143148","143148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902184","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the fire service is adequately funded.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143149","143149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902185","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that firefighters are paid fairly.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143150","143150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902186","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will publish the fair access and partnership plans of all grammar schools that are awarded additional funding from the selective school expansion fund.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143170","143170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902187","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that bowel cancer patients get high quality care.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143151","143151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902188","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will ensure that bowel cancer patients are routinely tested for Lynch syndrome.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143152","143152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902189","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s news story Drive to create more good school places for families published on 11 May 2018, how capital funding is planned to be made available to help create new voluntary-aided schools in each of the five fiscals years from and including 2018-19.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143171","143171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902190","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s news story Drive to create more good school places for families published on 11 May 2018, whether funding for new voluntary aided schools will be allocated on the basis of there being (a) a  need for additional schools places and (b) demand for additional places in faith schools, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143172","143172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902191","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s news story Drive to create more good school places for families published on 11 May 2018, what steps by voluntary aided schools would be seen by his Department as playing an active role in their community; and whether that is a condition of receiving funding to open new voluntary aided schools.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143173","143173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902192","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take into account whether Comcast’s bid for Sky includes commitments to maintain Sky’s employment levels in (a) Scotland and (b) throughout the UK.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143188","143188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902193","2018-05-16","Department for Education","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s news story Drive to create more good school places for families published on 11 May 2018, what timetable his Department has set for Wave 13 of free school applications.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143174","143174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902194","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the coastal communities fund that has been awarded to the fishing sector over the four funding rounds completed to date.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143207","143207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902195","2018-05-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to increase the proportion of the coastal communities fund which is awarded to the fishing sector.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143208","143208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902196","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Defence Procurement of 23 April, Official Report, column 593, what progress has been made on Qatar’s order of the Hawk aircraft.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143126","143126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902197","2018-05-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his oral contribution of 23 April, Official Report, column 582, when he plans to look at the whole defence procurement argument with regard to the real benefits to UK plc.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143127","143127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902198","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his oral statement of 2 May 2018, Official Report, column 315, on Breast Cancer Screening, what training was given to Serco staff responsible for responding to queries on the PHE phone helpline before the helpline number was made public.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143157","143157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902199","2018-05-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 May 2018 to Question 140674, on Planning: Public Inquiries, how many and what proportion of decisions of public planning inquiries, as a result of call-ins only, did not follow the advice of the planning inspector in each year since 2010 up to the most recent year for which data is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143135","143135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902200","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the change in prescription charges has been in real terms in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143158","143158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902201","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the spending per in-patient in England on NHS meals was per (a) hospital stay and (b) day in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143159","143159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902202","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of deaths from (a) pneumonia and (b) pneumococcal disease.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143160","143160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902203","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of fraud in the NHS.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143161","143161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902204","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what savings has been generated for the public purse through managed access agreements for new medicines since 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143162","143162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902205","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to encourage people to include fruit and vegetables in their diets using (a) subsidisation and (b) other new methods.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143163","143163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902206","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to ensure that the NHS does not ration access to vaccinations based on cost.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143164","143164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902207","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding was allocated by his Department to vaccination programmes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143165","143165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902208","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department has allocated for vaccination programmes in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20 and (c) 2020-21 following the 2015 spending review.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143166","143166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902209","2018-05-15","Department for International Development","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department is taking steps to prioritise tackling pneumonia throughout the world.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143195","143195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902210","2018-05-15","Department for International Development","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support developing countries to establish universal health coverage.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143196","143196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902211","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an estimate of the amount of funding his Department has spent on arts and culture provision in former coalfield communities in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143239","143239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902212","2018-05-15","Department for International Development","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to the Department of Health and Social Care to use the upcoming World Health Assembly as an opportunity to encourage other countries to Invest in strengthening their healthcare systems.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143197","143197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902213","2018-05-15","Department for Transport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time taken for the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency was to issue driving licence forms in the Welsh language when such forms were requested in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143121","143121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902214","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many local authority areas met the WHO recommended 95 per cent uptake target for childhood immunisation programmes in 2016-17.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143167","143167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902215","2018-05-15","Department for International Development","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on aid for the treatment of cholera cases in Yemen in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143108","143108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902216","2018-05-15","Department for International Development","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on aid for the treatment of diphtheria cases in Yemen in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143109","143109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902217","2018-05-15","Department for International Development","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the blockade in Yemen on the price of and accessibility of fuel in that country.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143110","143110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902218","2018-05-15","Department for International Development","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the blockade in Yemen on the supply and trucking of water across that country.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143111","143111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902219","2018-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many departmental jobs are being transferred from the Welsh Government building in Caernarfon to the site at Victoria Dock.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143122","143122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902220","2018-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the new departmental site in Victoria Dock, Caernarfon is owned by the Government or is rented property.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143123","143123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902221","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an estimate of the number of crossbows which have been sold in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143199","143199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902222","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) injuries and (b) deaths have been caused by crossbows in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143200","143200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902223","2018-05-16","Treasury","2018-05-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on establishing a UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143241","143241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902224","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April to Question 135259, on Members: Correspondence, when she plans to respond to the letter of 28 March 2018 from the hon. Member for Croydon North on a visa enquiry on behalf of a constituent.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143169","143169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902225","2018-05-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the deportation order against Omar Shakir the Israel and Palestine Director at Human Rights Watch; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143114","143114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902226","2018-05-16","Department for International Trade","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the objectives were of the meeting he held with President Duterte on 3 April 2017.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143221","143221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902227","2018-05-15","Department for Transport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings (a) he, (b) Ministers of his Department and (c) officials of his Department have held with Heathrow Airport Limited on the proposed north-west runway since 2 February 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143191","143191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902228","2018-05-15","Department for Transport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what days and for what purpose (a) he, (b) Ministers of his Department and (c) officials of his Department have met Heathrow Airport Limited since 2 February 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143192","143192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902229","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support NICE to update their guidelines on the delivery of structured education for people with (a) type 1 and (b) type 2 diabetes to make use of new digital models of delivery.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143175","143175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902230","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans there are to increase the number of diabetes apps available on the NHS Digital’s Apps Library.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143176","143176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902231","2018-05-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support is provided to (a) GPs and (b) other healthcare professionals to enable them to better utilise apps within the current NHS Diabetes Prevention Programme to improve patient care.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143177","143177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902232","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential correlation between the prevalence of diabetes and measures of deprivation across the country.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143178","143178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902233","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what impact assessment he has made of the advice of the Department of Transport’s Medical Advisory Panel on Driving and Visual Disorders on driving and diabetes on the uptake of glucose monitors for the management of diabetes.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143179","143179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902234","2018-05-15","Treasury","2018-05-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had with the European Commission on the application of a zero rate of VAT to sanitary products.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143222","143222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902235","2018-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 136840 on Armed Forces: Schools, who commissioned the study on the merits of military ethos in schools.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143193","143193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902236","2018-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 136840 on Armed Forces: Schools, what discussions he has had with cabinet colleagues on the commissioning of the study on the merits of military ethos in schools.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143194","143194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902237","2018-05-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government takes steps to measure the positive effect that holidays can play in family life.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143184","143184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902238","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps Government is taking to support social tourism initiatives throughout the UK.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143185","143185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902239","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions the Government has had with the tourism industry on helping families with low incomes take a holiday away from home.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143186","143186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902240","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the value of social tourism to the UK (a) domestic tourism industry and (b) economy.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143187","143187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902241","2018-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Myanmar Government on the persecution of the Rohingya in the past month.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143224","143224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902242","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the merits of prohibiting domestic abusers from using spyware and domestic surveillance to monitor their victim's movements.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143225","143225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902243","2018-05-15","Department for Transport","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the fines which were imposed on rail operators that failed to reach the expected level of service in 2017.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143226","143226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902244","2018-05-16","Home Office","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he has taken since the chemical contamination incident in Salisbury to ensure that medical counter measures are in place to protect police officers attending such incidents.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143112","143112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902245","2018-05-16","House of Commons Commission","2018-05-11","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what medical counter measures are in place to protect police officers responding to potential biological incidents on the Parliamentary estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143113","143113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/902246","2018-05-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to develop a new power generating plant with Hitachi; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143107","143107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901198","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for drink driving offences was for a person convicted of a further drink driving offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142807","142807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901199","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for driving whist disqualified was for a person convicted of a further driving whilst disqualified offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142808","142808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901200","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for public order act offences was for a person convicted of a further public order act offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142809","142809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901201","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for theft was for a person convicted of a further theft offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142810","142810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901202","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for a knife offence was for a person convicted of a further knife offence in each of the last thee years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142811","142811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901203","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for burglary was for a person convicted of a further burglary in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142812","142812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901204","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for drug offences was for a person convicted of a further drug offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142813","142813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901205","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for assaulting a police officer was for a person convicted of a further assault police officer offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142814","142814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901206","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for taking a vehicle without consent was for a person convicted of a further offence of taking a vehicle without consent in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142815","142815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901207","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for vehicle interference was for a person convicted of a further vehicle interference offence in each of the last three years who was not given a sentence of immediate custody; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142816","142816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901208","2018-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to Question 136906, whether his Department is taking steps to ensure that the spouse of a Minister who has financial interests divests themselves of those interests upon the Minister taking office in his Department.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142792","142792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901209","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment he has made of the number of school children with visual impairments who are subject to (a) Education Health Care Plans and (b) statements under the previous SEN and learning difficulties assessments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142869","142869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901210","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the use of restorative justice for young offenders.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142870","142870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901211","2018-05-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of NICE guidelines on the identification of, assessment of and interventions for children with autism.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142871","142871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901212","2018-05-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost on the public purse in compensation for the next of kin of women who died from breast cancer after not being sent an appointment for routine breast screening.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142748","142748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901213","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many universities are registered as apprenticeship providers in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142778","142778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901214","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what criteria his Department has used to assess the bids submitted by (a) 21st Century Fox and (b) Comcast for the takeover of Sky plc; and whether that criteria includes the activities of those companies in overseas jurisdictions.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142817","142817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901215","2018-05-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that progress is made on the Sussex and East Surrey Sustainability and Transformation Partnership's move to integrated care systems; and what the timetable is for that move.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142741","142741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901216","2018-05-15","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.14 of his Department's consultation on the use of section 19 and section 22 permits for road passenger transport in Great Britain, whether the West Lancashire Dial A Ride services will be considered to be substantially less than cost and therefore exempt under EU and UK regulations on PSV.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142802","142802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901217","2018-05-14","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.14 of his Department's consultation on the use of section 19 and section 22 permits for road passenger transport in Great Britain, whether the West Lancashire Dial A Ride services will be considered as only occasional and therefore exempt under EU and UK regulations on PSV.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142803","142803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901218","2018-05-15","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.14 of his Department's consultation on the use of section 19 and section 22 permits for road passenger transport in Great Britain, whether the West Lancashire Dial A Ride services will be considered as only operating in non-contestable markets and therefore exempt under EU and UK regulations on PSV.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142804","142804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901219","2018-05-15","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.20 of his Department's consultation on the use of section 19 and section 22 permits for road passenger transport in Great Britain, whether the West Lancashire Dial A Ride services will be considered as only incidental to a main, non-transport occupation and therefore exempt under EU and UK regulations on PSV.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142805","142805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901220","2018-05-15","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's consultation on the use of section 19 and section 22 permits for road passenger transport in Great Britain, whether the West Lancashire Dial A Ride services will be considered as only as only for short distances and therefore exempt under EU and UK regulations on PSV.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142806","142806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901221","2018-05-14","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether non-EU citizens who are spouses of British nationals and exercise free movement rights under the Surinder Singh principle are included in the citizens' rights agreement reached with the EU and will be eligible to apply for the settled status scheme.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142885","142885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901222","2018-05-15","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to his Department was of headteacher boards in 2017-18; and what estimate he has made of the potential cost of those boards in each year up to 2023.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142872","142872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901223","2018-05-15","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total value was of related party transactions made by academies and academy trusts in (a) the year ending 31 August 2016 and (b)  each of the previous five years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142873","142873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901224","2018-05-15","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2018 to Question 139972 on Disabled Students' Allowances,  what estimate he has made of the potential cost to the public purse of funding the £200 contribution made by students in receipt of Disabled Students’ Allowance for the purchase of computer hardware in each year up to 2023.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142874","142874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901225","2018-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the Theft Act 1968 on deterring the theft of pets.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142757","142757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901226","2018-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of animal welfare in fur farms in (a) Poland, (b) Finland, (c) China and (d) France that export fur to the UK.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142758","142758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901227","2018-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of reports of alleged use of torture and forced confessions in Bahrain.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142764","142764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901228","2018-05-14","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department’s memorandum of understanding with the Socialist Republic of Vietnam on the improvement of (a) identification, (b) notification, (c) referral and (d) assisted voluntary return of victims and potential victims of human trafficking.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142863","142863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901229","2018-05-15","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received on the effect of changes to higher education funding on the Open University.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142765","142765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901230","2018-05-14","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department’s memorandum of understanding with the Federal Republic of Nigeria on the improvement of (a) identification, (b) notification, (c) referral and (d) assisted voluntary return of victims and potential victims of human trafficking.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142864","142864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901231","2018-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many disqualification orders have been issued in England and Wales under s34 of the Animal Welfare Act 2006 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142790","142790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901232","2018-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many disqualification orders under s34 of the Animal Welfare Act 2006 have been breached in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142791","142791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901233","2018-05-15","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the timescale is for the Belfast and Londonderry city deals to become fully operational.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142780","142780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901234","2018-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135379, and the reference therein to there being no commercially available equipment for monitoring emissions of PM10 and PM2.5, to what sort of equipment the references on pages 7 and 9 of the Technical Guidance Note M15 on Monitoring PM10 and PM2.5 refer which give advice about continuous monitoring of PM10, PM2.5 and PM1.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142749","142749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901235","2018-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to of 19 April 2018 to Question 135379, what non-commercially available equipment there is for measuring emissions of PM10 and PM2.5.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142750","142750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901236","2018-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2017 to Question 117197 on Incinerators, who undertakes the strict monitoring regime for emissions of PM 10 and PM 2.5.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142751","142751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901237","2018-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is his Department's policy to advise British citizens living in France to obtain a Carte de Sejour.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142742","142742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901238","2018-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) the additional amount of extra traffic caused by a waste incinerator being in use and (b) the increase in emissions of (i) PM10, (ii) PM2.5, (iii) PM 1 and (iv) PM0.1 caused by that extra traffic.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142752","142752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901239","2018-05-15","Department for International Development","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will develop a cross-departmental strategy for the UK’s approach to supporting the (a) prevention of, (b) protection of and (c) solution to the increasing number of internally displaced people around the world.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142755","142755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901240","2018-05-15","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report Crumbling Futures published by the Children's Society in March 2018, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that 16 and 17-year-olds referred to children’s services are receiving adequate support as they transition into adulthood.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142756","142756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901241","2018-05-15","Cabinet Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the five most common cancer diagnoses were among (a) men and (b) women in (i) 2007 and (ii) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142781","142781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901242","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women were sent to immediate custody from the (a) the Crown Court and (b) magistrates' courts for sentences (i) below 6 months and (ii) above 6 months in each police force area in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142767","142767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901243","2018-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the change in the (a) grey and (b) red squirrel populations between 2007 and 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142782","142782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901244","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the loss of revenue to the public purse as a result of television licence fee evasion in (a) 2012 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142783","142783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901245","2018-05-14","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding he plans to make available from the Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy to increase the use of electric bikes.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142877","142877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901246","2018-05-14","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using the Cycle to Work Scheme to support the uptake of electric bikes.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142878","142878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901247","2018-05-14","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate improved access to and greater uptake of electric bikes in the UK.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142879","142879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901248","2018-05-14","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of an increase in the uptake of electric bikes on air quality and congestion.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142880","142880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901249","2018-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2018 to Question 123768 on Waste Disposal, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make the separate collection of compostable waste by local authorities mandatory.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142753","142753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901250","2018-05-14","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the (a) level of incidence and (b) risk of the use in violent crime of (i) phosphoric acid, (ii) hydrochloric acid, (iii) sodium hydroxide, (iv) ammonia and (v) hydrofluoric acid.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142821","142821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901251","2018-05-14","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the updated leaflet entitled Sell Chemical Products Responsibly, published by her Department on 4 April 2018, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of that leaflet in giving guidance to online retailers on their statutory duty to report suspicious purchases under the Poisons Act 1972.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142822","142822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901252","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  how many visa applicants seeking to join a family member in the UK had a DNA test to evidence their relationship to that family member in each year for which information is available; and how many of those DNA tests proved that the relationship between the visa applicant and their family member living in the UK was as they claimed it to be.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142891","142891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901253","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2018 to question 135723, on Prince Harry: Marriage,  whether Thames Valley Police have submitted an application to her Department for Special Grant funding for additional costs associated with policing the royal wedding.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142892","142892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901254","2018-05-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to respond to Questions 137158, 137159 and 137160, on Green Deal Scheme, tabled on 23 April 2018 by the hon Member for Rutherglen and Hamilton West.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142929","142929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901255","2018-05-14","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the Maritime and Coastguard Agency’s (MCA) national network of marine offices on the MCA’s capacity to enforce international maritime regulations.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142836","142836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901256","2018-05-15","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on implementing the recommendations of the Smith Review of post-16 mathematics since its publication on 20 July 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142743","142743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901257","2018-05-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he or Ministers of his Department have made an official visit to the Port of London since July 2016.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142865","142865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901258","2018-05-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which of the UK’s ports (a) he and (b) other Ministers in of his Department have visited since July 2016.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142866","142866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901259","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent meetings he has had with leading social media companies to discuss the prevalence, removal and prevention of hate speech and other extreme content on social media platforms.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142759","142759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901260","2018-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of effect on the local population of the recent Saudi-led coalition airstrikes on the business district in Sana'a, Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142760","142760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901261","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 8 May 2018 to Question 140136 on UK Border Force: Northern Ireland, whether the UK Border Agency (a) supports the Military Covenant and (b) recognises its UK-wide applicability.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142875","142875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901262","2018-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has commissioned an independent assessment on the need for more animal rendering plants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Caroline Johnson","Dr Caroline Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142911","142911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901263","2018-05-16","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to exempt small not-for-profit community groups from proposed additional licensing and vehicle testing conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142740","142740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901264","2018-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2018 to question 136899, if he will provide details of the minimum safe height/sink rate/speed/bank angle envelope, as stated in the tornado aircrew manual.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142876","142876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901265","2018-05-14","Department for Transport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether improvements to infrastructure and the capacity for East Midlands Trains will be completed in 2020; and what steps his Department is taking to prevent delays to services serving stations along that route post-2020.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142918","142918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901266","2018-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to ensure that the framework for the regulation of chemicals provided by the EU Registration, Evaluation, Authorisation & Restriction of Chemicals regulation will be replicated in the UK after it leaves the EU.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142900","142900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901267","2018-05-14","Department for International Development","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much financial assistance her Department has given to projects in Zimbabwe in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142772","142772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901268","2018-05-14","Department for International Development","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support internally displaced people in Iraq.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142773","142773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901269","2018-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which types of aircraft and how many of each type are in (a) the forward fleet, (b) sustainment and (c) storage.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142886","142886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901270","2018-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the protected nuclear safety baseline staff complement numbers are for each of the nuclear authorities within his Department; and how many authorisees were in post as of 31 December 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142887","142887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901271","2018-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many incidents excluding trivial incidents involving the nuclear weapons convoys between Coulport and Berkshire there have been in each of the last ten years which were classified as (a) engineering incidents to nuclear convoy vehicles and (b) operational incidents.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142888","142888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901272","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of whether local authorities providing unstaffed public libraries using open technology are fulfilling their duty to provide a comprehensive and efficient library service.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142903","142903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901273","2018-05-15","Cabinet Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to Devolution Guidance Note: Parliamentary and Assembly Primary Legislation Affecting Wales, for what reason only the devolution guidance relating to Wales mentions changes to devolved competence in relation to the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142826","142826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901274","2018-05-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding was allocated in 2017 to dementia care in (a) Mansfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142926","142926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901275","2018-05-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the broadcasting standards set out in the Enterprise Act 2002, if he will make an assessment of adequacy of Comcast's (a) compliance and (b) customer service record in the (i) UK and (ii) US in relation to that company's bid to take over Sky Plc.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142849","142849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901276","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department took to validate allegations made by ETS that individuals had cheated in their Test of English for International Communication; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142744","142744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901277","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many decisions since February 2014 to curtail a person's leave to remain in the UK on the ground of cheating in an English language test administered by ETS have been overturned on appeal.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142745","142745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901278","2018-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many decisions since February 2014 to curtail a person's leave to remain in the UK on the ground of cheating in an English language test administered by ETS are subject to appeal.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142746","142746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901279","2018-05-15","Home Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions Ministers in his Department (a) met representatives of ETS between May 2010 and February 2014 and (b) have met such representatives since February 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142747","142747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901280","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish a response to the feedback on his consultation on the implementation of T-level programmes; and if he will ensure that his response is sufficiently detailed to enable the sector to prepare effectively for the introduction of T-levels in 2020.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142833","142833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901281","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to promote the (a) awareness of and (b) the changes relating to T-Levels.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142834","142834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901282","2018-05-14","Department for Education","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that T-level (a) routes are sufficiently flexible to enable learners to change course and (b) qualifications are transferable to allow people a range of career options.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142835","142835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901283","2018-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether claimants of employment support allowance (ESA) judged by a tribunal to be eligible to be in the support group after the expiry of their 365 days of contribution-based ESA, become eligible for indefinite contributions-based ESA.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142904","142904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901284","2018-05-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many animal cruelty (a) offences and (b) convictions there have been in Kent in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142831","142831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901285","2018-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of animal rescue homes in the South East.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142832","142832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901286","2018-05-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support businesses and entrepreneurs.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142910","142910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901287","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings (a) he, (b) Ministers and (c) officials of his Department held with representatives of the Democratic Unionist Party prior to the proceedings on the Data Protection Bill [Lords] in the House on 9 May 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142784","142784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901288","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to his oral contribution of 9 May 2018, Official Report, column 712, for what reason he proposed a separate review of press standards in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142785","142785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901289","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to his oral contribution of 9 May 2018, Official Report, column 712, what steps he is taking to consult on the terms of reference of the review of press standards in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142786","142786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901290","2018-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that there is election monitoring (a) in the run-up to and (b) during the forthcoming general election in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142766","142766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901291","2018-05-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to announce how funding for the Integrated Communities Strategy will be allocated.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142793","142793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901292","2018-05-14","Prime Minister","2018-05-10","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to her oral contribution of 9 May 2018, Official Report, column 677, what the evidential basis was for her statement that the only people being investigated for past issues are people in our armed forces or those who served in law enforcement in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142787","142787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901293","2018-05-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to his oral contribution of 9 May 2018, Official Report, column 712, what criteria will be applied for the appointment of the named person to review press standards in Northern Ireland; by whom that criteria will be applied; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142788","142788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901294","2018-05-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has estimated the potential savings to the public purse annually from providing patients with timely nutritional care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142738","142738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901295","2018-05-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of deaths associated with malnutrition.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142739","142739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901296","2018-05-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from local authorities on their use of reserves; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142794","142794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/901297","2018-05-15","Northern Ireland Office","2018-05-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Kilmarnock and Loudoun, of 9 May 2018, Official Report, column 664, what discussions she has had with the Home Secretary on the proportion of additional customs officials who will be based in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 142893","142893"
