"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087044","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he is making to his Iraqi counterpart on the persecution of Christians in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231463","231463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087045","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with his international counterparts to bring those responsible for the persecution of Hazara people to justice.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231464","231464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087047","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what criteria his Department uses to classify wood-burning stoves as a smoke exempt appliance.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231514","231514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087048","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of personal independence payment tribunal cases were attended by (a) presenting officers and (b) departmental staff in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231468","231468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087049","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will extend the scope of EU Regulation 598/2014 relating to noise-related operating restrictions at Scottish Airports to include management of aircraft noise for communities who currently within the area of the proposed competent authorities but are badly affected by noise from the two main Scottish airports.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231562","231562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087050","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the penalties are for train operators that have not provided the level of service that they are contracted to deliver; what compensation is available to passengers of Northern Rail that have not met contractual obligations services; what steps he is taking to improve the provision of rail services in Rochdale; and whether he plans to withdraw the franchise of operators which have not fulfilled their contractual obligations.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231366","231366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087051","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to implement the recommendations in the document entitled, Blue Badge consultation: summary of responses and government response, published on 29 July 2018.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231515","231515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087052","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that people arriving in the UK on a refugee family reunion visa receive a Biometric Residence Permit that contains their National Insurance number.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231516","231516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087054","2019-03-15","Cabinet Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Joint Funds Unit will (a) conduct and (b) publish regular reviews of Conflict, Security and Stability Fund programmes for which information is not publicly available.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231399","231399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087055","2019-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the trends in the level of access to superfast fibre broadband in Bristol West constituency; and what steps he is taking to improve access to that service in the constituency.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231517","231517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087056","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to ensure the continued recognition by the EU and other world markets of organic standards of exports by UK-based producers and suppliers in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and whether compensation will be made available in the event that recognition is interrupted.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231422","231422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087058","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been prosecuted for causing serious injury by dangerous driving in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231486","231486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087059","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of causing serious injury by dangerous driving in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231487","231487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087060","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the value of blanket bog peat lands to (a) carbon sequestration and (b) flood prevention.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231367","231367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087061","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of causing serious injury by dangerous driving received a suspended sentence in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231488","231488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087062","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average prison sentence given to people jailed for causing serious injury by dangerous driving was in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231489","231489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087064","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of causing serious injury by dangerous driving received the maximum five year jail sentence in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231490","231490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087065","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the specifications of the Clinical Commissioning Group plans to improve medical services for homeless citizens in Birmingham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231370","231370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087066","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Care Quality Commission report on medical services for homeless citizens in Birmingham, published in October 2018, when he plans to re-tender the service; and if he will lay a copy of the specification for their service in the Library.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231371","231371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087068","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders sentenced to immediate custody of up to six months who had not received a previous community order were sentenced in (a) Magistrate's Courts and (b) Crown Courts in (i) 2015; (ii) 2016 and (iii) 2017.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231411","231411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087069","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked after children there were in each local authority in England in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231419","231419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087070","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children there were in Cumbria in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231420","231420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087072","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many complaints he has received on the use of restraint in specialist schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231483","231483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087073","2019-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many new Post Office branch franchise opportunities are available in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland. and (d) each region of England.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231519","231519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087074","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the UK Government has accepted responsibility for the contaiminated blood products that were imported from the US during the 1970s and 1980s that caused some people in the UK to be infected with both HIV and Hepatitis.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231547","231547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087075","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the support provided to people through the England Infected Blood Support Scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231548","231548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087077","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of 11 March 2019, Official Report, column 20, by the Minister for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation on the European University Institute (EUI), what the evidential basis is for the Minister's statement that the UK cannot be a member of the EUI if it is not an EU member state.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231491","231491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087078","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answers of 6 February 2019 and 26 February 2019 to Question 214478 on Foetuses: Surgery and Question 223137 on Abortion, which establish a variation in practice for some procedures in the womb for the administration of pain relief for unborn babies of 20 weeks, for what reasons there are such variations in practice; what steps he is taking to tackle such variations in practice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231425","231425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087080","2019-03-15","Department for International Development","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224486 on Niger: Marie Stopes International (MSI), what assessment her Department has made of the validity of reports of Nigerien authorities enforcing the cessation of MSI abortion procedures at a number of their clinics.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231426","231426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087081","2019-03-15","Department for International Development","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 21 February 2019 to Question 221581, in which other countries in receipt of aid from the UK does the UK not provide funding to support the provision of abortion services.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231427","231427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087082","2019-03-15","Department for International Development","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224485 on the Alan Guttmacher Institute, in what year her Department most recently verified the accuracy of the illegal abortion statistics provided by the Guttmacher Institute; and what the outcome was of that most recent assessment.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231428","231428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087083","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the number of NHS hospitals that offer non-invasive pregnancy testing onsite; and what steps are being taken to monitor the effect of that onsite provision on the birth rate of babies with Down's syndrome.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231429","231429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087085","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release of 11 March 2019, Thousands of places created in new special free schools, to which local authorities that £365 million funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231396","231396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087086","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release of 11 March 2019, Thousands of places created in new special free schools, what criteria was used to determine those local authorities selected to receive new special free schools.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231397","231397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087088","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-12","o ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release of 11 March 2019, Thousands of places created in new special free schools, where in the South West he plans for those new special free schools providing 500 new places to be located.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231398","231398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087089","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff have been seconded from HMRC to other Government departments (a) since June 2016, (b) in the last 12 months and (c) in the last six months.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231555","231555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087090","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed NHS Tariff and its alignment with the commitments set out in the NHS 10 Point Efficiency Plan on reducing infection rates in hospitals in the field of ophthalmology.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231465","231465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087091","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress the Government has made on reducing infection rates in hospitals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231466","231466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087092","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many procedures for glaucoma were undertaken alongside cataract treatment in the last year; and whether his Department has made an assessment of the effectiveness of that combined treatment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231467","231467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087093","2019-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he last discussed national minimum wage compliance and enforcement in the (a) shipping industry and (b) offshore energy sector with officials of the HMRC National Minimum Wage Enforcement Team.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231505","231505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087095","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many third party complaints of non-payment of the national minimum wage were received by the HMRC National Minimum Wage Enforcement Team in each calendar year since 2015.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231506","231506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087096","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the HMRC National Minimum Wage Enforcement Team has taken to promote national minimum wage compliance in the (a) shipping and (b) offshore energy industries in each calendar year since 2015.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231507","231507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087098","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress he is making in his plans to enable more people to have longer tenancies than the typical six months which is generally offered.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231404","231404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087099","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of (a) continuous glucose monitor sensors and (b) flash glucose monitoring to (i) assess glucose levels and (ii) validate a diabetic’s fitness to drive.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231523","231523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087100","2019-03-14","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the interest rate charged by HMRC is on back taxes incurred through reassessment of loan charge schemes.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231361","231361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087101","2019-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the grounding of Boeing 737 Max 8 aircraft, whether he has made a risk assessment of the award of the AWACS contract to Boeing for the provision of the E-7 wedgetail.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231535","231535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087102","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent steps he has taken to prepare companies that trade with countries under EU free trade agreements (FTA) where the provisions of those FTAs have not been replicated.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231476","231476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087103","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require commercial fishing enterprises to carry identification marks on their (a) nets, (b) gear and (c) ancillary equipment in UK waters.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231437","231437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087105","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to help tackle human rights abuses in Tibet.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231520","231520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087106","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made recent representations to his counterpart in China on allowing independent human rights observers into Tibet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231521","231521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087107","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made recent representations to his counterpart in China on respecting Tibetans' rights to freedom of expression; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231522","231522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087108","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which sites in the Llanelli constituency his Department has considered as a potential location for a new coastguard base.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231406","231406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087109","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of (a) Carmarthenshire County Council and (b) the Welsh Government on the relocation of the Loughor Coastguard to Llanelli.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231407","231407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087110","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of co-locating the Loughor Coastguard with (a) Llanelli Fire Station, (b) Wales Air Ambulance in Dafen and (c) any other co-location option within the Llanelli area.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231408","231408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087112","2019-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of women who work in the (a) tech and (b) ICT sectors.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231549","231549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087113","2019-03-15","Department for International Trade","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to ensure that future trade deals do not require the NHS to outsource further services to private providers.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231421","231421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087114","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of foreign direct investment in the UK tech sector.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231362","231362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087116","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the proportion of migrant detainees who were trafficked to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231363","231363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087117","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps his Department has taken to help businesses create more highly skilled jobs in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231364","231364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087118","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2019 to Question 207270 on Cycleways, what representations he has received on commencing provisions in Part 6 of the Traffic Management Act 2004 to allow local authorities in England outside London to enforce moving traffic offences, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231518","231518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087119","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of 4 March 2019 by the hon. Member for South Shields, Official Report, column 749, when he plans to make a statement on the Government's response to the Food Insecurity Bill.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231484","231484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087120","2019-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2017 to Question 2035 on Ascension Island: Airports,  whether a timetable of works has been agreed with the US Department of Defense and the US Department of State on their plans for interim repair work and a full resurfacing programme of Wideawake airfield on Ascension Island.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231376","231376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087122","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of countries breaking UN sanctions on North Korea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231356","231356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087123","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his department has made of the adequacy of the current regulations on IGCSEs, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231357","231357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087124","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the level of gender-based pay inequality in the education sector in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231358","231358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087126","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 216183 on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Buildings, what his Department's rationale is for owning two properties with an asset value of over £5 million in Accra.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231400","231400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087127","2019-03-14","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's policy is on entitlement to child tax credits once a dependent in full-time education turns 19 years old.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231457","231457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087128","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 216183 on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Buildings, what his Department's rationale is for owning two properties with an asset value of over £5 million in Belgrade.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231401","231401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087130","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Democratic Republic of Congo on their response to the violent clashes in Yumbi territory in December 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231359","231359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087131","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will place in the Library a copy of correspondence in the last year between Ofqual and universities on International GCSEs.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231477","231477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087132","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 4 July 2018 to Question 157685 on South Sudan: Sanctions, whether the power to issue sanctions under the Magnitsky clauses contained in the Sanctions and Anti-Money Laundering Act 2018 would come into force (a) on the day the UK leaves the EU or (b) at the end of a transitional period.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231402","231402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087133","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of deaths that can be attributed to poor air quality in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231360","231360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087135","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the legal basis was for the Bank of England’s decision to freeze approximately 1125 gold bars stored by the Venezuelan central bank in November 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231403","231403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087136","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of women in prison on a sentence of imprisonment for public protection that have children.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231458","231458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087137","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Financial Conduct Authority in protecting people transferring out of pensions schemes.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231500","231500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087138","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many bovine tuberculosis (a) new herd incidents and (b) officially free status withdrawn cases there were in the (i) Gloucestershire 01, (ii) Somerset 02 and (iii) Dorset 03 badger cull areas in each calendar year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231354","231354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087139","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of schools in England operating on reduced hours by (a) closing schools on one day a week and (b) shortening the normal school day.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231503","231503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087141","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the  number of schools in England (a) have or (b) are planning to close their resource base provision for children with special educational needs.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231504","231504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087142","2019-03-15","Department for International Trade","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make it his Department's policy to exclude health services from all future trade agreements.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231559","231559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087143","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was for a hearing for a claimant appealing a personal independence payment decision in Leeds in 2018.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231560","231560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087145","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average wait is for personal independence payment claimants in Leeds to attend a tribunal hearing.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231561","231561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087146","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to 228561 on Housing: Construction, whether any local authorities in the Sheffield City Region will be eligible for funding under each of those proposals.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231365","231365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087147","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answers of 12 March 2019 to Question 229808 and Question 229809 on Energy: EU Law, whether Ofgem's licensing mechanisms to recover costs for a new REMIT system require energy suppliers to pay increased fees to Ofgem.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231524","231524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087148","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2019 to Question 226712 on Travellers: Caravan Sites, what steps his Department is taking to gather evidence for its review into how to criminalise the act of trespassing when setting up an unauthorised encampment; and what engagement is taking place between officials of his Department and members of the Gypsy and Traveller communities.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231459","231459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087149","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to improve information for (a) job seekers and (b) employees on the support available through Access to Work.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231374","231374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087151","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of claimant complaints relating to the late receipt of letters advising of appointments with health professionals which did not arrive in time to allow for claimants' attendance at such appointments in each year for which such data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231368","231368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087152","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Education of 11 March 2019, Official Report, column 12 on Support for Pupils with Special Educational Needs and Disabilities, what are the terms of reference of the root and branch review of restraint his Department is undertaking with the Department for Health and Social Care; and what plans he has to consult with (a) children, (b) parents and (c) representatives of interested organisations as part of that review.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231485","231485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087153","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2019 to Question 226647 on Medical Treatments, whether suppliers have confirmed that they have plans in place to air freight short shelf-life medicines, including medical radioisotopes, to avoid any border delays that may arise in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231423","231423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087154","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2019 to Question 226647 on Medical Treatments, from which budget would an increase to the list price of a branded medicine be met in the event that his Department agreed such an increase.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231424","231424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087155","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent progress has been made on resolving the dispute between HMRC and  the Roadchef  Employee Benefits Trust; and if he will publish a Written Statement on that matter after the meeting that will be held between those parties on 27 March 2019.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231409","231409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087157","2019-03-15","Cabinet Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's budget for communications was in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231478","231478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087158","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in the number of people under the age of 18 being prosecuted for possession of a knife (a) Wansbeck constituency, (b) the North East and (c) the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231469","231469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087159","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much his Department has spent on tackling knife crime in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231470","231470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087160","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will set out where in the building regulations or guidance issued by his Department before the Grenfell Tower fire it was made clear that the limited combustibility requirements in the guidance covered the core filler of a cladding panel.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231479","231479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087162","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which budget is being used to rectify underpayments of employment and support allowance is being drawn.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231501","231501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087163","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made a recent assessment of the effect on levels of building safety of private building control companies providing other building-related services on construction projects which they sign off as safe.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231480","231480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087164","2019-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department plans to take to respond to Lord Tyrie's recommendations on the future role of the Competition and Markets Authority; and what the timetable is for the implementation of that response.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231536","231536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087165","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many expressions of interest his Department received from private-sector providers in the Framework Agreement for the provision of prison operator services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231525","231525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087167","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish a list of the private-sector providers which submitted an expression of interest in his Department’s Framework Agreement for the provision of prison operator services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231526","231526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087168","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the library a copy of the Prison Operator Services Framework Competition document.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231527","231527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087169","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will legislate for the mandatory provision by local authorities of treatment for drug misuse.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231550","231550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087171","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons currently designated as resettlement prisons are operated by the private sector.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231528","231528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087172","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many privately operated prisons have a regime management plan in place.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231529","231529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087173","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the findings of the February 2019 National Aids Trust report, Drug-related Deaths in England, what steps his Department is taking to ensure adequate provision of naloxone for people at risk of overdose.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231551","231551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087174","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in which privately operated prison the approach of the use of a voluntary sector co-ordinator was developed and evaluated.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231530","231530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087175","2019-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what changes HMPPS has made to the training programme for new prison officers in privately operated prisons since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231531","231531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087177","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what changes private prison operators have requested to make to their training programmes for new prison officers since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231532","231532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087178","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the National Aids Trust report of 5 February 2019, Drug-related deaths in England, if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a national naloxone programme.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231552","231552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087179","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will support the provision of heroin-assisted treatment services throughout England.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231553","231553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087180","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of drug consumption rooms on (a) providing people with harm reduction information and advice and (b) supporting people to engage with a structured drug treatment.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231554","231554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087181","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Government’s Inclusive Transport Strategy published in July 2018, what progress he has made towards the target of making the UK’s transport network fully inclusive by 2030; what his policy is on the inclusion of people with dementia on the UK's transport network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231434","231434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087182","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 222793 on applications for looked-after children through the EU Settlement Scheme, how many of the 19 applications made on behalf of looked-after children were made by (a) local authorities and (b) supporting organisations.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231405","231405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087184","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to support the Alzheimer’s Society’s Dementia-friendly communities programme.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231435","231435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087185","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the HMRC's helpline established to help advise people affected by the introduction of the loan charge.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231502","231502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087186","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the time taken for each Emergency Travel Document application to be secured for a person in immigration detention for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231563","231563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087188","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress his Department has made in negotiations with Apple Inc. on the scanning of documents and passports on Apple mobile devices for non-UK EU citizens seeking to apply to remain in the UK after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231355","231355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087189","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 228762 on Revenue and Customs: Staff, how many staff were employed in HMRC's Operational Appeals and Reviews Units in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231508","231508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087190","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made on the effect on the supply chains of coeliac produce of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231369","231369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087191","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on whether Uighur Muslims in Chinese camps have been denied their basic human rights.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231509","231509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087193","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of the introduction of universal credit on disabled people.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231543","231543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087194","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of natural migration to universal credit on severely disabled people.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231544","231544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087195","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the cumulative impact of social security changes from 2010 on disabled people.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231545","231545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087197","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of benefit (a) sanctions and (b) conditionality on disabled people.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231546","231546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087198","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received on the welfare of Uigher Muslims being held in internment camps in China.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231510","231510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087199","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support young people with eating disorders transferring from children's to adult care services.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231568","231568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087201","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what engagement his Department has had with the eating disorder charity Beats.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231569","231569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087202","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department has made any assessment of the impact of the part-privatisation of building control on fire safety in residential buildings.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231481","231481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087203","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the difference in (a) treatments available and (b) waiting times between adult and children's services for patients with eating disorders.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231570","231570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087205","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of adding football to the PE curriculum for girls.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231571","231571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087206","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of changes in the level of take-up of the pupil premium in each year since 2015; and what assessment his Department has made of the causes for such changes in the level of take-up.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231556","231556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087207","2019-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2019 to Question 220113 on Warships: Procurement, whether he plans to classify the Littoral Strike Ship as a warship.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231534","231534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087208","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of (a) personal independence payment and (b) disability living allowance were (i) entitled to the £10 Christmas bonus and (ii) received that Christmas bonus in 2018.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231471","231471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087210","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have contacted her Department since 1 December 2018 on non-payment of the 2018 Christmas bonus.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231472","231472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087211","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences relating to drugs was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231412","231412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087212","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences for criminal damage was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231413","231413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087214","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences for breach of an anti-social behaviour order or criminal behaviour order was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231414","231414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087215","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences for fraud was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231415","231415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087216","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences for vehicle taking was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231416","231416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087217","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which offences had been committed by (a) male and (b) female offenders sentenced to immediate custody of up to six months who had not received a previous community order in (i) 2015, (ii) 2016 and (iii) 2017.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231417","231417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087218","2019-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the debate of 25 February 2019, on Exiting the European Union (Consumer Protection) motion debate, Official Report column 75, what progress has been made on setting up the IT system intended to support the establishment of UK REACH.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231418","231418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087219","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to reinstate East Midland Train services to Bedford.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231537","231537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087221","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of schools are rated (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires Improvement and (d) inadequate by Ofsted in each decile of income deprivation in which the school is located in each region.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231492","231492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087222","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of schools are rated (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requires Improvement and (d) Inadequate by Ofsted, in each region of the country, by decile of the proportion of pupils in the school eligible for and claiming free school meals.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231493","231493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087224","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of 5 March 2019 of the Chief Secretary to the Treasury, Official Report column 804, what the evidential basis is for her statement that the Government is increasing school funding in real terms per pupil.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231494","231494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087225","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what engagement with (a) patients, (b) the public and (c) other stakeholders NHS England undertook for the second phase of tendering PET-CT services across England.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231557","231557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087226","2019-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for developing Weeton Barracks into HQ North West as part of the 2016 Strategic Defence Estate Review.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231436","231436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087227","2019-03-15","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the total spend on legal representation for police (a) forces and (b) staff at inquests on people who have died as a result of police contact.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231533","231533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087228","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the British Ophthalmological Surveillance Unit report of February 2017 on sight loss caused by delayed or cancelled hospital appointments, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the Government's Green Paper on prevention includes measures to tackle changes in the incidence of eye disease.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231351","231351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087229","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England consulted (a) MPs, (b) cancer charities (c) doctors' groups and (d) cancer specialists during the second phase of the PET-CT services tendering process throughout England; and how many people were consulted during that process.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231558","231558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087231","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Oldham East and Saddleworth, Official Report column 969, how she plans to merge the personal independence payment and work capability assessment processes; who will take part in that merger; whether there will be (a) a pilot and (b) an independent evaluation of that merger; and who will provide that assessment service.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231473","231473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087232","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the medical records of claimants will be made available automatically to her Department as part of the new digital system for social security assessments.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231474","231474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087233","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to improve the (a) quality, (b) validity and (c) reliability of the (i) work capability and (ii) personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231475","231475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087235","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of leaving the EU without a deal on the supply of medicine for juvenile idiopathic arthritis.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231455","231455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087236","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Human Medicines (Amendment) Regulations 2019 on the NHS England Commissioning Framework for Biological Medicines in relation to changes in medicine without prior consultation with a patient.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231456","231456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087238","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of taxi licenses granted to drivers with criminal records in the last five years.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231453","231453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087239","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that rules, regulations and standards do not diverge in quality between local taxi licensing authorities.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231454","231454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087240","2019-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress is being made towards standardised training for doctors and health professionals on eating disorders.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231375","231375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087241","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions,  what proportion of universal credit claimants have verified their identity face-to-face in a jobcentre in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231352","231352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087242","2019-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what methods universal credit claimants can use to confirm their identity other than face-to-face at a jobcentre or using GOV.UK Verify.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231353","231353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087243","2019-03-15","Department for International Trade","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether it is his policy to exclude contracts for the delivery of (a) NHS and social care services and (b) other public services from future trade negotiations after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231460","231460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087245","2019-03-15","Department for International Trade","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether it is the Government's policy to support future trade agreement which will reduce existing (a) consumer, (b) environmental and (c) animal welfare protections.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231461","231461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087246","2019-03-15","Department for International Trade","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether it is his policy to support the inclusion of investor-state dispute settlement-style measures in future trade agreements.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231462","231462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087248","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he (a) is taking and (b) plans to take to encourage portion control in food and soft drinks.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231438","231438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087249","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a maximum portion size for soft drinks.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231439","231439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087250","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to promote greater consumer awareness on the importance of portion control in food and beverages.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231440","231440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087251","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people in prison serving a custodial sentences of less than six months had previously served a short prison sentence of less than six months.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231441","231441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087253","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number was of previous prison sentences of less than six months served by people currently in prison for (a) less than six months and (b) less than 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231442","231442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087254","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the most recent quarterly reoffending rate is for (a) men and (b) women serving less than six months in prison.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231443","231443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087255","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of people serving a prison sentence of less than six months have been assessed as having a mental health need in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231444","231444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087257","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time is to access an accredited drug treatment programme in prison in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231445","231445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087258","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how long it takes on average to deliver an accredited drug treatment programme in prison in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231446","231446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087259","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who have described themselves as transgender when seeking asylum in the UK have been refused asylum since 2015.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231447","231447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087261","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) gay, lesbian or bisexual and (b) transgender asylum seekers have been deported from the UK since 2015.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231448","231448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087262","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who described themselves as gay, lesbian or bisexual when seeking asylum in the UK have been refused asylum on the grounds that there is not enough evidence to prove that they are gay, lesbian or bisexual since 2015.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231449","231449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087263","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on forced live organ harvesting in China.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231450","231450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087265","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of persecution of people who practise Falun Gong in China.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231451","231451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087266","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the reported targeting of (a) Uighur Muslims, (b) Christians, (c) people who practise Falun Gong and (d) Tibetans for live organ harvesting in China.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231452","231452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087267","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the  Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2018 to Question 217546, on Down's Syndrome, what plans she has to address the effect of her Department's description of Down's Syndrome as an abnormality on (a) people with Down's Syndrome who read or hear that description and (b) familities who read or hear that description of a member of their family either before or after birth.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231430","231430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087268","2019-03-14","Women and Equalities","2019-03-12","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, following the Answer to 18 February 2019 to Question 217546 on Down's Syndrome: Abortion, what steps the Government Equalities Office is taking to ensure that women have a complete picture of all the options available to them.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231431","231431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087269","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions what research her Department has conducted on life for people with Down's Syndrome in the 21st century.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231432","231432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087271","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 February 2019 to Question 217546, on Down's Syndrome, what research his Department has conducted on the effect of screening for (a) sickle cell anaemia and (b) gene-linked deafness on people and families who live with those conditions.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231433","231433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087272","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken to reduce illegal immigration since 2010.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231564","231564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087273","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will place in the Library all impact assessments his Department has made of changes to the immigration system since 2010.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231565","231565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087275","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment the Government has made of the changes to the immigration system that increased immigration since 2010.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231566","231566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087276","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment the Government has made of the changes to the immigration system that reduced net immigration since 2010.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231567","231567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087277","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of schools in England that are not teaching a full school week.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231495","231495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087279","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department issues to schools on the length of the standard school week.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231496","231496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087280","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of school buildings with flammable cladding.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231497","231497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087281","2019-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to his oral contribution of 6 March 2019, Official Report, column 994, on the Swedish derogation, what representations he has received on the timing of the abolition of the Swedish derogation; and when he plans to respond to those representations.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231538","231538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087282","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received from (a) head teachers, (b) local authorities and (c) parents on reductions in school hours.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231498","231498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087284","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to revise Building Bulletin 100: Design for Fire Safety in Schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231499","231499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087285","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the written answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126694 on Schools: Fire Extinguishers, whether his Department has completed the further work that will enable him to provide figures on sprinklers fitted in all schools delivered centrally by the Education and Skills Funding Agency.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231539","231539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087286","2019-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229147 on Buildings: Insulation, whether his Department plans to test standard class High-Pressure Laminate panels or fire-retardant High-Pressure Laminate panels.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231482","231482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087287","2019-03-19","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in phase two of the Priority Schools Building Programme have now been designed; and what proportion of those designs include sprinkler systems for fire safety.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231540","231540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087289","2019-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in Iran on the sentencing of Nasrin Sotoudeh.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231542","231542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087290","2019-03-15","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new school buildings have been built in phase one of the Priority Schools Building Programme.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231541","231541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087291","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what additional funding for staff (a) his Department and (b) its agencies have received in allocated expenditure in respect of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231377","231377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087293","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons tandem mobility scooters are prohibited from using public roads and footpaths; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231372","231372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087294","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to use the Outer Islands of the Chagos Archipelago for defence purposes.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231378","231378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087295","2019-03-15","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to regulate UK-registered vehicles that display an EU flag on their number plates after the UK has left the EU; whether he plans to fine the owners of those vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231373","231373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087297","2019-03-15","Treasury","2019-03-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to design and mint a £1 coin celebrating the heritage of the Falklands as part of the new pound coin roll-out to British overseas territories.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231379","231379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087298","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to review the UK Visas and Immigration guidelines on English language testing for English-speaking Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231380","231380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087299","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking with his counterpart in the US Administration on the denuclearisation of North Korea.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231381","231381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087300","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to deepen ties with Commonwealth states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231382","231382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087302","2019-03-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the amount the UK would pay to the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231383","231383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087303","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Metropolitan Police on the effect on police performance of the tri-borough merger in Havering.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231384","231384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087304","2019-03-14","Department for International Development","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to help the Government of Tanzania to host 335,000 refugees.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231385","231385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087306","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the number of incidents involving firearms in the London Borough of Havering in the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231386","231386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087307","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of maintaining regulatory alignment and the Common External Tariff with the EU on the work of his Department.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231387","231387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087308","2019-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his department has made of the benefit to the public purse of the outsourcing deal with Capita for military recruiting and associated IT systems.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231388","231388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087309","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has made an assessment of the possible merits of implementing Scotland's Violence Reduction Unit strategy in London in order to tackle knife crime.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231389","231389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087310","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the number of incidents involving armed burglary in the London Borough of Havering in the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231390","231390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087311","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the effect of toxic fumes from shipping.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231391","231391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087313","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to take further steps to deter dog smuggling into the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231392","231392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087314","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what additional funding for staff (a) his Department and (b) its agencies have received from EU exit funding.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231393","231393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087315","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's policy is on American food standards in relation to a UK-US trade deal after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231394","231394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1087317","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding for staff (a) his Department and (b) its agencies have received from EU exit funding.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231395","231395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088822","2019-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the UK has made to Israel on the effect of that country's blockade on the Gaza Strip on Palestinian refugees in Gaza.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232606","232606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1085844","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-11","When his Department plans to publish a response to its call for evidence on home education.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909689","909689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1085845","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-11","What recent assessment he has made of the effect of fines for unauthorised school absence on school attendance levels.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909690","909690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1085846","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-11","What recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on additional funding for rural schools.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909694","909694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1085847","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-11","What recent progress his Department has made on helping families to access childcare.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909697","909697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086472","2019-03-13","Cabinet Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been diagnosed with testicular cancer in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230728","230728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086473","2019-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what cold weather equipment his Department provides to soldiers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230729","230729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086474","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support his Department provides to young mothers with breast cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230730","230730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086475","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of implementing a READ code for chronic pain.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230731","230731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086476","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the security and safety of journalists throughout the world.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230732","230732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086477","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce rates of alcoholism among women.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230733","230733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086478","2019-03-13","Cabinet Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have died as a result of a flu-related illness in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230734","230734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086479","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has made an estimate of the number of secondary breast cancer patients who do not have access to a clinical nurse specialist or other support worker.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230735","230735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086480","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Government's policing and security policies of the ECHR decision in Catt v UK Government.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230736","230736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086481","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when criminal legal aid remuneration rates were last raised in real terms for legal professionals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230737","230737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086482","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of low remuneration rates for criminal solicitors on recruitment to the profession.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230738","230738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086483","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who his Department is consulting with as part of its review into criminal legal aid fees.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230739","230739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086484","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the continued viability of the criminal legal aid sector while his review of criminal legal aid fees is ongoing.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230740","230740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086485","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  what assessment he has made of the effect on justice of the limit on what can be paid through the Legal Aid Agency for experts’ reports in criminal cases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230741","230741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086486","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to require local authorities to ensure that school staff who teach young people with vision impairment have appropriate training from a specialist.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230742","230742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086487","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Administration on that country's diplomatic relationship with the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia following the murder of Jamal Khashoggi.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230743","230743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086488","2019-03-13","Department for International Development","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has allocated to Uganda in each of the last three years; what projects that funding supports; and whether her Department has experienced issues with corruption in Uganda over that period.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230856","230856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086489","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress he has made on (a) increasing the number of and (b) improving support for foster carers since the Fostering better outcomes report published in July 2018.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230857","230857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086490","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2019 to Question 227401 on HIV, what the timetable is for the rollout of additional places on the Pre-exposure Prophylaxis Impact trial in London .","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230858","230858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086491","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families in receipt of the lower child disability addition have transitioned from legacy benefits to universal credit.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230744","230744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086492","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 214022 on Courts: Closures, for how many years do staff who move their work location to an alternative court as part of the Estates Rationalisation Programme have access to the Excess Fares Allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230664","230664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086493","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has commissioned any research into changes to journey times to courts for (a) witnesses, (b) victims of crime and (c) court staff in areas where courts have closed as a result of the Estate Rationalisation Programme.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230665","230665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086494","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families are in receipt of the lower child disability addition on universal credit for (a) one child (b) two children and (c) three or more children.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230745","230745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086495","2019-03-13","Department for International Trade","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the level of international investment in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230604","230604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086496","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will meet representatives of the campaign group WorthLess? to discuss school funding.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230746","230746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086497","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times he has met representatives of school head teachers since he took office.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230747","230747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086498","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2019 to Question 226472 on Asthma: Prescriptions, what the prescription charge exemptions are for which someone with asthma may qualify.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230632","230632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086499","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the viability of removing all asbestos from schools.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230666","230666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086500","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts were affected by the temporary failure of the Crown Court Digital Case System during the week commencing 4 March 2019.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230667","230667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086501","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Crown Court Digital Case System is operated by HM Courts and Tribunals Service or contracted to a third-party supplier.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230668","230668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086502","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Salford residents are in prison.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230748","230748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086503","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women from Salford are in prison.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230749","230749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086504","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with head teachers on the funding situation in all state schools.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230859","230859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086505","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons house different categories of prisoner.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230750","230750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086506","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners there are in each category of prisoner.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230751","230751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086507","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners reside in each prison by region.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230752","230752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086508","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many residents of Salford are in prison by category type.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230753","230753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086509","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners there are by local authority of origin.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230754","230754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086510","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were charged with possession of cannabis in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230860","230860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086511","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2018 to Question 196793 on  Ministry of Justice: Public Expenditure, for what reason the annual real terms increase/(decrease) is -2% and the cumulative real terms decrease is 3% in 2011-12.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230861","230861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086512","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much has been spent on agency and locum staff in the NHS (a) in total, (b) for each job type and (c) in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230755","230755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086513","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2019 to Question 223981, what information he provides to primary schools on how they can meet their duties under the Equality Act 2010 and Public Sector Equality Duty if they choose to omit LGBT families from relationship education teaching.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230669","230669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086514","2019-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many video games businesses have breached the Competition and Markets Authority’s set of Principles for Online and App-based Games since 2014; and how many of those businesses were British games companies.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230633","230633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086515","2019-03-13","Department for International Development","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the potential implications for her policies of the recommendation to use international meetings and events including the UN High Level Political Forum to press other governments and international organisations to take action on intersecting inequalities in education in the Send My Friend to School report, Unlock education for everyone: delivering the pledge to leave no one behind in education published on 11 February 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230608","230608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086516","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many UK hauliers travelled to and from other EU countries in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230670","230670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086517","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many ECMT permits are available in the current window for applications.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230671","230671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086518","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency has made of the number of ECMT permit applications it will receive during the current window for applications.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230672","230672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086519","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applications for ECMT permits during the last window for applications were (a) received and (b) successful.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230756","230756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086520","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what bilateral agreements the UK has with the Republic of Ireland with respect to hauliers; and whether hauliers will be required to have ECMT permits to travel to the Republic of Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230757","230757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086521","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance he has provided to the police on street preachers; and what lessons have been learned from the arrest and subsequent release of Oluwole Ilesanmi in Enfield.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230673","230673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086522","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the arrest and release of Oluwole Ilesanmi in Enfield, what steps he is taking to ensure that church groups can preach on the street.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230674","230674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086523","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Rent Repayment Orders have been made by each of the five regional First-Tier residential property tribunals under (a) section 44, (b) section 45 and (c) section 46 of the Housing and Planning Act 2016.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230862","230862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086524","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what services will be provided at the women’s centre to be built on the former site of HMP Holloway.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230758","230758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086525","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department expects the women’s centre to be built on the former site of HMP Holloway to be opened.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230759","230759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086526","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women his Department expects the women’s centre to be built on the former site of HMP Holloway will provide services for (a) each month and (b) each year.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230760","230760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086527","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has identified an operator for the women’s centre to be built on the former site of HMP Holloway.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230761","230761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086528","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the money from the sale of the former site of HMP Holloway will be paid to his Department in a single instalment.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230762","230762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086529","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding the Government expects to make available each year to the women’s centre to be opened on the former site of HMP Holloway.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230763","230763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086530","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the profits from the sale of the former site of HMP Holloway will be invested by the Government in (a) existing women’s centres, (b) expanding the number of women’s centres, (c) existing female prisons, (d) existing male prisons, (e) new female prisons, (f) new male prisons, (g) other services operated by HMPPS, (h) other services operated by his Department and (i) other areas of expenditure.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230764","230764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086531","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions there were for (a) crimes involving the use of knives; (b) crimes involving the use of firearms and (c) all violent crimes in 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230765","230765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086532","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms were from a BAME background in 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230766","230766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086533","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders under the age of 18 convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 had previously been excluded from school.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230767","230767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086534","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders aged 18 to 25 convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 had previously been excluded from school.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230768","230768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086535","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 had previously been convicted for violent offences.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230769","230769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086536","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 have been identified as suffering with mental health issues.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230770","230770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086537","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 have been identified as having substance misuse issues.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230771","230771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086538","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 had been unemployed at the time of their offence.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230772","230772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086539","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 had previously been convicted for drug-related offences.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230773","230773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086540","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 lived in households where one or more parent was unemployed.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230774","230774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086541","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 lived in households where one or more parent was employed on contracts with no fixed hours of work.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230775","230775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086542","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders convicted of crimes involving the use of (a) knives and (b) firearms in 2018 lived in households identified as below the poverty line.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230776","230776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086543","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what railway franchises currently operate under a direct award contract; and for each such franchise when the contract (a) become live and (b) is due to expire.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230777","230777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086544","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 February 2019 to Question 221788, what the final legal costs are with respect to the court proceedings and the subsequent settlement agreed with Eurotunnel.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230778","230778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086545","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to tackle excessive fees charged to freehold homeowners by developers for maintaining common areas in housing estates.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230675","230675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086546","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his forthcoming legislation on excessive fees charged in relation to leasehold homes will also regulate charges levied on the owners of freehold homes by developers for maintaining common areas in housing estates.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230676","230676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086547","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on tackling excessive charges levied on the owners of leasehold homes.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230677","230677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086548","2019-03-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the legislation he plans to bring forward to tackle excessive charges levied on leaseholders will apply to existing arrangements or only to new homes completed after the legislation comes into force.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230678","230678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086549","2019-03-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to introduce legislative proposals to replicate the provisions of the Freehold Properties (Management Charges and Shared Facilities) Bill 2017-19 introduced by the Hon Member for Bishop Auckland.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230679","230679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086550","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Written Statement of 7 January 2019, Haulage Update, HCWS 1233, how much and what proportion of the monies awarded to (a) Brittany Ferries and (b) DFDS for the contingency transport provisions outlined in that Written Statement will be retained by the public purse in the event that the UK agrees a withdrawal agreement with the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230779","230779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086551","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what instructions he has issued to the Commissioner of the British Indian Ocean Territory on the advisory opinion of the International Court of Justice of 25 February 2019.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230780","230780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086552","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of CCGs in commissioning therapeutic services for survivors of sexual abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230781","230781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086553","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of their budget CCGs have spent on therapeutic services for survivors of sexual abuse.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230782","230782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086554","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what ordinances the Commissioner for the British Indian Ocean Territory has issued in 2019; and what additional legislative proposals are planned following the February 2019 advisory opinion of the International Court of Justice.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230783","230783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086555","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to have discussions with his counterpart in Mauritius before a decision is made on scientific work in the (a) Chagos Islands and (c) exclusive economic zone declared by Mauritius around those islands.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230784","230784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086556","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans the (a) British Indian Ocean Territory Commissioner and (b) his staff have to visit the Chagos Archipelago in 2019.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230785","230785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086557","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made any disposals of land under section 14 of the British Indian Ocean Territory (Constitution) Order 2004.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230786","230786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086558","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria he has to assess before making a decision on the disposal of land under section 14 of the British Indian Ocean Territory (Constitution) Order 2004.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230787","230787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086559","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants have been employed in primary schools in West Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230863","230863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086560","2019-03-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of maintaining a five-year land supply on the ability of local authorities to reject planning applications.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230864","230864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086561","2019-03-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of homeless veterans in Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230865","230865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086562","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much money has been allocated from the public purse to the National Park Authorities in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230866","230866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086563","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government,  how much has been spent on the Rough Sleeping Initiative in Yorkshire and the Humber in each month of financial year 2018-19.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230867","230867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086564","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are currently waiting for a decision on leave to remain as a stateless person in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230868","230868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086565","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has in place to ensure that people in Yorkshire of all categories of (a) gender, (b) sexuality, (c) age and (d) ethnicity and background with an eating disorder are able to access treatment and support.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230869","230869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086566","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has plans to (a) undertake a review the decision by the Health and Care Professions Council on 14 February 2019 to increase subscription fees for allied health professionals and (b) make an assessment of the effect of that decision on trends in the level of employees in that sector.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230870","230870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086567","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many puppies have been seized and taken into quarantine since the Animal and Plant Health Agency established an intelligence team to gather data, intelligence and information on the illegal movement of dogs and puppies in 2015.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230871","230871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086568","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many animals have been transported to mainland Europe for slaughter in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230872","230872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086569","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2018 to Question 155669 on Livestock: Exports, whether he has plans to include a ban on live animal exports for fattening.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230873","230873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086570","2019-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants took advance payments during the five-week waiting period for their first universal credit payment in (a) October, (b) November and (c) December 2018 in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230874","230874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086571","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been prosecuted for causing death by dangerous driving in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230788","230788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086572","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of causing death by dangerous driving in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230789","230789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086573","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of causing death by dangerous driving received a suspended sentence in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230790","230790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086574","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average prison sentence given to people jailed for causing death by dangerous driving was in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230791","230791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086575","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of causing death by dangerous driving received the maximum 14 year jail sentence in each of the last five calendar years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230792","230792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086576","2019-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions Tornado aircraft have been returned from Saudi Arabia to the UK for maintenance or refit since March 2015.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230875","230875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086577","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average length of time is for HS2 Ltd to answer complaints.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230602","230602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086578","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many claims have been received under the Small Claims Scheme for HS2; what the status is of each claim; and where what the remedy awarded was for each approved claim.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230603","230603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086579","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many complaints have been made for noise disturbance from HS2 works in each of the past two years.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230605","230605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086580","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2019 to Question 226169 on Hinkley Point B Power Station: Closures, what plans the Government has to replace the 965 megawatts generation capacity of Hinkley Point B; and what the timescales are for implementing the replacement of that capacity.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230793","230793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086581","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2019 to Question 226166 on Hartlepool Power Station: Closures, what plans the Government has to replace the 1185 MW generation capacity of Hartlepool; and what the timescales are for the replacement of that capacity.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230794","230794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086582","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March to Question 226167 on Heysham 1 Power Station: Closures, what plans the Government has to replace the 1155 megawatts generation capacity of Heysham 1; and what the timescales are for that replacement capacity.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230795","230795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086583","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when Ofsted plans to carry out a monitoring inspection of the John Roan secondary school in the Royal Borough of Greenwich.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230876","230876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086584","2019-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many meetings she had with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230634","230634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086585","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment of the implications for his policies of the March 2019 UK Onshore Oil and Gas report entitled Home grown UK shale gas: a bigger opportunity; and whether he has made an estimate of the date on which the UK will become a net exporter of gas.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230606","230606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086586","2019-03-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of current access rights to water on paddlesport participation in England.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230877","230877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086587","2019-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230878","230878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086588","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding has been allocated to (a) Mansfield and (b) Nottinghamshire from the Pothole Action Fund in each year since that fund's inception.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230879","230879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086589","2019-03-14","Department for International Development","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by her Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230880","230880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086590","2019-03-14","Women and Equalities","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by her Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230881","230881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086591","2019-03-14","Department for International Development","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many suppliers were excluded from bidding for contracts due to failing the meet the criteria specified in Procurement Policy Note 03/14 by (a) Government Department and (b) year since 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230882","230882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086592","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has in place to (a) expedite agri-environment funding (i) applications and (ii) claims and (b) review rates of reward for the production of public goods to tackle the effect on the cash flow of organic farmers of leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230680","230680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086593","2019-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK military personnel on exchange programmes with the US Air Force are working in (a) in Yemen (b) in the skies above Yemen.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230883","230883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086594","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Sudanese counterpart on human rights in that country, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230616","230616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086595","2019-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of providing a plane on standby at RAF Northolt for use by the Prime Minister from 8 to 11 March 2019 inclusive.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230681","230681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086596","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has held with the Secretary of State for International Trade on the potential role of the NHS in future trade deals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230617","230617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086597","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of companies who have transferred the apprenticeship levy in London.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230796","230796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086598","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the level of political stability in Algeria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230618","230618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086599","2019-03-14","Treasury","2019-03-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what statutory basis a bank is able to close an account without disclosure to the customer concerned.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230884","230884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086600","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate his Department has made of the annual cost of providing free sanitary products to all girls in secondary schools in England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230619","230619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086601","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the regulation of the new-build sector in relation to snagging issues.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230885","230885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086602","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 7 March 2019 on Immigration Rules, HCWS1388, what criteria his Department plans to use to determine suitability for the category of start-up visa.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230620","230620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086603","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 7 March 2019 on Immigration Rules given by the Minister for Immigration on 7 March 2019, HCWS1388, what criteria his Department plans to use to determine the suitability for (a) an extension of an existing visa and (b) accelerated settlement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230621","230621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086604","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what financial and non-financial support the Government has provided to the Coalition Joint Impact Assessment Team in Yemen in (a) 2017, (b) 2018 and (c) 2019 to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230622","230622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086605","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assurances he received from the internationally recognised Government in Yemen that humanitarian aid is able to reach Yemeni citizens during his visit to Yemen on 3 March 2019.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230623","230623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086606","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of UK citizens living in refugee camps in (a) Iraq, (b) Jordan, (c) Lebanon, (d) Syria and (e) Turkey.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230624","230624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086607","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings he held with civil-society organisations during his visit to Yemen on 3 March 2019.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230625","230625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086608","2019-03-13","Department for International Development","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate her Department has made of the number of Yemenis who have migrated from Saudi Arabia to Yemen in (a) 2017, (b) 2018 and (c) 2019 to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230626","230626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086609","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will ensure that (a) the NHS and (b) other public services are excluded from future trade deals.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230627","230627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086610","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the finding in Asthma UK's report, The Reality of Asthma Care in the UK -  Annual Asthma Survey 2018 that two-thirds of patients do not receive a follow-up appointment with their GP after receiving emergency care, if he will take steps tackle the reasons for that finding.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230635","230635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086611","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what funding the Government can provide to local councils to replace unreliable and ageing district heating systems.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230797","230797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086612","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of red-X non-compliance on smart motorways for each of the last two years for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230682","230682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086613","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were killed or seriously injured on the roadside when they were in the presence of a stationary vehicle using a warning beacon emitting a flashing red light in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230683","230683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086614","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were killed or seriously injured on the roadside when they were in the presence of a stationary vehicle using a warning beacon emitting flashing an amber light in each of the last 10 years for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230684","230684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086615","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were killed or seriously injured working alongside a stationary vehicle using a flashing amber warning beacon permitted for the purpose of (a) collecting refuse, (b) road clearance, (c) inspecting, cleansing, maintaining, adjusting, renewing or installing any apparatus which is in, on, under or over a road, (d) testing, maintaining, improving, cleansing or watering roads and (e) surveying in each of the last 10 years for which data is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230685","230685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086616","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make a comparative risk assessment of the safety of a vehicle stopping in a running lane during off peak times on (a) an all lane running motorway and (b) a traditional motorway with a hard shoulder.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230686","230686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086617","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's Clean Growth Strategy, what estimate he has made of the amount and proportion of the £3.6 billion Energy Company Obligation that will be allocated to the West Midlands metro area; over what time period that allocation will be spent; and what estimate he has made of the number of homes that will benefit from that allocation.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230636","230636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086618","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many privately owned vehicles are registered in the West Midlands metro area; and how many of those vehicles are electric vehicles.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230637","230637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086619","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what funding has been allocated to the West Midlands Combined Authority for the expansion of electric vehicle charging infrastructure; and over what time period that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230638","230638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086620","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the UK’s renewable energy supply in the last 12 months was generated from the West Midlands metro area.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230639","230639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086621","2019-03-13","Department for International Trade","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to help ensure that the NHS and other public services will not be included in future trade agreements for services after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230886","230886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086622","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to Answer of 4 March 2019 to Question 228139 on Special Educational Needs: Finance, whether he plans to launch his Department's call for evidence looking into the financial incentives in the SEND system by 14 June 2019.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230798","230798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086623","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when (a) he or (b) one of his Ministers give evidence to the All-Party Parliamentary Group on heritage rail for its inquiry into the potential effect on UK heritage railways of the proposals in the Government consultation on the cleaner domestic burning of solid fuels and wood; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230687","230687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086624","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children there are in households directly affected by the two-child limit on welfare payments in (a) Wallasey and (b) Wirral.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230640","230640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086625","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many successful appeals there have been against decisions on (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment claims in (a) Wallasey, (b) Wirral, (c) Liverpool city region and (d) the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230641","230641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086626","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many successful mandatory reconsiderations there have been of decisions on (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment claims in (a) Wallasey, (b) Wirral, (c) Liverpool city region and (d) the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230642","230642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086627","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number was of previous community orders given to an offender sentenced to immediate custody for a new offence of up to six months in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230688","230688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086628","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what main offence each prisoner given a sentence of six months or less was imprisoned in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230689","230689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086629","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February to Question 223184 on Sentencing, which of the offences listed his Department has classified as so grave that no other penalty but custody will suffice (a) as a single offence, (b) after multiple previous offences and (c) after multiple previous similar offences.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230690","230690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086630","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the effect on the sentencing decision of an offender's previous (a) convictions and (b) community orders under his proposals for a presumption against short-term prison sentences.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230691","230691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086631","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of removing the option of custody for some offences on the (a) level of compliance with community orders and (b) use of suspended sentences.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230692","230692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086632","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number was of recorded breaches of a single community order in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230693","230693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086633","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number was of breaches of all previous community orders by an offender with a further breach of an order in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230694","230694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086634","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether credits for approved training can be used towards (a) the second contribution condition for contribution-based employment and support allowance and (b) contribution-based jobseeker’s allowance.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230695","230695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086635","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to increase modern foreign language provision in schools.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230799","230799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086636","2019-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of youth centres that have closed in England since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230800","230800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086637","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the average waiting time for a PET-CT scan in (a) Oxford West and Abingdon constituency, (b) Oxfordshire and (c) England.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230887","230887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086638","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average prison sentence was for (a) possession of a blade or point and (b) threatening with a blade or point in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230696","230696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086639","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences a (a) male and (b) female offender committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230697","230697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086640","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences for possession of a blade or point a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230698","230698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086641","2019-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the total reduction in central Government funding for youth services provided by local authorities in England since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230801","230801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086642","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous offences for possession of an offensive weapon was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230699","230699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086643","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the number of children daily reading unaided in England.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230802","230802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086644","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous offences for assault was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230700","230700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086645","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to estimate the number of children in England who were permanently excluded from a school and did not return to full time education in in the academic year 2017-2018.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230803","230803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086646","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous offences for assaulting a police officer was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230701","230701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086647","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous offences for sexual assault was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230702","230702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086648","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous offences relating to the Public Order Act was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230703","230703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086649","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences for theft was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230704","230704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086650","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences for robbery was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230705","230705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086651","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences for burglary was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230706","230706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086652","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of total previous offences for benefit fraud was that a person committed before being given an immediate custodial sentence for that offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230707","230707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086653","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of providing PET-CT scanning services through a (a) private contractor and (b) a NHS trust.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230888","230888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086654","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has plans to make (a) the Advisory, Conciliation and Arbitration Service and (b) other services more accessible for non-English speaking workers.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230889","230889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086655","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to increase the resources allocated to labour inspection and labour law enforcement.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230890","230890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086656","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference the speech by the Minister of State for School Standards on the importance of knowledge-based education, delivered on 19 October 2017, what steps he is taking to ensure that classroom music teachers teach within their area of specialism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230708","230708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086657","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has any plans to increase the resources of the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230891","230891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086658","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage singing in schools.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230709","230709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086659","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost to the public purse is of a successful appeal for personal independence payment.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230643","230643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086660","2019-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to to reduce the number of claimants' successful claims that go through the tribunal appeal process.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230644","230644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086661","2019-03-13","Treasury","2019-03-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme in helping domestic film production companies raise funding.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230892","230892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086662","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal principal investigators in receipt of European Research Council funding who are based outside the UK will qualify for the Government's Horizon 2020 underwrite if they move their research base to the UK (a) before or (b) after the date of EU exit.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230645","230645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086663","2019-03-13","Cabinet Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on social media advertising related to the UK leaving the EU in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230804","230804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086664","2019-03-13","Department for International Trade","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on food imports from the US of the United States-European Union Negotiations: Summary of Specific Negotiating Objectives, published by the Office of the United States Trade representative in February 2019.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230805","230805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086665","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many radiotherapy centres deliver stereotactic body radiation therapy.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230710","230710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086666","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had recent discussions with the Welsh Government on the safety of horse riders on UK roads; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230893","230893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086667","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding he has allocated for police training to South Wales Police in 2019.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230894","230894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086668","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women were given a custodial sentence of under six months in (a) England (b) Wales in each year between 2010 and 2018.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230895","230895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086669","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to support the extension of stereotactic body radiation therapy services for lung cancer in radiotherapy centres throughout England.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230711","230711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086670","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to support the extension of stereotactic body radiation therapy services for lung cancer in radiotherapy centres throughout England.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230712","230712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086671","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will make an estimate of the number of cancer centres that will be delivering stereotactic body radiation therapy services by (a) 2020 and (b) 2029.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230713","230713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086672","2019-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Royal Navy vessel or vessels acted as the designated Fleet Ready Escort from 1 January to 8 March 2019.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230806","230806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086673","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2018 to Question 170339 on Ilois Finance, how much of the £40 million fund for Chagossians has been allocated to date; to whom that funding has been allocated; and for what purposes that money has been allocated.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230807","230807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086674","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary schools have specialist arts teachers.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230808","230808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086675","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans the Government has to provide dance and drama as subject areas in their own right at primary schools as recommended by the independent review, Cultural Education in England, published in 2012.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230809","230809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086676","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupil premium funding is spent by schools on artistic and cultural activities.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230810","230810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086677","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on childcare support for parents of ill or premature babies.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230896","230896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086678","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help support (a) older people and (b) people with (i) mental and (ii) physical health conditions to transition to universal credit.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230646","230646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086679","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Chagos Conservation Trust has returned any unspent funds that were provided by his Department for the purposes of the Chagossian Outreach Programme; and how much in total (a) was and (b) remains to be provided for that programme.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230811","230811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086680","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress his Department has made on ensuring that the UK meets its target of spending 2.4 per cent of GDP on R&D by 2027.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230812","230812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086681","2019-03-14","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress the Government is making on bringing forward legislative proposals on longer sentences for drivers who cause death by dangerous driving; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230628","230628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086682","2019-03-14","Cabinet Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to increase neurodiversity within the Government Digital Service.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230897","230897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086683","2019-03-14","Cabinet Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what mandatory cybersecurity courses are offered by the GDS Academy.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230898","230898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086684","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 5.16 of the Budget 2018 Red Book, what proportion of the £410 million for adult and children's social care will be allocated to Wirral Council.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230647","230647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086685","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when his Department plans to publish its response to the review into air weapons which was launched on 10 October 2017.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230648","230648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086686","2019-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the two space-based infra-red system radomes at NSA/NRO Menwith Hill are a fully operational part of the US missile defence system.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230899","230899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086687","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the UK is not seen as a safe haven for people suspected of committing international crimes.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230649","230649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086688","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the resources of the (a) Metropolitan Police and (b) CPS to (i) investigate and (ii) prosecute people residing in the UK who are suspected of committing international crimes; and if he will ensure that the investigation and prosecution of such individuals is prioritised.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230650","230650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086689","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the High Court decision not to extradite to Rwanda persons suspected of involvement in the 1994 genocide against the Tutsis, what steps the (a) Metropolitan Police and (b) CPS have taken to comply with the Government's obligations under national and international law to investigate and prosecute acts of genocide.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230651","230651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086690","2019-03-14","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to her oral contribution of 6 March 2019, Official Report column 949, that polls that they want to see change to the abortion laws in Northern Ireland—about 64%—are very clear that they want those changes to be made in Stormont, what the source is of that data.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230813","230813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086691","2019-03-13","Treasury","2019-03-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of UK SMEs with a turnover of £85,000 or more are prepared for the transfer to digital VAT records due to take effect in April 2019.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230714","230714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086692","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the report entitled, The Disability Price Tag 2019, published by Scope in February 2019, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that all families with disabled children receive adequate support under universal credit to help meet additional costs.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230652","230652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086693","2019-03-13","Treasury","2019-03-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on SMEs of the cost of purchasing software to meet the forthcoming online digital VAT records obligation.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230715","230715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086694","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the clinical effectiveness of low carbohydrate diets in reducing the risk of type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230814","230814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086695","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to ensure Clinical Commissioning Groups use consistent criteria in relation to the clinical effectiveness of low carbohydrate diets when making local commissioning decisions .","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230815","230815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086696","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what long term digital support his Department is providing for (a) people who are in remission from and (b) those at highest risk of type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230816","230816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086697","2019-03-13","Treasury","2019-03-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people not signed up to the transfer deadline for digital VAT records can sign up without a penalty or receive an extension.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230716","230716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086698","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to extend funding for the Syrian Vulnerable Person Resettlement Scheme beyond 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230629","230629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086699","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support family reunification as part of the Syrian Vulnerable Person Resettlement Scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230630","230630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086700","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities seeking to facilitate family reunification as part of the Syrian Vulnerable Person Resettlement Scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230653","230653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086701","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Syrian Vulnerable Person Resettlement Scheme, if he will expand the definition of a family unit beyond a spouse and minor children of a refugee.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230654","230654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086702","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of seasonal workers employed in Cornwall in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230817","230817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086703","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to consult with organisations from the higher education, further education and school sectors on the forthcoming recommendations of the post-18 education and funding review.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230900","230900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086704","2019-03-14","Cabinet Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) men and (b) women have died from anaphylaxis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230717","230717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086705","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children achieved five GCSEs graded A - C in each year for the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230718","230718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086706","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government’s commitment not to impose a cap on the number of students that can access post-18 education applies to all forms of post-18 education.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230901","230901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086707","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of looked-after children achieved five GCSEs graded A - C in each year for the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230719","230719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086708","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NICE diagnostics guidance DG27, when NHS England plans to decide whether it will prioritise genetic testing for Lynch syndrome; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230720","230720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086709","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what percentage of children in each reception class intake in each of the last 20 years have been in care.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230721","230721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086710","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what percentage of children in care have been (a) cautioned, (b) charged and (c) come into contact with the criminal justice system each year for the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230722","230722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086711","2019-03-14","Department for International Development","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in the al-Hol refugee camp in Syria; and what steps her Department is taking to support refugees within that camp.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230609","230609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086712","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number of individuals charged with crimes involving the production of cannabis for each year between 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230902","230902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086713","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his department has made of the number of individuals charged with crimes involving the distribution of cannabis for each year between 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230903","230903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086714","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the rate of recidivism for individuals charged with crimes involving the possession of cannabis for each year between 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230904","230904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086715","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his department has made of the rate of recidivism for individuals charged with crimes involving the production of cannabis for each year between 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230905","230905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086716","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his department had made of the rate of recidivism for individuals charged with crimes involving the distribution of cannabis for each year between 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230906","230906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086717","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to reduce the rate of recidivism for people convicted of possession of cannabis.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230907","230907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086718","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to the rate of recidivism for people convicted of production of cannabis.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230908","230908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086719","2019-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to reduce the rate of recidivism for people convicted of distribution of cannabis.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230909","230909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086720","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to promote vaping products as an effective way for smokers to quit smoking.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230723","230723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086721","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to tackle the decline in hedgehog numbers in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230910","230910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086722","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money from the public purse was allocated to the national drug treatment monitoring system by the Government in each year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230911","230911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086723","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to encourage smokers to switch to vaping products.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230724","230724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086724","2019-03-14","Cabinet Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to obtain agreement from the EU to an extension of the Article 50 period to enable (a) public and (b) parliamentary consideration of the outcome of the National Crime Agency investigation into possible collusion between prominent Leave campaigners and the Russian Government during the 2016 referendum campaign.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230725","230725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086725","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that local authorities are delivering value for money through their management of county council smallholding estates.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230610","230610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086726","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government last carried out an assessment of the performance of local authorities in delivering the objective for county council smallholding estates as set out in section 39 of the Agriculture Act 1970.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230611","230611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086727","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether recent disposals of county council smallholding estates have delivered the greatest possible return for the taxpayer.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230612","230612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086728","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to assist local authorities in the management of their county council smallholding estates for the benefit of new entrant and progressing farmers.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230613","230613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086729","2019-03-14","Treasury","2019-03-11","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that HMRC uses the rule of law rather than an opinion of fairness to determine what is payable for the loan charge.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230655","230655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086730","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the African Union and the Government of South Sudan on the UN Human Rights Council report on the human rights situation in South Sudan.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230818","230818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086731","2019-03-14","Cabinet Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with relation to the oral contribution from the Prime Minister on 20th February 2019 in Volume 654, Column 1465, whether the  commitment to waiving legal privilege in respect to the Infected Blood Inquiry was made on behalf of all Government Departments or just the Department of Health and Social Care.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230912","230912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086732","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the universities of Oxford and Cambridge on the implications of the findings of the Sutton Trust report on Access to Advantage for his Department's policies.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230819","230819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086733","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on affordable and social housing of expanding permitted development rights to include demolitions.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230913","230913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086734","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the nutritional value of hospital meals.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230820","230820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086735","2019-03-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of extending permitted development rights to include demolitions on his Department's plans to halve homelessness in this parliament.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230914","230914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086736","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what comparative analysis his Department has made of the quality of housing developments brought about through (a) permitted development rights and (b) the full planning system.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230915","230915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086737","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of homeless families housed in temporary accommodation which has been converted into residential use through the permitted development rights process.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230916","230916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086738","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of times hospital wards have closed to maintain safe staffing levels for each of the last ten years for which records are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230821","230821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086739","2019-03-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of homes delivered through permitted development rights that have been found to not comply with building regulations in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230917","230917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086740","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the income from NHS patients by NHS trusts in each of the last 10 years for which records are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230822","230822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086741","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data his Department holds on (a) the number of independent reviews for NHS Continuing Healthcare that have been undertaken for each year and (b) the length of time taken to complete those reviews in each of the last 10 years for which records are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230823","230823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086742","2019-03-14","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Fourteenth Report of the Defence Committee entitled Mental Health and the Armed Forces, Part Two: The Provision of Care, published on 19 February 2019, what plans his Department has to reform the medical and mental health services provided through the (a) RAF, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Army.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230824","230824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086743","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to improve mental healthcare for veterans in the North East.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230825","230825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086744","2019-03-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an estimate of the number of new properties that could be built if the housing revenue account borrowing cap was removed.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230826","230826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086745","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many golden hello incentives have been made to nursing students; and how much in total has been spent on that scheme since it was announced in May 2018.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230827","230827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086746","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the  Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fines have been issued for littering in each of the last 10 years for which records are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230828","230828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086747","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2019 to Question 227098 on Pre-School Education: Closures, how much of the £26.3 million investment in the network of English Hubs has been allocated in each (a) region and (b) local authority.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230829","230829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086748","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to ensure its commitment that the NHS and other public services are excluded from future trade deals is upheld.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230614","230614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086749","2019-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many constituent complaints have been referred to her Department by the Department for Work and Pensions in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230830","230830"
