"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798642","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been supplied with hearing aids by (a) age group and (b) gender, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117036","117036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798643","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage people to take the winter flu jab.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117037","117037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798644","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps is he taking to ensure that NHS Trusts provide value for money.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117038","117038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798645","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that NHS Trusts are not over-charged by private sector contractors and suppliers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117039","117039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798646","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS Trusts are required to review their procurement contracts with independent providers at periodic intervals.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117040","117040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798647","2017-12-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in India; and what issues were discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117041","117041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798648","2017-12-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many homes will have been offered a smart meter in the West Midlands by the end of 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117042","117042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798649","2017-12-06","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of treatment provision for people diagnosed with Acid Sphingomyelinase Deficiency.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117043","117043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798650","2017-12-06","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of treatment provision for people diagnosed with Alström syndrome.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117044","117044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798651","2017-12-06","Department for Education","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to (a) increase the membership and (b) expand the diversity of the Board of the Student Loans Company.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117045","117045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798652","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many fatalities have occurred when patients were (a) waiting for an ambulance to arrive and (b) in transit to a health facility, broken down by Ambulance Trust, for each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117046","117046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798653","2017-12-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to introduce legislative proposals to ban the use of animals in travelling circuses in the current session of Parliament.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117047","117047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798654","2017-12-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department expects to publish its response to its consultation on extending the remit of the Groceries Code Adjudicator which closed in January 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117048","117048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798655","2017-12-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on (a) food standards and (b) salmonella rates in eggs of a free trade agreement with the United States.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117049","117049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798656","2017-12-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he expects to conclude his review on whether the UK Government should sign the Safe Schools Declaration.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117050","117050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798657","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for her Department’s Review into harassment outside abortion facilities; what funding she has allocated to that review; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117051","117051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798658","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she make it her policy to include in the review into harassment and intimidation near abortion clinics (a) oral and (b) written evidence from groups involved in such protests; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117052","117052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798659","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the introduction of a tax exemption on residential cash balances for Share Incentive Plans donated to charities when an employee exits a scheme.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117053","117053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798660","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individuals in (a) each police force area and (b) England and Wales have been (i) prosecuted and (ii) convicted in each year since 2007 for alleged harassment or intimidation outside abortion facilities.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117054","117054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798661","2017-12-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to visit Khartoum; and what assessment his Department has made of whether it is safe for people who have sought asylum in the UK to return to Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117055","117055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798662","2017-12-05","Department for International Development","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to increase awareness of the Fairtrade Mark.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117056","117056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798663","2017-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department makes of a person's cognitive capacity when holding them responsible for ensuring that the financial data relating to them held by his Department is accurate.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117057","117057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798664","2017-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what processes are in place to protect people with diminishing cognitive capacity from accruing arrears when they have failed to offer updates of any changes to their circumstances that may affect their entitlement to pension credits.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117058","117058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798665","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the Financial Conduct Authority’s interim report on the Retirement Outcomes Review.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117059","117059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798666","2017-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 7357, how many of the 88,920 people aged 65-69 previously awarded disability living allowance who were reassessed as a personal independence payments case have (a) had an award reduced or (b) received no award.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117060","117060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798667","2017-12-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to adhere to UN Security Council Resolution 1325 with regard to its reaffirmation of the important role of women in (a) the prevention and resolution of conflicts, (b) peace negotiations, peace-building and peacekeeping and (c) humanitarian response and post-conflict reconstruction.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117061","117061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798668","2017-12-05","Department for International Development","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that humanitarian aid can reach civilians in (a) the besieged area of East Ghouta and (b) other besieged areas in Syria.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117062","117062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798669","2017-12-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions he has (a) received representations and (b) had discussions with Greater Manchester Combined Authority on further devolution to Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117063","117063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798670","2017-12-05","Cabinet Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of eligible people not on the electoral register in (a) England and (b) Bolton West constituency since 2010?","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117064","117064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798671","2017-12-05","Department for International Development","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to support women who are internally displaced in Syria.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117065","117065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798672","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on investing three per cent of gross domestic product in research and development.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117066","117066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798673","2017-12-05","Department for International Development","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the effect of providing support for gender equality in Syria on a) conflict resolution, and b) the role of women as carers in conflict situations.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117067","117067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798674","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions NHS England has had with (a) breast cancer charities and (b) patient groups on the introduction of the biosimilars of Herceptin, Trastuzumab.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117068","117068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798675","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which public sector organisations are responsible for the (a) commissioning and (b) funding of specialist breast feeding support services.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117069","117069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798676","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of trends in the provision of specialist breast feeding support services in (a) England and (b) Oxfordshire in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117070","117070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798677","2017-12-05","Department for International Development","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the effect of the allocation of UN World Food Programme rations by household on the (a) human rights and (b) welfare of refugee Rohingya women and girls in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117071","117071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798678","2017-12-05","Cabinet Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 112666, on Local Government: Elections, whether Bolton Council expressed an interest to his Department about participating in the Voter ID pilots for the May 2018 local elections; and if he will place details of conversations and copies of correspondence his Department had with Bolton Council regarding that pilot in the library.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117072","117072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798679","2017-12-05","Cabinet Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the reasons for Bolton Council declining to participate in the voter ID pilot for the May 2018 local elections.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117073","117073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798680","2017-12-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Government of Bangladesh about the effect of the Child Marriage Restraint Act 2017 on the rights, equality, and welfare of Rohingya child refugees in Bangladesh and the extent to which that law is enforced in refugee camps.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117074","117074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798681","2017-12-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the call for additional funding by the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees to address modern slavery and human trafficking in (a) Libya and (b) other African states.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117075","117075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798682","2017-12-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to improve the effectiveness of ombudsman services in the consumer markets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117076","117076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798683","2017-12-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to establish energy co-operation with other countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117077","117077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798684","2017-12-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of (a) modern slavery, (b) human trafficking and (c) associated violations of human rights and equalities in Libya.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117078","117078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798685","2017-12-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much electricity and gas was generated by anaerobic digestion in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016; and how much CO2 or CO2e, CO2 equivalent, was emitted by anaerobic digestion in each of those years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117079","117079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798686","2017-12-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of racism on modern slavery and human trafficking in Libya and other North African and Mediterranean states.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117080","117080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798687","2017-12-05","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the science and research community on ensuring that the UK will have compatible regulations with the EU clinical trials regulations after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117081","117081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798688","2017-12-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness of (a) UN sanctions targeted at individuals or organisations who are identified as being responsible for modern slavery and human trafficking of African refugees and migrants in Libya and other African states, and (b) an EU-funded scheme enabling greater voluntary repatriation of migrants currently held in detention camps in Libya; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117082","117082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798689","2017-12-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what further steps he plans to take to promote awareness and encourage the take-up of the Armed Forces Credit Union among military personnel and their families; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117083","117083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798690","2017-12-06","HM Treasury","2017-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to support access to credit unions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117084","117084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798691","2017-12-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether redundancy terms are being honoured for staff who have recently been made redundant at the Hebrides Range.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117085","117085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798692","2017-12-06","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his oral answer  of 14 November 2017, Official Report column, 143, what estimate he has made of the rates of inflationary increase in NHS tariff costs for musculoskeletal services under the Circle contract to Lewisham and Greenwich Healthcare Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117086","117086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798693","2017-12-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where air traffic control is undertaken for trials at the Hebrides Range.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117087","117087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798694","2017-12-06","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints he has received about ambulance and patient transfer services provided by G4S; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117088","117088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798695","2017-12-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many additional personnel visited the Hebrides Range in 2015 and 2017 for trials; and what estimate he has made of the number of additional personnel who will visit for trials in (a) 2018 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117089","117089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798696","2017-12-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many guards were employed at Hebrides Range in (a) 2010, (b) 2014 and (c) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the number of guards who will be employed in 2020.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117090","117090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798697","2017-12-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the number of guards at Hebrides Range has been decreased.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117091","117091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798698","2017-12-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff at the Hebrides Range had to take annual leave at the end of the year due to their being busy throughout summer.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117092","117092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798699","2017-12-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether (a) the Government and (b) a local authority commissioned services from Trimega (i) before 10 July 2013 and (ii) after 11 April 2014.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117093","117093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798700","2017-12-06","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 10.3 of the explanatory memorandum to the Mental Health Act 1983 (Places of Safety) Regulations 2017, whether funding has been provided as detailed in that paragraph.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117094","117094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798701","2017-12-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Questions 116201, 116202, 116204 and 116205, what recent assessment his Department has made of the availability of street parking close to Shettleston Jobcentre.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117095","117095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798702","2017-12-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Questions 116201, 116202, 116204 and 116205, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment of the potential effect of the increase of vehicular activity on traffic and parking in the vicinity of Shettleston Jobcentre following the merger of that jobcentre with Bridgeton, Easterhouse and Parkhead Jobcentres.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117096","117096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798703","2017-12-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Questions 116201, 116202, 116204 and 116205, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment of the potential effect of the increase of vehicular activity on air quality in the vicinity of Shettleston Jobcentre following the merger of that jobcentre with Bridgeton, Easterhouse and Parkhead jobcentres.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117097","117097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798704","2017-12-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Questions 116201, 116202, 116204 and 116205, what discussions his Department has had with Glasgow City Council on the potential effect on traffic volume and street parking in the vicinity of Shettleston Jobcentre following the merger of that jobcentre with Bridgeton, Easterhouse and Parkhead jobcentres.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117098","117098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798705","2017-12-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Questions 116201, 116202, 116204 and 116205, what discussions his Department has had with the local police force on the potential effect on traffic volume and street parking in the vicinity of Shettleston Jobcentre following the merger of that jobcentre with Bridgeton, Easterhouse and Parkhead jobcentres.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117099","117099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798706","2017-12-06","Department for Transport","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has made to Network Rail about safety following the recent report by the Rail Accident Investigation Branch on the wall collapse at Liverpool Lime Street station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117100","117100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798707","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Care Quality Commission's online map of designated places of safety includes details of every designated place of safety in England.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117101","117101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798708","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what real-time information NHS England provides to the police and ambulance services on the availability of health-based places of safety.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117102","117102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798709","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what powers are available to the Care Quality Commission to ensure that Care Commissioning Groups (a) identify and (b) inform police forces and ambulance services of health-based places of safety in their area.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117103","117103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798710","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to establish target times for the assessment of places of safety under the Mental Health Act 1983 (Places of Safety) Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 117104","117104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795947","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask Secretary for State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.95 of the Budget 2016, how much has been allocated on the policies listed in that paragraph in financial year 2017-18.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116262","116262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797587","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to review the categories for registering a death of an unmarried partner to include partner and not simply disposing of the body.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116550","116550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797629","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to extend the employment rights of workers on zero hour contracts to cover unfair dismissal.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116592","116592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797766","2017-11-30","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","If he will include Nissan electric vehicles in the Government’s car fleet.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902672","902672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797776","2017-12-04","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2017 to Question 2214,  which local authorities will participate in the proof of identity pilot for the May 2018 local elections.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116684","116684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797777","2017-12-05","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the factors affecting electoral registration and voter engagement in the Cheshire East Unitary Authority.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116685","116685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797778","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs and (b) representatives of the retail sector on to encourage supermarkets to make more of their packaging recyclable; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116686","116686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797779","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with (a) Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) HM Treasury officials on the possibility of providing multi-annual funding settlements for Police and Crime Commissioners; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116687","116687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797780","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterparts in the Bahraini Government on fairness of the first trial of civilians in secret military courts in Bahrain in October 2017 .","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116688","116688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797781","2017-12-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has the power to redraft the local plan for Calderdale council.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116689","116689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797782","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the appropriateness of the rule in relation to the Special Grant under which police forces are not able to claim additional funding for emergency or terrorism-related incidents unless they have spent one per cent of their budget on such incidents; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116690","116690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797783","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's consultation on Renewable Transport Fuel Obligation, published in September 2017, for what reasons the cap on bio-fuels will be reduced from 4 per cent to 2 per cent.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116691","116691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797784","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's consultation on Renewable Transport Fuel Obligation, published in September 2017, what comparative assessment he has made of the competitiveness of 2 per cent crop cap in the UK with a 7 per cent crop cap in EU countries.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116692","116692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797785","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Renewable Transport Fuels Obligation, what processes are in place to allow for the amending of the crop cap after its planned promulgation.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116693","116693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797786","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's consultation on Renewable Transport Fuel Obligation, published in September 2017, if he will make an assessment of the efficacy of the crop cap two years after the changes to that cap are implemented.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116694","116694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797787","2017-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 23 November 2017 to Question HL3124, on social security benefits: appeals, what assessment he has made of the reported comments by Sir Ernest Ryder, Senior President of Tribunals, at a Bar Council event on 7 November 2017 on the quality of evidence brought before the courts by his Department in cases involving employment and support allowance and personal independence payments; whether he has discussed those concerns with the Secretary of State for Justice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116695","116695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797788","2017-12-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which measures in the industrial strategy will help to reduce the rate of unemployment in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116696","116696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797789","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from police forces on the costs of policing fracking sites.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116697","116697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797790","2017-12-05","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, (a) who will carry out and (b) by what date, the independent review of funding and financing for Crossrail 2 announced in Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116698","116698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797791","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much time his Department spent in compiling impact assessments and other material for the sectoral analyses it provided to the Department for Exiting the European Union; how many FTE staff hours were dedicated to that compilation; and on what date his Department started and concluded its work on that compilation.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116699","116699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797792","2017-12-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much time her Department spent in compiling impact assessments and other material for the sectoral analyses it provided to the Department for Exiting the European Union; how many FTE staff hours were dedicated to that compilation; and on what date her Department started and concluded its work on that compilation.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116700","116700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797793","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much time his Department spent in compiling impact assessments and other material for the sectoral analyses it provided to the Department for Exiting the European Union; how many FTE staff hours were dedicated to that compilation; and on what date his Department started and concluded its work on that compilation.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116701","116701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797794","2017-12-04","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much time his Department spent in compiling impact assessments and other material for the sectoral analyses it provided to the Department for Exiting the European Union; how many FTE staff hours were dedicated to that compilation; and on what date his Department started and concluded its work on that compilation.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116702","116702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797795","2017-12-04","Scotland Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much time his Department spent in compiling impact assessments and other material for the sectoral analyses it provided to the Department for Exiting the European Union; how many FTE staff hours were dedicated to that compilation; and on what date his Department started and concluded its work on that compilation.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116703","116703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797796","2017-12-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to ensure that the General Service Respirator In Service Support contract stipulates that costs over those specified in the contract which are incurred by the company as a result of work to meet contractual obligations fall on that company and not on the public purse.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116704","116704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797797","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to ensure that the General Service Respirator In Service Support contract clearly stipulates who assumes liability for all masks, spares and replacement components provided under that contract irrespective of origin and combination.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116705","116705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797798","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2017 to Question 114759, on railways: Greater Manchester, how Leigh will benefit from improved rail connectivity in the Greater Manchester area.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116706","116706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797799","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure there are adequate numbers of NHS staff to care for people with dementia and what estimate he has made of the number of staff that will be required in each of the next 5 years","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116707","116707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797800","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to tackle unemployment among people over the age of 50 who have been made redundant.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116708","116708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797801","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received reports on reasons for a British judge not being re-appointed to the International Court of Justice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116709","116709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797802","2017-12-04","Wales Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department has (a) recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on the UK's leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116710","116710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797803","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union to the House of Lords European Union Committee on 31 October, how many civil servants his Department has (a) recruited and (b) expects to recruit to work on the UK's leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116711","116711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797804","2017-12-05","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of progress on the three initial divorce issues and whether this is sufficient to begin trade negotiations after the EU Council in December.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116712","116712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797805","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convicted criminals have been imprisoned in the UK after trial by the International Criminal Tribunal for crimes committed in the former Yugoslavia.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116713","116713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797806","2017-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will continue employment and support allowance payments while mandatory reconsideration decisions are being processed; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116714","116714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797807","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 4.51 of the Red Book, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Government’s decision not to introduce new low-carbon electricity levies until 2025 on the implementation of the Renewables Obligation (Amendment) (Energy Intensive Industries) Order 2017.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116715","116715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797808","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2017 to Question 9068, when he plans to re-introduce the further Renewable Heat Incentive reforms outlined in the Government consultation response published in December 2016 and included in the Renewable Heat Incentive Scheme Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116716","116716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797809","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what criteria his Department will use to determine a decision on consent for hydraulic fracturing at the Kirby Misperton site; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116717","116717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797810","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 4.51 of the Red Book, what his Department’s definition is for new low-carbon electricity levies.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116718","116718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797811","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department had with Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy in advance of the Autumn Budget 2017, on the effect of his plans to introduce no new low-carbon electricity levies until 2025, set out in paragraph 4.51 of the Red Book.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116719","116719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797812","2017-12-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 7 November 2017, HCWS232 on local government improvement, what further steps are needed to secure local consent.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116720","116720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797813","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by his Department and (b) his Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116721","116721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797814","2017-12-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the (a) number of officials to be employed by her Department and (b) her Department's payroll in (i) 2018, (ii) 2019, (iii) 2020, (iv) 2021 and (v) 2022 as a result of the UK leaving EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116722","116722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797815","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the response to his Department’s consultation on the draft transport accessibility action plan.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116723","116723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797816","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of potential merits of reducing the five-year holding period for Share Incentive Plans to three-years.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116724","116724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797817","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the contribution limits for (a) Share Incentive Plans and (b) Save As You Earn in line with inflation.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116725","116725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797818","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will review the operation of employee share ownership plans to identify measures to improve and simplify the administration of such schemes.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116726","116726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797819","2017-12-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Libyan Government regarding recent reports of African migrants being sold at slave auctions.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116727","116727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797820","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons publication of the house-building statistics House building; new build dwellings, England: September Quarter 2017 has been delayed.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116728","116728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797821","2017-12-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with charity representatives on the appointment of the next Chair of the Charity Commission in line with the Governance Code for Public Appointments.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116729","116729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797822","2017-12-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has assessed the potential implications of appointing a former Minister as Chair of the Charity Commission.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116730","116730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797823","2017-12-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Prime Minister’s Office has had any involvement in the appointment of the next Chair of the Charity Commission.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116731","116731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797825","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance his Department provides to local authorities on licensing for business selling pets on the sale of primates.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116732","116732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797826","2017-12-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that the next Chair of the Charity Commission upholds public trust and confidence in the Charity Commission.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116733","116733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797827","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how frequently the Code of Practice for the welfare of privately kept non-human primates has been reviewed; and if he will include that code in his Department’s review of other statutory animal welfare codes.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116734","116734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797828","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will ban the (a) trade or (b) keeping of primates as pets.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116735","116735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797829","2017-12-05","Wales Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the ability of organisations in Wales to secure low-cost, long- term and large-scale loans once European Investment Bank loans are no longer available.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116736","116736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797830","2017-12-05","Wales Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2017 to Question 114746 and the Answer of 20 November to Question 11334, if he will deposit in the Library a list of the documents his Department provided for the formulation of plans in the event that no deal is reached between the UK and the EU before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116737","116737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797831","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will publish annual reports on recorded wildlife crimes and related court proceedings and penalties.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116738","116738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797832","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment the Government has made of trends in wildlife crime; and what steps it is taking to tackle such crime.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116739","116739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797833","2017-12-05","Wales Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will place in the Library the full list of documents on planning for leaving the EU that have been sent from  his Department to (a) the Joint Ministerial Committee and (b) the European Union Exit and Trade Committee and its sub-committees.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116740","116740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797834","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to introduce legislative proposals or guidance to increase the severity of sentences for people convicted of wildlife crimes.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116741","116741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797835","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will introduce enhanced training for police officers and call handlers across all agencies on tackling wildlife crime.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116742","116742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797836","2017-12-05","Wales Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 27 November 2017 to Question 114746, what specific issues he discussed with the Welsh Government, other than at the Joint Ministerial Committee, on the UK leaving the EU in the last six months.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116743","116743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797837","2017-12-04","Department for International Development","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to increase the UK contribution to the Robert Carr Network Fund for civil society.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116744","116744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797838","2017-12-04","Department for International Development","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will publish her Department's policy on HIV/Aids.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116745","116745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797839","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department plans to take in response to the Office for Statistics Regulation report on Public value of statistics on housing and planning in the UK published in November 2017.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116746","116746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797840","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the issue of whaling was discussed during his visit to Iceland in August 2017.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116747","116747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797841","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding from the public purse has been spent to date on building starter homes.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116748","116748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797842","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many starter homes he expects to be built over the course of this Parliament.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116749","116749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797843","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to reduce the UK Chinook Force.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116750","116750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797844","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the importance of the UK Chinook Force for the wider capability of the armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116751","116751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797845","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons his Department made the decision not to use the existing category of specified exempt accommodation as the basis for funding short-term supported housing in the proposals contained in the consultation document, Funding Supported Housing: Policy Statement and Consultation, published in October 2017.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116752","116752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797846","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 21 November 2017, HCWS265, on toxicology, whether her Department distributed details of contract renewals and tenders to Trimega through the Pipeline Monitoring System (a) before 10 July 2013 and (b) after 11 April 2014; and if she will make a statement","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116753","116753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797847","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2017 to Question 115018 on Randox Testing Services and Trimega, whether it is a legal requirement for accreditation to be granted in order to supply forensic services.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116754","116754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797848","2017-12-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of the 29 November 2017 to Question 115018, whether Trimega was supplying services to (a) Government departments, (b) local authorities (c) police forces or (d) any other public or private body during the period in which that company did not hold UKAS accreditation to the international standard for test laboratories ISO/IEC 17025.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116755","116755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797849","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the proposals contained in the consultation document Funding Supported Housing: Policy Statement and Consultation, published in October 3017, what steps he is taking to ensure that an individual’s entitlement for help with their housing costs through (a) housing benefit and (b) the housing cost element of universal credit will be unchanged.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116756","116756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797850","2017-12-05","Department for International Development","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Memorandum of Understanding between the Palestinian Authority and her department, what discussions her department has had with the PA concerning the official PA daily Al-Hayat Al-Jadida’s description on 27 September 2017 of the Har Adar terrorist attack as an operation and the terrorist as a martyr.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116757","116757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797851","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, of the £2.3 billion allocated to starter homes in the Autumn Statement 2015, how much had been spent by April 2017; and what allowance is now being made for total capital spending under that heading to 2020-21 in the (a) Greater London Authority area and (b) England.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116758","116758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797852","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people aged 65 or over paid income tax at the (a) higher and (b) additional rate in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116759","116759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797853","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with representatives of the pensions industry on improving guidance and information on pensions provided to people at retirement age.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116760","116760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797854","2017-12-05","Department for International Development","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Memorandum of Understanding between the Palestinian Authority and her department, what discussions her department has had with the PA concerning the rebroadcast on Palestinian TV of a 1996 TV show which described Jews as wicked, oppressors and evil”.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116761","116761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797855","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the funding allocated to the Housing Infrastructure Fund, excluding Barnett Formula consequential spending, but including the Greater London Authority area, over the next 4 years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116762","116762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797856","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of making Pension Wise an opt-out service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116763","116763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797857","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of total spending on the Accelerated Construction Fund, excluding Barnett consequential spending, in the (a) Greater London Authority area and (b) England in each of the next four financial years to 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116764","116764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797858","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of total spending on the Land Assembly Fund, excluding Barnett consequential spending, in (a) the Greater London Authority area and (b) England in each of the next four financial years to 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116765","116765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797859","2017-12-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the total (a) cost and (b) man-hours relating to her Department on the preparation of guidance and application information for cities wishing to become European Capital of Culture 2023.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116766","116766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797860","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of total spending on small sites infrastructure and remediation, excluding Barnett consequential spending, in (a) the Greater London Authority area (b) England in each of the next four financial years to 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116767","116767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797861","2017-12-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on the UK continuing to be legally bound by the Paris Agreement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116768","116768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797862","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with an (a) Education, Health and Care Plan and (b) Statement of Educational Needs and Disability received a permanent or fixed-term exclusion in each local authority in the West Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116769","116769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797863","2017-12-04","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Government departments, agencies and arms’ length bodies do not use the gov.uk website.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116770","116770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797864","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many education, health and care plans have been provided to children in (a) the West Midlands (b) Coventry in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116771","116771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797865","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications have been made for education, health and care plans in (a) the West Midlands, (b) Coventry in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116772","116772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797866","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that mineworkers in deprived areas have access to a proportionate share of the profits made by the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116773","116773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797867","2017-12-04","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new Government websites have been approved through the Government's spending controls process in the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116774","116774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797868","2017-12-04","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many applications have been (a) received and (b) approved by the Naming and Approvals Committee in the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116775","116775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797869","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many successful convictions there have been for fly tipping in the past 12 months; and how many vehicles used in fly tipping have been seized and crushed in the past five years.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116776","116776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797870","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding has been allocated for estate regeneration in (a) the Greater London Authority area and (b) England in each of the next four financial years to 2020/21; and of how much of that funding is (i) grant spending and (ii) loans.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116777","116777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797871","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of total spending on garden cities, towns and villages, excluding Barnett consequential spending, in (a) the Greater London Authority area and (b) England in each of  the next four financial years to 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116778","116778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797872","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of international efforts to regulate crypto-currencies; and whether his Department has any plans to regulate crypto-currencies in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116779","116779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797873","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on human trafficking in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116780","116780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797874","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of total spending on the Home Building Fund, excluding Barnett consequential spending, in (a) the Greater London Authority area and (b) England in each of the next four financial years to 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116781","116781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797875","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he had had with his international counterparts on progress on the OECD's Base Erosion and Profit Shifting project.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116782","116782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797876","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the timescale is for the roll-out of the new financial guarantees for house building outlined in Autumn Budget 2017; what estimate has made of the amount that will be spent over each of the next four financial years to 2020-21; and what the expected output is in terms of new homes delivered.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116783","116783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797877","2017-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make a further review of the credit union expansion project to examine the possibility of additional changes that would allow credit unions to offer additional financial services.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116784","116784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797878","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of annual spend on the (a) Help to Buy ISA in each financial year between 2015-16 and 2020/21 and (b) Lifetime ISA in each financial year between 2017-18 and 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116785","116785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797879","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to review the areas in Northern Ireland that qualify for the rural fuel duty rebate scheme in light of the availability of cheaper fuel in the Irish Republic?","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116786","116786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797880","2017-12-05","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what change there was in the number of people employed by the national network for HM Coastguard between January 2016 and July 2017?","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116787","116787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797881","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households from (a) Barandon Walk, (b) Hurstway Walk, (c) Testerton Walk, (d) Treadgold House, (e) Bramley House and (f) other surrounding blocks in the Lancaster West Estate were evacuated from their homes following the Grenfell Tower fire of 14 June 2017; and how many of those households remain in emergency accommodation.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116788","116788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797882","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the ratio of health visitors to children is in each local authority area.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116789","116789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797883","2017-12-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, further to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110955, on fishing catches: British Overseas Territories, what fishing tonnage quota is assigned to EU member states other than the UK for each of the Overseas Territories; and what arrangements will be made after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116790","116790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797884","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will set out the details of any meetings or other contact that has taken place between his Department and representatives from the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea about allowing council tenants who formerly resided in Grenfell Tower to retain the right to buy.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116791","116791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797885","2017-12-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations she has received about the UK temporarily hosting the Bayeux Tapestry.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116792","116792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797886","2017-12-05","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons her Department has not produced a stand-alone youth policy statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116793","116793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797887","2017-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received on the application of universal credit criteria for those housed in temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116794","116794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797888","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions have taken place for the illegal sale of seahorses in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116795","116795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797889","2017-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is a requirement for firms supplying forensic services in support of family court cases to be accredited to ISO/IEC 17025 standards.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116796","116796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797890","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons the Education and Skills Funding Agency did not issue a financial notice to improve to Wakefield City Academies Trust in 2016 following the finding of 16 breaches of academy finance rules.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116797","116797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797891","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 07 November to Question 111967, whether she plans to publish the ESFA report into Wakefield City Academies Trust following the successful transfer to new trusts of schools ran by Wakefield City Academies Trust.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116798","116798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797892","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many separate breaches of the Academies Financial Handbook have been recorded by her Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116799","116799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797893","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many separate breaches of the Academies Financial Handbook have been recorded  by her Department since that handbook was created.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116800","116800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797894","2017-12-05","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, in light of his announcement to truncate the East Coast Main Line franchise and change to a Public Private Partnership operation, (a) for how long he expects Virgin Trains East Coast to continue to pay premiums under the remainder of the truncated franchise arrangement and (b) what estimate he has made of the value of those premium payments in each remaining year of that arrangement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116801","116801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797895","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any journalists have been placed under surveillance under (a) Operation Curable (b) any other operation since the leak of classified documents by Edward Snowden in 2013; what the cost of Operation Curable has been to date; if he has made an assessment of the effect of Operation Curable on public interest journalism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116802","116802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797896","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps his Department is taking to reduce unemployment in constituencies with high levels of unemployment.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116803","116803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797897","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) GP appointments and (b) A&E admissions that could have been treated by a pharmacy in 2016.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116804","116804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797898","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of raising the business rate thresholds for small firms located in London.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116805","116805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797899","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the additional funding required by his Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116806","116806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797900","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the additional funding required by his Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116807","116807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797901","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of the additional funding required by her Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116808","116808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797902","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the additional funding required by (a) his Department and (b) HM Revenue and Customs) over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116809","116809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797903","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the additional funding required by his Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116810","116810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797904","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the additional funding required by his Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116811","116811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797905","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the additional funding required by his Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116812","116812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797906","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the additional funding required by his Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116813","116813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797907","2017-12-04","Department for International Development","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent estimate she has made of the additional funding required by her Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116814","116814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797908","2017-12-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of waste collections in (a) Kent, (b) Surrey, (c) East Sussex, (d) West Sussex and (e) Hampshire went to landfill in 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116815","116815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797909","2017-12-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate she has made of the additional funding required by her Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116816","116816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797910","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the additional funding required by his Department over the next two years to prepare effectively for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116817","116817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797911","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to bring forward proposals for a de minimis tax exemption on residual cash balances held in the Share Incentive Plans of employees who terminate participation in such schemes.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116818","116818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797912","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions there have been under section 76 of the Serious Crime Act 2015, relating to controlling or coercive behaviour in an intimate or family relationship, broken down by the police forces by which each offender was charged.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116819","116819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797913","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage NHS Trusts to update their local guidelines as a result of the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists' September 2017 update to their clinical Green-Top guidelines on Group B Streptococcus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116820","116820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797914","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Family Hubs.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116821","116821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797915","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department is making on updating relationship and sex education guidance.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116822","116822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797916","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 13 November and 24 November to Questions 111757 and 114731, on Secure Psychiatric Units: Domestic Visits, for what reasons the information is not held.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116823","116823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797917","2017-12-04","Department for International Development","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to attend the International AIDS Conference in July 2018.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116824","116824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797918","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 13 November and 24 November to Questions 111757 and 114731, on Secure Psychiatric Units: Domestic Visits, for what reasons the Department does not hold information on the date and location of a visit made by the Secretary of State.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116825","116825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797919","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 13 November and 24 November to Questions 111757 and 114731, on Secure Psychiatric Units: Domestic Visits, in what format the data requested is held.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116826","116826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797920","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 13 November and 24 November to Questions 111757 and 114731, on Secure Psychiatric Units: Domestic Visits, for what reason the Answers given differ.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116827","116827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797921","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Welsh women are serving sentences in Eastwood Park prison.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116828","116828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797922","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Welsh women have been sentenced to prison in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116829","116829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797923","2017-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he is aware of an offer by the St Stephen's Shopping Centre, Hull, to host the replica of Amy Johnson's Tiger Moth produced by prisoners in HMP Hull; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116830","116830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797924","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what technologies will be permitted to participate in auctions for the £557 million for additional contracts for difference under the Control for Low Carbon Levies announced in Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116831","116831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797925","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of Welsh women sentenced to prison per month is.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116832","116832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797926","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage greater collaboration between investment in life sciences and innovative medicines in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116833","116833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797927","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether proposals for Contracts for Difference for new nuclear power stations other than Hinkley Point C will count as new levies under the Control for New Carbon Levies.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116834","116834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797928","2017-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to ensure that the replica of Amy Johnson's Tiger Moth produced in HMP Hull remains in Hull.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116835","116835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797929","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his review of support for the Energy Company Obligation beyond 2022 as set out in the Clean Growth Strategy of October 2017 will be based on the introduction of new levies to support the scheme.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116836","116836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797930","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of reintroducing the Local Educational Authority supply pool for schools in England.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116837","116837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797931","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of decreasing NHS spending on pharmaceuticals on the attractiveness of the UK as a location for research and development.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116838","116838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797932","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many homes will have been offered a smart meter by the end of 2017.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116839","116839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797933","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the UK's relationaship with the European Medicines Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116840","116840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797934","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the difference between the number of homes that will have been offered a smart meter by end of 2020 and the number of meters that will be installed by that date.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116841","116841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797935","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will bring forward legislation to ban finders fees being imposed by teaching supply agencies where a school seeks to appoint on a permanent basis a supply teacher originally provided by those agencies.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116842","116842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797936","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what new opportunities will be available to the life sciences sector after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116843","116843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797937","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will bring forward proposals regulate teaching supply agencies and cap costs charged for the provision of supply teachers.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116844","116844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797938","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the levy established to support energy intensive industries through the Electricity Supplier Obligations (Amended and Excluded Electricity) (Amendment) Regulations 2017 will count as a new levy under the terms of the Control for Low Carbon Levies.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116845","116845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797939","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the new Approved Driving Instructor Part 3 Test will be introduced.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116846","116846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797940","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the total strength of the Maritime Reserve as of 1 October 2017 are (a) Phase 1 Trained, (b) Phase 2 trained and (c) new entrants or recruits.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116847","116847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797941","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the total strength of the Maritime Reserve as of 1 October 2017 are eligible to (a) deploy on overseas exercises, (b) deploy on overseas operations and (c) be mobilised?","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116848","116848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797942","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the total strength of the Maritime Reserve as of 1 April 2017 qualified for their annual bounty.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116849","116849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797943","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of those Maritime Reservists who received their bounty in April 2017 qualified for (a) Year 1 (£440), (b) Year 2 (£972), (c) Year 3 (£1502), (d) Year 4 (£1502) and (e) Year 5 (£1742).","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116850","116850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797944","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average number of Man Training Days undertaken within the Maritime Reserve was by (a) an individual Reservist and (b) a Ships Company for the training year April 2016 to March 2017?","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116851","116851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797945","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average number of Man Training Days claimed by the Maritime Reserve was under the recruitment budget for (a) an individual Sailor and (b) a Ships company for the training year April 2016 to March 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116852","116852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797946","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Additional Duties Contracts and (b) Full Time Reserve Sailor contracts are affordable under the Maritime Reserve's recruitment Budget.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116853","116853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797947","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Naval Reservists in the Maritime Reserve as of 1 October 2017 are (a) on Full time Reserve Sailor contracts, (b) Additional Duties Contracts and (c) Regular Naval Personnel on fixed term attachments.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116854","116854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797948","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel on full time reserve sailor contracts in the Maritime Reserve are (a) eligible to deploy on overseas exercises, (b) eligible to deploy on overseas Operations, (c) eligible to be mobilised and (d) on a reduced commitment.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116855","116855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797949","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the total number of Maritime Reservists as of 1 October 2017 are ex-regulars brought into the service through Project Firefly.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116856","116856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797950","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many ex-regulars in the Maritime Reserve are (a) on a reduced commitment, (b) eligible to deploy on an overseas exercise, (c) eligible to deploy on an overseas operation and (d) eligible to be mobilised.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116857","116857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797951","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the total strength of the Maritime Reserve as of 1 October 2017 are (a) part of the Royal Naval Reserve and (b) part of the Royal Marines Reserve.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116858","116858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797952","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the total strength of the Royal Naval Reserve as of 1 October 2017 are eligible to (a) deploy on overseas exercises, (b) deploy on overseas operations and (c) be mobilised.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116859","116859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797953","2017-12-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many houses have been sold under right to buy in each year since 2010 in (a) England, (b) the West Midlands, (c) the City of Wolverhampton local authority area and (d) Wolverhampton North East Constituency.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116860","116860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797954","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the total strength of the Royal Marine Reserve as of 1 October 2017 are eligible to (a) deploy on overseas exercises, (b) deploy on overseas operations and (c) be mobilised.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116861","116861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797955","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the total strength of the Royal Naval Reserve as of 1 April 2017 qualified for their annual bounty.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116862","116862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797956","2017-12-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes for social rent have been built  in (a) England, (b) the West Midlands, (c) City of Wolverhampton local authority area and (d) Wolverhampton North East constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116863","116863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797957","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Naval Reservists who received their bounty in April 2017 qualified for (a) Year 1 (£440), (b) Year 2 (£972), (c) Year 3 (£1502), (d) Year 4 (£1502) and (e) Year 5 (£1742).","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116864","116864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797958","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Marine Reservists who received their bounty in April 2017 qualified for (a) Year 1 (£440), (b) Year 2 (£972), (c) Year 3 (£1502), (d) Year 4 (£1502) and (e) Year 5 (£1742).","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116865","116865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797959","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average number of Man Training Days undertaken by (a) an individual Reservist and (b) a Ships Company in the Royal Naval Reserves was for the training year April 2016 to March 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116866","116866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797960","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average number of Man Training Days in the Royal Marine Reserve as of 1 April 2017  undertaken by (a) an individual Reservist and (b) a Ships Company was for the training year April 2016 to March 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116867","116867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797961","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) additional duties contracts and (b) full time reserve sailor contracts are provided for by the current recruitment budget of the Royal Naval Reserve.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116868","116868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797962","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for his receipt of final proposals from the three services on which to base his decision as to what is included within the ambit of the National Security Capability Review.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116869","116869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797963","2017-12-05","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the National Security Capability Review will be completed.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116870","116870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797964","2017-12-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proposals are part of the National Security Capability Review on the provision of amphibious over the beach capability without recourse to HMS Albion and HMS Bulwark.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116871","116871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797965","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether further cost savings are being sought from his Department as part of the National Security Capability Review process.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116872","116872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797966","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Home Secretary, if she will make it her Department’s policy to grant asylum applicants who have been waiting for longer than six months for a decision on their application permission to work without the Shortage Occupation restrictions list.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116873","116873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797967","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applicants have been granted permission to work in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116874","116874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797968","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to increase the period for which refugees continue to receive asylum support after receiving a positive decision on their asylum application to 50 days on account of issues with gaining National Insurance numbers within the current 28 days.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116875","116875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797969","2017-12-05","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the level of asylum support on the physical and mental well-being of people seeking asylum who have been waiting on a decision for more than six months.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116876","116876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797970","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse is of his Department's stake in Surrey Satellite Technology.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116877","116877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797971","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library details of the Carbonite-2 demonstrator program.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116878","116878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797972","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many properties sold in 2016 in Wolverhampton were below the stamp duty threshold.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116879","116879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797973","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to ensure that (a) victims of crime and (b) witnesses of crime can come forward and report crimes to police services without risk of immigration enforcement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116880","116880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797974","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of police services referring victims and witnesses of crime to the Home Office for immigration enforcement on access to justice for victims of crime with irregular migration status.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116881","116881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797975","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Emergency Care Improvement Programme team is taking to improve patient flow and urgent care services at Oxford University Hospital's NHS Foundation in winter 2017.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116882","116882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797976","2017-12-05","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the mortality rates of (a) communicable disease,  (b) non-communicable disease and (c) injuries in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116883","116883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797977","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that the UK will benefit from the implementation of the EU's Tax Avoidance Directive in 2019.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116884","116884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797978","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) self-harm and (b) interpersonal violence on the overall mortality rates for children and young people aged between five and 14 in each region of England in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116885","116885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797979","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to continue the Community Pub Business Support Programme beyond March 2018.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116886","116886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797980","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the introduction of the duty of care; and what the (a) process and (b) timescale is for introducing the Duty of Care.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116887","116887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797981","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of Disability-Adjusted Life Years (DALYs) figures which can be attributed to alzheimer's disease and other forms of dementia in each region of England in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116888","116888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797982","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department holds information on the most prevalent (a) behavioural risk factors, (b) metabolic risk factors and (c) environmental risk factors associated with mortality rates for each region of England in each year for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116889","116889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797983","2017-12-05","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the mortality rate for diarrheal diseases has been in each region of England in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116890","116890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797984","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to take steps to increase the period of time refugees continue to receive support after receiving a positive decision on their asylum application to 50 days.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116891","116891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797985","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current value of contingency funding is for the Naval Nuclear Propulsion Programme for work related to the development of the PWR3 for the Dreadnought programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116892","116892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797986","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the PWR3 nuclear reactor programme will move into its manufacturing phase.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116893","116893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797987","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to sustain the number of nuclear suitably qualified and experienced engineers and scientists and develop the UK’s next generation of nuclear propulsion experts.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116894","116894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797988","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department is planning a nuclear propulsion capability review.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116895","116895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797989","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value is of efficiency savings identified to date by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116896","116896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797990","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many fully trained (a) Marine Engineers and (b) Weapons Engineers served in the Royal Navy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116897","116897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797991","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the recent fall in EU immigration on trends in NHS recruitment during Winter 2017.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116898","116898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797992","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) outflow (b) inflow and (c) netflow of fully trained Royal Navy (i) Marine Engineers and (ii) Weapons Engineers has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116899","116899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797993","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many former fully trained Royal Navy (a) Marine Engineers and (b) Weapons Engineers have rejoined the (i) regular naval service (ii) reserve naval service in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116900","116900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797994","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average age of Royal Navy (a) Marine Engineers and (b) Weapons Engineers has been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116901","116901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797995","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in England (a) are in schools rated good or outstanding and (b) were in such schools in 2010.","Biography information for Alan Mak","Alan Mak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116902","116902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797996","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the regular Army’s full-time trade trained strength was in each of the last 12 months","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116903","116903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797997","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in England (a) are in schools rated good or outstanding and (b) were in such schools in 2010.","Biography information for Alan Mak","Alan Mak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116904","116904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797998","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of schools in England (a) are rated good or outstanding and (b) were so rated in 2010.","Biography information for Alan Mak","Alan Mak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116905","116905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797999","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the regular Army’s full-time trained strength was in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116906","116906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798000","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in Turkey on repression of independent media and the right to free speech in that country.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116907","116907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798001","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Army Reserve total (a) inflow, (b) outflow and (c) netflow was for the (i) Infantry, (ii) Royal Artillery, (iii) Royal Corps of Signals, (iv) Army Medical Services, (v) Adjutant General's Corps, (vi) Royal Armoured Corps, (vii) Army Air Corps, (viii) Royal Engineers, (ix) Royal Logistics Corps, (x) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (xi) Intelligence Corps in each month in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116908","116908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798003","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Army Reserve total intake was for each month in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116910","116910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798004","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle the (a) organised crime, (b) gang activity and (c) drug dealing across county operating across county boundaries.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116911","116911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798005","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, will he give a commitment to refund all VAT paid by Police Scotland and the Scottish Fire and Rescue Service to date.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Gerard Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116912","116912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798006","2017-12-05","Department of Health","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to provide local authorities with additional funding to meet the sustainability shortfall identified in the Competition and Market Authority's report of 30 November 2017 on the Care Home Market.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116913","116913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798007","2017-12-05","Department for International Trade","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2017 to Question 115425 on small businesses, what the (a) rate of default was on loans provided by UK export finance during the period to which that answer refers and (b) cost to the UK Exchequer of such defaults.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116914","116914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798008","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of levels in investment in the development of Small Modular Reactors in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116915","116915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798010","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria control the number of night flights arriving at and departing from airports, and, with reference to the Civil Aviation Authority's recent assessment of Edinburgh Airport's proposed new flight path, whether that Airport has reached capacity for night flights.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116917","116917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798011","2017-12-05","Department for International Trade","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to his written statement of 28 November 2017, HCWS273, on trade remedies, what recent representations he has received from energy intensive industries on the implementation of trade remedy measures and any changes to those measures after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116918","116918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798012","2017-12-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to ensure that national collections and other recipients of public funding make digital image seize of copyright painting, prints and drawings held in public collections free of charge to non-commercial causes and for educational purposes.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116919","116919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798013","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to line 21 of table 2.1 of Autumn Budget 2017, from which allocation of capital spend the £7 billion in year 2022-23 has been re-allocated","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116920","116920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798014","2017-12-05","Women and Equalities","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, on what date the Government Equalities Office informed (a) the Prime Minister's Office and (b) the Minister of State for Disabled People, Health and Work of its decision to appoint Lord Shinkwin as a general commissioner on the Equalities and Human Rights Commission.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116921","116921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798015","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the reasons are for changing the name of the British Consulate General in the Kurdistan region to the British Consulate General Erbil on his Department's Facebook page; and what his policy is on UK relations with the Kurdistan Regional Government.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116922","116922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798016","2017-12-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government still plans to raise the National Living Wage to £9 by 2020.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116923","116923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798017","2017-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps is he taking to reduce levels of illiteracy among prisoners.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116924","116924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798018","2017-12-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what comparative assessment he has made of (a) current levels and (b) levels 10 years ago of illiteracy among those serving a prison sentence.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116925","116925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798019","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will remove the 50 per cent faith admissions cap.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116926","116926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798020","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, on what date his Department plans to publish the Consumer and Markets Green Paper.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116927","116927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798021","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to reduce the proportion of eligible voters who are not on the electoral register.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116928","116928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798022","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what evidence base his Department uses to assess what gaps exist in the electoral register.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116929","116929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798023","2017-12-07","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of implementing an automatic voter registration system.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116930","116930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798024","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department will spend on 30 funded hours  childcare in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116931","116931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798025","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to commence the second phase of the review of cycle safety announced on 21 September, into wider road safety issues.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116932","116932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798026","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2017 to Question 113639, on shipping: ownership, how many of the vessels on each of the three routes in the table are in company groups which qualify for the Tonnage Tax scheme.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116933","116933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798027","2017-12-04","Cabinet Office","2017-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many cases of Acoustic Neuroma have been diagnosed in each Clinical Commissioning Group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116934","116934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798028","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints have been made to his Department about Capita assessments for personal independence payments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116935","116935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798029","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who previously qualified for disability living allowance have not been awarded personal independence payments following assessments by Capita.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116936","116936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798030","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport,  pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2017 to Question 113639, on shipping: ownership, how many of the vessels on each of the three routes in the table are in company groups which qualify for the Tonnage Tax scheme.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116937","116937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798031","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111770, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of providing a secure means for childcare providers to provide detailed financial information on their costs and revenues.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116938","116938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798032","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of any difference between the proportion of personal independence payment claims that are unsuccessful following assessment by Atos and Capita.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116939","116939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798033","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2017 to Question 113639, on shipping: ownership, how many of the vessels on each of the three routes in the table are registered on (a) the UK Ship Register, (b) a Red Ensign Group register, (c) EEA register or (d) non-EEA register.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116940","116940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798034","2017-12-04","Department for Transport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2017 to Question 113639, on shipping: ownership, how many of the vessels on each of the three routes in the table are registered on (a) the UK Ship Register, (b) a Red Ensign Group register, (c) the EEA register and (d) a non-EEA register.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116941","116941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798035","2017-12-05","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to line 21 of table 2.1 of Autumn Budget 2017, from which allocation of capital spend the £7 billion in year 2022-23 has been re-allocated.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116942","116942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798036","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children have access to a maintained nursery school.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116943","116943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798037","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of reviewing the system for assessing the level of business rates levied on public houses and hotels; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116944","116944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798038","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2017 to Question 115754, on children: day care, on what date she expects a contractor to be appointed.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116945","116945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798039","2017-12-05","Department for Education","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what fire safety standards her Department expects childcare settings to meet.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116946","116946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798040","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what training Valuation Office staff receive on assessing business rates.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116947","116947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798041","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many appeals were made to the Valuation Office on business rate revaluation in (a) 2010 and (b) 2017 to date.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116948","116948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798042","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what property (a) his Department and (b) HM Revenue and Customs (I) leases or (ii) owns in Liverpool Walton constituency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116949","116949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798043","2017-12-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what property his Department (a) leases and (b)  owns in Liverpool Walton constituency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116950","116950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798044","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff HM Revenue and Customs employ in Liverpool Walton constituency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116951","116951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798045","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people his Department employs in Liverpool Walton constituency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116952","116952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798046","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the proportion of the £28m announced in Autumn Budget 2017 for housing first pilot scheme and allocated to the Liverpool City Region will be released to City Region leaders.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116953","116953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/798047","2017-12-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what grants her Department has allocated to arts projects in Liverpool Walton constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116954","116954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/795681","2017-11-30","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people aged under 40 die of undiagnosed heart conditions each week in England.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116035","116035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/796676","2017-11-29","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","What steps her Department is taking to promote trade between the UK and least developed countries.","Biography information for Huw Merriman","Huw Merriman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902624","902624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/796677","2017-11-29","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","What steps she is taking to promote universal access to free public education and health systems in developing and partner countries.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902625","902625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/796678","2017-11-29","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","What aid her Department provides to Central African Republic.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902626","902626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/796679","2017-11-29","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","What support her Department provides to assist developing countries with scientific research.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902627","902627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/796680","2017-11-29","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","What steps she is taking to enable small charities in the UK to access funding allocated by her Department.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902629","902629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/796681","2017-11-29","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","What steps she is taking to ensure that private contractors funded through Official Development Assistance are scrutinised and managed effectively.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902630","902630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/796682","2017-11-29","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","What steps she is taking to promote technology for development purposes.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 902631","902631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/796693","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders in the prison estate come from each of the three most represented overseas countries.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116291","116291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797329","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 107136, whether briefings given to UK military personnel in support of US counter-terror actions outside of war zones are given in writing.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116292","116292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797330","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether has had discussions with the US Defence Secretary on allegations of civilian deaths during US raids in the Yemeni villages of Yakla and Al Jubah in January and May 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116293","116293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797331","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Defence on allegations of civilian deaths during US raids in the Yemeni villages of Yakla and Al Jubah in January and May 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116294","116294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797332","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions the Government has authorised the use of lethal force in a non-military context under the legal basis of self-defence since August 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116295","116295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797333","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to announce the details and scope of her review of air gun licensing in England and Wales.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116296","116296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797334","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November to Question 111512 on Armed Forces: funerals, whether he intends to implement the recommendations on the revision of the Army Drill Manual directions for military funerals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116297","116297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797335","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether there is a formal mechanism by which educational organisations concerned about levels of funding can effectively communicate those concerns to the Department.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116298","116298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797336","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to Autumn Budget 2017, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of assistance to Bahrain in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116299","116299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797337","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department is taking steps to ensure that children in receipt of free school meals do not go hungry over the Christmas period.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116300","116300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797338","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Hartz Reforms on employment in Germany, what support his Department provides to people in marginal employment in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116301","116301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797339","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, (a) what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse for programmes providing technical assistance and training to Bahrain and (b) from what Departmental funding stream did this assistance come from between October 2016 to October 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116302","116302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797340","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what training and assistance his Department has provided to the Saudi-led Coalition's Joint Incident and Assessment Team in the financial year 2017/18.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116303","116303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797341","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the recent findings of the Saudi-led Coalition's Joint Incident Assessment Team into five bombing incidents, published on 19 November 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116304","116304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797342","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when officials of his Department last raised the cases of Mohamed Ramadan and Husain Moosa with the Government of Bahrain.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116305","116305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797343","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of schools which follow an Accelerated Christian Education curriculum.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116306","116306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797344","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on requiring independent schools to offer qualifications that are recognised and accredited by Ofqual; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116307","116307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797345","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of independent schools that are teaching a faith-based curriculum.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116308","116308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797346","2017-12-04","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2017 to Question 112323, on trade agreements, how many of the organisations listed in that Answer have made representations to him on the priority given by the Government to a trade deal with the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116309","116309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797347","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to findings by ECPAT UK of November 2017 on calls for reform of the National Referral Mechanism (NRM) by front-line professionals, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of making the NRM part of the existing child protection system.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116310","116310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797348","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with his overseas counterparts on the efficacy of ActiPhage novel technology for testing for bovine TB.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116311","116311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797349","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward proposals to introduce a Geo-Engineering Act.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116312","116312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797350","2017-12-04","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he made of the adequacy of social care funding prior to Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116313","116313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797351","2017-12-04","Women and Equalities","2017-11-29","To ask the Women & Equalities Minister, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues about the scale of bullying of disabled people.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116314","116314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797352","2017-12-01","Women and Equalities","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the level of bullying reported against LGBT+ people.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116315","116315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797353","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Home Secretary, what assessment she has made of the level of bullying reported against disabled people.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116316","116316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797354","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the pass mark for the International English Language Test for doctors and nurses was last reviewed; and when he next plans to review the pass mark.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116317","116317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797355","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of 1 November 2017, Official Report, column 418WH on puppy smuggling, if he will detail who the stakeholders are who believe that a third party ban is unnecessary.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116318","116318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797356","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Local Enterprise Partnerships' local energy strategies funded by his Department have evaluated the potential for solar power in their areas.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116319","116319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797357","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on supporting solar power.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116320","116320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797358","2017-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has had discussions with UK retailers on the sale of plants grown with neonicotinoid pesticides; and if he will issue guidance to retailers not to sell plants grown with those pesticides.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116321","116321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797359","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on the criteria for board membership of garden settlement development corporations; and will be responsible for appointing such board members.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116322","116322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797360","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that UK pensioners in other countries are subject to the same UK pension regulations and UK pension increases irrespective of country of residence.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116323","116323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797361","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that children born prematurely are not disadvantaged by delays to the start their education.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116324","116324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797362","2017-12-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with BT on charges to landline customers who phone mobile numbers.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116325","116325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797363","2017-12-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much has been spent from the public purse on (a) central and (b) local government funding for product safety in the last twelve months for which data is available.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116326","116326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797364","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will bring forward the Power Improvement Package for the Type 45 Destroyer to 2018.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116327","116327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797365","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Royal Naval Ships he plans to deploy to the Gulf to replace HMS Diamond.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116328","116328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797366","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of likely changes to the Type 45 programme for the fitting of the MK 41 Vertical Launch Cells.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116329","116329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797367","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the priority tasks are which he has set for the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116330","116330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797368","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the problems with the Childcare Service helpline have been resolved.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116331","116331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797369","2017-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what guidance his Department provided to other Government departments on what information they should retain or redact in the impact assessments they were providing on the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116332","116332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797370","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what proportion of spending on adaptation in countries receiving finance from the International Climate Fund has been on health-related adaptation.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116333","116333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797371","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of investing in rail infrastructure on the Great Eastern Main Line to increase capacity for rail service improvements; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116334","116334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797372","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what guidance her Department provides to architects and contractors on the construction of health facilities which her Department funds or supports.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116335","116335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797373","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the additional powers granted to Homes England that were announced in Autumn Budget 2017 will be; and what the timetable is for guidance to be given to planning inspectors on the nature, extent and exercise of those powers.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116336","116336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797374","2017-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, who made the determination that it was not in the public interest to retain in the sectoral analyses the information that has been redacted from them; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116337","116337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797375","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans announce the funding allocations for the Community Housing Fund.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116338","116338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797376","2017-12-01","Cabinet Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 10794 on the electoral register, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of establishing an online service to enable people to check if they are registered to vote; and if he will publish any cost-benefit analysis his Department has undertaken on that policy.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116339","116339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797377","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on the suppression and imprisonment of Baha’i people in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116340","116340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797378","2017-12-04","Department for International Trade","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government has made an assessment of whether the Chinese Government has been involved in steel dumping in the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116341","116341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797379","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding has been awarded to local authoiities for the improvement of fire safety in their housing stock since the Grenfell Tower disaster.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116342","116342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797380","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether additional resources will be made available to housing charities for retraining advisers to deal with the effect of the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116343","116343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797381","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Health of 14 November 2017, Official Report, column 129, on NHS Trusts: subsidiary companies, if he will list the 39 subsidiary companies which have been set up by NHS Foundation Trusts.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116344","116344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797382","2018-03-23","Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster","2017-11-29","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, how many (a) full-time, (b) part-time and (c) full-time equivalent staff are employed by HM Revenue and Customs in Northern Ireland; and what assessment he has made of a potential change in staff numbers in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116345","116345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797383","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Nigerian counterpart on the murder of nine Christians in Central Plateau State in November 2017 to ensure that those responsible are brought to justice.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116346","116346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797384","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have tried to make the sea crossing between North Africa and Europe in the last six months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116347","116347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797385","2017-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to ensure UK notified bodies continue to operate effectively after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116348","116348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797386","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to ensure that the preferred bidder for the general service respirator provides assurance of the quality of the (a) acquisition of tooling for that product, (b) building and testing of assembly lines and production runs for that product, (c) testing of that product at Porton Down and (d) testing of that product by service personnel so that those personnel have confidence in those products.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116349","116349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797387","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where under the plans of the preferred bidder for the General Service Respirator In Service Support contract will the filters for that respirator be manufactured.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116350","116350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797388","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the additional cost to the public purse of his Department's managing both the current General Service Respirator In Service Support contract until 2020 and the new General Service Respirator In Service Support contract from March 2018.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116351","116351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797389","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where under the General Service Respirator In Service Support contract will liability fall in the case of hybrid masks where the mask is made by one company and a filter or other spare is made by another.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116352","116352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797390","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what account his Department has made in retendering for the General Service Respirator In Service Support contract for the potential cost to the public purse of a change of supplier; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116353","116353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797391","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what extra testing the Department plans to undertake as a result of changing from a single-sourced General Service Respirator where all the components are made by one company to a hybrid respirator where different components are made by different companies.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116354","116354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797392","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse is of testing those components of a hybrid respirator manufactured by different companies in order to ensure the safety of service personnel.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116355","116355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797393","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what risk assessment his Department has undertaken on adopting a hybrid General Service Respirator the components and spares for which are sourced from different manufacturers.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116356","116356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797394","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where the filters for the General Service Respirator be manufactured under the plans of the preferred bidder for the in-service support contract.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116357","116357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797395","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what due diligence his Department plans to undertake under the new General Service Respirator In Service Support contract before making a final decision on the preferred bidder.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116358","116358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797396","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions (a) Ministers and (b) officials have held with (i) NICE and (ii) NHS England about issuing guidelines on the use of vaginal mesh operations.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116359","116359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797397","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether (a) NHS England and (b) his Department plan to update guidance on the delivery of non-emergency patient transport.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116360","116360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797398","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to publish his Department's 25-year plan for the environment before Christmas 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116361","116361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797399","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the ability to afford sanitary products of people who are seeking asylum pending the outcome of their application; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116362","116362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797400","2017-12-01","HM Treasury","2017-11-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations his Department received ahead of the autumn Budget 2017 on compensation for Equitable Life investors.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116363","116363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797401","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) Ministers and (b) officials of the Department for International Trade on the potential effect of future trade deals on (i) food, (ii) environmental and (iii) animal welfare standards.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116364","116364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797402","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police and crime commissioners employ a deputy commissioner or deputy commissioners, and what the average salary of a deputy police and crime commissioner has been in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116365","116365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797403","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU citizens currently have indefinite leave to remain, as opposed to permanent residency, broken down by nationality.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116366","116366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797404","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether EU citizens who have indefinite leave to remain will be required to apply for settled status.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116367","116367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797405","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether EU citizens who have historically been granted indefinite leave to remain will retain the same rights after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116368","116368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797406","2017-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions Tornado teams have been deployed to prisons since September 2010.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116369","116369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797407","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made made of the effect of personal independence payments assessments on stress levels for sufferers of Motor Neurone Disease.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116370","116370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797408","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his announcement of 9 November 2017 on exploring alternatives to neonicotinoids, what plans his Department has to encourage and support (a) better pest and disease forecasting, (b) disease resistant crop varieties, (c) agronomic methods such as companion cropping and maximising the control provided by natural predators and (d) other non-chemical techniques to help sugar beet farmers control aphids.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116371","116371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797409","2017-12-04","Scotland Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether there are any plans to identify a redundant floating oil exploration platform and convert it into a museum of the history of Scotland and North Sea Oil.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116372","116372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797410","2017-12-04","Prime Minister","2017-11-29","To ask the Prime Minister, when she plans to respond the letter of 8 November 2017 from the hon. Member for Ellesmere Port and Neston on the Ministerial and Other Pensions and Salaries Act 1991.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116373","116373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797411","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Government of (a) Bangladesh and (b) Myanmar to encourage those states to sign the 1954 Convention relating to the Status of Stateless Persons.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116374","116374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797412","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Government of (a) Bangladesh and (b) Myanmar to encourage those states to sign the 1951 Refugee Convention and its 1967 Protocol.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116375","116375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797413","2017-12-01","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2017 to Question 115311, whether the UK Government has policies and procedures in place to ensure that UK aid is not spent on projects aimed at encouraging refugee returns to Myanmar before conditions for their return are safe; and what assurances he has received from the Bangladeshi Government that they would not seek to return refugees to Myanmar before conditions for their return are safe.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116376","116376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797414","2017-12-04","Department for International Development","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2017 to Question 115311, whether the UK Government has policies and procedures in place to ensure that UK aid is not spent on projects aimed at encouraging refugee returns to Myanmar that would breach the principle of non-refoulement in international refugee law.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116377","116377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797415","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2017 to Question 114943, whether his Department has set a target for the proportion of resources manufactured in the UK that will be used to construct High Speed 2.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116378","116378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797416","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2017 to Question 114759, on railways: Greater Manchester, whether as part of the range of issues discussed his Department discussed with Transport for the North and Transport for Greater Manchester transport connectivity in Leigh was specifically discussed.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116379","116379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797417","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to provide nursing placements in community nursing homes as a means of expanding training placement availability.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116380","116380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797418","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to reduce attrition rates for students on nursing degree courses.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116381","116381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797419","2017-12-01","Department for International Trade","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent estimate he has made of the cost of trade negotiations that will be required after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116382","116382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797420","2017-12-01","Department for Transport","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to deliver all deferred Access for All projects by the end of 2020.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116383","116383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797421","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his is taking to ensure that national insurance numbers are issued within 28 days for people who have been granted refugee status to avoid a gap between receiving asylum support and jobseeker's allowance or housing benefit.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116384","116384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797422","2017-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that people granted refugee status receive jobseeker's allowance; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce the potential barriers to receiving jobseeker's allowance in respect of a refugee's difficulty (a) in opening a bank account without a permanent address and (b) gaining an address without a bank account.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116385","116385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797423","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of average class sizes in Coventry South constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116386","116386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797424","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of female prisoners.","Biography information for Fiona Onasanya","Fiona Onasanya","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116387","116387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797425","2017-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken to access rape crisis centres in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116388","116388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797426","2017-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the £28 million announced in the Autumn Budget for housing first pilot schemes will be allocated to (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116389","116389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797427","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Libyan counterpart on reports of gross human rights abuses, human trafficking and slavery involving migrants in that country.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116390","116390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797428","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to widen the Apprenticeship Levy to include money for wider skills traineeships and other forms of high-quality training.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116391","116391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797429","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will produce guidelines to regulate the sharing of human breast milk.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116392","116392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797430","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has plans to bring forward legislative proposals banning the keeping of game birds in cages; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116393","116393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797431","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to fund human milk banks.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116394","116394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797432","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that homeless people can access NHS services.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116395","116395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797433","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many women’s refuges have closed in (a) Kirklees, (b) West Yorkshire and (c) England in each of the last 7 years.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116396","116396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797434","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration he has given to establishing a network of human milk banks.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116397","116397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797435","2017-12-01","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the reduction in neighbourhood policing on the ability of police forces to protect vulnerable children.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116398","116398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797436","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the funding allocated to the NHS has been spent on agency staff in each of the last 7 years.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116399","116399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797437","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to review transport services for older people to attend hospital appointments.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116400","116400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797438","2017-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of moving the date of eligibility for over 80’s winter fuel allowance to the start of the financial year.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116401","116401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797439","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of human milk bank provision across the UK.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116402","116402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797440","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2017 to Question 112465, on armed forces: officers, from which branch of the armed forces the current Military Advisor embedded within HM Treasury Defence Spending Team came.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116403","116403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797441","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on encouraging clinical commissioning groups to require providers to complete the Improving Quality in Physiological Services (IQIPS) self-assessment tool and apply for accreditation with UKAS and achieve accreditation within the duration of their contract.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116404","116404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797442","2017-12-01","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of  (a) young and (b) older people who are not registered with a GP.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116405","116405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797443","2017-12-01","Department for International Trade","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many countries have informed his Department that they would like to have trade deals with the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116406","116406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797444","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many universal credit claimants have been investigated for fraudulently claiming free prescriptions; and in how many of those investigations claimants were found to have ticked an incorrect box on the reverse of the prescription form.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116407","116407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797445","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of (a) evidence and (b) recommendations regarding Drug Consumptions Rooms reported by the (i) Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs and (ii) Volteface report, entitled Back Yard.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116408","116408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797446","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date the (a) NHS prescription form (FP10), (b) claims for NHS-funded sight tests (GOS 1) and (c) vouchers for glasses or contact lenses (GOS 3) will be amended to include a universal credit tick box.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116409","116409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797447","2017-12-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to pilot the Housing First model to prevent homelessness in the Liverpool City Region.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116410","116410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797448","2017-12-01","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November to Question 112473, how many of the 150,000 education staff trained via the Autism Education Trust (AET) are (a) teachers and (b) school support staff; and what plans she has to continue the work of the trust.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116411","116411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797449","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2017 to Question 113243 on Palestinians: foreign relations, for what reason his the term safe and secure is not used in respect of a future Palestinian state.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116412","116412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797450","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the 21 November 2017 to Question 113243 on Palestinians: foreign relations, what his Department’s definition is for  viable and sovereign.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116413","116413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797451","2017-12-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the implications are for his Department's policies of a British judge not sitting on the International Court of Justice.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116414","116414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797452","2017-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether civil servants and members of the armed forces working in MoD Main Building are permitted to bring domestic pets to work.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116415","116415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797453","2017-12-01","Department for International Trade","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the agenda was for the discussion for the 3rd TF-X fighter aircraft programme at the steering committee meeting held in London between his Department and the Government of Turkey.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116416","116416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797454","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel from (a) 42 Commando (b) 40 Commando (c) 45 Commando Royal Marines have been deployed overseas in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116417","116417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797455","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions personnel from (a) 42 Commando (b) 40 Commando (c) 45 Commando Royal Marines have been deployed overseas in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116418","116418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797456","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to announce (a) the establishment of the proposed Cadet Forces Commission and (b) the proposed transfer of volunteer officers attached to the Combined Cadet Force (RAF) and Air Training Corps to a Cadet Forces Commission.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116419","116419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797457","2017-12-04","Home Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the threat level of the group Britain First; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116420","116420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797458","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions personnel from 3 Commando Brigade have been deployed on humanitarian aid and disaster relief-related operations in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116421","116421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797459","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse has been of non-lethal equipment supplied by the Government to Ukrainian armed forces in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116422","116422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797460","2017-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the retweet of 29 November 2017 from the @realDonaldTrump  twitter account of the tweet from the @JaydaBF twitter account, whether it remains the Government's policy to proceed with President Trump's forthcoming official visit to the UK.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116423","116423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797461","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to supply lethal aid to the Ukrainian armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116424","116424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797462","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which projects forming part of his Department’s core equipment plan were subject to virement at the close of Annual Budget Cycle 16; and what the value was of those transferred budgets.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116425","116425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797463","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which projects forming part of his Department’s core equipment plan and subject to virement at the close of Annual Budget Cycle 16 had costs transferred to another core equipment plan project; and what the value was of those transferred budgets.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116426","116426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797464","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much of the budget within (a) Navy Command, (b) Army Command, (c) Air Command, (d) Joint Forces Command, (e) DG Nuclear, (f) Defence Infrastructure Organisation, (g) Head Office and (h) Corporate Services have been subject to virement in the last financial year; and what the value was of those transferred budgets.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116427","116427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797465","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the shortfall was for the recruitment of reserve and regular soldiers and officers in (a) Infantry, (b) Royal Artillery, (c) Royal Corps of Signals, (d) Army Medical Services, (e) Adjutant General's Corps, (f) Royal Armoured Corps, (g) Army Air Corps, (h) Royal Engineers, (i) Royal Logistics Corps, (j) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (k) Intelligence Corps in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116428","116428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797466","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many regular and reserve conventional UK Army personnel from (a) Infantry, (b) Royal Artillery, (c) Royal Corps of Signals, (d) Army Medical Services, (e) Adjutant General's Corps, (f) Royal Armoured Corps, (g) Army Air Corps, (h) Royal Engineers, (i) Royal Logistics Corps, (j) Royal Electrical and Mechanical Engineers and (k) Intelligence Corps were deployed in each of the (i) 2012-13 (ii) 2013-14 (iii) 2014-15 (iv) 2015-16 and (v) 2016-17 financial years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116429","116429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797467","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Royal Navy and (b) Royal Marines personnel were deployed in the (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14, (iii) 2014-15, (iv) 2015-16 and (v) 2016-17 financial years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116430","116430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797468","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors have left employment in the NHS in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116431","116431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797469","2017-12-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to tackle the illegal trade in wildlife; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116432","116432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797470","2017-12-04","Department of Health","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many qualified nurses were (a) working as nurses and (b) not working as nurses in the NHS in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116433","116433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797471","2017-12-04","Department for Education","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of students who have undergone teacher training have still been teaching by the start of the second year of their teaching career in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116434","116434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797472","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many RAF personnel were deployed overseas in the (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15, (d) 2015-16 and (e) 2016-17 financial years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116435","116435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797473","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to assess the suitability of UK suppliers during the procurement competition for the Mechanised Infantry Vehicle Programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116436","116436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797474","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces reservists were paid a bounty in the (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15, (d) 2015-16 and (e) 2016-17 financial years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116437","116437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797475","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many flying hours have been logged by BAe146 (a) CCMk2 and (b) CMk3 aircraft in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116438","116438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797476","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many flying hours have been logged on (a) Griffin HT1, (b) Hawk T1, (c) Hawk T2, (d) King Air B200, (e) Tucano T1, (f) Tutor T1, (g) Squirrel HT1, (h) Vigilant T1 and (i) Viking T1 RAF aircraft in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116439","116439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/797477","2017-12-01","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Operational Pinch Points there are in the (a) Naval Service, (b) Army Service and (c) RAF Service; and what assessment he has made of the underlying reasons for any deficits in trained strength.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 116440","116440"
