"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443429","2016-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to publish sea bass landing data by metier for 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21666","21666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443430","2016-01-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what criteria were used to determine who in South Lakeland was entitled to £500 flood compensation payments.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21609","21609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443431","2016-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) title and (b) total cost is of each (i) ongoing and (ii) completed major risk assessment relating to her Department's main responsibilities over the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21661","21661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443432","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many properties in (a) the UK and (b) England have received any funding grants of up to £5,000 from the Environment Agency for the purchase and installation of flood prevention measures in their homes since 2012.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21691","21691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443433","2016-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how householders can access funding for flood prevention measures for their properties directly and without the requirement to be part of a flood action group.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21692","21692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443434","2016-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether payments made under the Flood Re insurance scheme are subject to any provisions to ensure that homes are (a) rebuilt or repaired to meet standards for improved flood resistance and resilience and (b) not rebuilt on flood plains; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21657","21657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443435","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will review the decision by the Environment Agency to turn off five satellite pumping stations in 2017 operating in the Alt Crossens catchment.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21677","21677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443436","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to help persuade Overseas Territories leaders to make registers of beneficial ownership publicly available.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21653","21653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443437","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what trips to Saudi Arabia government ministers plan to make in 2016.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21651","21651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443438","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contingency plans he has to respond in the event that the Burundian government does not peacefully accept the presence of 5,000 peacekeepers proposed by the African Union in December 2015.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21663","21663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443439","2016-01-12","Department for International Development","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to provide assistance to people in Madaya, Syria; and if she will work with allies of the UK, the United Nations and non-governmental organisations to provide humanitarian relief to that region.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21664","21664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443440","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the 5,000 peacekeepers proposed by the African Union to protect civilians within Burundi will be safely accepted by the Burundian government.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21662","21662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443441","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2016 to Question 20871, who the (a) applicants and (b) successful bidders were for the £5.5 million Human Rights and Democracy Programme; and how much funding each such successful bidder was allocated.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21660","21660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443442","2016-01-13","Department for International Development","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure aid is delivered to the Syrian town of Madaya.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21690","21690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443443","2016-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21614","21614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443444","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2015 to Question 5430, for what reasons those Overseas Territories with financial centres did not set out timetables for implementing central registries or similarly effective systems by November 2015.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21669","21669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443445","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to publish a timetable for those UK's Overseas Territories with financial centres producing credible plans to adopt public registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21670","21670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443446","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the humanitarian effect of the Israeli government's policy on demolition orders.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21628","21628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443447","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Israeli government on demolitions in the Bedouin community of Abu Nuwar in the West Bank on 6 January 2016.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21629","21629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443448","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) acute and (b) non-acute beds there were in each London hospital in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21632","21632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443449","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the projected end of financial year budget surplus or deficit is for each health trust in London in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21633","21633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443450","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 19827, which authority is overseeing the implementation of NICE Quality Standards; and what steps are being taken to (a) monitor progress in developing Inflammatory Bowel Disease (IBD) services against, (b) implement and (c) promote NICE Quality Standard Q581 on IBD.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21647","21647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443451","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21613","21613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443452","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department defines the pay envelope in its work on considering the junior doctor contract.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21702","21702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443453","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on public health in (a) England, (b) London and (c) each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21675","21675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443454","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2015 to Question 17889, whether all current junior doctors will receive an 11 per cent pay rise after (a) basic pay and (b) all other rates of pay have been taken into consideration under the proposed new contract.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21676","21676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443455","2016-01-13","Department of Health","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the budget for public health in (a) England, (b) London and (c) each London borough is for 2016-17.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21674","21674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443456","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many failed asylum seekers have been deported in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21643","21643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443457","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many claimants have had their asylum claim rejected in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21644","21644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443458","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she estimates her Department's investigations into applications for family reunion from Kuwaiti Bidoon people will be concluded; how many such application are outstanding in that category; when the earliest such application under that category that remains outstanding was submitted; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21679","21679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443459","2016-01-13","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many firearms and of what type have been seized at the UK border in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21686","21686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443460","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on proposals by the European Commission to establish a EU border guard.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21604","21604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443461","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to allow US border guards to patrol UK airports.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21605","21605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443462","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will adjust the points-based visa criteria to reflect differences in regional average income levels.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21619","21619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443463","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who have been granted asylum since 2000 have been (a) granted indefinite leave to remain after five years and (b) deported.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21641","21641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443464","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been granted leave to remain since 2000.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21642","21642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443465","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what national guidelines her Department provides to police authorities on the closure of motorway lanes in the event of motorway traffic accidents.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21630","21630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443466","2016-01-12","Department for International Development","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether it is her Department's policy to support the G7 Initiative on Climate Risk Insurance.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21638","21638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443467","2016-01-12","Department for International Development","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to provide aid to people in (a) Madaya and (b) other cities under attack by armed forces of the government of President Assad.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21607","21607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443468","2016-01-12","Department for International Development","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment has been made of the humanitarian situation in (a) Madaya and (b) other Syrian cities under attack by armed forces of the government of President Assad.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21608","21608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443469","2016-01-13","Department for International Development","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to encourage investment in infrastructure in the north and east of Sri Lanka; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21695","21695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443470","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the changes to personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 on the prevalence of the practice of third party capture; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21696","21696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443471","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 on the number of litigants in person in personal injury claims; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21688","21688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443472","2016-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment has he made of the potential effect of changes to personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 on the number of personal injury claims; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21689","21689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443473","2016-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the second bullet point of page 26 of the report, entitled Getting it right in social welfare law, published by the Low Commission in March 2015, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the Commission's recommendation.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21672","21672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443474","2016-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the feasibility of the recommendation of the Low Commission to establish a national advice and legal support fund funded through annual contributions from his Department, the Cabinet Office, the Big Lottery Fund and the Department for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21671","21671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443475","2016-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on the personal injury portal of the changes to personal injury law and procedures announced by the Chancellor in the Autumn Statement and Spending Review 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21639","21639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443476","2016-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to develop protocols with (a) the Department for Work and Pensions, (b) the Home Office and (c) other government departments and agencies to improve the quality of decision making to reduce the number of assessments overturned on appeal.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21636","21636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443477","2016-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the judiciary on the potential change in the number of litigants in person in personal injury claims as a result of the changes to personal injury law and procedures announced by the Chancellor in the Autumn Statement and Spending Review 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21635","21635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443478","2016-01-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent progress has been made on the remaining legacy issues in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21611","21611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443479","2016-01-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she plans to commence talks on the remaining legacy issues in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21612","21612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443480","2016-01-12","Prime Minister","2016-01-08","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans that company ownership transparency in the UK's Overseas Territories with financial centres be on the agenda for the forthcoming Anti-Corruption Summit.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21654","21654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443481","2016-01-12","Department for Transport","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 11.10 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, how the £55 billion budget for High Speed 2 has been split between phase 1 and phase 2 of that project.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21649","21649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443482","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff at HS2 Ltd and his Department have gone through or are going through disciplinary or employment tribunal process since HS2 Ltd was formed.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21682","21682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443483","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff have left HS2 Ltd or his Department and been re-engaged on a self-employed or consultancy basis by either organisation in each year since the formation of HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21680","21680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443484","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff have transferred from another government department to HS2 Ltd in each year since HS2 Ltd was formed; and from what Departments those staff transferred.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21681","21681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443485","2016-01-13","Department for Transport","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many personnel employed by or on secondment to HS2 Ltd of each grade have left the organisation in each year since it was formed.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21694","21694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443486","2016-01-12","Department for Transport","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will support a claim by (a) petroleum suppliers who supply home heating oil and (b) other petroleum suppliers for a derogation from the EU rules on the amount of weekly rest required by such suppliers' drivers; and what stage that application for a derogation has reached.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21606","21606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443487","2016-01-12","Department for Transport","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department currently uses for the cost of rolling stock for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21656","21656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443488","2016-01-12","Department for Transport","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 11.10 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, whether the figure of £55.7 billion for High Speed 2 is exclusive of the cost of rolling stock for that project.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21648","21648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443489","2016-01-12","Department for Transport","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that communities and environmental mitigation is allocated sufficient funding in Phase 2 of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21655","21655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443490","2016-01-13","Wales Office","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21617","21617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443491","2016-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his polices of the conclusion of the Joseph Rowntree Foundation report, entitled Monitoring Poverty and Social Exclusion 2015, that the number of people in low-income working households has risen from 5.2 million to 6.7 million in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21621","21621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443492","2016-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his polices of the conclusion of the Joseph Rowntree Foundation report, entitled Monitoring Poverty and Social Exclusion 2015, that the proportion of families in the bottom fifth of income distribution with no savings rose to 69 per cent over the last 10 years partly due to the rising cost of living","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21623","21623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443493","2016-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his polices of the conclusion of the Joseph Rowntree Foundation report, entitled Monitoring Poverty and Social Exclusion 2015, that people in the bottom fifth of income distribution saw their living costs increase faster than average because they spent more money on essential goods.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21624","21624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443494","2016-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of universal credit claimants who are employed on a zero-hours contract.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21673","21673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443164","2016-01-11","Attorney General","2016-01-07","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Crown Prosecution Service is taking to improve the number of successful prosecutions for human trafficking offences.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21543","21543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443165","2016-01-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his plans are for the future of the UK Commission for Employment and Skills.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21583","21583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443166","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21440","21440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443167","2016-01-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how the Government plans to adapt implementation of the apprenticeships levy for different sectors.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21438","21438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443168","2016-01-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the risk of employers waiting until the new digital voucher funding mechanism is in place before taking on new apprentices.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21461","21461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443169","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21441","21441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443170","2016-01-12","Cabinet Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) jobs and (b) residents in full-time employment there were in the London Borough of Newham in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21531","21531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443171","2016-01-12","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many credit unions were subject to intervention by the Financial Services Compensation Scheme in 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21538","21538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443172","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from (a) landfill operators and (b) environmental bodies on the proposed removal of third party contributions from the Landfill Communities Fund; and whether he plans to change that proposal in response to those representations.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21539","21539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443173","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding has been allocated to the Illegal Money Lending Units over the next three years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21492","21492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443174","2016-01-12","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 19047, what discussions he has had with the Office for Budget Responsibility on including the potential effect of recent Conservative Party manifesto commitments in its forecasting of economic growth.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21514","21514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443175","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what organisations he has met to discuss the introduction of the capping of housing benefit for tenants in supported housing at the local rate of local housing allowance.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21489","21489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443176","2016-01-12","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he is taking steps to enable his Department's child tax credit department to answer the enquiries of hon. Members electronically.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21582","21582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443177","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the chairman of the Financial Conduct Authority on that body's decision not to undertake its planned review of banking culture.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21570","21570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443178","2016-01-12","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2015 to Question 17211, how much revenue has been recovered by actively targeting operational and intelligence activity to tackle the issues of online VAT fraud in the last six months.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21591","21591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443179","2016-01-12","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much correspondence the child tax credits enquiry department receives by fax each day.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21596","21596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443180","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21454","21454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443181","2016-01-12","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will provide a list of all the departments within HM Treasury.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21456","21456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443182","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many illegal money lenders Illegal Money Lending Units prevented from operating in 2015.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21493","21493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443183","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support the Financial Conduct Authority has offered to people affected by the recent administration of Brightsource Debt Management; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that debt consolidation companies make timely payments to creditors so that their customers' loans are paid down as quickly as possible.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21495","21495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443184","2016-01-12","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 19017, what information his Department holds on the reasons why the Office for Budget Responsibility does not view changes to net migration as one of the key risks or sensitivities to the medium term forecast.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21477","21477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443185","2016-01-12","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on the outsourcing of its compliance review to Concentrix; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21505","21505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443186","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from (a) landfill operators and (b) environmental bodies on the proposed removal of third party contributions from the Landfill Communities Fund; and whether he plans to make changes to that proposed removal following these representations.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21497","21497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443187","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 19365, on supported housing, if he will place the remit of the evidence review in the Library.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21500","21500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443188","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding his Department provides for local authorities to discharge their responsibilities for vulnerable adult transport.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21507","21507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443189","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his policy that vulnerable adult transport can be funded through the two per cent Social Care Precept.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21508","21508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443190","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what consultation his Department has undertaken with councils with statutory responsibility for vulnerable people in supported housing (a) before and (b) since the announcement that housing benefit for tenants in supported housing will be capped at the local rate of local housing allowance.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21483","21483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443191","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans that the two per cent social care precept will be ring-fenced for particular items of expenditure.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21459","21459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443192","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21442","21442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443193","2016-01-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many £500 grants were provided to help households affected by flooding in each district and unitary authority in Lancashire between 5 December 2015 and 7 January 2016; and how much funding has been received by each of those councils to provide such grants up to 7 January 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21597","21597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443194","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 19365, on housing benefit, (a) when the evidence review began, (b) who has been commissioned to undertake that review and (c) when he expects that review to be published.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21572","21572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443195","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what consultation his Department has undertaken with organisations that provide supported housing for vulnerable people (a) before and (b) since the announcement that housing benefit for tenants in supported housing will be capped at the local rate of local housing allowance.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21484","21484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443196","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what organisations he has met to discuss the introduction of the capping of housing benefit for tenants in supported housing at the local rate of local housing allowance.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21485","21485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443197","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the likely number of (a) new tenants and (b) tenancies in supported housing in each of the next five years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21486","21486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443198","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) frail elderly people, (b) young people leaving care, (c) women fleeing domestic violence, (d) people recovering from alcohol and substance misuse, (e) people with mental health issues and (f) people with physical or learning disabilities live in supported housing and are eligible for housing benefit.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21487","21487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443199","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people who live in supported housing are eligible for housing benefit.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21488","21488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443200","2016-01-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many children in England have lived in overcrowded homes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21533","21533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443201","2016-01-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of homes in the social rented sector have been classified as overcrowded in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21534","21534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443202","2016-01-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, after how long it is his policy to take action when a local planning authority has not produced a playing pitch strategy; and what powers his Department has to taken such action after that period.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21513","21513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443203","2016-01-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to bring forward proposals to ensure service level agreement requirements incorporated into broadband supplier contracts with their customers ensure a reasonable minimum speed of download is maintained and commensurate with the advertised product.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21499","21499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443204","2016-01-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will commission independent research on the effect of fixed-odds betting terminals on the health of their users and on the communities in which they are prevalent.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21567","21567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443205","2016-01-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of devolving to the Scottish Parliament all aspects of (a) gaming and betting legislation, (b) including curbing the terminals' speed of play and maximum stakes for fixed-odds betting terminals and (c) other regulation of fixed-odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21566","21566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443206","2016-01-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21443","21443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443207","2016-01-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations his Department has received from professional football teams in England and Wales on the potential introduction of safe-standing facilities at higher tier sports stadia in the last year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21466","21466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443208","2016-01-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21481","21481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443209","2016-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21482","21482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443210","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21444","21444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443211","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) establishment and (b) strength personnel of (i) 6 SCOTS and (ii) 7 SCOTS have failed a medical in each year from 2012 to 2015.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21458","21458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443212","2016-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of Royal Navy search and rescue operations in the Mediterranean Sea in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21465","21465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443213","2016-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will direct the armed forces to drop emergency food aid to the under siege town of Madaya in Syria.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21436","21436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443214","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which military assets provide fisheries protection within the UK's exclusive economic zone.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21579","21579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443215","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the total strength of (a) 6 SCOTS and (b) 7 SCOTS attended (i) more than 50 per cent and (ii) more than 75 per cent of regular duties in each year between 2012 and 2015.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21576","21576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443216","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to build facilities to simulate the possibility of the future F35B Lightning II aircraft operating in austere operating bases.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21578","21578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443217","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date the decision was made not to proceed with developing a future theatre nuclear weapon (FTNW); and how much had been spent on (a) the vehicle element and (b) the warhead element of the FTNW programme up to that point.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21550","21550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443218","2016-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the outcome was of the recruitment campaign organised by the Reserve Forces and Cadet Association of Northern Ireland in Summer 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21536","21536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443219","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) enforcement action was taken and (b) warning letters were issue against the Atomic Weapons Establishment by regulatory authorities in 2014 and 2015; and which of those enforcement actions are ongoing.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21555","21555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443220","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish the UK's Future Nuclear Deterrent: 2015 Update to Parliament.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21558","21558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443221","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the costs were of repairing structural defects to the A45 facility at the Atomic Weapons Establishment (Project Phoebe).","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21551","21551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443222","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions since 1 January 2014 explosives stored at the Atomic Weapons Establishment have been found to be wrongly labelled; on what date it was discovered that such explosives were wrongly labelled; and what (a) types and (b) quantities of explosives were involved in each such case.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21552","21552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443223","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, further to his letter referenced MSU/4/5/8 which is placed in the Library, whether and to what timescale his Department plans to commission its own socio-economic report in addition to the economic impact assessment commissioned by the fishing community; if he will publish results of such a report; and what the implications of such work are for the timescales for determining the proposed byelaw changes for the inner sound between Raasay and the mainland.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21547","21547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443224","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what actions have been undertaken in response to finding reference TRF0195 of the Defence Nuclear Safety Regulator's assessment of the Astral Climb 12 nuclear emergency exercise; and on what dates each such action was closed out.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21556","21556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443225","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to address the disproportionate number of exclusions from school of Gypsy, Roma and Traveller pupils.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21520","21520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443226","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she will re-establish the Gypsy, Roma and Traveller Education Stakeholder Group; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21519","21519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443227","2016-01-12","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate how many pupils are being taught how to cook in the 2015-16 academic year.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21599","21599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443228","2016-01-12","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on local authorities offering council tax discounts to in-house foster carers but not to independent or agency foster carers looking after children in care from that authority; and what information she holds on which authorities have such arrangements.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21460","21460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443229","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many jobs in (a) her Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21445","21445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443230","2016-01-12","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many childcare providers waited longer than 25 weeks to receive registration from Ofsted in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21437","21437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443231","2016-01-12","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which children's services departments are rated as (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requiring improvement and (d) inadequate; and which such departments are subject to intervention measures.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21475","21475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443232","2016-01-12","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people of each gender work in her Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21480","21480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443233","2016-01-12","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what grants have been made by the Leadership Equality and Diversity Fund; and for what purpose each such grant has been made.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21472","21472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443234","2016-01-12","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding has been given to Local Safeguarding Children Boards in each year since 2010; and whether her Department plans to institute a nationally-defined funding formula for such boards.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21473","21473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443235","2016-01-12","Department for Education","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which children's services departments have been subject to multi-agency inspections since 2010; and what the results were of each such inspection.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21474","21474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443236","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many jobs in (a) her Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21446","21446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443237","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 19268, what (a) financial penalties and (b) other mechanisms are available to ensure that all private rented properties have an energy efficiency certificate.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21434","21434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443238","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 19268, what financial penalties and other mechanisms are available to ensure that all private rented sector landlords improve their properties to a minimum energy efficiency rating of E from April 2018.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21529","21529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443239","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will investigate the circumstances surrounding the leak of natural gas at the Brae Alpha platform of 26 December 2015; and what steps he plans to take to ensure that a similar incident does not occur on that platform or any other offshore installation.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21562","21562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443240","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions her Department has had with the operators of the Brae Alpha platform following the gas leak on 26 December 2015 that resulted in the shutdown of that platform.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21561","21561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443241","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with the oil and gas industry on the relationship between maintaining safety standards and reducing the cost of production.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21560","21560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443242","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what initial assessment she has made of the implications of the incident at Porter Ranch, California, for safety and engineering procedures and standards in the UK onshore unconventional gas extraction sector.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21523","21523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443243","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to make an assessment of the humaneness of hunting with dogs.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21544","21544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443244","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to extend the Farming Recovery Fund to provide support for farmers in all areas affected by the recent flooding.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21517","21517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443245","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of the implementation of the EU Water Framework Directive 2000 on how floods have been controlled in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21541","21541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443246","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of implementing the Natural England report, Vital Uplands, published in 2009, in respect of restoration of deep upland vegetation to control hillside water run-off and valley flooding.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21542","21542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443247","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her ministerial colleagues on the Hunting Act 2004.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21521","21521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443248","2016-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to establish a commission to examine the issue of hunting foxes with dogs before bringing forward proposals for a vote in the House on that issue.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21595","21595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443249","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the number of households affected by floods on 26 December 2015 in (a) Lancashire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21602","21602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443250","2016-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the number of homes affected by flooding in winter 2015-16 that do not have insurance.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21603","21603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443251","2016-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of legal provision relating to rights to grant or withhold access to caves.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21470","21470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443252","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many jobs in (a) her Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21447","21447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443253","2016-01-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings and communication Ministers and senior civil servants have had with Ruimte voor de Rivier regarding long-term flood prevention since June 2010.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21476","21476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443254","2016-01-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many oil refinery workers have been killed as a result of UK airstrikes in Syria; and whether such workers are classed as civilian.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21502","21502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443255","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21467","21467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443256","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on the number of political prisoners held in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21468","21468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443257","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on the continued detention and wellbeing of Hasan Mushaima.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21469","21469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443258","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21448","21448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443259","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the international legal implications of reports of Saudi Arabia bombing the Iranian Embassy in Sana'a; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21464","21464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443260","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 January 2016 to Question 15523, when he last discussed alleged violations of international humanitarian law in Yemen with his Saudi counterpart.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21462","21462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443261","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 January 2016 to Question 15523, when he last reviewed alleged violations of international humanitarian law in Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21463","21463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443263","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the US (a) government and (b) Congress on comments made by Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump on banning Muslims from entering the US.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21426","21426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443264","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to support initiative to the create an independent regional centre for security dialogue in the Middle East.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21580","21580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443266","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on Continuity of Education Allowance in independent schools in financial year (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15; how many children were in receipt of that allowance in each of those years; and which five schools had the highest spend on that allowance in each of those years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21577","21577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443267","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implementation to date of the Joint Comprehensive Plan for Action on the Iranian nuclear programme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21540","21540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443268","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of Laos on the treatment of the Christian minority in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21535","21535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443269","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 3 of the HMG Strategy for Abolition of the Death Penalty 2010-2015, as revised in October 2011, what bilateral agreements his Department promotes between the Government and the government of Saudi Arabia on reducing the number of executions carried out as part of that government's judicial process.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21549","21549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443270","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to Appendix Four of the HMG Strategy for Abolition of the Death Penalty 2010-15, as revised in October 2011, how his Department ensures that the EU minimum standards referred to are met in countries which maintain use of the death penalty as part of their judicial process.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21546","21546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443271","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Executive Summary of the HMG Strategy for Abolition of the Death Penalty 2010-2015, as revised in October 2011, what steps his Department is taking to help impose further restrictions on countries which continue to practise the death penalty as part of their judicial process; and what progress on the imposition of such restrictions has been made to date.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21553","21553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443272","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on whether any members of the Burmese army who have received training from the Government have been involved in military offensives in which war crimes have allegedly been committed against civilians.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21564","21564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443273","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page three of the HMG Strategy for Abolition of the Death Penalty 2010-2015, as revised in October 2011, what legal challenges to the mandatory death penalty his Department has been involved in involving (a) UK citizens and (b) non-UK citizens in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21554","21554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443274","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 January 2016 to Question 15523, what assessment he has made of whether incidents of alleged violations of international humanitarian law in Yemen have been investigated fully by each party involved in that conflict.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21584","21584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443275","2016-01-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 January 2016 to Question 15523, what assessment he has made of the credibility of assurances by Saudi Arabia that it is in compliance with international humanitarian law in the conflict with Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21585","21585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443276","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessments he has made of the reasons for the increase in excess winter mortality rates in England in the winter of 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21569","21569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443277","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many psychiatric nurses were in post in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21586","21586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443278","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training and professional development is given to (a) doctors, (b) nurses and (c) mental health professionals on (i) conflict resolution, (b) methodical empathy and (iii) mental self-care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21587","21587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443279","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training and professional development is given to (a) doctors, (b) nurses and (c) mental health professionals on managing their own stress levels.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21588","21588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443280","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of local authority funding reductions on the provision of transport for vulnerable adults.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21571","21571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443281","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the changes to personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 on the level of costs and changes for treatment for personal injury resourced by the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21524","21524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443282","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish NHS England's decision making criteria for the assessment of highly specialised technologies.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21563","21563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443283","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2015 to Question 19356, if he will make it his policy to collect information on the proportion of people identified as having experienced child abuse who are diagnosed with a mental health condition as a young person or adult.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21594","21594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443284","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20190, if he will make it his policy to collect centrally the number of (a) young carers accessing Children and Adolescene Mental Health Services (CAMHS) and (b) children provided with young carers assessments following contact with CAMHS.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21593","21593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443285","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many commissioning policies were developed through the NHS England Specialised Commissioning Oversight Group in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21575","21575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443286","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in excess winter mortality rates in North East England in the winter of 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21568","21568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443287","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many highly specialised technologies are awaiting assessment by NHS England which were not selected for consideration by NICE's highly specialised technology appraisal process.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21573","21573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443288","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many highly specialised technologies are currently being assessed by the NHS England highly specialised technologies assessment process.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21574","21574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443289","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the end of financial year budget surpluses or deficits was for each health trust in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21600","21600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443290","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of elective operations were cancelled in (a) England and Wales, (b) London and (c) each health trust in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21601","21601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443291","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to made the drug Everolimus available on the NHS for treating the subependymal giant cell astrocytoma form of tuberous sclerosis complex.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21598","21598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443292","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21449","21449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443293","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients were seen within four hours of arriving at each A&E department in London in December (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21503","21503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443294","2016-01-12","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many delays of over 12 hours there were in each A&E department in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21504","21504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443295","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of medicines selected by NHS England Clinical Reference Groups for the development of commissioning policies have been (a) approved and (b) not approved by each Programme of Care board.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21509","21509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443296","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many technologies have been assessed through NHS England's commissioning through evaluation process in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21510","21510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443297","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department provides for vulnerable adult transport.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21506","21506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443298","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees were resettled in each (a) region and (b) parliamentary constituency in the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21496","21496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443299","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many jobs in (a) her Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21450","21450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443300","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the applicability to Donald Trump of her Department's guidelines on excluding hate speakers from entering the UK.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21427","21427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443301","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential threat to minority communities in the UK of language used by US presidential election candidates which her Department defines as extreme.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21428","21428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443302","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has a policy on US  presidential candidates entering the UK who use hate speech.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21425","21425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443303","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many licences for experimentation with animals the Animals and Science Committee granted in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21581","21581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443304","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department provides for members of the Yemeni community in the UK to contact or find out information on relatives in Yemen affected by the civil war in that country.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21528","21528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443305","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's publication, Call to End Violence against Women and Girls' Action Plan 2014, published in March 2014, what progress has been made on putting in place a new code of practice to ensure that safe addresses of victims of domestic and sexual abuse are protected; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21527","21527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443306","2016-01-12","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to make an assessment of the performance of the National Crime Agency in its first year of full operation in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21537","21537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443307","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance has been issued to police forces on monitoring and recording Gypsy and Traveller status as separate ethnic categories.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21518","21518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443308","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many terrorism-related suspects on police bail have (a) been ordered to relinquish and (b) relinquished their UK passports since January 2013.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21511","21511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443309","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many terrorism-offence related suspects on police bail are understood by her Department to have broken bail and left the UK since January 2013.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21512","21512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443310","2016-01-11","Department for International Development","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many jobs in (a) her Department and (b) its non-departmental public body, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21451","21451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443311","2016-01-12","Department for International Development","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much is allocated in her Department's operational plan budget for projects in (a) Jordan and (b) Iraq for 2015-16.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21501","21501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443312","2016-01-12","Department for International Development","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many people of each gender work in her Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21478","21478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443313","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21452","21452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443314","2016-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has paid to (a) Rentokil and (b) other pest control companies in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21471","21471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443315","2016-01-11","Attorney General","2016-01-07","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20564, how many people were charged with jury (a) intimidation and (b) tampering in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21435","21435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443316","2016-01-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) his Department, (b) HM Courts and Tribunal Service, (c) HM Prison Service, (d) the Legal Aid Agency and (e) the National Offender Management Service; how many of those employees are paid more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those organisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21457","21457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443317","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many serving prisoners were not in prison on 25 December 2015; what offences were committed by each such offender; and how many such offences were in what category of violent offences against the person offences.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21530","21530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443318","2016-01-12","Northern Ireland Office","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many people of each gender work in her Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21479","21479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443319","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will meet with representative bodies of people acting for personal injury complainants to discuss the outcome of his discussions with the insurance industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21525","21525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443320","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is considering to reduce (a) CO2 and (b) NOx emissions for HGVs (i) domestically and (ii) at EU Level.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21545","21545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443321","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the use of longer-length or mega lorries in (a) the UK and (b) urban areas.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21565","21565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443322","2016-01-12","Department for Transport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the Government has not given financial and other support to British Airways' Green Sky project; and what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the potential cancellation of that project on the aviation industry's sustainable aviation agenda.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21516","21516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443323","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Government plans to commence its review of driving offences; when he plans that the public consultation on that review will take place; and what timetable he has set for the completion of that review.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21522","21522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443324","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21453","21453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443325","2016-01-12","Department for Transport","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information he holds on how many Volkswagen vehicles have been re-tested for emissions since September 2015.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21439","21439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443326","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what impact assessment his Department has carried out on the effects of reductions in universal credit work allowance on (a) incentives to work and (b) the number of hours worked.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21429","21429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443327","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what impact assessment his Department has carried out on the effects of reductions in the universal credit work allowance on carers.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21431","21431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443328","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what impact assessment his Department has carried out on the effects of reductions in the universal credit work allowance on employees of his Department.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21432","21432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443329","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what impact assessment his Department has carried out on the effects of reductions in universal credit work allowance on workers under the age of 25.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21430","21430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443330","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what impact assessment his Department has carried out on the effects of reductions in the universal credit work allowance on (a) working families and (b) people's ability to take on part-time work.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21433","21433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443331","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobs in (a) his Department and (b) each of its non-departmental public bodies, executive agencies, non-ministerial departments, advisory bodies and other accountable statutory bodies (i) have been abolished or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent since 2010 and (ii) will be abolished in or relocated from Stoke-on-Trent by 2020.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21455","21455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443332","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to proposed changes in personal injury law and procedure announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what assessment he has made of the level of potential reduction in recoupment of social security benefits paid to personal injury victims following such changes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21498","21498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443333","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the extent to which jobseekers required to obtain a Disclosure and Barring Service (DBS) check to take up new work can afford to do so; and if he will estimate the cost of jobcentres providing financial support for people in need of a DBS check.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21494","21494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443334","2016-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 20339, what the repayment requirements are for universal credit advance payments; and whether interest is charged on those payments.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21532","21532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443335","2016-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many men born in November 1954 resident in Preston parliamentary constituency have been notified of changes in the age at which they will receive the State Pension; and on what date his Department contacted those men with that information.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21515","21515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443336","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the likely change in the total cost of housing benefit as a result of the introduction of capping of housing benefit for tenants in supported housing at the local rate of local housing allowance in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20 and (c) 2020-21.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21490","21490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443337","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what organisations he has met to discuss the introduction of capping of housing benefit for tenants in supported housing at the local rate of local housing allowance.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21491","21491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443338","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the contract payment for each of the principal Work Programme providers is for each six month period or quarter.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21526","21526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443339","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Health and Safety Executive on ensuring reductions in operators' production costs do not adversely affect the safety of offshore workers in the oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21548","21548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443340","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the investigation conducted by the Office for Nuclear Regulation into the operability and availability of fire detection systems at the Atomic Weapons Establishment has been completed.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21559","21559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443341","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Health and Safety Executive was notified of any cases of non-compliance with explosives labelling regulations at the Atomic Weapons Establishment during 2015 on which action was subsequently taken to address this situation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21557","21557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443342","2016-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his contribution of 20 June 2011, Official Report, column 52, on the Pensions Bill [Lords], that the Government would consider transitional arrangements, what transitional arrangements the Government considered.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21592","21592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443343","2016-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2015 to Question 16608, how many potential overlapping payments between the Universal Credit Live Service and housing benefit have been identified since April 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21589","21589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443344","2016-01-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to notify universal credit claimants of the changes to their entitlement taking effect from April 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21590","21590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442823","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure greater collaboration between businesses and education to promote skills for potential future careers.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21179","21179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442824","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21250","21250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442825","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices with special educational needs or disabilities have not completed their NHS apprenticeship placements.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21243","21243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442826","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices with special educational needs or disabilities have not completed their apprenticeship placements with a five per cent club employer.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21244","21244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442827","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 3.22 of English Apprenticeships: Our 2020 Vision, how many apprentices with special educational needs or disabilities have not completed their transport-related apprenticeship placements.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21245","21245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442828","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 3.22 of English Apprenticeships: Our 2020 Vision, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of the planned 30,000 transport-related apprenticeships which will be taken up by apprentices with special educational needs or disabilities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21246","21246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442829","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 3.28 of English Apprenticeships: Our 2020 Vision, what information his Department holds on the proportion of planned apprenticeships provided by the five per cent club which are expected to be taken up by apprentices with special educational needs or disabilities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21247","21247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442830","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 3.22 of English Apprenticeships: Our 2020 Vision, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of the planned 17,000 NHS apprenticeship starts which will be taken up by apprentices with special educational needs or disabilities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21248","21248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442831","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps in the business rates review to make specific provision for energy intensive industries.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21274","21274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442833","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps in the business rates review to make specific provision for manufacturing industries.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21275","21275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442834","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps in the business rates review to make specific provision for the retail industry.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21276","21276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442836","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the letter from Lord Livingston of Parkhead to the Chairman of the European Scrutiny Committee of 3 July 2014, Deposited Paper DEP2015-0877, what progress HM Revenue and Customs has made establishing a cross departmental working group to take forward the modelling of the tax implications of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21295","21295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442837","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the sale of illegally-produced alcohol in shops.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21312","21312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442838","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been employed on a zero-hours contract in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21416","21416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442839","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of financial controls and reporting systems for charities in response to the liquidation of Kids Company.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21353","21353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442840","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been unemployed on a part-time basis in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21413","21413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442841","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been employed on a full-time basis in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21414","21414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442842","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21415","21415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442843","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the change in the proportion of the working age population employed by the public sector in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21280","21280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442844","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the most recent assessment of progress in the roll-out of the universal credit programme by the Infrastructure and Project Authority is.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21263","21263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442845","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in England were registered to vote at the end of (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21267","21267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442848","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21258","21258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442849","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of HM Revenue and Customs' strategy to enforce the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21217","21217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442850","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government will publish its response to the discussion document on Intermediaries Legislation (IR35).","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21182","21182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442851","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase the affordability of homes in the Greater London area for people under the age of 30.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21185","21185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442853","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) average and (b) contractually-specified maximum length of time is that a claimant has to wait for their complaint to be resolved by Concentrix.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21164","21164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442854","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many IT contractors were employed by HM Revenue and Customs on a self-employed basis in 2015.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21195","21195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442855","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs spent on IT contractors in 2015.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21196","21196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442856","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will increase the budget for IT contractors employed by HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21197","21197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442857","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the (a) potential effect on the UK economy of the decision by the US Federal Reserve to raise US interest rates and (b) potential effect of this decision on interest rates in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21189","21189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442858","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of trade between the UK and Switzerland was in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21190","21190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442859","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to maintain current levels of funding for the National Illegal Money Lending Team.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21266","21266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442860","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average time taken is  by (a) Concentrix and (b) HM Revenue and Customs to process each tax credit claim adjustment; and what guidance there is in Concentrix's contract on how long it should take to process each tax credit claim adjustment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21278","21278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442861","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many courts cases HM Revenue and Customs has initiated for tax abuse under the General Anti-Abuse Rule since its introduction; and how many people or companies found to have committed tax abuse under this Rule have been charged penalties.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21249","21249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442863","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the change has been in the numbers of people who missed the 31 January deadline for making their tax return between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21281","21281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442864","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the change has been in the numbers of people contributing to stock and share ISAs in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21283","21283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442865","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax avoidance schemes are registered with HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) under (a) the disclosure regime for VAT and (b) the disclosure of tax avoidance schemes; how many individuals are registered with each of those schemes; how many (i) individuals and (ii) schemes HMRC has estimated will be issued with accelerated payment notices (APNs) in (A) 2014-15, (B) 2015-16 and (C) 2016-17; and how many (1) individuals and (2) schemes HMRC has issued with APNs.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21391","21391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442866","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will prepare contingency plans for flexible funding for small and medium-sized enterprises to replace JEREMIE funding in the event of UK withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21381","21381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442867","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is the policy of the Government that a written contract of employment is prerequisite to making a claim for working tax credit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21398","21398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442868","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints the Counter-Avoidance Intelligence Team has received about tax avoidance in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21388","21388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442869","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many penalties have been issued by HM Revenue and Customs to (a) scheme promoters and (b) their clients for non-disclosure of tax avoidance schemes in each year since 2009-10 under the (i) disclosure regime for VAT and (ii) Disclosure of Tax Avoidance Schemes regime.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21389","21389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442870","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 by the Minister for Skills, Official Report, column 1401, if he will introduce a levy to continue to fund action against loan sharks by the National Illegal Money Lending Team.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21408","21408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442871","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have challenged HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) in court following the issue of an Accelerated Payment Notice (APN) for their alleged role in a tax avoidance scheme since the APN system came into force; and in such cases (a) on how many occasions the courts have found against HMRC and (b) what the total value is of tax paid back with interest to people who have won.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21390","21390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442872","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what advice the Financial Conduct Authority provides to UK banks and building societies offering mortgages on properties in the Occupied Palestinian. Territories.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21322","21322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442873","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) his Department, (b) the Office for Budget Responsibility, (c) the Financial Conduct Authority and (d) HM Revenue and Customs; how many of those employees earn more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those organisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21341","21341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442874","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what forecast he has made of the change in population in each London borough up to 2030.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21340","21340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442875","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2015 to Question 16795, if he will undertake an assessment of activities by third parties fully funded by local authorities designed to influence Government and Parliament; and if he will extend the Code of Recommended Practice on Local Authority Publicity to cover such groups.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21410","21410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442876","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21279","21279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442877","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount that will be raised in each local authority by the two per cent social care precept in the first year of its operation.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21291","21291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442878","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on what local government services can be funded by the two per cent social care precept.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21290","21290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442879","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the new town of Northstowe will be developed to schedule.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21221","21221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442883","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations his Department has received about exit fees from retirement homes and villages; and if he will bring forward legislative proposals to regulate such fees.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21355","21355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442884","2016-01-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to (a) encourage the training of new behind the scenes production staff and (b) promote Britain's position in the global film industry.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21361","21361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442885","2016-01-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21251","21251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442886","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has sent a letter of request to the Defense Security Cooperation Agency for the purchase of P-8 Maritime Patrol Aircraft.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21228","21228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442887","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to lease US Air Force Poseidon P-8 aircraft prior to the entry into service of the UK P-8 aircraft in 2019-20.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21229","21229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442888","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 17 December 2015, HC WS431, on UK Embedded Forces, what the (a) rank and (b) military unit is of the UK personnel embedded with (i) French and (ii) Spanish armed forces.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21225","21225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442889","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many golf courses his Department owns; and what plans his Department has to sell such property.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21222","21222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442890","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment has been made of the health and wellbeing of refugees and asylum seekers who arrived at the UK Sovereign Base Areas in Cyprus (a) in 1998 and (b) in October 2015; and what steps are being taken to support their health and wellbeing.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21203","21203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442891","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure former aircraft carrier personnel do not become deskilled before the Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carriers come into active service.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21186","21186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442892","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what airstrikes have been conducted by the Royal Air Force against Daesh in the last three weeks.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21187","21187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442893","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the future of the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21309","21309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442894","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information he holds on whether the purchase of P-8 Maritime Patrol Aircraft through the US foreign military sales procedure will require US Congressional approval.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21329","21329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442895","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in states which allow women to engage in close combat operations on effective implementation of that policy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21394","21394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442896","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 21 July 2015 to Question 8367, how many UK troops are embedded in (a) Syria, (b) Lebanon, (c) Libya, (d) Yemen, (e) Turkey and (g) USA.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21238","21238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442897","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the planned multi-role ministerial transport aircraft will have an updated livery to reflect its new purpose.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21239","21239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442898","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many HGV drivers were trained at the Defence School of Transport, Leconfield, in the last 12 months; and what the maximum student capacity of that school was in the last year.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21356","21356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442899","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether training in celestial navigation is provided for new recruits to the Royal Navy.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21360","21360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442900","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the armed forces are taking in cooperation with other countries to prevent piracy off the coast of West Africa.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21350","21350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442901","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20200, what estimate his Department has made of its total spend on mental health specialists in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21330","21330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442902","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the use of private companies to arrange foster care placements.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21352","21352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442903","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2015 to Question 18680, for what reasons her Department does not hold information on (a) the number of academies in England that were in deficit and (b) the total deficit of those academies in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21397","21397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442904","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reason his Department sets an age limit for the receipt of funding for Masters degrees; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21327","21327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442905","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the total funding for Southwell Minster School in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21174","21174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442906","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of per pupil funding for Southwell Minster School in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21175","21175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442907","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what per pupil funding for Southwell Minster School was in 2014-15.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21176","21176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442908","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total funding for Southwell Minster School was in 2014-15.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21177","21177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442909","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average level of funding per pupil in secondary schools in Newark constituency has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21178","21178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442910","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2015 to Question 19591, what alternative provision is available for bullied children who subsequently develop complex needs; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure government funding attaches to a child requiring alternative provision but lacking an EHC plan because the damage from bullying has caused a collapse in self-esteem and wellbeing rather than a physical medical condition.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21192","21192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442911","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average level of funding per pupil has been in secondary schools in Nottinghamshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21214","21214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442912","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of changes in the cash level of per pupil funding for secondary schools in the county of Nottinghamshire in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21211","21211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442913","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the level of funding per pupil at Southwell Minster School has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21212","21212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442914","2016-01-11","Department for Education","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total level of funding at Southwell Minster School has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21213","21213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442915","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21252","21252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442917","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she plans to publish a response to the consultation carried out by her Department between July and September 2014 into energy issues affecting park homes including energy supply and use of the application of energy efficiency measures.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21401","21401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442918","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she will announce details of the amount to be made available in the next round of Contracts for Difference auctions in the UK energy market; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21236","21236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442919","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she will announce the results of the next round of Contracts for Difference auctions in the UK energy market; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21237","21237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442920","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people of each gender work in her Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21287","21287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442921","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether it is Government policy to attain technology neutrality; and what progress has been made towards that objective.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21289","21289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442922","2016-01-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what support her Department provides for the development of small modular nuclear reactions.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21348","21348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442923","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has allocated for the maintenance and restoration of peatlands in 2016-17.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21354","21354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442924","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her article of 30 December 2015 in the Yorkshire Post, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the Government is investing £54 per person on flood defences in Yorkshire, Lancashire and Cumbria, the East Midlands and Northumbria, and £42 per person in the South East.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21375","21375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442925","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what additional flood support Salford City Council is likely to receive; when such support will be granted; what such support will cover; and how such support can be accessed.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21366","21366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442926","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support will be provided to offset the costs incurred by Salford City Council as a result of flooding which are not covered by the Bellwin scheme.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21367","21367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442927","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what use she plans to make of the granting of (a) exemptions and (b) increased vessel limits for gillnetting of sea bass to achieve quota recommendations from the International Council for Exploration of the Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21368","21368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442928","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the findings of the report by the Dogs Trust entitled, Puppy Smuggling, the Scandal Continues, published in July 2015, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the reasons for the illegal landing of puppies for commercial sale identified in that report.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21392","21392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442929","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps is she taking to achieve an end to overfishing by 2020.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21320","21320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442930","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on British agriculture of the Nairobi Package agreed by the World Trade Organisation on 19 December 2015.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21342","21342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442931","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many marketing standards conformity checks for consignments of fresh fruit and vegetables exported to the UK by Israel have not been accepted on the grounds that the products in those consignments originated in the Occupied Palestinian Territories in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21326","21326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442933","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of goods imported into the UK labelled as products of Israel that are from the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21323","21323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442934","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of fruit and vegetables imported into the UK have postcodes that show that the produce originated from the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21324","21324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442935","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what marketing standards conformity checks are applied to produce from settlements in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21325","21325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442937","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21253","21253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442938","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding will be made available to Salford City Council in financial years (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17 to develop flood defences along the river Irwell.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21240","21240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442939","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward proposals to ban the use of plastic microbeads in cosmetics and soaps.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21162","21162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442940","2016-01-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to respond to the proposals on licences set down in Clause 23 of the draft Wildlife Bill produced by the Law Commission.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21159","21159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442941","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Colombian government about alleged historical practices by the Colombian security services against trade unions.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21160","21160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442943","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Iranian government on respecting UN resolutions on Holocaust denial.","Biography information for Lord Pickles","Sir Eric Pickles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21161","21161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442944","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when and where he plans to publish the Government's new Africa Strategy.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21163","21163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442945","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Bahrain on the treatment in prison of Hasan Mushaima.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21199","21199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442946","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of discrimination by the Bahraini government against Bahraini Shia.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21200","21200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442947","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in Bahrain on implementation of the recommendations of the Bahrain Independent Commission of Inquiry report.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21201","21201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442948","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of political prisoners in Bahrain; and what discussions he has held with the Bahraini government on the release of political prisoners.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21198","21198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442949","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21254","21254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442950","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he held with his Swiss counterpart on that country's relationship with the EU as part of his Department's preparations for the renegotiation of the UK's relationship with the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21191","21191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442951","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Indian and Portuguese counterparts on the detention and potential deportation of Paramjeet Singh; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21333","21333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442952","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with Turkish authorities on the illegal trade in oil by Daesh across the Syrian-Turkish border.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21393","21393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442953","2016-01-11","HM Treasury","2016-01-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2015 to Question 20068, how many British-based individuals have breached the sanctions regime against Daesh; and how many bank accounts have been frozen in the UK as part of the efforts by the UN and the Government to prevent funds from being transferred to Daesh.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21395","21395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442954","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2015 to Question 19413, if he will change the policy on awards offered by other countries to allow recognition of knighthoods awarded on the advice of the governments of Britain's Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21396","21396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442956","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to support EU task force on the death penalty.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21300","21300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442957","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what projects in which countries his Department promotes on reducing the number of judicial killings; and how much his Department has provided in funding to each such project.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21301","21301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442958","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what involvement the UK has had in discussions relating to talks between North and South Korea.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21302","21302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442959","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions and in which countries his Department has declined to offer police, justice and security assistance to countries which retain the death penalty as part of their judicial system in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21293","21293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442960","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from his Indian and Portuguese counterparts on the detention and potential deportation of Paramjeet Singh; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21308","21308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442961","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons his Department did not include Saudi Arabia in Appendix One of its publication entitled HMG Strategy for the Abolition of the Death Penalty 2010-2015.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21362","21362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442962","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to restore the full value of the UK's rebate from the EU as part of the process of renegotiating the UK's membership.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21277","21277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442963","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage other countries to abolish the death penalty as part of their judicial process.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21292","21292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442964","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the change has been in average levels of individual obesity of children between 2005 and 2010.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21282","21282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442965","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many portions of milk have been reimbursed by his Department under the nursery milk scheme in each month of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21271","21271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442966","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the responses received to his Department's pre-consultation on reducing legal costs in clinical negligence claims.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21272","21272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442967","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many senior civil servants in his Department left to take up jobs in the (a) for-profit and (b) not-for-profit healthcare sector in the last six months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21270","21270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442968","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been claimed in reimbursement expenses by press officers in (a) his Department and (b) his Department's executive agencies and public bodies in each fiscal year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21269","21269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442969","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has assessed or commissioned on potential links between prostate cancer treatment and Alzheimer's disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21305","21305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442971","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which groups were consulted in preparation of the equality impact assessment for the introduction of fixed recoverable costs in medical negligence cases.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21378","21378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442972","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health visitors there were in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21379","21379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442973","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has assessed or commissioned on potential links between prevention of Alzheimer's disease and maintaining positive thinking into later life.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21303","21303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442974","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has assessed or commissioned on potential links between male infertility and diabetes or heart disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21304","21304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442975","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children in England were diagnosed as anaemic or iron deficient in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21373","21373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442978","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to renew the national stoke strategy when it expires; and how he plans to build on the work done under that strategy.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21288","21288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442979","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents of A&E departments diverting admissions to other hospitals there were in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21374","21374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442980","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the take-up of the School Fruit and Vegetable Scheme by children from low-income families.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21372","21372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442981","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding was allocated to raising awareness of diabetes by Public Health England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21296","21296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442982","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to support the NHS recruit, retain and help the professional development of consultants specialising in (a) rare and (b) ultra-rare diseases.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21310","21310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442983","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support cooperation between rare diseases organisations through the EU Policy Action and Information for Rare Diseases in Europe.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21311","21311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442984","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 20082, what the (a) dates, (b) locations and (c) organisations of the 19 visits and meetings referred to in that Answer were.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21403","21403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442985","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 10 of NHS England's board paper, Allocation of resources to NHS England and the commissioning sector for 2016/17 to 2020/21, reference PB.17.12.15/04, if he will quantify the legally binding funding pressures regarding the introduction of treatments for (a) hepatitis C and (b) cystic fibrosis in 2016-17; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21387","21387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442986","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of (a) GPs and (b) clinical commissioning groups have plans in place to identify avoidable deaths.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21404","21404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442987","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2015 to Question 19338, how the effect of the Equality Act 2010 on service provision in the NHS is monitored.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21405","21405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442988","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 14919, what decisions have been made on how to spend the remaining funds that was allocated for perinatal mental health for 2015-16; and whether NHS England plans to spend the full £15 million allocation by the end of 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21406","21406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442989","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Band 7 NHS psychologists were employed in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21407","21407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442990","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much is available to each NHS trust to fund new drugs and treatments assessed and recommended by NICE.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21204","21204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442991","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on the implementation of the Rare Disease Strategy.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21208","21208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442992","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure greater levels of genetic testing for cancer and ultra rare diseases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21209","21209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442993","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the National Council for Care Excellence on the development of a clinical guideline for pancreatic cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21210","21210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442994","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether full funding for the implementation of the new access target for early intervention in psychosis is included in the Government's commitment to an additional £600 million of funding for mental health in 2016-17.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21223","21223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442995","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve post-acute stroke rehabilitation.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21226","21226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442996","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many days of (a) acute and (b) non-acute delayed transfers of care there were in each health trust in London in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21227","21227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442997","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21255","21255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442998","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on treating health problems associated with tuberculosis sclerosis in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21205","21205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/442999","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase research into the causes and types of rare diseases in England.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21206","21206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443000","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the processes undertaken by the NICE for approving and commissioning new medicines for cancers and ultra rare diseases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21207","21207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443001","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the longest a patient waited for discharge from hospital after being declared fit to leave was in (a) England and Wales, (b) London and (c) each health trust in London in (i) the last month for which figures are available and (ii) that month in each year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21166","21166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443002","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the national stroke strategy in improving stroke outcomes.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21167","21167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443003","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contribution the national stroke strategy has made to developing new technologies for use in treating stroke; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21168","21168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443004","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria are used by his Department to determine which health priorities require a national strategy.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21169","21169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443005","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average hospital waiting time was for NHS patients in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21417","21417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443006","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS doctors were employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21419","21419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443007","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS nurses were employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21418","21418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443008","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency plans his Department has for the event of a major care home provider ceasing operations.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21346","21346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443009","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there was in the number of NHS beds in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21421","21421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443010","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS dentists were employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21422","21422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443011","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his contribution of 9 September 2015, Official Report, column 88WH, when he expects the National Archives to publish those documents on contaminated blood from 1986 to 1995.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21424","21424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443012","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage the take up of organ donor cards among South Asian and other minority ethnic communities.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21358","21358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443013","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nursing training places were provided in each region in the last 12 months for which figures are available; and how many such places he expects to be provided in the current year.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21359","21359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443014","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS beds there were in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21420","21420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443015","2016-01-11","Department of Health","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS GPs were working in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21423","21423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443016","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refused asylum seekers with dependants have been supported in Scotland under section 95 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 for (a) up to two years, (b) more than two years and (c) more than four years.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21170","21170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443017","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refused asylum seekers with dependants have been supported under section 95 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 for (a) up to two years, (b) more than two years and (c) more than four years.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21171","21171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443018","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refused asylum seekers have been supported in Scotland under section 4 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 for (a) up to two years, (b) more than two years and (c) more than four years.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21172","21172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443019","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refused asylum seekers were granted, continued on, or reinstated back onto, support under section 4 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 after lodging an appeal with the First-tier Tribunal (Asylum Support) in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21173","21173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443020","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to continue with the visa scheme which allows Filipino nurses to come to the UK to work on its current basis; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21218","21218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443021","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees who have been admitted to the UK since 2010 (a) have since returned to their country of origin and (b) her Department is in regular contact with.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21188","21188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443022","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what documents set out current arrangements with the government of Cyprus regarding responsibility for refugees and asylum seekers arriving at the UK Sovereign Base Areas in Cyprus; and how much has been paid as a result of such arrangements.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21202","21202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443023","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refused asylum seekers have been supported under section 4 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 for (a) up to two years, (b) more than two years and (c) more than four years.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21181","21181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443024","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2015 to Question 15757, what proportion of clandestine illegal entry attempts in 2014-15 were intercepted by the (a) French authorities and (b) UK authorities.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21184","21184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443025","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21256","21256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443026","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20252, if she will collect information centrally on convictions for domestic violence.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21262","21262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443027","2016-01-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent developments there have been in the detention and potential deportation of Paramjeet Singh to India; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21332","21332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443028","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects the new secure zone for British-bound lorries at Calais to be operational; and what steps are being taken to protect UK-bound lorries from attack before that time.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21402","21402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443029","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she had made of the implications for her policies of the findings on domestic violence in the report of the chief inspector of Borders and Immigration entitled, An Inspection of Settlement Casework, published in November 2015.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21411","21411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443030","2016-01-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the Government has to attempt to remove or deport refugees and asylum seekers at the the UK Sovereign Base Areas in Cyprus to third countries.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21365","21365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443031","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the recorded level of gun crime was in (a) England and (b) the West Midlands between (i) January 2010 to December 2012 and (ii) January 2013 to December 2015.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21235","21235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443032","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are held in each immigration holding or removal centre in the UK.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21316","21316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443033","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average duration of stay in an immigration holding or removal centre was in the last year.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21317","21317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443034","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the longest length of time is that a person has spent in an immigration holding or detention centre in the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21318","21318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443035","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been re-admitted to an immigration holding or removal centre having been previously removed from the UK in the last three years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21319","21319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443036","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's Counter-Extremism Strategy, published in October 2015, what constitutes non-violent extremism.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21384","21384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443037","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's Counter-Extremism Strategy, published in October 2015, what her definition is of non-violent expressions of religious belief which are (a) extreme and (b) not extreme.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21385","21385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443038","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it the policy of the Government to refer to the European Court of Justice the failure of the French government to register non-EU citizens in France who are in need of international protection.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21399","21399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443039","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 113 of the Government's Counter-Extremism Strategy, published in October 2015, what definition her Department uses of extremism; and what steps she is taking to ensure that that definition does not close down debate or limit free speech.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21386","21386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443040","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has made to her French counterparts on the proposed construction of a new camp for migrants close to Dieppe.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21400","21400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443041","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's Counter-Extremism Strategy, published in October 2015, whether a religious group or individual which claims that their religion is the only one true faith is included in its definition of extremism.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21382","21382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443042","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's Counter-Extremism Strategy, published in October 2015, what plans the Government has to consult with faith groups on its definition of extremism.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21383","21383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443043","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in which (a) towns, (b) cities and (c) regions were the recorded locations of exploitation of potential victims of human trafficking referred to the UK National Referral Mechanism in 2014.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21370","21370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443044","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) arrests and (b) convictions have been made in connection with gun-related crime in the West Midlands metropolitan area in each quarter of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21371","21371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443045","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funds the Government has provided for (a) humanitarian efforts and (b) security at the refugee camp in Calais in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21376","21376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443046","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for how long people under the age of 18 who were transferred to a place of safety under section 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983 were detained on average in (a) a police cell and (b) a police vehicle in England and Wales in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21299","21299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443047","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the greatest number of times is that a person has been admitted to an immigration holding or removal centre having been previously removed from the UK.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21298","21298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443048","2016-01-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many sexual assaults and rapes have taken place at UK universities in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21306","21306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443049","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to improve police responses to sexual assaults and rapes at universities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21307","21307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443050","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was spent on tackling gun crime in (a) England and (b) the West Midlands between (i) January 2010 to December 2012 and (ii) January 2013 to December 2015.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21233","21233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443051","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was spent on policing in (a) England and (b) the West Midlands between (i) January 2013 and December 2015 and (ii) January 2010 and December 2012.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21363","21363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443052","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to prevent the supply of guns and ammunition at a neighbourhood level.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21234","21234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443053","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what legal grounds her Department has sought to pass responsibility for assessing the claims of refugees arriving at the UK Sovereign Base Areas in Cyprus to the government of the Republic of Cyprus.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21364","21364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443054","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies  of the proposal in December 2015 from Save the Children to relocate 3,000 unaccompanied refugee children in Europe.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21268","21268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443055","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20252, how her Department assesses the effect of Government policy on domestic violence.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21261","21261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443056","2016-01-11","Home Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people of each gender work in her Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21285","21285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443057","2016-01-11","Department for International Development","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20540, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the distribution of Syria crisis response funds in (a) Lebanon and (b) Jordan; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21331","21331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443058","2016-01-11","Department for International Development","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21257","21257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443059","2016-01-11","Department for International Development","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the contribution of wider access to efficient refrigerated transport to reducing (a) food waste in developing countries and (b) carbon dioxide emissions.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21349","21349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443060","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2015 to Question 20011, on animal welfare: sentencing, what steps his Department has taken in response to the concerns expressed by Ministers of the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21216","21216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443061","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of enforcement powers for court orders relating to child custody.","Biography information for Seema Kennedy","Seema Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21165","21165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443062","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department last discussed votes for prisoners with the Council of Europe.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21343","21343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443063","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to announce changes to procedures to deal with motor accident claims for whiplash.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21344","21344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443064","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many press and public relations staff are employed by (a) his Department, (b) HM Courts and Tribunal Service, (c) HM Prison Service, (d) the Legal Aid Agency and (e) the National Offender Management Service; how many of those employees are paid more than (i) £50,000 and (ii) £100,000; and what the total expenditure was on press and public relations by each of those organisations in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21339","21339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443065","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time spent on paperwork by prison officers.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21313","21313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443066","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much illicitly-brewed alcohol was seized in prisons in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21315","21315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443067","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of levels of computer literacy among prison staff.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21314","21314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443068","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people of each gender work in his Department.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21286","21286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443069","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many settlements his Department estimates have been affected by errors on his Department's Form E divorce form.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21273","21273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443070","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals were returned to their home country up to (a) six and (b) 12 months before their prison release dates under the early removal scheme in the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21264","21264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443071","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been charged with trying to escape from a prison van in each of the last five years; and how many such people have avoided recapture.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21265","21265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443072","2016-01-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the Government has paid in compensation claims for injuries while in custody in the last two years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21377","21377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443073","2016-01-11","Prime Minister","2016-01-06","To ask the Prime Minister, when he last met or spoke to the head of government in each British Overseas Territory.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21230","21230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443074","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what alternative arrangements have been made for residents of Flintshire to take driving tests during the temporary closure of the Chester driving test centre.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21294","21294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443075","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average journey time northbound between junction 3 and junction 30 on the M25, between the hours of (a) 6am to 9am, (b) 11am to 2pm and (c) 4pm to 7pm in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21231","21231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443076","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of what the average journey time southbound between junction 30 and junction 2 on the M25, between the hours of (a) 6am to 9am, (b) 11am to 2pm and (c) 4pm to 7pm in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21232","21232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443077","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which departments have members on the cross-departmental Maritime Business Services working group; and how often he expects that group to meet.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21242","21242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443078","2016-01-12","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what mechanisms are in place to ensure that the public are made fully aware beforehand of planned road works to be carried out by contractors on trunk roads and motorways which involve either lane or whole carriageway closures.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21409","21409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443079","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passengers have used Stratford International station in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21338","21338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443080","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with (a) HM Treasury and (b) other government departments on the extension of renewable transport fuels obligation beyond road transport.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21321","21321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443081","2016-01-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to the private parking industry on the appropriate levels of penalties for motorists.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21345","21345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443082","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will request that Southeastern Trains and Network Rail explain the reasons for disruption to services at London Bridge on 4, 5 and 6 January 2016; and if he will publish the responses of those organisations to that request.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21328","21328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443083","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations the Government has received from the aviation and aerospace industries on supporting investment in development of cleaner jet fuels.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21334","21334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443084","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the cycle to work scheme on the number of non-cyclists taking up cycling.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21193","21193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443085","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of the cycle to work scheme to meeting the Government's objective to double the number of journeys made by bicycle by 2020.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21194","21194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443086","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the costs and benefits of ending the paper vehicle tax disc.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21347","21347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443087","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many requests have been made to the DVLA for vehicle owner addresses in the last 12 months by private parking companies.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21351","21351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443088","2016-01-11","Department for Transport","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of new HGV drivers who will be required in each of the next five years.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21357","21357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443089","2016-01-11","Cabinet Office","2016-01-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been unemployed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside and (c) the North East in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21412","21412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443090","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women in Preston constituency who were born in November 1954 have been notified of changes in the age at which they will receive the state pension; and when his Department notified each such person.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21183","21183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443091","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) men and (b) women will not qualify for a pension under the new state pension rules.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21180","21180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443092","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will make it its policy to collect data on the cause of death of individuals who have flowed off incapacity benefit or severe disablement allowance and employment and support allowance whose date of death was at the same time; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21224","21224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443093","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to prepare for the outcome of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21259","21259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/443094","2016-01-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-01-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 19711, if he will provide equivalent data for the financial years 2010-11, 2011-12 and 2012-13.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 21215","21215"
