"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42484","2014-03-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy that planning permission is only granted on condition that shale gas pads pipe water and gas on and off sites.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191481","191481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42485","2014-03-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to develop a UK standard in mitigation measures, operating conditions and planning requirements for shale gas pads.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191483","191483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42486","2014-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what grants his Department has made to UK conservation charities in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191653","191653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42487","2014-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2014, Official Report, column 287W on unmanned air vehicles, if he will publish a full list of all unmanned air vehicles systems used by those agencies; how many such systems have been acquired for use by those agencies; and what his Department's policy is on the storage and use of data obtained by such systems. [R]","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191663","191663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42488","2014-03-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish the Independent Expert Report on the badger cull in Somerset and Gloucester before the debate on the badger cull takes place in the House on 13 March 2014.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191688","191688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42489","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take in response to the recommendations of the UN Special Rapporteur on human rights and counter-terrorism in his report dated 28 February 2014 on the use of armed drones in extraterritorial lethal counter-terrorism operations.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191665","191665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42490","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, where annual reports of the Inter-departmental Conflict Pool for (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13 or equivalent information are published.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191669","191669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42491","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce Iranian military and financial support for the Assad regime.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191616","191616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42492","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much financial support the UK provides to the Commonwealth Secretariat each year.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191595","191595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42493","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss the current situation on torture in Bahrain with the UN Special Rapporteur; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191572","191572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42494","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received about the shooting of Fadel Abbas by security forces in Bahrain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191574","191574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42495","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Israeli authorities about their handling of visa requests from Palestinian medical students for travel to the UK in connection with the work of the International Federation of Medical Students' Association; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191541","191541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42496","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of progress in implementing the Framework for Fiscal Responsibility in the Cayman Islands.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191569","191569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42497","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of human rights violations in Bahrain; if he will designate Bahrain as a country of concern; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191570","191570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42498","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of progress in implementing the recommendations of the Bahrain Independent Commission of Inquiry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191571","191571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42499","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what effect the reported interception of Iranian arms shipments to Gaza has had on his assessment of the role of President Rouhani in promoting stability in the Middle East.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191537","191537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42500","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on levels of settlement construction.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191562","191562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42501","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to prevent drug smuggling into Gibraltar.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191469","191469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42502","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to strengthen ties with the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191470","191470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42503","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking in order to prevent further Russian aggression towards Ukraine; and what steps he plans to take following any further such aggression.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191457","191457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42504","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to demonstrate to the Spanish government that the UK does not intend to negotiate on the matter of Gibraltar.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191472","191472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42505","2014-03-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2014, Official Report, column 46W, on Falkland Islands, and with reference to the Answer from the Minister for Universities and Science of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 447W, on overseas students, British Overseas Territories, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on the correct use of the name of the Falkland Islands by Government departments; and what cross-governmental guidance his Department has issued on this matter.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191513","191513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42506","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what correspondence his Department has received from the group For a Humanitarian Frontier.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191506","191506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42507","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which technology appraisals conducted by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and completed in each year since 2005 (a) did and (b) did not have a Patient Access Scheme attached to them for consideration; to what technology each such Patient Access Scheme related; what the outcome of the appraisal in each case was; and in each such case whether the technology was (i) fully recommended, (ii) partly recommended and (iii) not recommended.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191488","191488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42508","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many former staff of the NHS Information Centre were employed in the Health and Social Care Information Centre.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191490","191490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42509","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many senior staff at what level in the Health and Social Care Information Centre previously worked at the NHS Information Centre.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191491","191491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42510","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ground E abortions for chromosomal abnormalities other than trisomies 21, 18 and 13 were diagnosed by (a) amniocentesis, (b) ultrasound, (c) chronic villus sampling and (d) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what other methods of diagnosis were listed under heading (d), other; and how many such diagnoses which did not result in abortion were recorded in the same period.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191458","191458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42511","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of physical activity programmes to address the needs of people with painful conditions such as arthritis.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191426","191426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42512","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many lower limb amputations procedures took place through the NHS in each NHS trust in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191446","191446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42513","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ground E abortions for trisomy 13 (Patau syndrome) were diagnosed by (a) amniocentesis, (b) ultrasound, (c) chronic villus sampling and (d) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what other methods of diagnosis were listed under heading (d); and how many such diagnoses which did not result in abortion were recorded in the same period.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191459","191459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42514","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the reasons for the differences in the statistics gathered by his Department and the Wolfson Institute on the number of abortions carried out in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012 for (i) Down's syndrome, (ii) Edwards' syndrome and (iii) Patau syndrome; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191460","191460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42515","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with medical authorities on the use of electrical current to treat brain injuries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191461","191461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42516","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many stenting procedures in the (a) iliac, (b) femoral and (c) anterior arteries below the knee have taken place in each NHS trust in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191447","191447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42517","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on the use of electrical current as a medical treatment in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191462","191462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42518","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people suffering with mental health problems were treated using cognitive behavioural therapy in the UK in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191448","191448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42519","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Avastin form of the drug bevacizumab will be made available through the NHS for the treatment of cervical cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191463","191463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42520","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the inclusion of indicators in the Public Health Outcomes Framework on physical activity levels among people with (a) back pain, (b) osteoarthritis and (c) other painful musculoskeletal conditions.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191423","191423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42521","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding has been allocated by each local authority to (a) prevent the onset of musculoskeletal conditions and (b) mitigate the effects of such conditions.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191424","191424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42522","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce salt consumption by children.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191563","191563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42523","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) outside earnings from use of data, (b) third party payment of staffing costs and (c) other funding sources of the operations and staffing of the Health and Social Care Information Centre are.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191540","191540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42524","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has issued any guidance to hospital trusts on the management of car parks and the issuing of parking charge notices.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191556","191556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42525","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many diagnoses of trisomy 18 leading to a ground E abortion were diagnosed by (a) amniocentesis, (b) ultrasound, (c) chorionic villus sampling and (d) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what those other methods of diagnosis were; and how many diagnoses of that condition, which did not result in abortion, were recorded in that period.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191547","191547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42526","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints have been received about the Health and Care Professions Council or its predecessor in the last five years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191561","191561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42527","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many diagnoses of trisomy 21 leading to a ground E abortion were diagnosed by (a) amniocentesis, (b) ultrasound, (c) chorionic villus sampling and (d) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what those other methods of diagnosis were; and how many diagnoses of that condition, which did not result in abortion, were recorded in that period.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191546","191546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42528","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what standards of data collection are required of Clinical Commissioning Groups in respect of abortion services delivered in the independent sector.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191548","191548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42529","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many serious data breaches the NHS has registered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191560","191560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42530","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) change and (b) percentage change there was in the estimated number of delayed discharges in each London hospital trust in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191534","191534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42531","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) change and (b) percentage change there was in Accident and Emergency (i) admissions and (ii) attendance in each NHS trust in each of the last 4 years.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191535","191535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42532","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the name, job title and salary level is of each director who has worked in NHS England since its formation.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191533","191533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42533","2014-03-18","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many elderly people have received help with (a) low, (b) moderate, (c) substantial and (d) critical needs in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191567","191567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42534","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many accident and emergency attendances there were by children in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191579","191579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42535","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will consider introducing a national lung allocation system based on need and not location.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191577","191577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42536","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who currently manages the GP dataset; what commercial companies are involved in its management; and where each server on which data are stored is located.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191576","191576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42537","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ground E abortions for cleft palate were diagnosed by (a) ultrasound and (b) other diagnostic tests in each of the last 10 years; what other methods of diagnosis were listed under other; and how many such diagnoses which did not result in abortion were recorded in the same period.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191643","191643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42538","2014-03-17","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS providers deliver care that meets the quality statements contained within QS33, the quality standard for rheumatoid arthritis development by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191640","191640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42539","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Salisbury of 4 March 2014, Official Report, column 766W, on abortion, how many abortion notification forms which initially offered no information on the method of diagnosis for a ground E termination were returned to practitioners for completion following the decision to return incomplete forms in 2010; how many of those notification forms were subsequently returned completed; and how many such completed forms identified the method of diagnosis as (a) amniocentesis, (b) ultrasound, (c) chorionic villus sampling and (d) other.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191670","191670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42540","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2014, Official Report, column 292W, on unmanned air vehicles, whether any policies of her Department are developed or monitored through use of data collected by remotely-piloted aircraft systems not directly employed by her Department.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191664","191664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42541","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what controls are in place to ensure that wild animals imported into the UK under scientific licences are only used for scientific purposes and not sold as pets or used for other purposes.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191654","191654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42542","2014-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which CITES Annex A and B listed species have been (a) imported into and (b) exported from the UK in each of the last five years; and what the reasons for each such import and export were.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191655","191655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42543","2014-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the number of CITES-listed animals imported into the UK in each month of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191656","191656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42544","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish her Department's briefing for the then Minister of State, Giles Shaw, for the adjournment debate on 19 December 1984.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191573","191573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42545","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) Cabinet papers and (b) papers of her Department relating to the Hilda Murrell case will be released under the Freedom of Information Act 2000 on the 30th anniversary of Hilda Murrell's abduction and murder.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191568","191568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42546","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will extend the review into the Special Demonstration Squad to include also the National Public Order Intelligence Unit.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191566","191566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42547","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to answer Named Day written question 185520 tabled on 28 January 2014 for answer on 3 February 2014; and what the reasons are for the delay in answering this question.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191536","191536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42548","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she or Ministers in her Department have had with (a) Association of Chief Police Officers and (b) Her Majesty's Inspectorate of Constabulary (HMIC) about HMIC conducting a review of police forces' performance in issuing and monitoring firearms certificates; and if she will make it her policy to request HMIC undertake such a review.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191516","191516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42549","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will open an inquiry into the death of Hilda Murrell in 1984.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191558","191558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42550","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to conduct a full child rights impact assessment of the Immigration Bill covering (a) its effect on both migrant and British children, (b) the implications of Article 8 of the European Convention in Human Rights for Clause 14, (c) healthcare charges and (d) immigration checks by landlords in the private rental sector; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191550","191550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42551","2014-03-17","Home Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with chief constables on the proportion of reported rape cases being referred to the Crown Prosecution Service for a decision on prosecution; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191428","191428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42552","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much and what proportion of the victim surcharge imposed by adult courts since 1 October 2012 has been collected where the main sentence in the case was (a) a conditional discharge, (b) a fine, (c) a community order, (d) a suspended prison sentence of up to six months, (e) a suspended prison sentence of more than six months, (f) a prison sentence of up to six months, (g) a prison sentence of between six months and two years, (h) a prison sentence of between two and four years, (i) a prison sentence of between four and 14 years and (j) life imprisonment.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191440","191440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42553","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of (a) men and (b) women convicted of benefit fraud in each of the last five years received a prison sentence; and what the average prison sentence was for those of each gender so convicted.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191465","191465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42554","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women convicted of benefit fraud in each of the last five years received (i) a conditional discharge, (ii) a fine, (iii) a community order and (iv) a suspended prison sentence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191466","191466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42555","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) charged with and (b) convicted of any offences relating to scrap metal theft in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191467","191467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42556","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the action by barristers on (a) 6 January 2014 and (b) 7 March 2014; and what his policy is on imposing a costs sanction on the barristers involved.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191468","191468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42557","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department collects on the number of men in prison who have been victims of domestic violence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191431","191431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42558","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department collects on the number of women in prison who have been perpetrators of domestic violence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191432","191432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42559","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department collects on the number of men in prison who have been victims of sexual abuse.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191433","191433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42560","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department collects on the number of (a) men and (b) women in prison who had alcohol-related issues prior to conviction.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191434","191434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42561","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department collects on the number of men and women in prison who have previously been in local authority care.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191435","191435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42562","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders received a driving ban alongside a prison sentence of a longer length in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191436","191436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42563","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders received a driving ban before the age of 17 in each of the last three years; and in what proportion of such cases the ban expired before the offenders' 17th birthday.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191437","191437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42564","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many private family law cases there were in (a) Gwent and (b) Wales civil and family tribunals cluster between April 2012 and April 2013; and in how many such cases both parties had legal representation.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191564","191564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42565","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2014, Official Report, column 866W, on prisoners: females, in how many of those cases were the women victims of (a) partner domestic violence where the perpetrator was (i) male and (ii) female and (b) family domestic violence where the perpetrator was (i) male and (ii) female.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191528","191528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42566","2014-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2013, Official Report, column 127W, on squatting, what the cost to the public purse has been of hearings in relation to the case of a constituent of the hon. Member for Workington, Gary Tomlinson, Claim Number OWH00080, Cert Number JBIRQK61BB77/A/E/1; for what reasons legal aid funding in relation to this case was withdrawn; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the report in relation to that withdrawal decision.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191542","191542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42567","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young offenders have breached referral orders in each year since they were introduced.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191652","191652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42568","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have been electronically monitored under Part 3 of the Criminal Justice and Court Services Act 2000 since its introduction.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191651","191651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42569","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many deaths in custody there were in the secure estate between 2 and 9 March 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191679","191679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42570","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) acts of active concerted indiscipline, (b) acts of passive concerted indiscipline, (c) hostage situations and (d) incidents at height occurred in the prison system between 2 and 9 March 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191678","191678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42571","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department maintains a public register of restorative justice and similar schemes operating in England and Wales.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191650","191650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42572","2014-03-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish a detailed breakdown of his Department's £85 million budget for a Secure College.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191649","191649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42573","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he was informed of the problem with the reactor cooling system at the Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment on taking office.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191635","191635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42574","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when his Department was first informed of the problem with the reactor cooling system at the Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191633","191633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42575","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his predecessor was informed of the problem with the reactor cooling systems at the Dounreay Naval Reactor Test Establishment when he visited the facility on 2 April 2012.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191634","191634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42576","2014-03-17","Scotland Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with Scottish organisations and businesses on their preferred currency in an independent Scotland.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191554","191554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42577","2014-03-13","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Bolton North East constituency.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191551","191551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42578","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted by Sheffield City Council.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191538","191538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42579","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in the London Borough of Wandsworth.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191641","191641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42580","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many voters in (a) London, (b) each London borough and (c) each parliamentary constituency in London could not be matched as part of the recent confirmation dry run carried out by the Electoral Commission.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191642","191642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42581","2014-03-13","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Sheffield.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191658","191658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42582","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) each London borough and (b) each parliamentary constituency in London.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191681","191681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42583","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in Warrington North constituency in the recent confirmation dry run.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191487","191487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42584","2014-03-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Hull.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191489","191489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42585","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average change in rail fares was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191557","191557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42586","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people of pensionable age using rail services.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191515","191515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42587","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 22 November 2013, Official Report, column 1052W, on road traffic control, and of 11 December 2013, Official Report, column 221W, on roads: repair and maintenance, what the real terms funding for local road maintenance spent but not announced was in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191630","191630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42588","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to introduce car parking charges at rail stations in West Yorkshire as part of the Northern franchise.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191687","191687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42589","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the pension entitlement is of people of pensionable age who served long sentences in prison.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191684","191684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42590","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was paid in disability living allowance and personal independence payments to recipients in (a) Glasgow, (b) Edinburgh, (c) Dundee and (d) Aberdeen in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191621","191621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42591","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was paid in employment and support allowance payments to recipients in (a) Glasgow, (b) Edinburgh, (c) Dundee and (d) Aberdeen in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191623","191623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42592","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was paid in jobseeker's allowance payments to recipients in (a) Glasgow, (b) Edinburgh, (c) Dundee and (d) Aberdeen in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191624","191624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42593","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people and what proportion of the working population have been in receipt of incapacity benefit or employment and support allowance for over (a) two years, (b) five years and (c) 10 years in each region of England.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191625","191625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42594","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of the claimants who have returned to Jobcentre Plus after 104 weeks on the Work Programme are attached to each jobcentre in the UK; and what proportion of each jobcentre's caseload such people represent.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191627","191627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42595","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much in housing benefit payments was paid to recipients in (a) Glasgow, (b) Edinburgh, (c) Dundee and (d) Aberdeen in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191626","191626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42596","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Brigg and Goole constituency who have begun an apprenticeship through support provided on the work programme.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191638","191638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42597","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what effect on the budget of universal credit the decision to develop a second IT system will have; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191629","191629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42598","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people and what proportion of the working age population have been in receipt of jobseeker's allowance for over (a) two years, (b) five years and (c) 10 years in each region of England.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191628","191628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42599","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 15 January 2013, Official Report, column 715W, on child poverty, what estimate his Department has made of the effect of (a) the new timetable for the implementation of universal credit and (b) changes to work allowances on the level of relative income poverty among (i) children and (ii) adults.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191594","191594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42600","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take to monitor the effect of recent restrictions on Access to Work funding for communication support for deaf and deafblind people.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191583","191583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42601","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason his Department has changed the requirements for access to funding through Access to Work for communication support for deaf and deafblind people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191584","191584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42602","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on the housing benefit budget of limiting all rents to local authority rent levels.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191578","191578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42603","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the number of people who face reduced work incentives as a result of changes to council tax support.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191529","191529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42604","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect on the time taken to receive universal credit of a claimant (a) moving to live in an area where universal credit is not being piloted, (b) forming a new relationship and being re-classified as part of a couple and (c) having a child.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191524","191524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42605","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have been sanctioned for (a) four weeks, (b) three months and (c) three years in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191565","191565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42606","2014-03-13","Cabinet Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many graduates of British universities aged 21 to 25 are claiming unemployment-related benefits.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191449","191449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42607","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to penalise those who fail to attend scheduled meetings at jobcentres.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191450","191450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42608","2014-03-13","Cabinet Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people living in the London Borough of Havering have moved off unemployment benefit as a result of gaining employment in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191451","191451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42609","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many migrants from non-EU countries claim benefit payments.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191452","191452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42610","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many migrants from EU countries living in the UK receive child benefit.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191453","191453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42611","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help people with mental illnesses find appropriate work.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191454","191454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42612","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been signed off work in the UK as a result of having obsessive compulsive disorder.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191455","191455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42613","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to prevent married couples from fraudulently claiming council and housing tax-related benefit available only for single people.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191456","191456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42614","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) men and (b) women were (i) investigated, (ii) given an administrative penalty, (iii) given a caution and (iv) convicted in court for benefit fraud in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191464","191464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42615","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on the payment of pensions into post office card accounts.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191485","191485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42616","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions he has had with the Welsh Executive on the closure of the Independent Living Fund.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191486","191486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42617","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on the payment of benefits into post office card accounts.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191484","191484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42618","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Universal Credit system will accept new claims for employment and support allowance by the end of 2016.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191507","191507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42619","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether claimants who begin claiming employment and support allowance prior to new claims being accepted by the Universal Credit system will be transferred to the universal credit system by the start of 2017 or end of 2017.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191508","191508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42620","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the universal credit system will accept (a) any and (b) all new claims for employment and support allowance at the start of 2017 or end of 2017.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191509","191509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42621","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost of processing a change in a claimant's circumstances when he or she (a) moves to live in an area where universal credit is not being piloted, (b) forms a new relationship and are re-classified as part of a couple and (c) has a child.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191510","191510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42622","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the IT systems supporting universal credit are able to process a change in a claimant's circumstances when he or she (a) moves to live in an area where universal credit is not being piloted, (b) forms a new relationship and is re-classified as part of a couple and (c) has a child.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191511","191511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42623","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people of pensionable age providing unpaid childcare support.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191512","191512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42624","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the future use of the Post Office Card Account; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191493","191493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42625","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of (a) new joseeker's allowance claimants and (b) existing jobseeker's allowance claimants reporting a change in circumstances receive their benefit payments within (i) one week, (ii) two weeks, (iii) three weeks, (iv) four weeks, (v) eight weeks, (vi) 12 weeks and (vii) more than 12 weeks.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191498","191498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42626","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of (a) new employment and support allowance claimants and (b) existing employment and support allowance claimants reporting a change in circumstances receive their benefit payments within (i) one week, (ii) two weeks, (iii) three weeks, (iv) four weeks, (v) eight weeks, (vi) 12 weeks and (vii) more than 12 weeks.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191499","191499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42627","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to tackle delays faced by people waiting for a medical assessment following their application for personal independence payment.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191500","191500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42628","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the future use of the Post Office Card Account.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191494","191494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42629","2014-03-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) Post Office Limited and (b) the National Federation of Sub-Postmasters on the future use of the Post Office Card Account.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191495","191495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43024","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress his Department has made on its work at MoD St Athan.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903052","903052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43213","2014-03-19","Scotland Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the potential cost to cross-border companies if Scotland becomes independent.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903079","903079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43273","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on upgrading army helicopter capability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903061","903061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43274","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the British Army plans to begin flying Watchkeeper unmanned aerial vehicles.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903066","903066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43275","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve the Army's recruitment process.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903067","903067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43276","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take to ensure that human rights legislation does not apply to troops deployed in combat operations.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903060","903060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43277","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what arrangements have been made for the withdrawal of UK personnel and heavy equipment from Afghanistan through Russian territory; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903062","903062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43278","2014-03-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to increase opportunities for injured service personnel to participate in competitive sporting events.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903064","903064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43920","2014-03-19","Scotland Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many 18 to 24 year olds in Scotland have been unemployed for two years or more.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903091","903091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43921","2014-03-19","Scotland Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many 18 to 24 year olds in Scotland have been unemployed for two years or more.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903089","903089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/43922","2014-03-19","Scotland Office","2014-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps he is taking to encourage small and medium-sized businesses to participate in the debate on Scottish independence.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903092","903092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42098","2014-03-13","Attorney General","2014-03-10","To ask the Attorney General, how many Crown Prosecution lawyers have been trained to deal with offences of stalking under sections 2A and 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997, in each Crown Prosecution Service area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191332","191332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42099","2014-03-13","Attorney General","2014-03-10","To ask the Attorney General, in respect of how many alleged offences under section 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997 proceedings are currently active in magistrates' and Crown Courts in England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191333","191333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42100","2014-03-13","Attorney General","2014-03-10","To ask the Attorney General, in respect of how many alleged offences under section 2A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997 proceedings are currently active in magistrates' courts in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191334","191334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42101","2014-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support UK manufacturing in offshore projects based on the UK continental shelf.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191351","191351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42102","2014-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many undergraduate students are studying music in the UK in the current academic year.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191402","191402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42103","2014-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many undergraduate students are studying music at a conservatoire in the UK in the current academic year.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191403","191403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42104","2014-03-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the Competition Commission's decision not to consider issues specific to Northern Ireland within their inquiry into the car insurance industry.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191262","191262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42105","2014-03-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in (a) Coventry, (b) Coventry North East constituency, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England employed an apprentice in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191278","191278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42106","2014-03-12","Cabinet Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many consultants have been engaged in the Crown Oversight Function since its creation; what each of their job roles were; and how much has been paid in consultancy fees to date.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191301","191301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42107","2014-03-12","Cabinet Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants of what grades have been employed on the Crown Oversight Function since its creation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191302","191302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42108","2014-03-12","Cabinet Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Honours and Decorations Committee's report from its last meeting to consider the recommendations of Sir John Holmes will go forward for final approval.","Biography information for James Wharton","James Wharton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191246","191246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42109","2014-03-12","Cabinet Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Honours and Decorations Committee last met to consider the recommendations put forward by Sir John Holmes regarding the rules for the awarding of military medals.","Biography information for James Wharton","James Wharton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191245","191245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42110","2014-03-12","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-10","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether he plans to meet charities and other interested parties to discuss the issuing of guidance on the implementation of the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191232","191232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42111","2014-03-12","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-03-10","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether he plans to publish guidance to inform charities and other affected organisations about the implementation of the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191233","191233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42112","2014-03-13","Cabinet Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Government contracts have been awarded to companies based in Brigg and Goole constituency since May 2010; and what the value of such awards was.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191363","191363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42113","2014-03-13","Cabinet Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost of purchasing a home in (a) London and (b) the South East in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191336","191336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42114","2014-03-12","HM Treasury","2014-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits of a sector-specific cut in VAT for the tourism industry.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191207","191207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42115","2014-03-17","HM Treasury","2014-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on the introduction of a salary sacrifice scheme for bus commuters.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191295","191295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42116","2014-03-13","HM Treasury","2014-03-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will include measures in the 2014 Budget Statement to support small and medium-sized enterprises in the hospitality sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191273","191273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42117","2014-03-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals relating to the Transitional Protection Regulations for England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191220","191220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42118","2014-03-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when all publications and literature, including press releases and statements made by officials on behalf of his Department will be politically impartial in accordance with the principles and requirements of the Code of Recommended Practice on Local Authority Publicity.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191298","191298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42119","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department gives to local authorities on preventing the proliferation of betting shops and fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191345","191345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42120","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reducing the qualifying period of Right to Buy from five to three years on the feasibility of local authorities ensuring a replacement of homes sold.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191288","191288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42121","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Departments is taking to ensure that local authorities ensure a one-for-one replacement of homes sold under Right to Buy.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191289","191289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42122","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish data on the level of women's homelessness; and if he will ensure that such data includes (a) the number of women who become homeless in a reporting period and (b) the length of their homelessness.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191329","191329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42123","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to local authorities of administering housing benefit in each of the last four years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191378","191378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42124","2014-03-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on devolution of the Affordable Homes programme to (a) combined authorities and (b) local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191376","191376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42125","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits of local authorities charging businesses for enforcement of the Health and Safety at Work Act 1974 and the Food Safety Act 1990 as is currently allowed for the Health and Safety Executive.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191362","191362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42126","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what obligations public beach operators have to carry out risk assessments and provide a minimum level of life saving equipment on public beaches.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191361","191361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42127","2014-03-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people were living in local authority social rented housing in the London Borough of Havering in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191392","191392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42128","2014-03-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how long the average family will spend on the waiting list for social housing before being allocated a property in (a) the London Borough of Havering and (b) England.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191390","191390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42129","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the research on fixed odds betting terminals to be conducted by the Responsible Gambling Trust is due to be completed and published.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191342","191342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42130","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times her Department has met (a) the National Association of Bookmakers and (b) representatives from individual bookmakers since the appointment of the Minister for Sport, Tourism and Equalities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191343","191343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42131","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times her Department has met (a) local authorities and (b) local government representative bodies to discuss licensing of betting shops since the appointment of the Minister for Sport, Tourism and Equalities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191344","191344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42132","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities, which have issued Article 4 directions, have subsequently received planning applications for change of use to a betting shop in the last year.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191346","191346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42133","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what timetable her Department has adopted for reform of the Electronic Communications Code.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191277","191277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42134","2014-03-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to limit the level of gambling advertisements on television.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191318","191318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42135","2014-03-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the new licensing regime issued by the Gambling Commission on the international business operations of prospective licensees; and what representations she has received relating to this matter from prospective licensees. [R]","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191244","191244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42136","2014-03-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether companies already licensed by the Gambling Commission will be required to demonstrate the same business practices as those newly-applying under the forthcoming licensing regime. [R]","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191242","191242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42137","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Triennial Review of the Armed Forces Pay Review Body will be completed; and what estimate he has made of the cost of this review.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191251","191251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42138","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Royal Air Force bases and establishments in England are currently in use.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191167","191167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42139","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Typhoon, (b) Tornado GR4 and (c) Sentinel R1 aircraft are (i) fully serviceable, (ii) undergoing first line maintenance, (iii) undergoing second line maintenance and (iv) undergoing third and fourth line maintenance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191168","191168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42140","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which RAF bases and establishments (a) have been closed since 2010 and (b) are due to be closed.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191169","191169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42141","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library copies of the (a) operating cost statement, (b) balance sheet, (c) statement of recognised gains and losses, (d) cash flow statement and (e) fixed asset register for each of Air Command's basic level budget groups for financial years 2010-11 to 2012-13.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191170","191170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42142","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which RAF bases and establishments are held on a leasehold basis.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191171","191171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42143","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) C-17A Globemaster, (b) Hercules C1/C3 (K), (c) Hercules C4/C5 (J), (d) Tristar and (e) VC10 aircraft are (i) fully serviceable, (ii) undergoing first line maintenance, (iii) undergoing second line maintenance and (iv) undergoing third and fourth line maintenance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191172","191172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42144","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which military bases and establishments in the UK are occupied by US visiting forces; how many US personnel are stationed at each; and what the name and rank of the commander is at each.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191173","191173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42145","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) location and (b) value is of all land and buildings, dwellings - tangible fixed assets valued at £1 million or over held on Air Command's balance sheet.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191174","191174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42146","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Royal Air Force bases and establishments in Wales are currently in use.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191175","191175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42147","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Royal Air Force bases and establishments in Northern Ireland are currently in use.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191176","191176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42148","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which overseas Royal Air Force bases and establishments are currently in use.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191177","191177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42149","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) establishment and (b) number of established posts filled is for each RAF operational squadron.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191178","191178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42150","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's Single Integrated Capability Priority List.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191179","191179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42151","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) location and (b) value is of all land and buildings, non-dwellings tangible fixed assets valued at £1 million or over held on Air Command's balance sheet.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191180","191180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42152","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of Air Command's Command Plan for financial years 2012-13 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191181","191181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42153","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library copies of Air Command's (a) operating cost statement (b) balance sheet, (c) statement of recognised gains and losses, (d) cash flow statement and (e) fixed asset register for financial years 2010-11 to 2012-13.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191182","191182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42154","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Royal Air Force bases and establishments in Scotland are currently in use.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191183","191183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42155","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list each branch and trade in the Royal Air Force.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191184","191184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42156","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) quantity and (b) value is of all transport equipment tangible fixed asset items valued at £1 million or over held on Air Command's balance sheet.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191185","191185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42157","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) quantity and (b) value is of all plant and machinery tangible fixed asset items valued at £1 million or over held on Air Command's balance sheet.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191186","191186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42158","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the procurement process of the Type 26; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191187","191187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42159","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which types of unmanned aerial vehicles are (a) currently deployed by the Royal Navy and (b) being (i) procured and (ii) considered.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191188","191188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42160","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the key procurement decisions relating to the Type 26 frigate will be made; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191189","191189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42161","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what provision he has made to allocate UK troops to any UN deployment of troops to Ukraine.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191326","191326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42162","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Office for Nuclear Regulation (ONR) was informed of the leak of radiation which occurred at the Vulcan nuclear test reactor at Dounreay in January 2012; and for what reason there was a delay in informing ONR of that incident.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191350","191350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42163","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the statement of 6 March 2014, Official Report, columns 1077-9, on nuclear submarines, what consultations his Department undertook with the Scottish Environmental Protection Agency on measurable levels of increased radiation at the Vulcan test reactor between the leak at that reactor and the date of that statement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191371","191371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42164","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to station any of the new F35 Joint-Strike Fighters in the Falkland Islands following their commissioning into service.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191400","191400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42165","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the new planning regime for non-military development in the Cyprus Sovereign Base areas will be subject to public consultation before it its introduced.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191412","191412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42166","2014-03-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will investigate what happened to the citation written for Corporal Stewart McLaughlin who was killed in the Falkland Islands in 1982.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191388","191388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42167","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral Statement of 6 March 2014, Official Report, columns 1077-9, on nuclear submarines, what the evidential basis is for the statement that there has been no detectable radiation leak from the sealed circuit of the nuclear reactor in HMS Vanguard at Dounreay.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191389","191389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42168","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to conduct a strategic environmental assessment on the new planning regime to be developed in the Cyprus Sovereign Base areas.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191406","191406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42169","2014-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Sovereign Base Areas Administration or the government of the Republic of Cyprus will be responsible for formulating the new planning regime for the Cyprus Sovereign Base areas.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191398","191398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42170","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure free schools do not teach intolerance to their students.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191408","191408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42171","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the study of classical music in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191404","191404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42172","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students were permanently excluded from school for violence against a member of staff in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191405","191405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42173","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure school children are taught about the harmful effects of drugs.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191410","191410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42174","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department provides to teachers to be politically neutral when teaching on subjects pertaining to current affairs, politics and history.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191411","191411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42175","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department provides on the required level of experience a substitute teacher must have to provide leave cover.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191409","191409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42176","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure children are taught about the Commonwealth during their primary school years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191407","191407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42177","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance he has issued to schools on ensuring inclusive practice for children with autism spectrum disorders.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191372","191372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42178","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many places are occupied in each secure children's home; and what the total capacity is of each such institution.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191385","191385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42179","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on the provision of guaranteed reception class places for children aged five who were born between 1 August and 1 September.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191359","191359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42180","2014-03-13","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department last visited a Sure Start children's centre that was not in their constituency.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191374","191374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42181","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary school teachers who are science subject leaders have a science degree.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191323","191323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42182","2014-03-12","Department for Education","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary school chemistry teachers have a chemistry degree.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191324","191324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42183","2014-03-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2014, Official Report, column 990, on the wholesale energy market, whether his Department has undertaken an impact assessment of the effects of ring fencing between supply and generation businesses within vertically integrated companies.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191285","191285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42184","2014-03-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what funding his Department has allocated to the Coventry Switch and Save scheme through the Cheaper Energy Together fund.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191281","191281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42185","2014-03-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what reports he has received of safety breaches during the clearance of the Pile Fuel Storage Pond at Sellafield nuclear plant.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191265","191265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42186","2014-03-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the Coventry Switch and Save scheme supported by the Cheaper Energy Together fund.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191201","191201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42187","2014-03-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many incidents of safety breaches occurred during transport of nuclear material through the Irish Sea in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191264","191264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42188","2014-03-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with Ofgem on steps to take against energy companies that do not comply with the (a) carbon emissions reduction target and (b) community energy saving programme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191313","191313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42189","2014-03-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, columns 11-12W, on the Green Deal scheme, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) Green Deal assessments made, (b) Green Deal plans installed and billed and (c) energy company obligation measures installed in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland, (iii) England and (iv) Wales in each month since June 2013.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191284","191284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42190","2014-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to ensure that the upland entry level scheme is maintained; and what discussions he has had of other funding mechanisms to assist upland farmers.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191286","191286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42191","2014-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to tackle the illegal dumping of commercial waste.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191327","191327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42192","2014-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department plans to make available to farmers whose crops are late or reduced as a result of severe wet weather.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191383","191383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42193","2014-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations he has received from (a) the British Association for Shooting and Conservation and (b) the Countryside Alliance on micro-chipping ferrets to reduce thefts of those animals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191381","191381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42194","2014-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Russian Foreign Ministers on Russian troops leaving the Crimea region of Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191401","191401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42195","2014-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to improve relations between the governments of Russia and Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191399","191399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42196","2014-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent reports that Hezbollah is stockpiling missiles. [R]","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191240","191240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42197","2014-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent reports of rocket fire from southern Lebanon into Israel. [R]","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191241","191241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42198","2014-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to protect children in Syria from sexual abuse.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191322","191322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42199","2014-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the imposition of sanctions which directly affect President Putin.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191319","191319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42200","2014-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what more his Department can do to protect Christians in Syria from Al-Qaeda splinter groups who demand payments in gold and curb any displays of faith by threatening death by sword.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191320","191320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42201","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the NHS hospital episode dataset uploaded by PA Consulting is removed after the agreement end date.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191222","191222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42202","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has concluded a memorandum of understanding with US medical authorities over the future sharing of NHS patient data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191223","191223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42203","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any security audits have been conducted by his Department on PA Consulting following that company's cancellation of its contracts with the Home Office.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191224","191224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42204","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of accident and emergency doctors.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191317","191317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42205","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has received payment for allowing PA Consulting to use NHS data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191225","191225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42206","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the contract between the NHS and PA Consulting is due to end.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191221","191221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42207","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England plans to upload care.data to Google servers or use Google's Big Query service.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191218","191218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42208","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2014, Official Report, column 949W, on abortion, whether the general discussions with the British Pregnancy Advisory Service and Marie Stopes International involved sharing with those organisations any of the interpretations of the law which it is proposed should be included in the new guidelines; on what date each such discussion took place; what discussions his Department had over the same period with pregnancy and abortion counselling organisations which do not provide abortion services; what representations he has received from private sector abortion providers regarding the proposed new guidelines; what the name of each such organisation is; on what date each such representation was made; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191211","191211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42209","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 20 of NHS England Board Paper NHSE 180 716, what is meant by the exploitation of sequencing data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191212","191212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42210","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether informed consent must be obtained before genomic data is (a) taken from patients and (b) stored.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191248","191248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42211","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to ensure that psychological support is always provided alongside medical interventions for Tier 3 obesity treatment of children, adolescents and adults.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191200","191200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42212","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spends on reproductive health education and family planning; and what his policy is on such matters.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191192","191192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42213","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on improving accident and emergency facilities at Calderdale Royal Hospital in the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Linda Riordan","Mrs Linda Riordan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191193","191193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42214","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have accessed treatment at Calderdale Royal Hospital in (a) each of the last 12 months and (b) each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Linda Riordan","Mrs Linda Riordan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191194","191194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42215","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether PA Consulting or any other commercial company has or will have access to NHS genomic data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191231","191231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42216","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any directors of NHS England are on the board of (a) HSCIC, (b) Genomics England Limited and (c) PA Consulting.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191208","191208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42217","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether advice on the use of data without consent has been obtained from the Confidentiality Advisory Committee.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191209","191209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42218","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what work has been done by NHS England to consider how genomic sequencing data might be held, connected to patient records and used.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191226","191226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42219","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether genomic data will be extracted as part of care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191227","191227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42220","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether proposed links between care.data and genetic data will be reviewed by an independent ethics committee.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191228","191228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42221","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether representatives of commercial companies will be appointed to the board of Genomics England Limited.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191229","191229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42222","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contractual or similar relationship exists between NHS England, PA Consulting and Genomics England Limited.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191230","191230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42223","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with tuberculosis in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191417","191417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42224","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more older people to become kidney donors.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191416","191416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42225","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the lives of people experiencing mental health problems.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191394","191394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42226","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on mental health research in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191397","191397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42227","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support the carers of people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191395","191395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42228","2014-03-12","Cabinet Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been diagnosed with ovarian cancer in each of the last three years; and what the survival rate of women with ovarian cancer has been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191414","191414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42229","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the provision of care to people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191396","191396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42230","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the British Medical Association and the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence about approval of the Tecfidera form of dimethyl fumarate as a treatment for MS through the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191380","191380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42231","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2013, Official Report, columns 831-32W, on health services: hearing impairment, if he will place in the Library a copy of the initial survey on the implementation of AQP in audiology services.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191312","191312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42232","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the private availability of vaccines on different measures of health equality.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191375","191375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42233","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials at Public Health England are tasked specifically with tackling obesity.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191377","191377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42234","2014-03-13","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the NHS is taking to tackle obesity among members of its workforce.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191360","191360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42235","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether patients can opt out of their hospital data being shared or uploaded to anyone who does not directly provide them with care.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191349","191349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42236","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of passengers (a) leaving the UK and (b) entering the UK had their passport details checked against Interpol's SLTD database in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191337","191337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42237","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests for asylum in the UK cited female genital mutilation as a factor in the asylum application in each year for which figures are available; and how many such applications were (a) accepted and (b) refused.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191370","191370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42238","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will set out how the (a) existence and (b) risk of female genital mutilation to applicants for asylum in the UK is treated under the immigration rules.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191369","191369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42239","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions passengers or potential passengers have been arrested as a result of Interpol identifying stolen passports used or about to be used on (a) flights to and (b) transit flights through UK airports in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191347","191347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42240","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to open historic civil registers of births, marriages and deaths and transfer them from superintendent registrars' offices to county record offices.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191331","191331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42241","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have been trained to deal with offences of stalking under sections 2A and 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997 in each police force area; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191335","191335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42242","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people entered the UK on Tier 2 visas to study medicine in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191340","191340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42243","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passengers travelled to the UK on routes connected to the Semaphore system in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191338","191338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42244","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people working through an ICT visa in the UK have applied to move from a short-term to long-term visa in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191314","191314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42245","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people on Tier 2 visas studying medicine left the country in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191339","191339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42246","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from (a) the British Association for Shooting and Conservation and (b) the Countryside Alliance on the review of the EU Firearms Directive.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191382","191382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42247","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many government victim care contract specialist support providers work (a) full and (b) part-time.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191304","191304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42248","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) men and (b) women who are victims of human trafficking are nationals of non-EEA countries have received return and reintegration assistance through the Assisted Voluntary Returns for Irregular Migrants programme since April 2011; and how much was so made available to those trafficked from (i) inside and (ii) outside the EU.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191303","191303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42249","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of air passengers showing passports to UK Border agents are from Schengen area countries.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191203","191203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42250","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the security risk caused by the boarding pass exchange at Gatwick arrivals, where Irish and Channel Islands passengers mix with passengers needing passports to go through UK Border Control.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191204","191204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42251","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employees of the Child Exploitation and Online Protection Centre have arrest powers.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191205","191205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42252","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with how many victims of human trafficking the government victims care contract specialist support providers are now working; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191306","191306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42253","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many survivors of human trafficking who have been placed in shelters funded by the Government through the Salvation Army received support from the government victim care contract specialist support providers to develop a move-on strategy in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013; how many of these victims were (i) men and (ii) women; how many (A) men and (B) women are still receiving such support; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191305","191305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42254","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of shame/violence intervention for violent prisoners.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191210","191210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42255","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the number of births which took place where no medical attendant was present in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191263","191263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42256","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking via social media to help tackle misinformation from extremist and radicalisation groups.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191190","191190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42257","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter from the hon. Member for Walsall North of 11 February 2014 on behalf of a college in his constituency.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191274","191274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42258","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2014, Official Report, column 732W, of the 113 cases of births in the last five years not registered with the General Register Office, what assessment has been made of the whereabouts and wellbeing status of these cases.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191269","191269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42259","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2014, Official Report, column 732W, of the 113 cases of births in the last five years not registered with the General Register Office, what assessment has been made of those births not registered; and whether any of these cases have been the subject of police investigations, care orders or serious case reviews.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191267","191267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42260","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2014, Official Report, column 732W, of the 113 cases of births in the last five years not registered with the General Register Office, how many remain unregistered.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191268","191268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42261","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on returning to Somalia those without permission to remain in the UK.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191299","191299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42262","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who were previously classified as unaccompanied asylum seeking children have been forcibly returned to another country as adults in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191300","191300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42263","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to promote child protection through more stringent enforcement of the Birth and Death Registration Act 1953.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191266","191266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42264","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter to the Chief Executive of HM Passport Office of 3 February 2014 on behalf of a constituent.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191276","191276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42265","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter to the interim Director General of UK Visas and Immigration of 3 February 2014 on behalf of a constituent, reference M1583/14.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191275","191275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42266","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken in response to recommendations 5.1 and 5.66 in the Report on an unannounced inspection of Colnbrook Immigration Removal Centre, 28 January to 8 February 2013 published by HM Chief Inspector of Prisons.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191308","191308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42267","2014-03-13","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2014, Official Report, column 738W, on human trafficking: Victim Support Schemes, how many Government victim care contract specialist support providers are employed by (a) the Government, (b) local authorities, (c) quasi-automomous non-governmental organisations (NGOs), (e) shelter NGOs, (f) charities and (g) voluntary organisations.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191328","191328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42268","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to answer Questions tabled by the hon. Member for Birkenhead on 28 February 2014 for answer on 6 March 2014 on the Assisted Voluntary Return and Reintegration project.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191307","191307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42269","2014-03-12","Department for International Development","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much additional aid the Government plans to give to Ukraine.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191325","191325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42270","2014-03-12","Department for International Development","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the total budget for overseas development assistance is allocated for reproductive health education and family planning.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191191","191191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42271","2014-03-12","Department for International Development","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the safety of women's human rights defenders in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191413","191413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42272","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which secure children's homes Ministers of his Department have visited since May 2010; and what the date of each such visit was.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191387","191387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42273","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who (a) were given a non-custodial sentence and (b) were given their first custodial sentence in each year from 2004 had previously had (i) no criminal convictions, (ii) one criminal conviction, (iii) two criminal convictions, (iv) three criminal convictions, (v) four criminal convictions, (vi) five to 10 criminal convictions, (vii) 11 to 20 criminal convictions, (viii) 21 to 30 criminal convictions, (ix) 31 to 40 criminal convictions, (x) 41 to 50 criminal convictions, (xi) 51 to 75 criminal convictions, (xii) 76 to 100 criminal convictions and (xiii) more than 100 criminal convictions.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191341","191341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42274","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) self-inflicted, (b) non self-inflicted, (c) other non natural causes, (d) restraint, (e) homicide, (f) awaiting classification deaths there were in (i) adult male prisons, (ii) adult female prisons, (iii) youth male prisons and (iv) youth female prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191290","191290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42275","2014-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost is of preparing (a) halal and (b) non-halal food in the Prison Service.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191311","191311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42276","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many activity spaces per prisoner there were in (a) adult male prisons, (b) adult female prisons, (c) youth male prisons and (d) youth female prisons on 1 March (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013 in (A) the prison estate and (B) each prison.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191287","191287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42277","2014-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2014, Official Report, column 641W, on reoffenders, what (a) offence type and (b) sentence length each offender with more than one fixed term recall is serving.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191309","191309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42278","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many places are currently occupied in each (a) youth offenders' institution and (b) secure training centre; and what the total capacity is of each such institution.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191386","191386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42279","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to introduce GPS technology for the electronic monitoring of offenders.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191384","191384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42280","2014-03-17","Cabinet Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer to Lord Lexden of 18 July 2013, Official Report, House of Lords, column 872, on the Profumo Inquiry, how many of the people interviewed by Lord Denning in his inquiry into the circumstances surrounding the resignation of Mr Profumo are still alive.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191368","191368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42281","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons saw (a) a change and (b) more than one change of governor in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191291","191291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42282","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many deaths in custody in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013 were prisoners of black, Asian and minority ethnic origin.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191292","191292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42283","2014-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he Department will review the length of sentencing given to those who kill by dangerous driving and speeding.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191321","191321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42284","2014-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 24 February 2014, Official Report, column 262W, on sentencing, in how many of the cases listed in each year (a) there was a plea of (i) guilty or (ii) not guilty and (b) the case had been sent to the Crown Court (i) by magistrates for trial, (ii) by magistrates for sentence or (iii) as the result of the defendant electing a jury trial.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191283","191283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42285","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost was of a (a) jury trial at the Crown Court for (i) either way offences sent by magistrates where their sentencing powers were not deemed sufficient, (ii) either way offences where the defendant has chosen to elect jury trial and (iii) indictable only offences and (b) trial in a magistrates' court for (i) summary only offences and (ii) either way offences in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191282","191282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42286","2014-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have been recalled to prison and given a fixed term recall since 3 December 2012 whilst (a) on home detention curfew and (b) serving a sentence for a violent or sexual offence as listed in schedule 15 to the Criminal Justice Act 2003.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191216","191216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42287","2014-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many defendants elected jury trial in each of the last five years and (a) pleaded guilty and (b) were found guilty by each offence category; what proportion of defendants in each offence category received a prison sentence; and what average prison sentence per offence category was handed down.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191217","191217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42288","2014-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders who were recalled to prison from home detention curfew have been subsequently released back onto home detention curfew since 3 December 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191214","191214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42289","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many defendants charged with each offence type were sent to the Crown Court for sentence by magistrates in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191271","191271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42290","2014-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of eligible (a) male and (b) female offenders were recalled on a fixed term recall instead of a standard recall (i) in 2008, (ii) in 2009, (iii) in 2010, (iv) in 2011, (v) in 2012 and (vi) since 3 December 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191215","191215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42291","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost was of an either way office case dealt with at the Crown Court where (a) a guilty plea was entered at the magistrates' court and (b) a guilty plea was entered on the day of trial at the Crown Court in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191272","191272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42292","2014-03-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many defendants (a) elected jury trial at the Crown Court for either way offences where magistrates had accepted jurisdiction and deemed the case to be suitable for summary trial and (b) were sent to the Crown Court for trial by magistrates declining jurisdiction over the case in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191270","191270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42293","2014-03-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many letters of comfort have been sent since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191259","191259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42294","2014-03-13","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the investigation into the operation of the Military Reaction Force in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191261","191261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42295","2014-03-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many royal pardons have been granted to terrorists convicted of offences in connection with the Northern Ireland troubles.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191234","191234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42296","2014-03-13","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in the Newcastle City Council area.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191293","191293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42297","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Gateshead Council and (b) Blaydon constituency.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191206","191206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42298","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures in each ward were in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Oldham Metropolitan Borough and (b) Tameside Metropolitan Borough.","Biography information for David Heyes","David Heyes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191196","191196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42299","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Stockport Metropolitan Borough Council, (b) Tameside Metropolitan Council and (c) Denton and Reddish constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191197","191197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42300","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Nottingham City Council and (b) Nottingham North constituency.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191198","191198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42301","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Oxford East constituency.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191199","191199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42302","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Bridgend County Borough Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191195","191195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42303","2014-03-13","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Birmingham, Northfield constituency.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191202","191202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42304","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) St Helens Metropolitan Borough Council area and (b) St Helens North constituency.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191239","191239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42305","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the potential benefits of using (a) student unions and (b) other university and college venues as polling stations.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191354","191354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42306","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what percentage of those registered to vote by post did so in (a) police commissioner elections and (b) the local European elections in each electoral area; and what the percentage turnout was at polling stations in each election and in each area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191355","191355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42307","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which local authority (a) augmented and (b) did not augment Department for Work and Pensions data matching with the electoral register with local authority data matching.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191356","191356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42308","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which local authority databases may be consulted by local authority electoral registration officers for the purpose of data matching for the electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191357","191357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42309","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will place in the Library a copy of the newly-designed Household Registration Form and the Invitation to Register forms.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191358","191358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42310","2014-03-13","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Doncaster Metropolitan Borough Council and (b) Don Valley constituency.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191364","191364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42311","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Lancashire County Council and (b) Hyndburn constituency.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191315","191315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42312","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-10","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made on the viability of permitting people to vote in any polling station in their constituency or local authority area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191353","191353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42313","2014-03-12","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will raise the age of compulsory driving licence renewals to 80 years to reduce administration costs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191415","191415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42314","2014-03-12","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, columns 721-3W, on shipping: employment, whether he has initiated a review of the (a) collection and (b) use of data projecting future numbers of UK seafarers in the annual Seafarer Statistics publication.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191310","191310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42315","2014-03-13","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what total sum was spent on safety improvements on the A595 in each of the last four years; and what schemes have been completed using that funding.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191373","191373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42316","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many representations were received in response to the Environmental Statement on (a) the High Speed 2 project and (b) the High Speed 2/High Speed 1 link project in each week of the consultation.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191367","191367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42317","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many representations were received in response to the Environmental Statement on (a) the High Speed 2 project and (b) the High Speed 2/High Speed 1 link project.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191365","191365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42318","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many representations from Londoners were received in response to the Environmental Statement on (a) the High Speed 2 project and (b) the High Speed 2/High Speed 1 link project.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191366","191366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42319","2014-03-12","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the most recent (a) volume and (b) speed measurements were taken for vehicles on the A31 in or around Four Marks; and what assessment he has made of trends in such measurements in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191260","191260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42320","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the economic costs and potential benefits of a salary sacrifice scheme for bus commuters.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191297","191297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42321","2014-03-12","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he last estimated the existing stocks of low sulphur fuel available for use by commercial ships.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191249","191249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42322","2014-03-12","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to minimise the effect on seafarers' employment of the introduction of new sulphur dioxide emission limits for the shipping industry on 1 January 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191250","191250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42323","2014-03-12","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the level of access to low sulphur fuel products for vessels working from UK ports in the short seas shipping sector in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191252","191252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42324","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase rail competition for passengers on the West Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191294","191294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42325","2014-03-17","Department for Transport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to help young people in apprenticeship schemes with the cost of travel to work by bus.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191296","191296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42326","2014-03-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to tackle women's homelessness.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191330","191330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42327","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households which claim housing benefit do not have access to a kitchen.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191316","191316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42328","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the system for paying benefits into Post Office card accounts under the universal credit programme.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191348","191348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42329","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of his Department's databases of people (a) in receipt of and (b) not in receipt of benefits for the purposes of data matching with the electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191352","191352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42330","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to his Department was of administering job seeker's allowance in each of the last four years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191379","191379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42331","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many EU migrants living in the UK were in receipt of unemployment benefit in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191393","191393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42332","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have received sanctions in relation to their jobseeker's allowance for non-attendance in (a) the London Borough of Havering and (b) England to date.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191391","191391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42333","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department undertook (a) an impact assessment and (b) consultation with deaf and deafblind users of Access to Work, their representative organisations and with employers prior to the implementation of Access to Work funding limitations for the provision of communication support for deaf and deafblind people in the workplace.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191236","191236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42334","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what consultation his Department undertook with deaf users of the Access to Work scheme and their representative groups prior to introducing recent restrictions on the funding available for communication support through that scheme; and what alternative cost-reduction measures his Department considered.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191235","191235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42335","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the surplus or deficit of the Access to Work budget was in each financial year for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191257","191257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42336","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department applies quotas to different disability groups for funding available through Access to Work; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191237","191237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42337","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance is provided to deaf and deafblind users of the Access to Work scheme regarding that scheme's complaints procedure and the process for requesting a decision review.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191258","191258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42338","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many fraudulent claims were received by Access to Work for communication support for deaf and deafblind people in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191238","191238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42339","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the suitability of the work capability assessment to establish the fitness to work of those suffering from (a) mental, (b) progressive or (c) fluctuating illnesses.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191280","191280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42340","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department made of the potential effect on deaf and deafblind people of restrictions on access to work funding for the provision of communication support for such people prior to the introduction of those restrictions.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191255","191255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42341","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) deaf and (b) deafblind people have employed a full-time communication professional following recent changes in the implementation of access to work guidance.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191256","191256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42342","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the market value of a NRCPD-registered sign language interpreter; and how this estimate was used during the identification of an appropriate Access to Work funding cap for a full-time sign language interpreter.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191253","191253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42343","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what protections have been built into Universal Job Match to ensure the service cannot be infiltrated with non-existent jobs with the aim of accessing personal data; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191219","191219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42344","2014-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to improve the claimant experience of the work capability assessment.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191279","191279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42345","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of potential additional financial costs for employers resulting from newly implemented restrictions on Access to work funding for communications support for deaf and deafblind people; and what consultation he undertook with employers of deaf people on that matter.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191254","191254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42346","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2014, Official Report, column 564W, on personal independence payment, what monitoring of the proportion of new claims referrals that involve a consultation assessment his Department is undertaking.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191247","191247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42347","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what additional funding his Department allocated to the town of Rhyl for the purpose of piloting back-to-work projects in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191213","191213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42348","2014-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of his Department's Access to Work budget was spent on communication support for (a) deaf and (b) deafblind individuals in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191243","191243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42395","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information her Department holds on the number of local newspapers that have closed since May 2010; and what steps she plans to take to support such newspapers.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903018","903018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42396","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the resource needs of English Heritage over the next five years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903013","903013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42397","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will hold discussions with UK and international film production companies to promote Shropshire as a film location.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903026","903026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42718","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of whether £100 stakes in fixed-odds betting terminal machines in betting shops contribute to problem gambling.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903031","903031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42719","2014-03-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-03-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that superfast broadband reaches rural areas.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903029","903029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41979","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what contribution cyber-security exports made to the UK economy in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191109","191109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41980","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many jobs were created in the UK online and digital industries in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191110","191110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41981","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs which remain unfilled in the UK online and digital industries due to a lack of people with the prerequisite skills for those jobs.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191111","191111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41982","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what data the Land Registry holds on the number of leasehold domestic premises in (a) Worthing West constituency, (b) Worthing borough, (c) Arun district, (d) West Sussex county, (e) South East England region, (f) England and (g) England and Wales; what data collection the Land Registry makes on housing tenure types; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191127","191127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41983","2014-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and which post offices were subject to temporary closure in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and what the length of the temporary closure was in each such case.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191140","191140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41984","2014-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total value of Government business given to Post Office Ltd was in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191149","191149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41985","2014-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he last met the Chief Executive of (a) Post Office Ltd and (b) Royal Mail Group.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191152","191152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41986","2014-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions his Department has had with Post Office Ltd on the Post Office Card Account.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191154","191154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41987","2014-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was received from Royal Mail by Post Office Ltd are in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191155","191155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41988","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many post office accounts have been opened as part of the Post Office Ltd pilot in East Anglia and the East Midlands.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191148","191148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41989","2014-03-11","Cabinet Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate the net benefit to the UK economy of data.gov.uk since it publicly launched in January 2010.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191143","191143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41990","2014-03-11","Cabinet Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are employed in the (a) commerce and (b) manufacturing sectors in (i) Wrexham constituency, (ii) Wales and (iii) the UK.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191137","191137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41991","2014-03-11","Cabinet Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change there has been in median gross weekly earnings for (a) men and (b) women in Wrexham constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191138","191138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41992","2014-03-11","Cabinet Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how the Office of National Statistics (ONS) can best estimate the number and trends of the stock in the leasehold domestic premises in (a) Worthing West constituency, (b) Worthing borough, (c) Arun district, (d) West Sussex county, (e) South East England region, (f) England and (g) England and Wales; what data collection the ONS makes on housing tenure types; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191128","191128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41993","2014-03-11","Cabinet Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of jobseekers over the age of (a) 50 and (b) 60 in (i) Wrexham constituency, (ii) Wales and (iii) the UK in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191125","191125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41994","2014-03-11","Cabinet Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change there has been in median gross pay for women in Wrexham constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191115","191115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41995","2014-03-11","Cabinet Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children living in households in Wrexham constituency where one or both parents are (a) working-part-time because they are unable to find full-time work and (b) employed on a zero-hours contract.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191112","191112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41996","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid in corporation tax by businesses registered in Wrexham constituency in the last year for which figures are available; and what proportion of such taxation was paid by small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191108","191108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41997","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid in corporation tax by businesses registered in Wrexham constituency in the last year for which figures are available; and what proportion of such taxation was paid by small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191113","191113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41998","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) higher rate taxpayers and (b) people who earn over £1 million there were in Wrexham constituency in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191119","191119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41999","2014-03-12","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Autumn Statement of 5 December 2013, Official Report, column 1130, what his definition is of stable house prices; and what steps he is taking to achieve such stability.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191150","191150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42000","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs which would be created in 2014 if he removed the Alcohol Duty Escalator in that year rather than in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191158","191158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42001","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of removing the Alcohol Duty Escalator on levels of alcohol fraud in 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191159","191159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42002","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of Ernst & Young's report entitled Economic Impact Assessment into the Wine and Spirit industry in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191160","191160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42003","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the UK largest export industry by value is.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191161","191161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42004","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total annual economic contribution of the wine and spirit industries to the UK economy is.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191162","191162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42005","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the Wine and Spirit Trade Association's Budget 2014 submission; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191163","191163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42006","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what further fiscal steps he plans to take to support small and medium-sized enterprises in the hospitality sector.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191157","191157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42007","2014-03-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what data (a) his Department holds and (b) can be estimated from the Land Registry, the Census and the Office of National Statistics on the number of leasehold domestic premises in (i) Worthing West constituency, (ii) Worthing borough, (iii) Arun district, (iv) West Sussex county, (v) South East England region, (vi) England and (vii) England and Wales; what data collection his Department makes on housing tenure types; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191129","191129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42008","2014-03-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he last reveiwed the purposes of LEASE; and if he will ask LEASE to make a public report to him on the problems in the leasehold sector known to LEASE.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191120","191120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42009","2014-03-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the European Commission to bring forward a directive which would implement across the EU the Office of Fair Trading's guidance on micro-transaction gaming.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191133","191133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42010","2014-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the continued classification of RAF Northolt as a military aerodrome; and what account that policy takes of the proportion of flights using that aerodrome that are commercial.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191136","191136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42011","2014-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made on RAF Northolt's fulfillment of its obligations under Regulation (EC) No. 1108/2009.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191106","191106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42012","2014-03-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, column 519W, on energy competition, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's assessment of the effects of the introduction of a ring-fence between the generation and retail arms of vertically integrated energy companies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191107","191107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42013","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer given to the hon. Member for Corby of 27 February 2014, Official Report, columns 406-7, how much compensation beyond the £28 million already stated for the Emission Trading System is expected to be provided; and when that additional compensation will be provided.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191141","191141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42014","2014-03-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, at what stage of development the conversion of Drax power station to biomass is; and when that project is due to be completed.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191145","191145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42015","2014-03-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the conversion to biomass at Drax power station will continue to ensure that the station provides seven to eight per cent of the UK's electricity needs.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191146","191146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42016","2014-03-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what socio-economic benefits the local community will receive from Drax power station's conversion from coal-fire to biomass.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191147","191147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42017","2014-03-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department plans to bid for European Union funding for carbon capture and storage projects; and if he will allocate part of any of such funding to Drax power station.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191144","191144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42018","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the European Commission on when the compensation scheme for the carbon floor price will be approved.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191142","191142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42019","2014-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many visits and checks Trading Standards has carried out in relation to equine passports and microchipping since 2005.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191135","191135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42020","2014-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent reports that Israeli forces intercepted an Iranian shipment of advanced, long-range M-302 missiles bound for Gaza.","Biography information for Michael Ellis","Michael Ellis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191134","191134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42021","2014-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of (a) military and (b) financial support of the Syrian government by the government of Iran; if he will raise this issue at the United Nations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191117","191117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42022","2014-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had at the United Nations about the financial and military support given to the government of Syria by the government of Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191118","191118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42023","2014-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he bring forward proposals to impose further sanctions against the government of Iran for its continued support of terrorism in (a) Iraq, (b) Syria and (c) Israel; and if he will be make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191100","191100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42024","2014-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of human rights abuses in Iran; if he will raise that matter at the United Nations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191101","191101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42025","2014-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had at the United Nations about the Iranian nuclear programme; and if he will be make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191102","191102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42026","2014-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of weapons from Iran reaching Syria across Iraqi airspace; if he will raise that matter at the United Nations; and if he will be make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191103","191103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42027","2014-03-11","Department of Health","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which companies outside the NHS have received NHS patient data over the last 10 years; what data was provided; and how much was charged for that data in each case.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191104","191104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42028","2014-03-11","Department of Health","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many senior staff employed at the Health and Social Care were previously employed at the NHS Information Centre; and what the grade is of each such member of staff.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191116","191116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42029","2014-03-11","Department of Health","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff are employed at the Health and Social Care Information Centre; and how many of those staff were previously employed at the NHS Information Centre.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191121","191121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42030","2014-03-12","Department of Health","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Clause 34 of the Immigration Bill, HL Bill 84, what his policy is on exempting immunisation for children from NHS charging provisions for persons not ordinarily resident in Great Britain.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191153","191153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42031","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many properties she has allocated for dispersed asylum seekers in the area of Wrexham County Borough Council.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191151","191151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42032","2014-03-12","Home Office","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the sale of legal highs.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191139","191139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42034","2014-03-11","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-07","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which local authorities in Great Britain failed the Standard Three performance standard for the completeness and accuracy of electoral registration records in 2013.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191114","191114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42035","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-07","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Cardiff County Council and (b) Vale of Glamorgan Council.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191131","191131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42036","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-07","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in Dudley Metropolitan Borough.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191132","191132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42037","2014-03-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-03-07","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent confirmation dry run conducted in (a) Sandwell Metropolitan Borough, (b) Walsall Metropolitan Borough, (c) Wolverhampton Metropolitan Borough and (d) Birmingham City.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191130","191130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42038","2014-03-11","Department for Transport","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre in Stornoway was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in February 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191122","191122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42039","2014-03-11","Department for Transport","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre in Liverpool was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in February 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191123","191123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42040","2014-03-11","Department for Transport","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times the Maritime Rescue Co-ordination Centre in Belfast was staffed at below risk-assessed levels in February 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191124","191124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42041","2014-03-12","Department for Transport","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance he issues to the Highways Agency on minimising the effect of road works on local business.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191164","191164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42042","2014-03-12","Department for Transport","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the Highway Agency's complaints procedures.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191165","191165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42043","2014-03-12","Department for Transport","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department issues guidance on the level of acceptable disruption to local traffic and business caused by road works.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191166","191166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42044","2014-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will assess the potential for improved administration and awareness of the short-term benefit advances scheme to affect demand for food banks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191156","191156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42045","2014-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the quality of the administration of the short-term benefit advances scheme since its inception.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191105","191105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/42046","2014-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been in receipt of out-of-work benefits for (a) one year, (b) two years and (c) three years or more in (i) Wrexham constituency, (ii) Wales and (iii) the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191126","191126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41761","2014-03-11","Attorney General","2014-03-06","To ask the Attorney General, whether his Department is aware of any undertakings of (a) amnesty, (b) immunity and (c) implied immunity from prosecution given to any (i) former or serving members of the security forces, (ii) person who has acted as an agent of the security forces or Government intelligence services and (iii) member of a paramilitary organisation.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191085","191085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41762","2014-03-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to begin naming employers who do not comply with the National Minimum Wage under the revised scheme adopted on 1 October 2013; whether all employers investigated by HM Revenue and Customs where a Notice of Underpayment is then issued will be named; where that information will be published; and whether his Department will take steps to inform the media of the publication of that information.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191067","191067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41763","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what programmes he has for public engagement with science; what the cost of those programmes is; what evaluation he has made of their effectiveness; and if he will publish the results of that evaluation.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191032","191032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41764","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of debt relief orders filed in 2011-12 failed due to an increase in the debtor's income invalidating the procedure.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190924","190924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41765","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average total debt was of individuals who filed for (a) a debt relief order, (b) bankruptcy and (c) an individual voluntary arrangement in 2012-13.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190925","190925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41766","2014-03-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many individual voluntary arrangements failed because an increase in the debtor's income invalidated the procedure in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190927","190927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41767","2014-03-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints about official receiver fees were received in each year between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190893","190893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41768","2014-03-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints about the Official Receiver were received in each year between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190894","190894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41769","2014-03-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of young people without a university qualification working in the (a) high-tech manufacturing and (b) space industry.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190889","190889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41770","2014-03-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support the use of electric vehicles.","Biography information for Andrew Jones","Andrew Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190962","190962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41771","2014-03-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the UK agricultural technologies strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190937","190937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41772","2014-03-10","Cabinet Office","2014-03-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will review his Department's civil contingencies response.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190934","190934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41773","2014-03-11","Cabinet Office","2014-03-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what points he has identified from the recent flooding crisis to enable COBR to work more effectively.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191057","191057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41774","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to warn people of the dangers of using lookalike websites when completing their tax return online; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191012","191012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41775","2014-03-10","HM Treasury","2014-03-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what right of appeal account holders have in disputes over dormant bank accounts.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191076","191076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41776","2014-03-10","HM Treasury","2014-03-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the future of the HM Revenue and Customs centre in Newry.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 191077","191077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41777","2014-03-11","HM Treasury","2014-03-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to maintain the current fuel differential between road fuel gases and petrol and diesel for a rolling 10 year period.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190922","190922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41778","2014-03-10","HM Treasury","2014-03-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will review the Green Book in regard to flood defence investment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190935","190935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41779","2014-03-10","HM Treasury","2014-03-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with mortgage lenders on their policy that domestic mortgages must be repaid in full before the mortgagor's 75th birthday.","Biography information for Mr Charles Kennedy","Mr Charles Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190899","190899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/41780","2014-03-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to allow elected council leaders to take over the role and responsibilities of council chief executives.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 190926","190926"
