"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864413","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 71366, on Diesel Vehicles: Exhaust Emissions, whether the Government has provided any assistance to customers or their legal representatives in their bid for civil action against Volkswagen.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132896","132896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864414","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government has taken to (a) quantify the amount and (b) assess the effect of extra air pollution produced by cars affected by emission data manipulation in the United Kingdom.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132897","132897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864415","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the average waiting time on HM Revenue and Custom's phone lines in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132898","132898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864416","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many web chats HM Revenue and Customs have had with service users in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132899","132899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864417","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Government's policy is on UK laboratories continuing to be able to be certified to EU standards under the ATEX directive after March 2019.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132900","132900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864418","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cars of what makes in the Government Car Service were affected by Volkswagen's manipulation of emissions data; what the cost was to the public purse of the purchased or hired cars in that service that were affected; and what the cost was to the public purse of rectifying the faulty devices on those cars and of hiring or buying replacement vehicles as a result of those faulty devices.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132901","132901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864419","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cars of what makes in departmental fleets were affected by Volkswagen's manipulation of emissions data; what the cost was to the public purse of such fleet cars purchased or hired that were so affected; and what the cost was to the public purse of rectifying the faulty devices on those cars and of hiring or buying replacement vehicles as a result of those faulty devices.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132902","132902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864420","2018-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of former employees of Carillion working in (a) HM Prison and Probation Service and (b) HM Courts and Tribunals Service have been transferred to (i) Gov Facilities Services Ltd and (ii) taken up employment with re-contracted providers.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132903","132903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864421","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department will take in 2018 to ensure that schools in England are (a) aware of and (b) comply with the statutory guidance on pupils with medical conditions at school.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132904","132904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864422","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to schools on the amount of time required to advise pupils on food and nutrition.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132905","132905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864423","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's paper, SFR56/2017 published on 15 February 2018, what plans his Department has to increase the take-up of apprenticeships through university technical colleges; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132906","132906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864424","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance he has issued to schools on the amount of time to be allocated to physical activity for pupils.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132907","132907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864425","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to schools on the amount of time to be allocated to pupils for emotional well-being help and support.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132908","132908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864426","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support is provided by his Department to children who are absent from school as a result of diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132909","132909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864427","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many core planning strategy documents have been withdrawn by local authorities in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132910","132910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864428","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what role staff in his Department have in the assessment of the level of threat involving artificial intelligence.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132911","132911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864429","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to improve the security of the IT systems in the NHS since the cyber attack of May 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132912","132912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864430","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much debt was outstanding in each case where people were sent to prison for council tax non-payment in each year between 2010 and 2017.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132913","132913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864431","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will ensure that rights for child refugees under the Dublin III regulations are maintained after the UK leaves the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132914","132914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864432","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average cost is of developing a local plan for a county council.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132915","132915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864433","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average cost has been for the development of neighbourhood plans by town and parish councils in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132916","132916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864434","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that GPs receive a copy of Crohn's & Colitis UK's latest Inflammatory Bowel Disease toolkit to improve (a) awareness, (b) early diagnosis and (b) treatment plans for that condition.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132917","132917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864435","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the use of smart meters on (a) domestic household energy bills and (b) the level of domestic energy switching; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132918","132918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864436","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the viability of the future of the Energy Companies Obligation scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132919","132919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864437","2018-03-20","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the level of funding for West Midlands Police.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132920","132920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864438","2018-03-20","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of the change in the level of police funding on the capacity of the police to investigate burglaries in Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132921","132921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864439","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS child and adolescent psychiatrists have been employed in the West Midlands in the last two years for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132922","132922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864440","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have been (a) suspended and (b) had their employment terminated in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132923","132923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864441","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate has been made of the number of people with undiagnosed HIV, broken down by NUTS 1 region, in each year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132924","132924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864442","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps (a) his Department, (b) NHS England and (c) Public Health England is taking to ensure the equity of access to antiretoroviral therapy in the regions.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132925","132925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864443","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of people diagnosed with HIV infection are not receiving antiretroviral treatment by NUTS 1 region in each year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132926","132926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864444","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the reasons for regional differences in the uptake of antiretroviral therapy.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132927","132927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864445","2018-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to protect UK fans planning to travel to Russia this year, ahead of the Football world cup.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132928","132928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864446","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the effect of the reduction in funding for Lincoln’s Citizens Advice on the provision of advice to claimants of Universal Credit in Lincoln.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132929","132929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864447","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask the Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how frequently the contractor's compliance with the government childcare service contract is assessed by his Department.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132930","132930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864448","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to reduce class sizes in secondary schools in Portsmouth South.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132931","132931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864449","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will meet the Competition and Markets Authority, Financial Conduct Authority and Ofcom to discuss the applicability of the energy price cap to other service markets.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132932","132932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864450","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure geographical equality in the level of breast cancer care in (a) Lincoln constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132933","132933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864451","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the closure of Lincoln’s walk-in centre on people’s access to care in (a) Lincoln constituency and (b) Lincolnshire.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132934","132934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864452","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS England has the power to prevent the implementation of minimum waiting times for routine elective care.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132935","132935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864453","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of wholly owned subsidiary companies in the NHS on (a) joined-up care and (b) staff (i) coordination, (ii) retention and (iii) morale.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132936","132936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864454","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will list the (a) names and (b) ICAO identifiers of all current Civil Aviation Authority-licensed airfields in the UK.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132937","132937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864455","2018-03-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the independent review of full-time social action, published in January 2018, whether the Government plans to allocate money raised from dormant accounts to fund youth full-time social action programmes.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132938","132938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864456","2018-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of universal credit claims by heterosexual couples (a) with children and (b) without children who do not receive split payments are made to the female partner.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132939","132939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864457","2018-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the amount of court time that has been made available as a result of his Department's policy to allow people accused of shoplifting items under the value of £200 to plead guilty by post.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132940","132940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864458","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Government of the United Arab Emirates on the persecution of Christians in that country.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132941","132941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864459","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is taking steps to ensure that UK citizens who require dialysis in EU member states after the UK leaves the EU will be able to access that treatment free of charge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132942","132942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864460","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing mandatory recommended dietary allowance guidelines on (a) fast food packaging and (b) in fast food outlets.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132943","132943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864461","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that minors trafficked to the UK are able to receive (a) welfare and (b) protection for as long as they require.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132944","132944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864462","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what research her Department has undertaken on the potential merits of adopting the Swedish model of prosecuting people who pay for sex.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132945","132945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864463","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will introduce legislation to ensure that businesses erect signage stating that all service animals are welcome on their premises.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132946","132946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864464","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is developing a new child obesity plan; and what assessment he has made of the potential merits of developing a new child obesity plan that includes steps to reduce child tooth decay.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132947","132947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864465","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on children's oral health of a ban on advertising high-sugar products on television before 9pm.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132948","132948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864466","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is assessing the potential merits of limiting the availability of high sugar products as part of supermarket price promotions and at the point-of-sale.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132949","132949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864467","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of (a) gym membership and (b) other recreational therapies for the treatment of mental health issues.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132950","132950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864468","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage free and fair elections in Commonwealth nations.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132951","132951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864469","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of mandatory drug testing for people who operate heavy plant machinery.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132952","132952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864470","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that the sale of pro-terrorist merchandise cannot take place.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132953","132953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864471","2018-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the presence of plastic particles in bottled water.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132954","132954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864472","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department are taking to ensure universal coverage of (a) audio and (b) visual assistance to (i) deaf or (ii) blind travellers.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132955","132955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864473","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Autism and education in England 2017, published by the All Party Parliamentary Group on Autism, if he will introduce a national autism and education strategy.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132956","132956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864474","2018-03-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of Right to Buy on the number of young people in rented accommodation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132957","132957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864475","2018-03-20","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of Civil Service Fast Stream applicants were women in each financial year since 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132958","132958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864476","2018-03-20","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of successful Civil Service Fast Stream applicants were women in each financial year since 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132959","132959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864477","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what meetings he has had with (a) NSPCC and (b) Children in Need in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132960","132960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864478","2018-03-20","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of successful Civil Service Fast Stream applicants were black Asian or minority ethnic in each financial year since 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132961","132961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864479","2018-03-20","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office,what proportion of Civil Service Fast Stream applicants were black Asian or minority ethnic in each financial year since 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132962","132962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864480","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to help end child poverty.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132963","132963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864481","2018-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of Hong Kong as a result of the disqualification of lawmakers from its Legislative Council.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132964","132964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864482","2018-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to (a) the Government of Hong Kong and (b) the Government of the People's Republic of China on the status of the Hong Kong bookseller, Gui Minhai.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132965","132965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864483","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in Iran on ensuring that visa applications from Iranian nationals to visit the UK are processed as quickly and fairly as possible.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132966","132966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864484","2018-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to develop religious literacy among its staff in the past two years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132967","132967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864485","2018-03-20","Department for International Development","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what work has been undertaken by his Department to develop religious literacy among its staff in the last two years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132968","132968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861930","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","What assessment he has made of the effect of the Government’s policy on funded childcare on the financial viability of childcare settings.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904432","904432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861937","2018-03-14","Wales Office","2018-03-14","What recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the timetable for the delivery of the North Wales growth deal.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904283","904283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861938","2018-03-14","Wales Office","2018-03-14","What recent discussions he has had with the Welsh Government on the abolition of hospital car parking charges in Wales.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904285","904285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861939","2018-03-14","Wales Office","2018-03-14","What recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the effect on Wales of the UK leaving the EU Customs Union and single market.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904286","904286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861940","2018-03-14","Wales Office","2018-03-14","What recent discussions the Government has had with the Welsh Government on child protection in Wales.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904287","904287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861941","2018-03-14","Wales Office","2018-03-14","What assessment he has made of the potential effect on Welsh ports of the Government’s proposed future customs arrangements with the EU.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904288","904288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861942","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to promote apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904448","904448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861988","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","What steps his Department has taken to increase the take-up of STEM subjects.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904441","904441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862025","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to tackle no platform practices at universities.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132444","132444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862026","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2017 to Question 116798, when he plans to publish the Education Funding Agency reports on Wakefield City Academy Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132445","132445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862027","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will launch a consultation on the merits of duty free sales to EU countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132446","132446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862028","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to reduce the time between EU marketing authorisation and NICE appraisal of treatments for serious and progressive conditions and improve the timeliness of making such treatments available to patients.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132447","132447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862029","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what timeline is for NHS England to complete commercial negotiations with pharmaceutical companies after a treatment has met the NICE budget impact test; and what steps he is taking to ensure that those treatments are available to patients in a timely manner.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132448","132448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862030","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March to Question 129527 on Carillion: Insolvency, how much in funds has been raised from recovering trade debts owed to Carillion; and what proportion of these funds have been passed on to sub-contractors and workers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132449","132449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862031","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of  23 February 2018 to Question 128589, if her Department will collect data on the number of recipients of Support for Mortgage Interest at geographies smaller than Government Office Region.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132450","132450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862032","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect on household income of the replacement of Support for Mortgage Interest with a new loans-based system from April 2018.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132451","132451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862033","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people receiving their first universal credit payment have had money deducted from that payment to repay debt from (a) the Social Fund and (b) other benefits; and how much and what proportion of that debt has been repaid to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132452","132452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862034","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what professional qualifications are required to work as a careers advisor in prisons.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132453","132453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862035","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the use of high pressure laminate cladding is permitted under Approved Document B.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132454","132454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862036","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Building Research Establishment has represented the Government in an official capacity on fire safety in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132455","132455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862037","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2018 to Question 129973 on Slavery, for what reasons an extension of support for victims of trafficking will not be automatic until (a) her Department publishes its updated guidance on discretionary leave to remain and (b) a decision has been made on those cases in accordance with that updated guidance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132456","132456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862038","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the merits of the application of the principle of universal jurisdiction for alleged war crimes during the Sri Lankan civil war; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132457","132457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862039","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Sri Lanka on the establishment in that  country of an office on missing persons.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132458","132458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862040","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many vacancies were there for (a) nurses, (b) junior doctors, (c) doctors and (d) consultants, in the Barking, Havering and Redbridge University Hospitals NHS Trust, in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132459","132459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862041","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the PFI payments made by Barking, Havering and Redbridge University Hospitals NHS Trust relating to (a) capital costs and (b) service payments for each year since 2015.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132460","132460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862042","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the levels of PFI payments to made by the Barking, Havering and Redbridge University Hospitals NHS Trust over the next two decades.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132461","132461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862043","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to Pages 7 and 8 of his Department's document, entitled Regulatory Futures Review, published in January 2017, whether his Department received such a report from a working group regulators.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132462","132462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862044","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 4 of the Directly Operated Railways Limited annual report and statements for the year ended 31 March 2017, what the revised role for Directly Operated Railways is.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132463","132463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862045","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many domestic trips for the purpose of visiting friends and relatives were made in England in 2017.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132464","132464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862046","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March to Question 129926, what response the Minister of State for Europe and the Americas received from the Russian Ambassador to the UK on 27 February 2018 regarding the UK’s concerns about the ongoing targeting of civilians in eastern Ghouta; and whether the Government has made any further representations since that date.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132465","132465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862047","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons the deadline of the end of 2017 for Public Health England to publish data on hand gel usage in NHS trusts has not been met.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132466","132466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862048","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has evaluated usage of its careerometer.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132467","132467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862049","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the proportion of apprenticeships started by (a)  people of black and minority ethnic backgrounds and (b) with a learning difficulty or disability is increased by 20 per cent by 2020.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132468","132468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862050","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage the Zimbabwean diaspora in the UK to return to Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132469","132469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862051","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to raise awareness of engineering as a career among secondary school pupils.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132470","132470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862052","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how the Government Office for Artificial Intelligence plans to improve diversity in the artificial intelligence workforce.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132471","132471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862053","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had on (a) complete and (b) partial privatisation of the National Health Service's Property Services.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132472","132472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862054","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the NHS Property Services' (a) agreements and (b) completion dates for the delivery of building works at (i) Sidney West in West Sussex, (ii) Horsham Hospital and (iii) Crawley Hospital.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132473","132473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862055","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 7.4 of his Department's report, Regulatory Futures Review, published in January 2017, what proportion of arms-length bodies with regulatory functions operate under a full cost-recovery model.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132474","132474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862056","2018-03-19","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 7.4 of his Department's report, Regulatory Futures Review, published in January 2017, whether it is his policy that arms-length bodies should operate under models of full cost-recovery where possible.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132475","132475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862057","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance he has provided to arms-length bodies with regulatory functions on data sharing with each other.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132476","132476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862058","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Office of the Registrar of Consultant Lobbyists was included in the Regulatory Futures Review, published by his Department in January 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132477","132477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862059","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what employment services are provided by Interserve in prisons; in which prisons that company provides such services; and what the value is of each of those contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132478","132478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862060","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to roll-out the programme relating to the installation of telephones and basic computers in prison cells as a result of the conclusion of the pilot for that programme.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132479","132479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862061","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of including a statement on the right to freedom of religion or belief in the Commonwealth Heads of Government Joint Communiqué.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132480","132480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862062","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has revised the assumptions set out on page 8 of the impact assessment on Converting support for mortgage interest from a benefit into a loan that (a) 5 per cent of eligible working age claimants and (b) 8 per cent of eligible pension age claimants will not claim support for mortgage interest when it is converted into a loan.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132481","132481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862063","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of whether Russian companies listed on the London Stock Exchange and supplying raw materials such as aluminium to Russia represent a threat to the UK's national interests and security; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132482","132482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862064","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of whether the listing of EN+ Group on the London Stock Exchange received appropriate security checks; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132483","132483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862065","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2018 to Question 124788, what the evidential basis is for the Government’s estimation that parents with children under the age of twelve have higher childcare costs than parents with children under the age of fifteen.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132484","132484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862066","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the (a) social, (b) economic and (c) humanitarian effects of the ongoing Israeli naval blockade on Gaza.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132485","132485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862067","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what (a) legislative frameworks and (b) guidance are in place to ensure the protection of children from practices that (i) encourage them to gamble and (ii) expose them to situations that may lead to gambling through in-game purchasing in video games.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132486","132486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862068","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the source of consumer concerns relating to ownership and use of electric vehicles; and what steps his Department taking to allay those concerns.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132487","132487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862069","2018-03-19","Department for International Trade","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of whether the recent European Court of Justice ruling issued on 6 March 2018 in the Slowakische Republik v Achmea BV case that the ISDS mechanism in an intra-EU bilateral investment agreement is incompatible with EU law; and whether the UK  plans to follow that ruling and terminate its intra-EU bilateral investment agreements.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132488","132488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862070","2018-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to run a competition to replace the RAF’s airborne early warning aircraft.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132489","132489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862071","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2018 to Question 130543, by what method his Department assesses the cost-effectiveness of funding given to adopters under the Adoption Support Fund in the absence of information on adoption breakdown.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132490","132490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862072","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure the production of statistics to a common, harmonised standard after the UK exits the European Union.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132491","132491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862073","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to seek regular reports from the British Embassy in Beijing on the wellbeing of the two delegates of the Chinese Parliament who voted against the plan to abolish presidential term limits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132492","132492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862074","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on whether any UK citizens are serving as judges in Israeli military courts in the West Bank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132493","132493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862075","2018-03-19","Church Commissioners","2018-03-14","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, pursuant to the answer of 13 March 2018 to Question 131116 on Churches: Blackburn, what assessment has been made of the potential merits of drafting contracts for church spires and towers to host broadband and mobile facilities which take into account circumstances in which Church authorities subsequently wish to demolish such buildings to make alternative use of Church land.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132494","132494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862076","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what checks were made by his Department before the listing of EN+ Group on the London Stock Exchange; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132495","132495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862077","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of changes to journey time on the Midland Mainline in the event that the Mark 4 InterCity 225 stock is cascaded onto that route.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132496","132496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862078","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what classification of fragility her Department uses for the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132497","132497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862079","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of free early education places for disadvantaged two year-olds.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132498","132498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862080","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households received (a) Working Tax Credit, (b) Child Tax Credit and (c) both Working and Child Tax Credit in 2015-16.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132499","132499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862081","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much money was paid in compensation to prisoners in December 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132500","132500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862082","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to Question 127599 on Courts: Buildings, to whom each court was sold.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132501","132501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862083","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which companies were contracted by his Department to provide training for prison staff in 2017; and how much his Department paid to each of those companies for such training.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132502","132502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862084","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people won an appeal against the withdrawal of their (a) disability living allowance and (b) personal independence payment at a tribunal in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132503","132503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862085","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what financial deductions were levied against companies with which his Department had a contract during 2017; and if he will list for each financial deduction the (a) reason for that deduction and (b) company the deduction was made against.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132504","132504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862086","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many key performance indicators in contracts signed by his Department were (a) met and (b) not met in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132505","132505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862087","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2017 to Question 112641 on Ministry of Justice: Finance, what the projected change of his Department's budget for legal aid in real terms is in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132506","132506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862088","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2017 to Question 112641 on Ministry of Justice: Finance, what is the projected change of his Department's budget for prisons in real terms is in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132507","132507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862089","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2017 to Question Ministry of Justice: Finance, what is the projected change of his Department's budget for probation in real terms is in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132508","132508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862090","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2017 to Question Ministry of Justice: Finance, what the projected change of his Department's budget for courts in real terms is in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132509","132509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862091","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2018 to Question 130495 on Disability Living Allowance: Appeals, for what reason data on the number of people who win an appeal against the withdrawal of their disability living allowance is not centrally held.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132510","132510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862092","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victim liaison officers have been employed to work in each constituency in each year since 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132511","132511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862093","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average salary for a victim liaison officer has been in each year since 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132512","132512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862094","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victim liaison officers have been employed to work in each region in each year since 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132513","132513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862095","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2018 to Question 130494 on Ministry of Justice: Amey, for what reason his Department does not hold centrally information on whether Amey is meeting Key Performance Indicators.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132514","132514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862096","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a free bus pass scheme for armed forces veterans across the UK similar to the Veterans Concessionary Travel Scheme operating in London.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132515","132515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862097","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, what the process is for approving licences for hydrocarbon activity in the Falklands; which bodies are consulted with for that process; and what (a) funding and (b) staff are allocated to undertake those assessments.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132516","132516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862098","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the Government classes older apprentices as those over the age of 25; and if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of raising that age.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132517","132517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862099","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has plans to publish information on the number of parents eligible for tax-free childcare by constituency.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132518","132518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862100","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2018 to Question 127416, whether his Department has plans to collect data on the number of parents who (a) plan to stop and (b) have stopped using childcare vouchers in order to use tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132519","132519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862101","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2018 to Question 124451, what the evidential basis is for the Government’s estimate that 1.5 million families with childcare costs will be eligible for tax-free childcare; and for what reasons that estimated number differs from the number of families currently in receipt of childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132520","132520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862102","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on families with children between the age of 12 and 15 who (a) do not claim childcare vouchers before the closure of the scheme but would meet the scheme's eligibility requirements after its closure, and (b) cannot claim for tax-free childcare because of the age of their child.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132521","132521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862103","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to promote social work as a career choice.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132522","132522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862104","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department estimates that its funding allocated to Greater Manchester Police will increase or decrease in real terms in each year until 2019-20.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132523","132523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862105","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the level of funding for Greater Manchester Police.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132524","132524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862106","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of the change in the level of police funding on the capacity of local police forces in Greater Manchester to investigate burglaries.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132525","132525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862107","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS child and adolescent psychiatrists have been employed in the North West in the last two years for which data is available.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132526","132526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862108","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in the Thornbury and Yate constituency his Department estimates will benefit from the rise in tax free personal allowance during the 2018-2019 financial year.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132527","132527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862109","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in South Gloucestershire his Department estimates will benefit from the rise in tax free personal allowance during the 2018-2019 financial year.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132528","132528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862110","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in the South West his Department estimates will benefit from the rise in tax free personal allowance during the 2018-2019 financial year.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132529","132529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862111","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she has taken to reduce the number of people declaring incorrect incomes to avoid child support payments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132530","132530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862112","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people using limited companies to declare incorrect incomes to avoid child support payments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132531","132531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862113","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure compliance with the (a) Government's fit and proper person test and (b) NHS duty of candour had been applied in relation to the evidence gathered during the review into Liverpool Community Health NHS Trust conducted by Dr Bill Kirkup.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132532","132532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862114","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the (a) Government's fit and proper person test and (b)  NHS duty of candour is suspended in the eventof evidence of (i) harm and (ii) wrongdoing in relation to independent reviews funded by the Department of Health.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132533","132533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862115","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the amount that councils are required to pay back in right to buy receipts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132534","132534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862116","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Public Space Protection Orders in preventing intimidation around abortion clinics.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132535","132535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862117","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken in partnership with his international counterparts to encourage the Government of the Democratic Republic of Congo to adhere to the terms of the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132536","132536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862118","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on military intervention in the Democratic Republic of Congo to support the supply of humanitarian assistance to its citizens.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132537","132537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862119","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what right to buy receipts each local authority has paid to HM Treasury in each financial year since 2012-13.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132538","132538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862120","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff were employed by the Environment Agency (a) directly, (b) on a contracted basis and (c) on a subcontracted basis in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132539","132539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862121","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many water quality tests the Environment Agency carried out in 2017 compared with the previous seven years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132540","132540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862122","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to section 4.4 of the United Kingdom Anti-Corruption Strategy 2017-2022, which Ministers are in the Inter-Ministerial Group; and when the first meeting of that group will take place.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132541","132541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862123","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any funding from the Reducing Parental Conflict programme will be made available for relationship support services for in-work low-income families in addition to the support for workless families set out in Improving Lives: Helping Workless Families.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132542","132542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862124","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Improving Lives: Helping Workless Families, what proportion of the 11 per cent of children in couple-parent families who experience parental conflict are in (a) workless families, (b) families where one parent is in work and (c) families where both parents work.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132543","132543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862125","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the NHS in England has to adopt the definition of an ultra-rare disease as a condition with a prevalence of 1 in 50,000 or less, as used by the Montgomery Review of Access to Medicines in Scotland.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132544","132544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862126","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many medicines have been rejected by the National Institute of Health and Care Excellence’s Highly Specialised Technology programme because they did not meet the criterion on the number of patients expected to benefit from the medicine; and what plans he has to increase the figure in that criterion of 500 people affected to reflect population growth.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132545","132545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862127","2018-03-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the UK video games industry.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132546","132546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862128","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to improve mobile phone signals in rural areas.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132547","132547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862129","2018-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage Parish Councils to adopt single-use plastic-free policies.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132548","132548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862130","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to the Answer of 13 March 2018 to Question 131300, how many requests for transfer into the UK under the Dublin Regulation in 2017 were refused; and for what reasons those requests were refused.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132549","132549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862131","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help increase job opportunities for adults in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132550","132550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862132","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether it is the Government’s policy to continue to contribute to EU International Development efforts after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132551","132551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862133","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","what proportion of her Department's staff are (a) female and (b) male.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132552","132552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862134","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131303, of the 55 pregnant women detained in the immigration detention estate in 2017, how many were subsequently (a) released back into the community and (b) granted refugee or humanitarian protection status.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132553","132553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862135","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of people from each ethnic group have a custody image on the Police National Database.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132554","132554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862136","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the policy to enable individuals who did not receive a criminal conviction to request the deletion of their custody images from the National Police Database.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132555","132555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862137","2018-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on the Submarine Dismantling Project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132556","132556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862138","2018-03-16","Department for International Trade","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to work with the devolved administrations on future trade deals for UK agriculture.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132557","132557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862139","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on trade deals for the agriculture sector after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132558","132558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862140","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many out-of-area placements there have been for children with mental health issues (a) in England and (b) by region in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132559","132559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862141","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many out-of-area placements there have been for patients with eating disorders (a) in England and (b) by region in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132560","132560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862142","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the Health and Safety Executive has the necessary powers to enforce the requirement for landlords to hold a gas safety certificate for the property they are letting.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132561","132561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862143","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many out-of-area placements there have been for patients with (a) peri-natal psychosis and (b) peri-natal depression (a) in England and (b) by region in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132562","132562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862144","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to review Ofsted guidance to enable inspectors to evaluate a school's medical conditions policy and the effective implementation of that policy as part of a routine inspection; and whether he has received any representations on that matter.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132563","132563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862145","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans are in place to ensure the timely delivery of the Felixstowe-to-Nuneaton freight rail link.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132564","132564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862146","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities to ensure that unused brownfield sites are redeveloped for housing.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132565","132565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862147","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what Government funding has been made available to people who have experienced (a) child sexual exploitation, (b) domestic abuse and domestic violence, (c) sexual violence and sexual exploitation and (d) modern slavery in each of the last five years .","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132566","132566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862148","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of young people aged between 16 and 24 who started an apprenticeship remained in their placement after (a) three months, (b) six months and (c) 12 months in the most recent 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132567","132567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862149","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 130487, on Clinical Commissioning Groups: Halton, for what reasons two successive Chief Officers have been appointed on an interim basis; and when the timetable for the appointment of a permanent Chief Officer will be decided.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132568","132568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862150","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with food manufacturers on calorie labelling per portion on pre-packaged foods.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132569","132569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862151","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 4 April 2017 to Question 69321, on Right of Abode: Veterans, what the timetable is for the decision to be made on whether to grant the right of abode to former British-Hong Kong servicemen.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132570","132570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862152","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with food manufacturers on increasing the uptake of front-of-pack traffic light labelling on pre-packaged foods.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132571","132571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862153","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking with the Department for Education to implement the student electoral registration provision of the Higher Education and Research Act 2017.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132572","132572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862154","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of his time the interim Chief Officer for Halton Clinical Commissioning Group spends in (a) Halton and (b) Warrington.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132573","132573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862155","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with consumer groups on the effect on consumers of LINK's proposals to reduce the interchange fee.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132574","132574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862156","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with LINK and the Payment Systems Regulator on LINK's ability to guarantee the protections outlined in its Financial Inclusion Programme.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132575","132575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862157","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to increase the level of real term funding for mental health services in England.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132576","132576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862158","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department are taking to reduce patient waiting lists for mental health services in England.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132577","132577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862159","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Clinical Commissioning Groups in (a) Cheshire and (b) Merseyside do not have a permanent Chief Officer.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132578","132578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862160","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have received mental health treatment from South Tees NHS Trust since 2010.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132579","132579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862161","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Payment Systems Regulator on the future provision of ATMs and wider issues related to consumers' access to cash.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132580","132580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862162","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate the Government has made of the number of deaths per year caused by air pollution in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132581","132581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862163","2018-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Mayor of London on steps to tackle air pollution.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132582","132582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862164","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of changing the timing of National Democracy Week to avoid it coinciding with the school holidays in Scotland; and what steps he is taking to ensure that school children in Scotland are able to take part in that event.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132583","132583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862165","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to fund research into improving the diagnostics for Lyme disease.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132584","132584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862166","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the food industry to adopt the front-of-pack traffic light food labelling system.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132585","132585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862167","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to encourage food retailers to adopt calorie labelling on  menus or at the point of purchase.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132586","132586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862168","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve food labelling for people with diabetes.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132587","132587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862169","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to simplify electoral law.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132588","132588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862170","2018-03-19","Department for International Trade","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the volume of steel that will be re-directed to the UK which would have otherwise gone to the US as a result of the recent announcement on steel tariffs by the US administration.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132589","132589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862171","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to address concerns over interruption to schooling arising from the use of schools as polling places ahead of the local government elections in May.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132590","132590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862172","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125704, on Mortgages: Interest Payments, how the application process for the new loan will operate in cases where there is an existing charge on the property.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132591","132591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862173","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 128033, on prescription drugs, when his Department first became aware of the NHS Business Services Authority data showing the number of unique patients prescribed (a) benzodiazepines and (b) z drugs.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132592","132592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862174","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on the commitment in the Early Years Workforce Strategy 2017 to develop criteria for the content of level two childcare qualifications; how many meetings have taken place with the childcare sector and awarding organisations; and who attended such meetings.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132593","132593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862175","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what changes have been made to his Department's existing data collection as a result of the commitment to review workforce data in the Early years Workforce Strategy 2017.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132594","132594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862176","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have been awarded early years teacher status in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132595","132595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862177","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have taken part in early years initial teacher training in each year since September 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132596","132596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862178","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many early years teacher trainees who have started an early years teacher qualification have switched to initial teacher training to become a qualified teacher in each year since September 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132597","132597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862179","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average salary of an (a) early years, (b) primary school, (3) secondary school and (d) special school teacher was in each year since September 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132598","132598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862180","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average salary of a trainee (a) early years, (b) primary school, (c) secondary school and (d) special school teacher was in each year since September 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132599","132599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862181","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average salary of an (a) early years, (b) primary school, (c) secondary school and (d) special school teacher was five years after they started teaching.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132600","132600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862182","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many early years teachers have trained through each of the four teacher training routes referred to in paragraph 24 of the Early Years Workforce Strategy 2017 since September 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132601","132601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862183","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of graduates who were already employed in an early years setting have undertaken early years initial teacher training in each year since September 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132602","132602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862184","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many bursaries have been provided to trainee early years teachers in each year since September 2013; and what the average amount was of those bursaries.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132603","132603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862185","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what support his Department is providing to charities to improve their digital fundraising infrastructure.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132604","132604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862186","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes in the level of police funding on the ability of police forces to maintain financial reserves.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132605","132605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862187","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many early years teachers who have previously received an early years bursary remain an early years teacher working in a maintained setting.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132606","132606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862188","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been made available for early years teacher training courses in each year since September 2013; and how much funding will be made available in the next three years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132607","132607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862189","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to tackle (a) eating disorders and (b) body image issues among young people in schools.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132608","132608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862190","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated to nursery employers to help those employers support graduates in their settings to become early years teachers.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132609","132609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862191","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many training providers there are for (a) level two, (b) level three and (c) graduate early years teacher training routes.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132610","132610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862192","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many visits the landing page for the specific early years area on the Get into teaching website had in each year since that website was launched compared with the equivalent landing page for (a) primary teaching and (b) secondary teaching.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132611","132611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862193","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the annual marketing budget is for recruiting (a) early years, (b) primary and (c) secondary school teachers.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132612","132612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862194","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to publish the results of the review into early years initial teacher training announced in the Early Years Workforce Strategy 2017.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132613","132613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862195","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Early Years Workforce Strategy 2017, what progress has been made on the feasibility study due to report in March 2018 into developing a programme that specifically seeks to grow the graduate workforce in disadvantaged areas.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132614","132614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862196","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government was represented at the US-led meeting at the White House on 13 March 2018 on the humanitarian crisis in Gaza; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132615","132615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862197","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which projects have (a) been funded by and (b) had funding approved from the Cultural Development Fund; and what the overall value is of that funding for those projects.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132616","132616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862198","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the overall value of the Cultural Development Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132617","132617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862199","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of trends in the weekly level of physical activity for people aged 16 years and under since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132618","132618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862200","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of his Department's spending by region and constituent part of the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132619","132619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862201","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department has spent from the public purse on supporting sport in primary schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132620","132620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862202","2018-03-19","Department for International Trade","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make an assessment of whether a UK steel company can individually request an exemption for its product from the steel tariffs imposed by the US administration under Section 232 of the Trade Expansion Act; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132621","132621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862203","2018-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the number of war disablement pension claims from veterans with mesothelioma from (a) 16 December 2015 to 3 April 2016, (b) 4 April 2016 to 2 April 2017 and (c) 3 April 2017 to 9 March 2018.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132622","132622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862204","2018-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the number of war widow(er)s pensions awarded for veterans who died of mesothelioma between (a) 6 April 2015 to 3 April 2016, (b) 4 April 2016 2 April 2017 and (c) 3 April 2017 to 9 March 2018.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132623","132623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862205","2018-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the potential number of mesothelioma claims by veterans in the next five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132624","132624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862206","2018-03-16","Cabinet Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to review the appointment of Regional Returning Officers.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132625","132625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862207","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made as assessment of the compatibility of Government provision of back-pay to care providers for sleep-in shifts with EU state aid rules.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132626","132626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862208","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many firms are registered as Scottish Limited Partnerships in the UK.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132627","132627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862209","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, to which chemical weapons treaties the UK is a signatory; and to which such treaties it is a joint signatory with Russia.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132628","132628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862210","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many CCG guidelines have been updated, how much funding has been saved and how much he expects to save in 2018-19 following the consultation on items which should not routinely be prescribed in primary care.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132629","132629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862211","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on focus groups in December 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132630","132630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862212","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department supports the United Nations Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs Occupied Palestinian Territories Humanitarian Response Plan.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132631","132631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862213","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on opinion polling in December 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132632","132632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862214","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Secretary of State for Education's oral contribution of 13th March 2018, Official Report, column 802, what discussions he has had with employers on the potential confusion over eligibility for childcare vouchers in the middle of the tax year.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132633","132633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862215","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Education of 13 March 2018, Official Report, Column 802, what steps his Department is taking to alert (a) employers and (b) employees to the extension of the childcare vouchers scheme.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132634","132634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862216","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the change in tax liabilities for shipping companies in the tonnage tax scheme in each financial year from 2015-16 to 2018-19.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132635","132635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862217","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information she holds on the number of child and adolescent psychiatrists in the NHS in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132636","132636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862218","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 27th February 2018 to Question 129366, what financial support he plans to provide to working parents of disabled children in full-time education aged 16 to 20 and whose earnings status makes them ineligible for carer's allowance.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132637","132637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862219","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children under the age of (a) 11 and (b) 18 were taken into care in each of the last three years as a result of their mother being imprisoned; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132638","132638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862220","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children were born to women in custody in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132639","132639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862221","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women received custodial sentences of less than (a) three and (b) six months in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132640","132640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862222","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints have been made against the Children and Family Court Advisory and Support Service in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132641","132641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862223","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding the Children and Family Court Advisory and Support Service received in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132642","132642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862224","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will set out all films that benefited from UK film tax relief in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132643","132643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862225","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will issue national insurance numbers to all asylum seekers when they are granted refugee status.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132644","132644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862226","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of offences under the (i) Game Act 1831, (ii) Poaching Prevention Act 1862 and (iii) the Night Poaching Acts 1828 and 1844 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132645","132645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862227","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are eligible for free school meals.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132646","132646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862228","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the 8.6 million smart meters installed by the end of 2017 were (a) advanced and (b) SMETS1 meters.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132647","132647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862229","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that High Street stores are not empty.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132648","132648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862230","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much from the public purse was spent on employing agency (a) doctors and (b) nurses in the NHS in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132649","132649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862231","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has any plans to remove charges for parking at hospitals.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132650","132650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862232","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government is taking steps to (a) educate young people on the risks of cancer and (b) ensure that young people attend regular check-ups.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132651","132651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862233","2018-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Government plans to release the funding for the Yorkgate Interchange project.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132652","132652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862234","2018-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information she holds on policing costs during St Patrick’s Day celebrations in 2017 in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132653","132653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862235","2018-03-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking with foreign governments to help internally displaced people overseas.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132654","132654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862236","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of whether refugees should be required to pass a habitual residence test for benefits after being granted refugee status.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132655","132655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862237","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2017 to Question 117050, on armed conflict: schools, what assessment the Government has made of the implications of signing the Safe Schools Declaration; and whether it plans to sign that declaration.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132656","132656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862238","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which of the sites listed in the Particulate Numbers and Concentrations Network monitors emissions of particulate matter of less than 2.5 microns.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132657","132657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862239","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how the Government monitors emissions of persistent organic pollutants by waste incineration facilities.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132658","132658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862240","2018-03-16","House of Commons Commission","2018-03-14","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of withdrawing Press Gallery passes being issued to (a) Russia TV and (b) RT; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132659","132659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862241","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits to the Scottish manufacturing sector of the development of floating offshore wind technology.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132660","132660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862242","2018-03-16","Department for International Trade","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the export potential for floating offshore wind technology to the UK economy.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132661","132661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862243","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the development of (a) Dounreay TrÍ, (b) Forthwind and (c) Kincardine offshore wind projects on the (i) the UK and (ii) Scottish economy.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132662","132662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862244","2018-03-16","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the Renewables Obligation support to floating offshore wind projects after October 2018.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132663","132663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862245","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS child and adolescent psychiatrists have been employed in the North West in each of the last two years for which information is available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132664","132664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862246","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which external recruitment agencies are used by his Department's non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132665","132665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862247","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to reply to the letter of the hon Member for Harrow West of 13th February on UNAIDS.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132666","132666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862248","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle physical inactivity among children through sport.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132667","132667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862249","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost of obesity to the (a) NHS and (b) the social care sector in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132668","132668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862250","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many couples receiving universal credit (a) with dependent children and (b) with no children have (i) one partner in work and (ii) both partners in work.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132669","132669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862251","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many couples receiving universal credit have a child under the age of three in their household.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132670","132670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862252","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many couples receiving universal credit have nominated one partner as being responsible for a child; and how many of those so nominated are (a) female and (b) male.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132671","132671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862253","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the decision was made to expand the 26-30 railcard trial to 10,000 extra participants.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132672","132672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862254","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with SEND have not been transferred to Education and Health Care Plans.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132673","132673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862255","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to extend the trial of the 26-30 Railcard outside of (a) Great Anglia and (b) 10,000 railcards that have been issued.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132674","132674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862256","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the legal status will be from 1 April 2018 of children’s SEN statements that have not been transferred to an education, health and care plan.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132675","132675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862257","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the effect of the NHS (Charges to Overseas Visitors) (Amendment) Regulations 2017; and if he will publish an assessment of the effect of those regulations to date.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132676","132676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862258","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases he is aware of where patients have been provided with access to cancer treatment as a result of the NHS (Charges to Overseas Visitors) (Amendment) Regulations 2017; and how many of those cases related to people who were (a) confirmed foreign nationals and (b) undocumented.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132677","132677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862259","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what powers he has to intervene in cases where long-term British residents are denied cancer care as a result of the introduction of the NHS (Charges to Overseas Visitors) (Amendment) Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132678","132678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862260","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in Indonesia on the potential criminalisation of LGBT acts and extramarital relations by that country's Parliament.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132679","132679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862261","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in the Philippines on the potential withdrawal of that country from the Rome Statute of the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132680","132680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862262","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Minister of Sport and Civil Society has to meet with the Chair of the Independent review of full-time social action following that report's publication.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132681","132681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862263","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were attempting to obtain a 26 to 30 railcard when the website crashed on 13 March 2018.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132682","132682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862264","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the average number of hours spent on administrative tasks each week by (a) nurses and (b) GPs in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132683","132683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862265","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on what the maximum amount is that a national government can spend on farming subsidies according to World Trade Organisation rules.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132684","132684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862266","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on helping develop a five-year strategy for the National Retail Crime Steering Group.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132685","132685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862267","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of GPs in England are over 50 years old.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132686","132686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862268","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, from which Departmental funding stream will the £50 million integration fund outlined by the Secretary of State on 14 March 2018, be allocated from.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132687","132687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862269","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department provides to employers on supporting employees who return to work after a period of mental illness.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132688","132688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862270","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that mental health services take account of the experiences and needs of women (a) in general and (b) who have experienced extensive abuse.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132689","132689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862271","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of the different categories of crime to UK businesses.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132690","132690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862272","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what resources his Department has allocated to tackle loneliness among older people in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132691","132691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862273","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of mental health service users also have co-morbid alcohol and drug dependence.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132692","132692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862274","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department has allocated for mental health (a) prevention and (b) treatment in the last year.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132693","132693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862275","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many mental health beds have been closed since August 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132694","132694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862276","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children and adolescents were admitted to hospital as a result of intentional self-harm in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132695","132695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862277","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the level of the skills shortage in the general aviation sector; and what steps his Department is taking to address that shortage.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132696","132696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862278","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of whether further price reductions on innovative branded medicines are necessary given the majority of medicines are capped through the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132697","132697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862279","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department’s press release of 14 March 2017, how much of the £50 million of funding allocated to support the new Integrated Communities Strategy will be used to expand English for Speakers of Other Languages teaching.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132698","132698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862280","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what Kettering General Hospital needs to do to get out of special measures.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132699","132699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862281","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Government of Kyrgyzstan on the case of Klara Kabilova, the chairwoman of Kyrgyzstan's Central Election Commission.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132700","132700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862282","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding allocated to programmes in his Department has been reallocated to programmes preparing for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132701","132701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862283","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing (a) national minimum standards and (b) eligibility criteria to the administration of public health funerals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132702","132702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862284","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government has plans to introduce a children's funeral fund.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132703","132703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862285","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the maximum level of funeral expenses payments, in relation to recent trends in funeral costs.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132704","132704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862286","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of teachers on each point of the main pay range.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132705","132705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862287","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of teachers on each point of the upper pay range.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132706","132706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862288","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask the Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution from the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions of 13 March 2018, Official Report, column 768, on what date he plans to provide further details of the roll out of childcare support in Northern Ireland similar to 30 hours of funded childcare in England.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132707","132707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862289","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases have been referred to the Court of Appeal by the Criminal Cases Review Commission more than once since 1997.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132708","132708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862290","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to increase funding from the public purse to the creative industries.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132709","132709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862291","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department is taking steps to ensure that the European Convention on Cinematographic Co-Production applies to the UK after it leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132710","132710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862292","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the loss of freedom of movement on the UK entertainment sector.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132711","132711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862293","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has plans to replicate Creative Europe funding for UK creative industries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132712","132712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862294","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 130778 on Nabiximols, what progress his Department has made on reducing the cost of the drug Sativex.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132713","132713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862295","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has held with (a) examination boards, (b) teachers, (c) students and (d) other stakeholders on the creation of a GCSE in British Sign Language; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132714","132714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862296","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the use of (a) the arts and (b) culture was included in the consultation on the Green Paper on Transforming children and young people's mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132715","132715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862297","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to implement Public Health England's Health in all policies, published in October 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132716","132716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862298","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the cost of bidding for funds from the City Transformation Fund.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132717","132717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862299","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Greater Anglia rail franchise is meeting its financial performance targets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132718","132718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862300","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the premium payments of £3.8 billion on the Greater Anglia rail franchise will be paid in full.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132719","132719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862301","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of whether the Greater Anglia rail franchise contract will be fulfilled.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132720","132720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862302","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department is taking steps to assist people with Mayer-Rokitansky-Küster-Hauser syndrome with the financial costs of (a) adoption and (b) surrogacy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132721","132721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862303","2018-03-16","Department for Transport","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of Transport, for what reasons his Department's consultation entitled Road Vehicles Improving Air quality and Safety has run for a period of four weeks rather than the 12 weeks recommended in the Code of Practice on Consultation.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132722","132722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862304","2018-03-16","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to her oral contribution of 12 March 2018, Official Report, columns 641 to 642, whether she plans to set the budget for Northern Ireland through an Order-in-Council; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132723","132723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862305","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to publish statistics on applications by survivors and relatives of victims and survivors under the Grenfell Tower relatives policy.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132724","132724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862306","2018-03-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to her oral contribution of 12 March 2018, Official Report, column 642, if she will set out the timescale to receive full and final representations from the Northern Ireland political parties before she makes a final decision on reducing the salaries of Members of the Legislative Assembly; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132725","132725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862307","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2018 to Question 127010, on employment and support allowance, how many ESA65B letters her Department has sent to doctors.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132726","132726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862308","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2018 to Question 127010, on employment and support allowance, when her Department started sending ESA65B letters to GPs; and whether that policy was authorised by Ministers.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132727","132727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862309","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of progress on the Belfast City Deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132728","132728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862310","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2018 to Question 127010, on employment and support allowance, if she will place a copy of the ESA65B letter that her Department sends to GPs in the Library.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132729","132729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862311","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet representatives of Employers for Childcare to discuss its concerns about the closure of the childcare voucher scheme  to new entrants after the six-month extension; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132730","132730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862312","2018-03-16","Leader of the House","2018-03-14","To ask the Leader of the House, with which political parties she has discussed reducing the amount of representative money given to Sinn Fein; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132731","132731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862313","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in Witham constituency (a) attained and (b) exceeded the minimum standard for reading at (i) key stage 1 and (ii) key stage 2 in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132732","132732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862314","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to raise standards of literacy at schools in Essex.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132733","132733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862315","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to monitor foreign national offenders who are subject to multi-agency public protection arrangements; and if he will set out the number of foreign national offenders who are subject to multi-agency public protection arrangements in each police area.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132734","132734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862316","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign national offenders were deported to each country in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132735","132735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862317","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who had been deported from the UK as a result of (a) a criminal prosecution and (b) committing terrorism-related offences subsequently returned to the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132736","132736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862318","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national offenders have been convicted of multiple offences in the UK.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132737","132737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862319","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how long it takes on average to deport a foreign national offender between their release from custody and their departure from the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132738","132738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862320","2018-03-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to her oral contribution of 12 March 2018, Official Report, column 642, if she will publish the full and final representations from the Northern Ireland political parties about reducing the salaries of Members of the Legislative Assembly; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132739","132739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862321","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 129007, if he will meet with the family of Asa Hutchinson.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132740","132740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862322","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on what date will planning applications be accepted for the proposed North Essex Garden Communities; and what role will his Department play in the process.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132741","132741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862323","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what funds his Department has provided for the North Essex Garden Communities scheme; and what limits his Department has placed on the expenditure of those funds.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132742","132742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862324","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage and support private sector investment in proposed garden settlements.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132743","132743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862325","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the criteria for and restrictions on borrowing for local authorities are in relation to garden settlement proposals.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132744","132744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862326","2018-03-16","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans the Secretary of State has to visit the border between the Republic of Ireland and Northern Ireland in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132745","132745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862327","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131575, on Local Government: Dorset, what assessment he has made of the finding in paragraph 1.42 of the Final Report of Opinion Research Services on Researching your councils' consultation that the household survey is a better guide than the open questionnaire to the balance of public opinion across Christchurch.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132746","132746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862328","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has met the campaign group Code Blue to discuss concerns about sexual harassment at UNAIDs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132747","132747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862329","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 7 November 2017, Local Government Improvement, HCWS 232, what public consultation preceded that policy announcement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132748","132748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862330","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the merits of a system for reporting sexual harassment which is independent of senior management at UNAIDs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132749","132749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/862331","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what response his Department received to its suggestion that councils in Dorset should apply a voluntary cap of £95,000 to any exit payments arising from local government reorganisation.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132750","132750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860913","2018-03-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-13","What estimate the Government has made of the value of the UK’s financial and professional services to the EU.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904384","904384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860914","2018-03-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-13","What recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of the services sector on the implications for that sector of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904396","904396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860916","2018-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","What steps he is taking to support the marine energy industry.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904338","904338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860917","2018-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","What steps he is taking to support the renewable energy sector.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904339","904339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860918","2018-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","What steps he is taking to support the renewable energy sector.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904340","904340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860919","2018-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","What steps he plans to take to help elderly people manage their energy bills.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904341","904341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860920","2018-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","What progress his Department has made on implementing the Good Work Plan.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904344","904344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860921","2018-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","What change there has been in the amount of UK energy provided by solar power in the last two years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904345","904345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860922","2018-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","If he will use his powers under the Enterprise Act 2002 to intervene in the takeover bid for GKN by Melrose.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904346","904346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/860923","2018-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","What steps the Government is taking to support the growth of the agri-tech sector.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904347","904347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861028","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for completing the phase 4 roll-out of the Superfast Essex scheme; and what steps will be taken to support people in target areas who fail to receive the intended higher levels of broadband connectivity.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132177","132177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861029","2018-02-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what evidence his Department holds of energy retail price caps having been successfully introduced into competitive markets in other jurisdictions.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132178","132178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861030","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 June 2015, HCWS42, on local planning, whether the Government plans to remove those additional planning conditions which apply on onshore wind projects in England.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132179","132179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861031","2018-03-15","Cabinet Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2018 to Question 128314 on One Public Estate Programme, what progress the Government has made on recruiting more experts; and to which specialisms the Government is recruiting.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132180","132180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861032","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the compatibility of burning wood in coal power stations with the Clean Growth Strategy and the UK's obligations under the Paris Agreement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132181","132181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861033","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons his Department returned £817m of housing funding to HM Treasury; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132182","132182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861034","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of NICE's consideration of drugs for rare diseases.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132183","132183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861035","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she will provide additional staff and funding to tackle the illegal wildlife trade prior to the October 2018 Illegal Wildlife Trade conference in London.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132184","132184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861036","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce smoking prevalence rates amongst (a) serving armed forces personnel and (b) veterans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132185","132185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861037","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will take steps to ensure that people employed by contractors at the 2022 Commonwealth Games are paid the Real Living Wage.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132186","132186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861038","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on the heritage sector of the reduction in the Heritage Lottery Fund distribution budget for 2017-18 from the previous year; and whether his Department plans to take steps to help the heritage sector replace that funding.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132187","132187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861039","2018-03-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether his Department plans to provide support for health services in Gaza as a result of the recent findings of the United Nations Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132188","132188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861040","2018-03-16","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will take steps to ensure the accessibility of early legal advice; and what steps are being taken to include proposals to increase the provision of such early legal advice in the Government's review of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132189","132189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861041","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for asylum submitted by victims of trafficking are awaiting a decision to date.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132190","132190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861042","2018-03-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department is taking steps to encourage collaboration between artists in the UK and the US within the music industry.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132191","132191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861043","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the loss of specialist teams for unaccompanied asylum-seeking minors on their (a) physical health, (b) mental health and (c) learning and development.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132192","132192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861044","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the Credit Union Expansion Project has been closed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132193","132193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861045","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the report of the Financial Conduct Authority, FCA Mission: Our Future Approach to Consumers, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a duty of care on financial services firms towards consumers.","Biography information for Emma Little Pengelly","Emma Little Pengelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132194","132194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861046","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequacy of provision of (a) emotional and (b) psychological support for people with blood cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132195","132195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861047","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to develop a support strategy for families of people with cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132196","132196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861048","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what contingency plans he has put in place to ensure the provision of mains water to (a) businesses and (b) households in the event of severe weather conditions.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132197","132197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861049","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints relating to the equalisation of the state pension age investigation case managers at the office of the Independent Case Examiner are investigating; and what the average waiting time for such a complaint lodged with the Independent Case Examiner to be allocated to an investigation case manager was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132198","132198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861050","2018-03-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many independent case managers at the office of the Independent Case Examiner are working on cases relating to complaints on the equalisation of the state pension age.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132199","132199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861051","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will meet with representatives of NatWest to discuss the potential effect on that bank's elderly and vulnerable customers of the proposed closure of its Millhouses branch in Sheffield.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132200","132200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861052","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether (a) any policy has been changed and (b) guidance has been implemented to reduce the number of Tier 5 (Temporary Worker - Charity Worker) visa applications granted in the last 5 years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132201","132201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861053","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Sri Lanka on that government's failure to implement the UK-sponsored resolution 30/1 of the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132202","132202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861054","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on services provided by Uber in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132203","132203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861055","2018-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on services provided by Uber in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132204","132204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861056","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many vacancies there were for (a) nurses, (b) junior doctors, (c) doctors, and (d) consultants, at Barts Health NHS Trust, in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132205","132205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861057","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether it remains his Department's policy to  close King George Hospital Accident and Emergency Department.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132206","132206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861058","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of notice periods for people on agency contracts with regard to dismissal procedures.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132207","132207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861059","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the regulations, procedures and guidelines on the police using mobile phone extraction tools.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132208","132208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861060","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what comparative assessment her Department has made of the ethnicity of individuals who have had data extracted from their mobile phones by the police compared with the ethnicity of the general population.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132209","132209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861061","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the military assets his Department has sold to other countries; and what the criteria was for those sales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132210","132210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861062","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK companies have received a financial return from his Department's sale of military assets in each of the last five years; and what the value was of those returns.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132211","132211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861063","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many environmental impact assessments his Department has made in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132212","132212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861064","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the accurate prescription of antibiotics to patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132213","132213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861065","2018-03-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132214","132214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861066","2018-03-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132215","132215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861067","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132216","132216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861068","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132217","132217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861069","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132218","132218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861070","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of her Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132219","132219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861071","2018-03-15","Department for International Development","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132220","132220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861072","2018-03-15","Department for International Trade","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132221","132221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861073","2018-03-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132222","132222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861074","2018-03-15","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of her Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132223","132223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861075","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132224","132224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861076","2018-03-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132225","132225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861077","2018-03-15","Scotland Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132226","132226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861078","2018-03-15","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132227","132227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861079","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132228","132228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861080","2018-03-15","Wales Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of his Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132229","132229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861081","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of her Department's estate is (a) rented, (b) owned and (c) occupied through any other type of agreement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132230","132230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861082","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterparts in (a) Hong Kong and (b) the People’s Republic of China on the case of the missing Hong Kong bookseller, Gui Minhai.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132231","132231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861083","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on new IT capabilities to enable the (a) registration and (b) regulation of chemical substances in the UK market, after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132232","132232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861084","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department has made on systems for the (a) licensing and (b) marketing of veterinary medicines after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132233","132233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861085","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department has made on developing a new catch certificate system for UK (a) fish and (b) fish products exported to the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132234","132234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861086","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department has made on the development of a UK system to manage the quota of (a) fluorinated gases and (b) ozone depleting substances required under the UN Montreal Protocol, after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132235","132235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861087","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on developing data exchange arrangements to identify the movement of (a) EU and (b) third country vessels in UK waters, and the movement of UK vessels in (i) EU and (ii) third country waters, after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132236","132236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861088","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information on (a) labour rights and (b) access to advice and remedy is routinely provided to workers who (i) file a complaint with and (ii) are encountered during labour inspections conducted by the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132237","132237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861089","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure adequate levels of funding for organ transplant operations after the roll-out of the opt-out only scheme for organ donations.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132238","132238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861090","2018-03-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his French counterpart on that government’s policies for the requirement to remove the turban for identification documents.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132239","132239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861091","2018-03-16","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the head of the Security Industry Authority on the treatment of visitors wearing turbans to establishments where registered security staff are working; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132240","132240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861092","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the UK Space Agency on Cornwall Newquay Airport's bid to become a spaceport.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132241","132241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861093","2018-03-15","Department for Transport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Civil Aviation Agency on licenses for space flights and the location of spaceports in (a) the UK and (b) Cornwall.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132242","132242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861094","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  what assessment he has made of the implications for his polices of the report of  the Money and Mental Health Policy Institute on people with debt problem debt while receiving hospital treatment for mental health issues.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132243","132243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861095","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to allocate funding for the training of educational psychologists after 2020.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132244","132244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861096","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2018 to Question 126339 on Collective Spirit Multi-Academy Trust and the Answer of 8 February to Question 126463 on Collective Spirit Multi-Academy Trust, if he will publish the invoices for all the related party transactions held by the Education and Skills Funding Agency relating to the Collective Spirit Multi Academy Trust.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132245","132245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861097","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much local content television channels established under the Local Digital Television Programme Services Order 2012 have broadcast since their inception.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132246","132246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861098","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the annual operating (a) profits and (b) losses of local television stations established under the Local Digital Television Programme Services Order 2012.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132247","132247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861099","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what due diligence checks were undertaken on the (a) suitability to run and (b) experience and knowledge of running schools of the people who set up the Collective Spirit multi-academy trust.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132248","132248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861100","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2018 to Question 118594, on Government Departments: Flags, whether any government buildings in (a) Whitehall and (b) central London routinely fly the EU flag.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132249","132249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861101","2018-03-16","Leader of the House","2018-03-13","To ask the Leader of the House, what the cost to the House has been of payments made to hon. Members who have not taken their seats in the House in respect of their Parliamentary duties, in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132250","132250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861102","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's policy is on the provision of health care for asylum seekers in interim accommodation centres.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132251","132251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861103","2018-03-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his Answer of 8 March 2018 to Question 130486 on Clinical Commissioning Groups: Halton, what recent assessment he has made of the financial sustainability of Halton Care Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132252","132252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861104","2018-03-16","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 21 January 2016 to Question 22952 on Schools Admissions, whether he plans to strengthen the position of siblings in school admissions policy.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132253","132253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861105","2018-03-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of divergence from EU food and drink regulations on continued frictionless trade with the 27 countries of the EU.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132254","132254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861106","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Government’s policy is on onshore wind farming; and what plans he has to encourage growth in that sector when implementing the Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132255","132255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861107","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask the Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps she is taking to ensure that funds raised by foreign companies through initial public offerings in London do not finance companies under US and EU sanctions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132256","132256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861108","2018-03-16","Department for International Development","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 129962, on Democratic Republic of Congo: Politics and Government, what recent (a) meetings and (b) discussions the UK Government has had with the Government of the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132257","132257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861109","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to encourage people from low-income households to save towards their pensions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132258","132258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861110","2018-03-16","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 126732, what the evidential basis is for HMRC’s estimation that less than one per cent of families eligible to receive tax-free childcare will not be able to use online services or access the internet.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132259","132259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861111","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he held discussions with Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman of Saudi Arabia on the number of executions in that country.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132260","132260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861112","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in the Government of Ethiopia on the imprisonment of British citizen Andy Tsege in that country.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132261","132261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861113","2018-03-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy,  what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing in England a Transition Training Fund for employees in the fossil fuel industry to move to the renewable energy sector.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132262","132262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861114","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase the number of eligible child refugees who are able to enter the UK.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132263","132263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861115","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to publish a new five year AMR Strategy, and whether that strategy will include best practice on infection prevention and control, including hand hygiene compliance.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132264","132264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861116","2018-03-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will take steps to prohibit the scorching of moorland in areas surrounding rivers and lakes with a high flood risk.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132265","132265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861117","2018-03-16","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve hand hygiene compliance in hospitals to tackle antimicrobial resistance; and what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using health technology to improve such compliance.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132266","132266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861118","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department determines which refugees automatically get a National Insurance number as soon as they receive their refugee status; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132267","132267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861119","2018-03-16","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much National Lottery funding as been allocated to projects in (a) Leeds North West constituency and (b) West Yorkshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132268","132268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861120","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to work with police forces to reduce the risk to pedestrians and motorists during high-speed police persuits.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132269","132269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861121","2018-03-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children are included on universal credit claims in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132270","132270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861122","2018-03-15","Department for Education","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons Northern Ireland is not included in the Government's plans to increase the threshold for free school meals for universal credit claimants.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132271","132271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861123","2018-03-15","Treasury","2018-03-13","To ask the Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2017 to Question 112340 on Owner Occupation, if his Department will take steps to ensure that lenders take into account (a) council tax and (b) rental payments when assessing a borrower's creditworthiness.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132272","132272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861124","2018-03-16","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many houses rented by his Department are currently unoccupied.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132273","132273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861125","2018-03-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in the Azerbaijan Government on human rights in that country.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132274","132274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861126","2018-03-15","Attorney General","2018-03-13","To ask the Attorney General, how many successful prosecutions there have been for child sexual abuse-related offences in (a) Telford constituency and (b) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132275","132275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861127","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to prevent the grooming and sexual exploitation of vulnerable young women.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132276","132276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861128","2018-03-15","Home Office","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking with police forces across England to protect children from sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132277","132277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/861129","2018-03-16","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will permit people running in local council elections to put their electoral ward as their address for personnel security reasons.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132278","132278"
