"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046121","2019-01-24","Treasury","2019-01-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a preferential rate of duty for draught beer.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211303","211303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046122","2019-01-24","Treasury","2019-01-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will undertake a review into the effect of business rates on traditional pubs compared with new small bars.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211304","211304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046123","2019-01-28","Home Office","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Library briefing paper entitled Police Service Strength, published on 16 October 2018, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the level of crime of the 18 per cent reduction in the police workforce between 2010 and 2018.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211359","211359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046125","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of generic drugs his Department is currently paying a premium for due to shortage of supply.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211090","211090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046126","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for his policies of recent trends in the shortage of supply for drugs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211091","211091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046127","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to reduce the turnover of staff in his Department.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211127","211127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046128","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Institute for Government report of January 2019 entitled Moving On: The costs of high staff turnover in the civil service, for what reasons his Department has the second highest proportion of staff who left compared to other Departments in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211128","211128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046129","2019-01-28","Department for Education","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the introduction of T Levels on the number of people starting B Tech courses.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211129","211129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046130","2019-01-28","Department for Education","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the proportion of early years providers that are co-operatives.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211360","211360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046131","2019-01-28","Department for Education","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the specific funding needs of early-years settings in deprived communities where provision is almost exclusively local authority funded.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211361","211361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046132","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his oral contribution of 7 January 2019, Official Report, column 84, on NHS Long Term Plan, when he plans to write to the hon. Member for Greenwich and Woolwich with further details of the effect of changes to the market forces factor on funding for NHS Trusts in London to be allocated as part of the Plan.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211306","211306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046133","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the market forces factor on future funding for NHS Trust and Clinical Commissioning Groups in London.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211307","211307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046134","2019-01-28","Department for Education","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average annual per pupil cost is of a Pupil Referral Unit.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211308","211308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046135","2019-01-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the speech made in Halifax by the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State, Minister for the Northern Powerhouse and Local Growth, what plans he has for a secretary of state for the north of England.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211362","211362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046136","2019-01-28","Treasury","2019-01-22","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people subject to the 2019 Loan Charge were contractors who were contracted to (a) HMRC, (b) a Government Department, (c) a local authority and (d) another public sector body for some or all of the period of the contract the renumeration for which is now subject to the Loan Charge.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211081","211081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046137","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January to Question 208287, what figure of miles per train incident he will use to measure the performance of new trains as they are introduced onto the rail network between 2019 and 2021.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211309","211309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046138","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 February 2019 to Question 208287, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of train operating company training and planning with respect to (a) traincrew and (b) depots in order to facilitate the introduction of the new trains due onto the rail network between 2019 and 2021.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211310","211310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046139","2019-01-28","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent assessment he has made of the extent to which the EU has acted in accordance with its principle of sincere co-operation with the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211092","211092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046140","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport,pursuant to the Answer of 21 February 2019 to Question 208287, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of Network Rail’s investment and planning with respect to (a) signalling, (b) platforms and (c) power supply in order to facilitate the introduction of the new trains due onto the rail network between 2019 and 2021.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211311","211311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046141","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 February 2019 to Question 208287, what target for public performance measure he will use to determine the performance of new trains as they are introduced onto the rail network between 2019 and 2021.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211312","211312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046142","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 February 2019 to Question 208287, what plans he has to ensure (a) train operators and (b) Network Rail take the necessary steps to inform rail passengers about (i) different carriage layouts and (ii) door configurations (iii) platform embarkation/disembarkation points prior to the introduction of new trains due onto the rail network between 2019 and 2021.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211313","211313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046143","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 February 2019 to Question 208287, how many of the 11 train operating companies with routes into London offer (a) season tickets on smartcards, (b) flexible season ticket and (c) single leg ticketing.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211314","211314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046144","2019-01-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 31 of the Government's response, dated 27 March 2018 to the Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy Committee's report on the safety of electrical goods, HC920, whether the UK block on the fridge freezer Standard being accepted at European level is still in place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211093","211093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046145","2019-01-28","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that all Band D council taxpayers in Christchurch make the same financial contribution to the Bournemouth Christchurch and Poole Unitary Authority in 2019-2020 whether they live in Hurn, Burton or Christchurch; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211094","211094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046146","2019-01-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the Government's policy is on whether all UK citizens living in the EU after 29 March 2019 and in receipt of a UK state pension will benefit from annual uprating of state pensions irrespective of whether all EU countries make reciprocal arrangement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211095","211095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046147","2019-01-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reason guidance entitled, Taking your pet abroad if there's no Brexit deal, which was updated on 19 December 2018, was withdrawn on 11 January 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211096","211096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046148","2019-01-24","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps the Government is taking to promote peace and reconciliation in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211181","211181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046149","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Backbench Business debate on Mental Health First Aid of 17 January 2019, how the Government plans to make employers aware of examples of best practice concerning mental health in the workplace.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211315","211315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046150","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Backbench Business Committee debate on Mental Health First Aid on 17 January 2019, by what date the Government plans to put out to tender the contracts to provide mental health first aid training for a primary school staff member in each school.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211316","211316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046151","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 7 of the NAO Report of 18 January 2019 on NHS financial stability, what assessment his Department has made of the additional cost of agency staff as a result of staff shortages.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211317","211317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046153","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the research undertaken by The King’s Fund published on 30 December 2018, for what reason there has been a 13 per cent reduction in funding for sexual health services between 2013 and 2017 despite an increase in attendance for those services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211318","211318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046155","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the The Nuffield Trust paper published on 30 December 2018, what steps his Department is taking to address the increased likelihood that patients residing in deprived areas will be admitted as an emergency compared to those in less deprived areas.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211319","211319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046156","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the research entitled Sexual health services and the importance of prevention, published by the King’s Fund  30 December 2018, for what reason there has been a 13 per cent reduction in funding for those services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211320","211320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046157","2019-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Crown Post Offices across the UK are currently not providing post office services.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211321","211321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046160","2019-01-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department or its agencies maintain a list of local authorities in England that undertake separate food waste recycling collections.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211097","211097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046161","2019-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Malaysian Government on the Malaysian Prime Minister's (a) comments on the State of Israel of the Jewish people and (b) decision to ban Israeli swimmers from participating in sporting events in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211363","211363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046163","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the equitable allocation of funding to local authorities.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211182","211182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046164","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to clarify to local authorities their powers relating to unintended consequences to neighbouring parking spaces in relation to planning permission to install a dropped kerb.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211183","211183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046166","2019-01-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Greyhound welfare boosted through multi-million pound deal with gambling industry, published in January 2019, whether (a) a full audit of the requirements needed has been made in relation to capital costs for repairs to trainers' kennels and tracks and (b) all revenue expenses have been calculated to ensure that no greyhound suffers (i) on the track and (ii) through lack of a good home.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211184","211184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046168","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many deployments of British personnel from the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Royal Marines, (c) Army and (d) Royal Air Force there have been in each year of Operation Shader.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211185","211185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046169","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many deployments of British personnel from the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Royal Marines, (c) Army and (d) Royal Air Force there have been in each year of Operation Toral.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211186","211186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046171","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many deployments of British personnel from the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Royal Marines, (c) Army and (d) Royal Air Force there have been in each year of Operation Cabrit.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211187","211187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046172","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of incursions into British airspace by foreign military aircraft.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211188","211188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046174","2019-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of armed forces veterans in prison.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211189","211189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046175","2019-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received on the persecution of Christians in North Africa; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211190","211190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046176","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the re-basing of the British Army from Germany to the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211191","211191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046177","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of awarding the General Service Medal to British forces personnel who are serving on Operation Cabrit.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211192","211192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046178","2019-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of religious freedom in Iraq; and what steps the Government is taking to promote and protect the right to freedom of religion or belief in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211193","211193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1046803","2019-01-28","Cabinet Office","2019-01-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the work force in each (a) region and (b) local authority area is employed in the knowledge economy.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211822","211822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1041772","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many solar-based projects were on the Renewal Energy Planning Database in each quarter of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 208941","208941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043689","2019-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Ofsted's Freedom of Information request datasets 2017: Residential education provision as at 16 November 2017, published on 9 January 2019, when the most recent Ofsted inspection of the residential education provision at Medway Training centre took place; and what the effectiveness grade was of that assessment.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210035","210035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043690","2019-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Ofsted's Freedom of Information request datasets 2017: Residential education provision as at 16 November 2017, published on 9 January 2019, when the most recent Ofsted inspection of the residential education provision at Oakhill Secure Training centre took place; and what the effectiveness grade was of that assessment.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210036","210036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043691","2019-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Ofsted's Freedom of Information request datasets 2017: Residential education provision as at 16 November 2017, published on 9 January 2019, when the most recent Ofsted inspection of the residential education provision at Rainsbrook Secure Training centre took place; and what the effectiveness grade was of that assessment.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210037","210037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043710","2019-01-22","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help reform the education curricula in Pakistan to remove derogatory references to Ahmadis and other minorities.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210013","210013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1044958","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-21","What plans his Department has to maximise opportunities for qualified EU health workers to work in the NHS after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908665","908665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1044959","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-21","What recent assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on his Department’s priorities.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908667","908667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1044960","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-21","What steps he is taking to tackle domestic abuse.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 908668","908668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045467","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have applied for settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme pilot in (a) the UK and (b) Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210489","210489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045468","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been deemed eligible for settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme pilot in (a) the UK and (b) Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210490","210490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045469","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to extend the eligibility for settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme pilot for EU citizens that can financially sustain themselves but do not work.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210491","210491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045470","2019-01-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions the Government has met with (a) property development companies and (b) builders to discuss the leasehold law for existing leaseholders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210492","210492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045471","2019-01-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many responses the Government received from leaseholders in response to the Tackling unfair practices in the leasehold market consultation.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210493","210493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045472","2019-01-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have met with  property development companies during the consultation entitled Tackling Unfair Practices in the Leasehold Market.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210494","210494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045473","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will instruct the Serious Fraud Office to investigate the activities of Mukhtar Ablyazov, in relation to international money laundering.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210427","210427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045474","2019-01-23","Attorney General","2019-01-21","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of resources available to the Serious Fraud Office to undertake investigations into (a) Mukhtar Ablyazov and (b) other cases of large-scale international money laundering.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210428","210428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045475","2019-01-23","Attorney General","2019-01-21","To ask the Attorney General, what his powers are in relation to the Serious Fraud Office.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210429","210429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045476","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has powers to require the SFO to investigate cases of international money laundering.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210430","210430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045477","2019-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Khazakstani counterpart on the former banker Mukhtar Ablyazov who is accused of murder.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210431","210431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045478","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of the Republic of Kazakhstan on legal action against Mukhtar Ablyazov in relation to accusations of international money laundering.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210432","210432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045479","2019-01-24","Attorney General","2019-01-21","To ask the Attorney General, what representations the Serious Fraud Office has received on (a) Sudhir Choudhrie, (b) Bhanu Choudrie and (c) other related parties.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210433","210433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045480","2019-01-23","Attorney General","2019-01-21","To ask the Attorney General, what is the status of (a) SFO and (b) CPS investigations into (i) Sudhir Choudhrie, (ii) Bhanu Choudhrie and (iii) other related parties.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210434","210434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045481","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Unexplained Wealth Orders in tackling the illicit arms trade and related financial flows in London.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210435","210435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045482","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential use of Unexplained Wealth Orders against Sudhir Choudhrie and related parties.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210436","210436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045483","2019-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has consulted (a) parents, (b) employers and (c) other organisations as part of its internal review of workplace provision for parents of premature babies.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210495","210495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045484","2019-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's internal review of workplace provision for parents of premature babies, what steps his Department is taking to understand the experiences of those parents who live outside of London.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210496","210496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045485","2019-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Department's internal review of workplace provision for parents of premature babies, what steps his Department is taking to understand the experiences of employed fathers with babies receiving neonatal care.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210497","210497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045486","2019-01-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's Consultation on Protecting and Enhancing England’s Trees and Woodlands, if he will ensure that appropriate measures include local authority tree officers in the duty to consult.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210441","210441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045487","2019-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has made an assessment of whether military training activities constitute hazardous work as defined in Article 3(d) of ILO Convention 182 on the Worst Forms of Child Labour and its accompanying Recommendation 1902.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210553","210553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045488","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of civil servants in his Department who would be seconded to work in other Departments in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a negotiated deal.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210554","210554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045489","2019-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will list in full the UK's (a) financial and (b) legal obligations to the EU in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210681","210681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045490","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the effect a seasonal agricultural workers scheme would have on small labour providers.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210555","210555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045491","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to provide feedback to labour providers on the effectiveness of the Seasonal Agricultural Workers Pilot Scheme.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210556","210556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045492","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has to extend the Youth Mobility Scheme to additional non-EEA countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210557","210557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045493","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding for the proposed new Environmental Land Management Schemes after 2022.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210558","210558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045494","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2019 to Question 205247 on Drugs: refrigerators, what proportion of the (a) ambient storage pallets, (b) refrigerated storage pallets and (c) controlled drug storage pallets purchased as part of the Department's contingency planning in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal were manufactured in the UK.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210498","210498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045495","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the role of public advice in the effective delivery of the proposed new Environmental Land Management Schemes.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210559","210559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045496","2019-01-23","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many individual capital projects were awarded to (a) Northern Ireland, (b) Wales and (c) Scotland in (i) 2017, (ii) 2018 and (iii) 2019 to date by the Government; and what was the value of those projects.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210499","210499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045497","2019-01-23","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list the Government's Growth Deal announcements in (a) 2017, (b) 2018 and (c) 2019 that included allocated funding for (i) Northern Ireland, (ii) Wales and (iii) Scotland.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210500","210500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045498","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to (a) monitor and (b) mitigate the risks to patient safety that could result from a Serious Shortage Protocol and planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210457","210457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045501","2019-01-23","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 206432, whether he plans to hold a further route refinement consultation in relation to the High Speed Two Phase 2b route this year.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210561","210561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045502","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to tackle antisemitism against women.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210562","210562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045503","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Sara conference of 26 November 2018, what plans his Department has to encourage more Jewish women to participate in public life.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210563","210563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045504","2019-01-24","Women and Equalities","2019-01-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much funding her Department has allocated to interfaith projects in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210564","210564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045505","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of (a) gout, (b) rickets, (c) cholera, (d) tuberculosis, (e) malnutrition, (f) whooping cough, (g) measles, (h) scurvy, (i) typhoid, (j) scarlet fever, (k) diphtheria, (l) mumps, and (m) vitamin D deficiency have been reported by each NHS Trust since 2015.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210501","210501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045506","2019-01-23","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) Official Development Assistance and (b) other resources her Department has allocated to the rule of law initiative in Pakistan; and if she will publish her Department's human rights assessment of that initiative for 2018-2019.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210565","210565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045507","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on Zimbabwe’s application to re-join the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210566","210566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045508","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department is providing to (a) areas of Salford and (b) the UK who experience poor air quality.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210567","210567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045510","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional financial provision local authorities have received to help implement the Government’s commitment for 30 hours free childcare for working parents.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210569","210569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045513","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will release all documents relating to the 1984 strike at Cammell Lairds Shipyard and the subsequent arrest and imprisonment of 37 striking workers.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210572","210572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045514","2019-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have received an Imprisonment for Public Protection sentence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210573","210573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045515","2019-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners serving Imprisonment for Public Protection sentences have served time in excess of the original sentence.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210574","210574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045516","2019-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what comparative assessment he has made of the number of prisoners serving life sentences in (a) the UK (b) EU countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210575","210575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045517","2019-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question HL1673, what proportion of the UK's gas supply comes from Russia.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210576","210576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045518","2019-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, from which countries the UK imports gas; and what proportion of the UK gas supply each of those countries exports to the UK.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210577","210577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045519","2019-01-23","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to increase the safety of people that use bicycles.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210578","210578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045520","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether London North Eastern Railway sets the rates of pay for staff that are employed under its Rail Gourmet contract.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210502","210502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045521","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many contracts London North Eastern Railway holds with Rail Gourmet; and what the cost to the public purse is of each of those contracts.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210503","210503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045522","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the industrial relations of Rail Gourmet.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210579","210579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045523","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for  Transport, what steps London North Eastern Railway has taken to assess whether Rail Gourmet follow appropriate bullying and harassment policies.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210580","210580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045524","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time support staff in his Department work on (i) visa applications and (ii) asylum applications (A) in 2019 and (B) in 2009.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210581","210581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045525","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time decision-making staff deal with (i) visa applications and (ii) asylum applications (A) currently and (B) in 2009.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210582","210582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045526","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of his staff leave their respective posts on an annual basis; how many vacant posts there are in his Department; and what proportion of posts in his Department are currently vacant.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210583","210583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045528","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending free school meal eligibility to children in households in receipt of working tax credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210459","210459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045529","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are ineligible for free school meals as a result of their household, meeting the income threshold but is in receipt of working tax credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210460","210460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045530","2019-01-23","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a tax on the gambling industry to provide funding for people that have been made destitute as a result of gambling addiction.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210461","210461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045531","2019-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of universal credit are classified as gainfully self-employed.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210462","210462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045532","2019-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress her Department has made on ensuring that 50,000 claimants of universal credit are in gainful self-employment by Summer 2019.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210463","210463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045533","2019-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will increase the number recording devices available for benefits assessments in Wirral.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210464","210464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045534","2019-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of the availability of recording devices for benefits assessments on the (a) quality and (b) timeliness of those assessments.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210465","210465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045535","2019-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations has he made to the Government of Zimbabwe in relation to the political situation in that country; and what guidance he has issued to officials from his Department in that country on official contact with the Zimbabwean President.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210442","210442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045536","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many and what proportion of staff of his Department have undertaken the course on religious literacy run by his Department's Diplomatic Academy.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210584","210584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045537","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for which of his Department's posts is attendance on the religious literacy course run by his Department's Diplomatic Academy a mandatory part of pre-posting training.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210585","210585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045538","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to undertake a review of the provisions of the Vagrancy Act 1824.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210683","210683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045539","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 1.55 on page 31 of the NHS Long Term Plan, published in January 2019, when the development of the integration index will begin; which organisations will be consulted on the development of that index; what criteria will be used to determine metrics for inclusion in the index; when the index will be implemented; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210586","210586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045540","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum seeking children have been received by Nottinghamshire County Council under the voluntary national transfer scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210466","210466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045541","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum seeking children Nottinghamshire County Council has accepted under the voluntary national transfer scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210467","210467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045542","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will list the number of unaccompanied asylum seeking children each local authority area has accepted under the voluntary national transfer scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210468","210468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045543","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has for the future of the voluntary national transfer scheme for unaccompanied asylum seeking children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210469","210469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045544","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to promote inclusivity in religiously selective schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210470","210470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045545","2019-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-UK EU citizens have been refused universal credit on the basis that they do not have a right to reside in each month since January 2017.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210587","210587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045546","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service inquiries have been conducted when a serious injury has occurred on training exercise or selection event between 2013-2019;  and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210504","210504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045547","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what processes exits within his Department has put in place to ensure that the recommendations of service inquires are implemented; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210505","210505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045548","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) serious injuries and (b) deaths have occurred in training or selection events across all three armed services since 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210506","210506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045549","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what diseases were involved in the 27 disease-related deaths within the armed forces between 2000-2018 during exercises and training events; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210507","210507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045550","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that online vendors of medical (a) products and (b) treatments to consumers in the UK provide medical evidence that a (i) product and (ii) treatment delivers a clinical benefit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210684","210684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045551","2019-01-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to ensure that online fundraising platforms advertise prominently on their webstes, information on deductions from donations for fees charged.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210685","210685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045552","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Government of Venezuela on (a) upholding Article 233 of the Venezuelan Constitution and (b) recognising the president of the National Assembly of Venezuela Juan Guaidó, as the acting president of that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210686","210686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045553","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to provide independent legal guardianships for (a) unaccompanied and (b) trafficked children in (i) Oxfordshire and (ii) the UK.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210687","210687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045554","2019-01-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with community-led housing groups in (a) Oxfordshire and (b) England on the future of the Community Housing Fund in advance of the next Spending Review.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210688","210688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045555","2019-01-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the ability of community-led housing groups in receipt of awards from the Community Housing Fund to complete schemes by March 2020.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210689","210689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045556","2019-01-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will undertake a review of the requirement for community-led housing groups in receipt of awards from the Community Housing Fund intending to provide fewer than 100 homes to become Registered Providers.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210690","210690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045557","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the agreed budgeted FTE figure is for (a) his Department and (b) its agencies.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210508","210508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045558","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what additional funding for staff (a) his Department and (b) its agencies have received from EU exit funding.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210509","210509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045559","2019-01-24","Cabinet Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2018 to Question 208424 on Cybercrime, whether he has held any meetings with his European counterparts on the UK's continued partnership with the EU on cyber-related matters in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210691","210691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045560","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost to the public purse is of a mandatory reconsideration process for welfare benefits.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210588","210588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045561","2019-01-24","Cabinet Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many public sector computers are operating the Windows 7 operating system; and what preparations he has made for the forthcoming conclusion of Windows support for that system.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210692","210692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045562","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of applicants for personal independence payment have gone on to apply for mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210589","210589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045563","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of mandatory reconsideration cases for welfare benefits have resulted in the original ruling being overturned in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210590","210590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045564","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2018 to Question 162042 on Mental Health Services: Acute Beds, how many acute consultant-led child and adolescent mental health services beds there have been in the NHS in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210510","210510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045565","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July 2018 to Question 162042 on Mental Health Services: Acute Beds, how many acute consultant-led alcohol detoxification beds there have been in the NHS in England since 2009.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210511","210511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045566","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what planning restrictions for house building there are in areas of outstanding natural beauty.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210512","210512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045567","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what development restrictions there are in areas of outstanding natural beauty.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210513","210513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045568","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what protections there are to protect areas of outstanding natural beauty against new road building.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210514","210514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045569","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding his Department has allocated to support armed forces veterans living in (a) the Local Authority of St Helens and (b) the North West in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210591","210591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045570","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to St Helens Council to repair potholes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210592","210592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045571","2019-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department’s policy is on the provision of postal services where a post office has closed due to unforeseen circumstances.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210593","210593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045572","2019-01-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what funding his Department has allocated to arts and culture projects in St Helens Council in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210594","210594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045573","2019-01-23","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that UK aid is (a) effective, (b) transparent and (c) targeted at ending extreme poverty.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210471","210471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045574","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fire inspections have been carried out by fire and rescue services in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210443","210443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045575","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what studies his Department has commissioned into the long-term effect of abortion on (a) women’s health and (b) younger women's health including risk of future miscarriage, premature birth and suicide in the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210515","210515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045576","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to address concerns raised in the CQC Report on BPAS Merseyside published in January 2017.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210516","210516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045577","2019-01-24","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2018 to Question 173969, whether she now has the breakdown of the proportion of her Department's funding for family planning in Kenya which will be allocated to abortion provision; and what estimate she has made of the number of abortion procedures funded by previous DFID programmes in that country.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210517","210517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045578","2019-01-24","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 10 December 2018 to Question 199384 on developing countries: abortion, which states that DFID does not disaggregate figures solely relating to safe abortion procedures and the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 119743 on Marie Stopes International, which states that DFID has robust monitoring procedures, if she will request information from Marie Stopes International on the number of abortions funded by her Department in 2017.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210518","210518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045579","2019-01-24","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 10 December 2018 to Question 199384 on developing countries: abortion, which states that DFID does not disaggregate figures solely relating to safe abortion procedures and the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 119743 on Marie Stopes International, which states that DFID has robust monitoring procedures, what steps she is taking to ensure accountability of UK funding to Kenya for sexual and reproductive health and rights.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210519","210519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045580","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of local authorities that allow their tenants to keep pets.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210595","210595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045581","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the number of housing associations that allow their tenants to keep pets.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210596","210596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045582","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the levels of attainment inequality in primary education across different local education authority areas of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210472","210472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045583","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of levels of attainment inequality in secondary education across different local education authority areas of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210473","210473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045584","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of adults receiving local authority-run social care services in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210474","210474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045585","2019-01-23","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of traffic collision fatalities attributed to heavy goods vehicles.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210693","210693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045586","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to (a) decrease the total number of knife crimes and (b) support programmes that aim to educate young people of the dangers and consequences of carrying such weapons.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210694","210694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045587","2019-01-23","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the Rail, Maritime, and Transport Union RMT to resolve the dispute with Northern on train guards.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210695","210695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045588","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the continuation of UK clean air policy as provided for in EU Directive 2008/50/EC after the UK leaves the EU on 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210696","210696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045589","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the fair distribution of the recently announced additional £2 billion further funding for mental health; and whether his Department has plans to ensure that Southport benefits from such funding.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210697","210697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045590","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to evaluate the effect of cladding remediation work on residents in tower blocks where such work is taking place.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210698","210698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045591","2019-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with his counterparts in the Governments of Greece and the former Yugoslav Republic of Macedonia on the Prespa Agreement, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210475","210475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045592","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many (a) social sector and (b) private sector tower blocks do not currently have cladding due to ongoing remediation works.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210699","210699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045593","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the health-related effects on residents affected by cladding remediation work.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210700","210700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045594","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the financial effect on residents affected by cladding remediation work in relation to heating costs.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210701","210701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045595","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which locations in Belfast lough are suitable for berthing HMS Queen Elizabeth.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210702","210702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045596","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of people with autism in care homes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210597","210597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045597","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UN Working Group on Arbitrary Detention Opinion 28/2016 adopted in August 2016 calling for the immediate release by Iran of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe is legally binding.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210520","210520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045599","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people with chronic pain in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210598","210598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045600","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) RAF and (b) Government-funded subcontracted personnel work in Saudi Arabia to provide technical and maintenance support to the Saudi Arabian air force.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210521","210521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045601","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of HMS Queen Elizabeth visiting Belfast lough.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210703","210703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045602","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which UK-supplied military equipment has been used by Saudi Arabia in Yemen since March 2015.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210522","210522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045603","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the extent to which Saudi Arabian-supplied arms are reaching Al Qaeda or other terrorist groups in Yemen.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210523","210523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045604","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British ground forces are operating in Syria; and with which countries those forces are embedded.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210524","210524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045605","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of reports that Turkey has trained and recruited former Islamic State militants to aid its operations in Afrin.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210525","210525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045606","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to which South American countries the UK provides military training.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210526","210526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045607","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 208362 on Buildings: Insulation, how many of the 1,421 non-aluminium composite material cladding samples submitted to the Building Research Establishment for testing were (a) metal composite material cladding, (b) high-pressure laminate cladding and (c) expanded polystyrene insulation in external wall insulation systems.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210599","210599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045608","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with Ecuadorian officials on the matter of Julian Assange since November 2018; and on what dates those discussions were held.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210527","210527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045609","2019-01-23","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the value was of bilateral aid provided to (a) Bolivia, (b) Colombia, (c) Ecuador and (d) Peru in each year since 2015; and what plans he has for such spending in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210528","210528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045610","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of students studying STEM-related courses in further education colleges in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210476","210476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045611","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to update its document, Teachers’ standards: Guidance for school leaders, school staff and governing bodies, last updated in June 2013; and for what reason care experienced children are not identified as a cohort of children in Standard 5 of that document.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210600","210600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045612","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of amending the universal credit payment system so that claimants paid on a four-weekly basis for part-time or casual work do not have their benefit payment substantially reduced as a result of receiving two work payments four weeks apart in one calendar month.","Biography information for Bill Grant","Bill Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210704","210704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045613","2019-01-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many public swimming pools were closed in the North West in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210529","210529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045614","2019-01-23","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what unforeseeable events led his Department to award contracts for additional shipping freight capacity under Regulation 32 of The Public Contracts Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210601","210601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045615","2019-01-23","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department used to identify new entrants to the market in the absence of an invitation to tender being published when awarding contracts for additional shipping freight capacity under Regulation 32 of The Public Contracts Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210602","210602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045616","2019-01-23","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department used to select existing cross channel operators in the absence of an invitation to tender being published when awarding contracts for additional shipping freight capacity under Regulation 32 of The Public Contracts Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210603","210603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045617","2019-01-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the number of smaller energy companies who have been unable to participate in the Warm Home Discount scheme as a result of having fewer than 250,000 customers.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210705","210705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045618","2019-01-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that smaller companies in the energy supply market are eligible to participate in the Warm Home Discount scheme.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210706","210706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045619","2019-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Employment Support Allowance (ESA), how many and what proportion of people with the most severe health conditions and disabilities with lifetime award of ESA have been placed in the ESA Support Group or Universal Credit Limited Capability for Work and Work Related Activity category and are exempt from repeat assessments; what steps his Department has taken to ensure individuals with lifelong illnesses will not be required to be reassessed; and for what reasons decision-makers are allocating timeframes for the award of ESA for applicants whose ESA 50 forms have not been reviewed.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210604","210604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045620","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the new prostate cancer radiotherapy will be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210605","210605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045621","2019-01-23","Cabinet Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have a diagnosis of myeloid leukaemia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210606","210606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045622","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when MRI-guided thermal laser ablation treatment will be made available on the NHS to tackle brain tumours.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210607","210607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045623","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with an eating disorder in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210608","210608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045624","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with inflammatory bowel disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210609","210609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045625","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people by (a) age group and (b) gender have been diagnosed with hand arthritis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210610","210610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045626","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for GP appointments.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210611","210611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045627","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have been diagnosed with dyslexia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210612","210612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045628","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that pre-eclampsia is diagnosed in the early stages of pregnancy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210613","210613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045629","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to promote the early diagnosis of dementia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210614","210614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045630","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to promote eating well to help prevent depression.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210615","210615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045631","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to prioritise the reduction of waiting times in the NHS.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210477","210477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045632","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with sector representatives on the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210616","210616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045633","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made on the health-related effects of electromagnetic fields.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210707","210707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045634","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to enhance animal welfare standards as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210617","210617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045635","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the consistency between B1 English tests carried out at different centres.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210708","210708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045636","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fly-tipping incidents there have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210618","210618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045637","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many fixed penalty notices were issued by local authorities for environmental protection crimes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210619","210619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045638","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question 202737 on HIV Infection, when his Department plans to make an announcement on the next steps in reducing new HIV transmissions in England.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210444","210444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045639","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2018 to Question 202737 on HIV Infection, what steps his Department is taking to inform the next steps in reducing new HIV transmissions in England.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210445","210445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045640","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what new initiatives his Department plans to bring forward to tackle environmental crimes.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210620","210620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045641","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on police forces cancelling rest days for the after 29 March 2019 as part of contingency plans for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210621","210621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045642","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the minimum staffing levels required by police forces after 29 March 2019 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210622","210622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045643","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness of reducing noise emissions from motorways by reducing speed limits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210478","210478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045644","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Midlands Connect on its proposed expressway from Leicestershire to Gloucestershire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210479","210479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045645","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with dairy farmers in Northern Ireland on the (a) cost of production and (b) the sale price of milk.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210530","210530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045646","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bringing forward regional salary thresholds for non-UK workers to allow businesses to recruit employees in line with regional economic circumstances after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210709","210709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045647","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to reduce risks for farmers at work.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210531","210531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045648","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to support farmers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210532","210532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045649","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to advise farmers on the risk of livestock theft.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210533","210533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045650","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people had their visas to visit the UK revoked in 2018.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210534","210534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045651","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what sums his Department received in payments for visa applications in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210535","210535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045652","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2018 to Question 185531 on Germany: Thalidomide, what progress he has made on making it easier for UK Thalidomide victims to apply for compensation from the Contergan Foundation.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210710","210710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045653","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the DVLA on testing blood glucose levels using flash and continuous glucose monitoring technology for the purposes of assessing fitness to drive; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210480","210480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045654","2019-01-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on the consultation to include additional ivory species in the Ivory Act 2018, and whether he has set a date for this consultation to be published.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210623","210623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045655","2019-01-23","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that disabled people have suitable transport access when seeking employment opportunities.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210711","210711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045656","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress he has made on the roll-out of the pilot Seasonal Agricultural Workers Scheme.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210712","210712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045657","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to provide further support for veterans with mental health issues.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210713","210713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045658","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many Potential Pilot Operators responded to the request for information for the pilot Seasonal Agricultural Workers Scheme.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210714","210714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045659","2019-01-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has he made on the Local Full Fibre Networks Programme in rural locations throughout Scotland.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210715","210715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045660","2019-01-23","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department is having with the devolved Administrations on government support for high street businesses.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210716","210716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045661","2019-01-23","Women and Equalities","2019-01-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of her Department’s work to ensure that women are not held back in the workplace.","Biography information for Kirstene Hair","Kirstene Hair","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210717","210717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045662","2019-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to lay an amended Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme before the House during the current Parliamentary session.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210624","210624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045663","2019-01-24","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure  that the Government of Zimbabwe distributes UK bilateral aid fairly through civic and representative community organisations.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210718","210718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045664","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children who have special educational needs and disability in West Sussex; and how many of those children are supported with formal education, health and care plans.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210437","210437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045665","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the waiting time is for an education, health and care plan application to be processed in West Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210438","210438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045666","2019-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Office for Product Safety and Standards is taking to review fireworks regulations.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210719","210719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045667","2019-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of the UK negotiating a permanent UK-EU customs union.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210720","210720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045668","2019-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on contingency planning for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210721","210721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045669","2019-01-24","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterpart on extending Article 50.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210722","210722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045670","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress the Driving Vehicle Licensing Agency is making to update its guidance on the use of new monitoring technologies for people with diabetes.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210446","210446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045671","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to hold discussions with the National Centre for Rural Health and Care on rural health issues.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210625","210625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045672","2019-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sex offenders convicted in each of the last five years were sentenced to a (a) non-custodial sentence, (b) custodial sentence of less than six months, (c) custodial sentence of 6-12 months, (d) custodial sentence of one-five years, (e) a custodial sentence of 5-10 years and (f) a custodial sentence of more than 10 years by sexual offence type.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210626","210626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045673","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2019 to Question 206886 on Leyla Guven, when UK Government officials last raised the case of Leyla Güven with the Turkish government; and what assurances the Government it has sought from the Turkish Government on her welfare.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210723","210723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045674","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions (a) his Department and (b) the NHS have had with their counterparts in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland in relation those administration's policies on tackling rural health inequalities.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210627","210627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045675","2019-01-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the UN on the Government's commitment to combat torture in advance of the UN's forthcoming review of Vietnam's implementation of the UN Convention against Torture.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210447","210447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045676","2019-01-23","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has plans to allocate funding for research into acting/extended-release (a) injectable and (b) implantable forms of Antiretroviral drugs to help (a) a patients adherence to treatment and (b) decrease HIV drug resistance.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210448","210448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045677","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the programme to vaccinate adolescent boys against human papillomavirus will start in September 2019.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210628","210628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045678","2019-01-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 206860, on Stonewell: National Lottery, what processes are in place to ensure that providing information for key public sector institutions does not constitute lobbying or break any rules on political funding.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210629","210629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045679","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an estimate of the number of boys who would be eligible to receive the HPV vaccination under a catch-up programme for cohorts since 2008.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210630","210630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045680","2019-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps his Department has taken to support high street retailers.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210536","210536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045681","2019-01-23","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has taken to support better cross-border cooperation to tackle the human rights situation in South Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210481","210481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045682","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) recruit and (b) retain GPs in (i) Medway, (ii) Kent and (iii) England.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210537","210537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045683","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many specialist chemistry supply teachers are available in each region of England.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210631","210631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045684","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the National FGM Centre.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210632","210632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045685","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has for the funding arrangements of the National FGM Centre after 2020.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210633","210633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045687","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that young people with mental health problems can access treatment on the NHS.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210635","210635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045688","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people asked for a mandatory reconsideration of their universal credit application in 2018; and how many of those reconsiderations led to a different outcome.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210538","210538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045689","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the average cost of supporting an FGM victim in the UK, including the provision of (a) mental health support, (b) safeguarding costs, (c) medical support, and (d) other associated costs.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210636","210636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045690","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people asked for a mandatory reconsideration of their personal independence payment application in 2018; and how many of those reconsiderations led to a different outcome.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210539","210539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045691","2019-01-24","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 208357, for what reasons his Department delayed the closure of the HMRC office in Peterlee.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210724","210724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045692","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps the Government has taken to develop a cross-departmental strategy on tackling FGM.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210637","210637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045693","2019-01-24","Department for International Trade","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether an Aardvark JSFU is a controlled good.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210725","210725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045694","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has plans to allocate future funding to the National FGM Centre.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210638","210638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045695","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to allocate future funding to the National FGM Centre.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210639","210639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045696","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons the NHS Long Term Plan did not include commitments on waiting time targets for (a) treatment in Accident & Emergency, (b) routine operations and (c) cancer treatment.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210640","210640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045697","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of General Electric about the future of its factory in Rugby.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210540","210540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045698","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the national security implications of General Electric transferring its operations from Rugby to France.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210541","210541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045699","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the outcome of his Department's consultation entitled Calorie labelling for food and drink served outside of the home; and what the timetable is for implementing the recommendations from that consultation.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210542","210542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045700","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of staff in her Department including those employed in executive agencies and non-ministerial Departments declared a disability in 2017-18.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210482","210482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045701","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of staff in his Department including those employed in executive agencies and non-ministerial Departments declared a disability in 2017-18.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210483","210483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045702","2019-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of staff in his Department including those employed in executive agencies and non-ministerial Departments declared a disability in 2017-18.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210484","210484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045703","2019-01-23","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff in his Department including those employed in executive agencies and non-ministerial Departments declared a disability in 2017-18.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210485","210485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045704","2019-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prison staff exposed to new psychoactive substances during the course of their work in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210641","210641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045705","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last met with representatives of General Electric.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210543","210543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045706","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many young people have been educated in temporary alternative provision in (a) London and (b) England in the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210642","210642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045707","2019-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, on what date the Government was made aware that Hitachi was considering withdrawing from the Wylfa Newydd project.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210643","210643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045708","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment on the security implications of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210644","210644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045709","2019-01-23","Department for International Trade","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether decisions of the Trade Remedies Authority on the imposition of a trade defence measure will take effect immediately or within a specified number of days.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210449","210449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045710","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contingency plans his Department has made to ensure that people wanted by the UK criminal justice system can be extradited to the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210645","210645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045711","2019-01-24","Wales Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the free flow of goods at the ports of Holyhead and Pembroke in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210646","210646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045712","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum cases remain unresolved after 52 weeks.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210647","210647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045713","2019-01-23","Department for International Trade","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the timeframe will be in which the Trade Remedies Authority will be required to conclude proceedings in respect of a WTO Article 5 investigation.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210450","210450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045714","2019-01-24","Department for International Trade","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether trade unions will be defined as interested parties in trade remedies investigations once the UK has an independent trade policy.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210451","210451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045715","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure it is able to process large numbers of applications from EU citizens applying for settled status under the EU settlement scheme.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210544","210544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045716","2019-01-23","Department for International Trade","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the number of British companies in EU supply chains in which a party has an outstanding trade complaint being (a) considered and (b) investigated by the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210452","210452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045717","2019-01-23","Department for International Trade","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the volume of (a) legislation and (b) regulations required to be (i) introduced and (ii) amended to give effect to the work of the Trade Remedies Authority; and how many of those items will be brought forward in secondary legislation.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210453","210453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045718","2019-01-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2018 to Question 193467 on Tech City UK: Ethnic Groups and Females, how many BAME members are on the Executive team of Tech City; and what proportion of the technical roles within the organisation are held by women.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210648","210648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045719","2019-01-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of the business founders receiving funds from Tech City were female in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210649","210649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045720","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the public consultation on the Government’s Healthy Start scheme he plans to publish.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210486","210486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045721","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when Health Education England's Mental Wellbeing Review of NHS staff and learners will be published; and how the recommendations of that review will be incorporated into the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210650","210650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045722","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure the continued effective operation of the Fisheries Protection patrol in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210651","210651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045723","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when (a) HMS Medway and (b) HMS Trent will be completed for deployment.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210652","210652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045724","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure the continued effective patrolling of the (a) North Sea, (b) English Channel, (c) Western Approaches, (d) Bristol Channel and (e) Irish Sea; and what plans he has to increase the number of vessels based at the South Atlantic station.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210653","210653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045725","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what time limits apply to a claim of compensation arising from an injury on duty.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210654","210654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045726","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what time limits apply to a claim of compensation arising from an injury sustained while training.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210655","210655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045727","2019-01-24","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate the Government has made of the level of non-compliance with judgements in small claims courts; and what plans he has to strengthen the powers of courts to enforce judgements in small claims cases.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210656","210656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045728","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Malaysian counterpart since that country’s decision to ban Israeli swimmers from participating in the Tokyo 2020 Paralympic Qualifiers it is due to host in July 2019.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210726","210726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045729","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has issued a standardised specification for the job description for teaching assistants.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210657","210657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045730","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children with Educational, Health and Social Care plans are from (a) Black, (b) Asian and (c) Minority Ethnic backgrounds.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210658","210658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045731","2019-01-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support small rural businesses to become more (a) productive and (b) competitive.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210439","210439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045732","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has allocated to the Extended Schools Programme in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210659","210659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045733","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has allocated to the Troubled Families programme in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210660","210660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045734","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his Answer of 2 July 2018 to Question 158171, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the response of Abacus Land 4 Ltd to tenants of Heysmoor Heights, Liverpool who have been charged in relation to replacement of cladding following the Grenfell Tower disaster; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210545","210545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045735","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of immigration detainees entered the immigration detention estate for more than 24 hours in Quarter 3 of 2018 as a result of prior decisions to detain those detainees.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210454","210454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045736","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of immigration detainees who are (a) foreign national offenders (b) other detainees had been in immigration detention for (i) 28 days or fewer and (ii) over 28 days at the end of quarter 3 of 2018.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210455","210455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045737","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the Every Child Matters programme on social mobility.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210661","210661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045738","2019-01-24","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Simple Assessment tax demands his Department has issued in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210546","210546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045739","2019-01-24","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people aged (a) over 65, (b) over 70, (c) over 75, (d) over 80, (e) over 85 and (f) over 90 have been issued with a Simple Assessment of their tax liability in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210547","210547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045740","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 205952 on Offences against Children: Internet, whether be plans to bring forward proposals for statutory regulation to enforce safety rules on social media platforms.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210662","210662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045741","2019-01-24","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the establishment is of the Royal Navy Reserve; and how many reservists there are at each rank in the Royal Naval Reserve.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210440","210440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045742","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 205952 on Offences against Children: Internet, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Facebook’s use of technology to proactively detect grooming on Instagram, WhatsApp and other sites owned by Facebook.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210663","210663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045743","2019-01-24","Cabinet Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the 2017 Annual Report of the Investigatory Powers Commissioner has been submitted to the Prime Minister.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210548","210548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045744","2019-01-23","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2019 to Question 205952 on Offences against Children: Internet, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Snapchat’s use of technology to proactively detect grooming on their site.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210664","210664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045745","2019-01-23","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has plans to allocate funding to the introduction of a UK hospital ship.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210727","210727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045746","2019-01-24","Cabinet Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Prime Minister plans to publish the 2017 Annual Report of the Investigatory Powers Commissioner.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210549","210549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045747","2019-01-23","Department for International Development","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, on how many occasions (a) she and (b) officials in her Department have held discussions with counterparts in the Ministry of Defence on the potential procurement of a UK hospital ship.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210728","210728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045748","2019-01-24","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the letter setting out a person's tax liability under the Simple Assessment procedure includes an address to which a cheque can be sent in settlement of that liability.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210550","210550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045749","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with the US Department of Defense on (a) US hospital ships and (b) lessons for (i) procurement and (ii) specification of a UK hospital ship.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210729","210729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045750","2019-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a UK hospital ship would be classed as a complex warship and eligible for a restricted tender for UK shipyards for its construction.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210730","210730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045751","2019-01-24","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to ensure people who are not online are able to process communications on tax liabilities under the Simple Assessment procedure.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210551","210551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045752","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of immigration detainees who are (a) foreign national offenders (b) other detainees had been in immigration detention for (i) 28 days or fewer and (ii) over 28 days at the end of quarter 2 of 2018.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210456","210456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045753","2019-01-24","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will waive any fines incurred by elderly people assessed as having a liability under the simple assessment tax liability procedure who have difficulty in dealing with HMRC online.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210552","210552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045754","2019-01-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent (a) discussions and (b) meetings (i) he, (ii) Ministers of his Department and (iii) officials of his Department have had with trade unions representing employees of Jaguar Land Rover.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210665","210665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045755","2019-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has plans to update the training module on Fibromyalgia issued by her Department on 18 April 2018; and whether her Department has made an assessment of (a) the level of compliance with the training module by benefits assessors and (b) the effectiveness of the guidance in identifying suffers of Fibromyalgia.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210666","210666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045756","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 208869 on Channel Ferries: Freight, how many companies have made representations to the Government.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210667","210667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045757","2019-01-23","Department for Transport","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to The Motor Vehicles (Driving Licences) (Amendment) Regulations 2017, when the DVLA plans to update its guidance on diabetes testing and driving to allow the testing of interstitial fluid.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210487","210487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045758","2019-01-24","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether solar panels installed on domestic properties have a right to light protection under planning legislation.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210668","210668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045759","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU citizens have already paid £65 to apply for Settled Status and will be refunded.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210731","210731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045760","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has received representations on the potential effect of the Mental Capacity (Amendment) Bill on the liberty of people living with (a) dementia, (b) brain injuries and (c) learning difficulties.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210488","210488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045761","2019-01-23","Treasury","2019-01-21","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the (a) finances and (b) usage of the football pools of the reduction in pools duty from 15 per cent to 10 per cent.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210669","210669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045762","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the training for designated senior leads for mental health includes training in awareness of speech, language and communication needs and their links to mental health.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210670","210670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045763","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to (a) identify and (b) tackle children’s communication difficulties under its Children in Need policy.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210671","210671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045764","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to allow speech and language therapists to train as approved mental capacity professionals.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210672","210672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045765","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the implications are for his policies of the conclusion in the paper entitled, Mental Health of Children and Young People in England, 2017, published by NHS Digital in November 2018 that children with a mental disorder were five times more likely to have speech or language problems.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210673","210673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045766","2019-01-24","Home Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether EU citizens that do not have five years continual residency who are (a) married to a UK citizen and (b) have other long periods of residency will be entitled to settled status after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210674","210674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045767","2019-01-24","Department for Education","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) children and (b) children eligible for free school meals reached a Good Level of Development at age five in Newcastle upon Tyne Central constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210675","210675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045768","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Backbench Business Committee debate on Mental Health First Aid on 17 January 2019, Official Report columns 1366-1395, what steps the Government has taken to implement each of the recommendations of the Farmer-Stevenson review.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210676","210676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045770","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Backbench Business Committee debate on Mental Health First Aid on 17 January 2019 Official Report columns 1366-1395, by what date the Government plans to ensure that the recommendations of the Farmer-Stevenson review that are not yet implemented are implemented.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210677","210677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045771","2019-01-28","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Backbench Business Committee debate on Mental Health First Aid on 17 January 2019, Official Report columns 1366-1395, by what date the Government plans to ensure that at least one member of staff in each primary and secondary school has received mental health first aid training.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210678","210678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045772","2019-01-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions with reference to the Backbench Business Committee debate on Mental Health First Aid on 17 January 2019 Official Report columns 1366-1395, what steps her Department is taking to ensure employers are aware of the the Health and Safety Executive's guidelines on existing requirements to consider mental health alongside physical health when undertaking a first aid needs assessment, published in November 2018.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210679","210679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045773","2019-01-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Backbench Business Committee debate on Mental Health First Aid on 17 January 2019, Official Report columns 1366-1395, by what date the Government plans to have implemented the Thriving at Work mental health recommendations in (a) the NHS and (b) the Civil Service.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210680","210680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045895","2019-01-28","Cabinet Office","2019-01-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons (a) the Civil Service Widows Pension Scheme rules include the 1972 Section in which premium deductions are taken should an individual marry after retirement and (b) the premium deduction is not paid out to children following the death of the policyholder; and whether MyCSP retains premium deductions.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211200","211200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043081","2019-01-21","Women and Equalities","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what progress her Department has made on the consultation on a renewed access to elected office fund.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209832","209832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043169","2019-01-21","Department for International Trade","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, who the members of the reconvened Board of Trade are; and what assessment he has made of the most significant achievements of that Board for the Scottish economy have been since June 2017.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209848","209848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043686","2019-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an estimate of the total debts owed by domestic energy suppliers that have ceased trading in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210011","210011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043687","2019-01-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward legislative proposals on the testing of microchips intended for implantation in humans.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210034","210034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043688","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children under the age of 18 have been denied UK citizenship in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210012","210012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043692","2019-01-23","Department for International Development","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the scale of anti-vaccination fake news in (a) Pakistan and (b) Afghanistan.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210005","210005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043693","2019-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many incidents of potential concern on violations of international humanitarian law in Yemen his Department has tracked in each month since January 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210006","210006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043694","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 May 2018 to Question 142518 on employment support allowance, what guidance her Department has issued to GPs on the provision of medical notes to claimants of employment and support allowance that are appealing her Department's decision on their claim.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210007","210007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043695","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of nurses and non-clinical staff paid under £30,000 per annum who will be able to continue to work in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210018","210018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043696","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release Funding announced to train 900 new children’s social workers dated 8 January 2019, how many applications his Department’s tender 142495-2018 received.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210038","210038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043697","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release Funding announced to train 900 new children’s social workers dated 8 January 2019, when the supplier information day was for the tender 142495-2018; and what the attendance at that event was.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210039","210039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043698","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of spending on social work education.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210040","210040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043699","2019-01-23","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2018 to Question 196094, whether Interserve has submitted its living will.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210019","210019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043700","2019-01-22","Scotland Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the total value of exports of goods and services from Scotland under WTO rules was in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210041","210041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043701","2019-01-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of ministerial oversight of the Competition and Markets Authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210020","210020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043702","2019-01-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the cost has been of the Competition and Markets Authority investigation into (a) Viagogo and (b) other secondary ticket sites.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210021","210021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043703","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which agencies and bodies outside of Government will have access to the data of non-UK EU citizens who register under the settled status scheme.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210042","210042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043704","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to protect the data of non-UK EU citizens who register under the settled status scheme.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210043","210043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043705","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what purposes the data of non-UK EU citizens who register under the settled status scheme will be shared with organisations outside his Department.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210044","210044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043706","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the status is of negotiations between Roche and NHS England on access to ocrelizumab for people with primary progressive MS on the NHS; and if he will take steps to help the two parties reach an agreement to deliver access to that drug.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210045","210045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043707","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with (a) Roche and (b) NHS England on introducing a managed access scheme for ocrelizumab to made available for people living with primary progressive MS.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210046","210046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043709","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to encourage the growth of free range dairy herds.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210009","210009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043711","2019-01-22","Department for International Development","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made on improving girls’ access to education throughout the world.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210047","210047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043712","2019-01-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to introduce priority housing status for all homeless survivors of domestic abuse in the forthcoming Domestic Abuse Bill.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210048","210048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043713","2019-01-23","Department for International Trade","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many compliance audits have been undertaken in relation to the Open Individual Export Licences granted to BAE Systems (Operations) Ltd on (a) 5 December 2013 for Storm Shadow air-to-surfaces missiles, (b) 5 March 2014 for Paveway Guided Bombs and (c) 21 August 2018 for Brimstone air-to-surface missiles for which Saudi Arabia was the end user country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210049","210049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043714","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's target timetable is for applicants of personal independence payments to be notified of the decision on their application; and what (a) proportion and (b) number of applications met that target in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210050","210050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043715","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of infrastructure spending on the Network Rail Wales route.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210022","210022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043716","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the difference between Intercity Express Train service speeds on Network Rail routes between (a) Bristol and London and (b) the Severn Tunnel and Swansea.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210051","210051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043717","2019-01-24","Department for Transport","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the feasibility of giving the Welsh Government shared oversight over the specification and operation of all rail franchises operating in Wales.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210052","210052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043718","2019-01-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what contingencies are in place to protect against drug price increases in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210053","210053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043719","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of transferring responsibility for horse welfare from the British Horse Racing Authority and to an independent body to help ensure the welfare of racehorses.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210054","210054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043720","2019-01-23","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) males and (b) females working for GCHQ in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210014","210014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043721","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money has been spent from the public purse on the running of the office of the Independent Case Examiner for each available year; and what her Department's plans are for the future funding on that office.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210055","210055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043722","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the Independent Case Examiner's ability to process complaints in a timely manner.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210056","210056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043723","2019-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's target timetable is for complaints to the Independent Case Examiner to be concluded; and what (a) proportion and (b) number of complaints met that target in each year for which information.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210057","210057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043724","2019-01-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of steps his Department has taken to support high streets in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210015","210015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043725","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of checks in place to ensure that schools do not discriminate as part of the admissions process accepting students with special educational needs or disabilities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210016","210016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043726","2019-01-23","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what dates he has held discussions with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport on the role of Huawei in the UK's Critical National Infrastructure.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210058","210058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043727","2019-01-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, on what dates he has held discussions with the National Cyber Security Centre on the role of Huawei in the UK's Critical National Infrastructure.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210059","210059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043728","2019-01-23","Treasury","2019-01-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government's review of the loan charge is planned to (a) seek external evidence about, (b) evaluate all aspects of and (c) be able to recommend any changes to the loan charge.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210060","210060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043729","2019-01-23","Treasury","2019-01-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that members of the public can contribute to the review of the 2019 Loan Charge.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210061","210061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043730","2019-01-23","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Interserve has submitted its living will.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210023","210023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043731","2019-01-23","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether it has plans to publish its document entitled The role of communication in rebuilding political trust.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210024","210024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043732","2019-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of India on non-refoulement of Rohingya refugees.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210017","210017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043733","2019-01-23","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to publish information on project Santiago.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210025","210025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043734","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on instances in which the Education and Skills Funding Agency has issued a contract that does not include provisions that any payment due from the contracting authority to the contractor under the contract is to be made no later than the end of a period of 30 days from the date on which the relevant invoice is regarded as valid and undisputed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210026","210026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043735","2019-01-23","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants have been employed in the Public Procurement Review Service in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210027","210027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043736","2019-01-22","Treasury","2019-01-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2018 to Question 172591 on Mozambique: Loans, what steps he is taking with UK and Mozambican authorities to ensure that London-based banks and individuals concerned are held to account for undisclosed loans to state owned companies.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210062","210062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043737","2019-01-22","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2018 to Question 197338 on Pubic Sector: Billing, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of using a business' ability to meet the core standard of paying 95 per cent of invoices within 60 days over the previous two six month periods to determine whether those businesses will be able to pay their sub-contractors within 30 days as required by the Public Contract Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210028","210028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043738","2019-01-22","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2018 to Question 197334 on public sector: procurement, how many of those spot checks carried out by the Procurement Review Service were targeted at a contracting authority that had previously not complied with a part of public procurement regulations.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210029","210029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043739","2019-01-22","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many cases have been raised with the Procurement Review Service broken down by (a) contracting authority and (b) contractor in each year since that service was established.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210030","210030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043740","2019-01-22","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has received any complaints on not paying invoices within the 30 day period required by statutory guidance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210031","210031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043741","2019-01-23","Department for International Development","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 11 May 2018 to Question 141671, what assessment her Department has made of whether the Palestinian Authority has resumed directly paying salaries to those serving sentences in Israeli jails for terrorist offences.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210004","210004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043742","2019-01-23","Cabinet Office","2019-01-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2019 to Question 205837 on British-Irish Council, what that agreed date is for the next Summit of the British-Irish Council.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210032","210032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043743","2019-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January to Question 208315 on universal credit, which stakeholders her Department is working with to design the managed migration process.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210033","210033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045509","2019-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce air pollution in (a) Salford and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210568","210568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045511","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authorities have participated in the National Assessment and Accreditation Scheme for Social Workers.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210570","210570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045512","2019-01-23","Department for Education","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many social workers have volunteered to participate in the National Assessment and Accreditation Scheme for Social Workers.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 210571","210571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1045891","2019-01-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural affairs, what his Department's policy is on individuals busking with dogs.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 211197","211197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042998","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the consequences will be for EU citizens who do not register for EU settled status.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209787","209787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1042999","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans he has in place to assist people with iPhones in (a) accessing and (b) using the settled status registration app.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209788","209788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043000","2019-01-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the trends in the levels of penalties charged by private parking operators.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209789","209789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043001","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much was spent in each of the main categories of NHS commissioner spending as recorded by NHS England by (a) NHS England and (b) clinical commissioning groups in aggregate in (i) 2014-15, (ii) 2015-16, (iii) 2016-17 and (iv) 2017-18.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209790","209790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043002","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much is planned to be spent in each of the main categories of NHS commissioner spending as recorded by NHS England by (a) NHS England and (b) clinical commissioning groups in aggregate in 2018-19.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209791","209791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043003","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many GP practices in England are (a) a member and (b) not a member of a primary care network.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209792","209792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043004","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will list all GP practices in England and the primary care network they are a member of.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209793","209793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043005","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department made of ETS’s proposal to provide English language tests for overseas students before awarding a contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209727","209727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043006","2019-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of reports of recent violence in Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209728","209728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043007","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many bidders other than ETS were awarded contracts to provide English language tests for overseas students on behalf of his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209729","209729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043008","2019-01-21","Cabinet Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 16 January 2019, Official Report, column 1269, if she will meet with (a) leaders (b) senior members and (c) Members of the Legislative Assembly from political parties represented in the Northern Ireland Assembly that are not represented in the House of Commons.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209851","209851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043009","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total value is of contracts between his Department and Tata Consultancy Services for work on the Disclosure and Barring Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209739","209739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043010","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of occasions on which referrals to the Disclosure and Barring Service have been set aside for over (a) one, (b) six, and (c) nine months.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209740","209740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043011","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total value is of contracts between his Department and Swiss Post Solutions for work outsourced from the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209741","209741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043012","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total value is of contracts between his Department and Swiss Post Solutions for work outsourced from the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209742","209742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043013","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the quality of service provided by Swiss Post Solutions on work outsourced from the Disclosure and Barring Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209743","209743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043014","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of occasions on which sensitive information has been attached to incorrect case files by Swiss Post Solutions in the course of work outsourced from the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209744","209744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043015","2019-01-21","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of whether the tool to redact sensitive case information used by the Disclosure and Barring Service is fit for purpose.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209745","209745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043016","2019-01-22","Cabinet Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the change in the number of deaths caused by an excess of prescription drugs being the primary cause was between 2011 and 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209755","209755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043017","2019-01-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish its evaluation of shared parental leave.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209794","209794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043018","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to publish his consultations on the proposals in the resources and waste strategy.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209795","209795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043019","2019-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has plans to prohibit the consumption of dog meat in the UK.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209852","209852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043020","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will (a) clarify the objectives of the changes to the aspect of the National Planning Policy Framework where design and style have a value and (b) make it his policy that (i) appropriateness should be defined by clarifying local and commercial interests, (ii) the views of the community should be taken into account and (iii) through early engagement expectations should be clarified where previously it was explicit that decisions and policies should not impose style nor taste.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209796","209796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043021","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support the improvement of local authority-run services for children with special educational needs and disabilities.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209746","209746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043022","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether policy, guidance and coding restrictions on style will be (a) based on the outcomes of a transparent, explicit and comprehensive consultation with the relevant local authority and (b) expressed in clear and unambiguous terms.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209797","209797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043023","2019-01-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) EU representatives on holding European parliamentary elections in the UK in 2019 in the event that the UK's withdrawal from the EU is delayed.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209747","209747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043024","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 3.92 of the NHS Long Term Plan, whether four-week waiting time targets for community mental health teams will include services for adults with eating disorders.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209853","209853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043025","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 3.92 in the NHS Long Term Plan, when four-week waiting time targets for community mental health teams will begin.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209854","209854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043026","2019-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment his Department has made of the number of courts that require repair work.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209748","209748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043027","2019-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political and security situation in Mali; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209749","209749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043028","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 206828 on Channel Ferries: freight, whether essential (a) food supplies and (b) medicines will be prioritised through those ports by the Government in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and on what basis ferry ports will be prioritised.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209798","209798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043029","2019-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason under universal credit (a) statutory maternity pay is classed as earnings and subject to partial disregard and (b) maternity allowance is classed as income with the full payment taken into account.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209855","209855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043030","2019-01-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many people have been supported through the cyber security critical national infrastructure apprenticeship.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209856","209856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043031","2019-01-21","Department for International Development","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of anti-vaccination fake news on polio (a) vaccination and (b) eradication efforts in (i) Pakistan and (ii) Afghanistan.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209731","209731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043032","2019-01-22","Department for International Development","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with social media platforms on ending the spread of anti-vaccination fake news relating to polio vaccination and eradication programmes in (a) Pakistan and (b) Afghanistan.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209732","209732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043033","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for support in urgent and exceptional circumstances under the Windrush scheme have been (a) made and (b) accepted; how much has been paid from the public purse to people whose applications have been accepted; and how many applications have been rejected on the ground that the applicant was a British national.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209799","209799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043034","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason it was decided to give responsibility for the Wales and Borders rail franchise to the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209756","209756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043035","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the 38 owner-occupiers in Chalfont St Giles who were sent a Land Interest Questionnaire by HS2 in the last three months will now have their land or part of their land taken on a temporary basis; for what period of time that land will be required; and what compensation will be offered.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209725","209725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043036","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is taking steps to ensure that British Members of Parliament are able to engage adequately with the Welsh Government on Wales and Borders train services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209757","209757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043037","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to table A2 of the statistical release Information on looked after children at both national and local authority levels for the financial year 2016-17, how many of the 8,830 looked-after children who were cared for in a friends and family foster placement on 31 March 2017 had also been in (a) an unrelated foster placement, (b) another family and friends care placement, (c) a children's home and (d) other provision for looked-after children.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209733","209733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043038","2019-01-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on Huawei; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209750","209750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043039","2019-01-22","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to table A2 of the statistical release Information on looked-after children at both national and local authority levels for the financial year 2017-18, how many of the 9,720 looked-after children who were cared for in a friends and family foster placement on 31 March 2018 had also been in (a) an unrelated foster placement, (b) another family and friends care placement, (c) a children's home and (d) other provision for looked-after children.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209734","209734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043040","2019-01-22","Department for Transport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish revised estimates for the (a) additional costs identified through the ground investigations for phase two of High Speed Two and (b) construction costs of phase two.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209726","209726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043041","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many historical arrears cases there were at the beginning of the migration of cases from the Child Support Agency to the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209800","209800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043042","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much of the £4.5 billion allocated to community care in five years' time as part of NHS England’s Long Term Plan is planned to be spent on provisions for people diagnosed with Alzheimer’s disease and dementia.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209801","209801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043043","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to have secured parity of esteem for dementia with cancer, cardiovascular disease, stroke care, mental health and other conditions supported by NHS England’s Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209802","209802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043044","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many historical arrears cases have been transferred from the Child Support Agency to the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209803","209803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043045","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to work with the wider NHS, the voluntary sector, developers and individuals to create a range of digital services to support people with (a) dementia and (b) similar specific conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209804","209804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043046","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the enhanced health in care home model set out in NHS England's Long Term Plan will support people affected by dementia.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209805","209805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043047","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many arrears-only cases are registered with the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","Mr Jacob Rees-Mogg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209806","209806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043048","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS England Long Term Plan, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the use of the Electronic Frailty Index in a proactive population health approach focused on moderate frailty accounts for the needs of people living with dementia.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209807","209807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043049","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS England Long Term Plan, how NHS England plans to continue working closely with (a) the Alzheimer’s Society and (b) other voluntary sector organisations to extend the society's Dementia Connect programme which offers a range of advice and support for people following a dementia diagnosis.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209808","209808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043050","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS England Long Term Plan, what discussions he has had with NHS England on how it plans to support the Dementia Connect programme which offers a range of advice and support for people following a dementia diagnosis.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209809","209809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043051","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the merits of participation by women’s organisations in the UN-led peace consultations on Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209735","209735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043052","2019-01-21","Scotland Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in February 2019.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209857","209857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043053","2019-01-21","Department for International Trade","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the highest hourly rate was that (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms-length bodies paid for legal advice in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209810","209810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043054","2019-01-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his oral contribution of 7 January 2019, Official Report column 80, when he plans to publish the local provision funding increases for the first year of the NHS Long Term Plan.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209758","209758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043055","2019-01-21","Department for Transport","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the highest hourly rate was that (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms-length bodies paid for legal advice in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209811","209811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043056","2019-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the highest hourly rate was that (a) her Department and (b) each of her Department's arms-length bodies paid for legal advice in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209812","209812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043057","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the highest hourly rate was that (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms-length bodies paid for legal advice in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209813","209813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043058","2019-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209814","209814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043059","2019-01-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the highest hourly rate was that (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms-length bodies paid for legal advice in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209815","209815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043060","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Ofsted grades the Army Foundation College in Harrogate on the same basis as civilian colleges for the age group.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209858","209858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043061","2019-01-22","Home Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Minister of State for Immigration plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow East of 27 November 2018, reference DL2002.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209859","209859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043062","2019-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which activities undertaken by under-18s in the armed forces constitutes hazardous work as defined under Article 3 (d) of ILO Convention 182 and its accompanying Recommendation 190.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209860","209860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043063","2019-01-21","Northern Ireland Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the highest hourly rate was that (a) her Department and (b) each of her Department's arms-length bodies paid for legal advice in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209816","209816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043064","2019-01-21","Scotland Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the highest hourly rate paid for legal advice was by (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's arms length bodies in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209817","209817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043065","2019-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions Minimising and Managing Physical Restraint (MMPR) has been used in each secure institution which uses it in each year for which information is available by reason for the use of MMPR.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209818","209818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043066","2019-01-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether desktop studies can still be used  in lieu of tests as a route to compliance for combustible materials on high-rise hotels.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209819","209819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043067","2019-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of self-harm have been recorded in relation to children in each secure institution that holds children during each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209820","209820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043068","2019-01-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether desktop studies can still be used in lieu of tests as a route to compliance for combustible materials on high-rise offices.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209821","209821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043069","2019-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time was that a child spent in the segregation unit in each secure institution that holds children in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209822","209822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043070","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the longest length of time was that a child spent in the segregation unit in each secure institution that holds children in each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209823","209823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043071","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hours on average per day young people spent unlocked from their rooms in each secure training centre in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209824","209824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043072","2019-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress on reopening the Sanaa-Hodeidah road in Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209736","209736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043073","2019-01-21","Department for Education","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to replace access to funding universities receive from the Erasmus+ programme for UK students undertaking placements abroad before 2020 in the event that the UK leaves the EU on 29 March 2019 without a deal.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209825","209825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043074","2019-01-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether systems incorporating combustible materials are still able be approved for use by desktop studies.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209826","209826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043075","2019-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on reports from the UN Committee on the Elimination of Racial Discrimination on the treatment of Uighur Muslims in Xinjiang.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209759","209759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043076","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many band three to five prison officers at each high-security institution had (a) less than three years' experience and (b) three or more than three years’ service in (i) 2010 and (ii) 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209827","209827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043077","2019-01-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the compatibility of the Mental Capacity Act (Amendment) Bill with the United Nations Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209828","209828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043078","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many assaults on staff in each year from 2010 were (a) recorded at each high-security institution and (b) involved staff at high-security institutions with less than three years’ experience.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209829","209829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043079","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many uses of force in each year from 2010 were (a) recorded at each high-security institution and (b) involved staff with less than three years’ experience.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209830","209830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043080","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of self-harm were recorded at each high-security institution in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209831","209831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043082","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of homicide were recorded at each high-security institution in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209833","209833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1043083","2019-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many band three to five prison officers at each high-security institution left within three years of starting their role in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 209834","209834"
