"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176338","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average proportion of working age people unemployed for longer than (a) 12 months and (b) two years was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222453","222453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176339","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) has been and (b) is expected to be raised by the annual charge for non-domiciled individuals who elect to pay tax on the remittance basis and who have lived in the UK for (i) seven of the last nine years, (ii) 12 of the last 14 years and (iii) 17 of the last 20 years in (A) 2012-13, (B) 2013-14, (C) 2014-15, (D) 2015-16 and (E) 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222440","222440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176340","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies of the findings of research by the London School of Economics and Political Science and the universities of Manchester and York entitled the Coalition's Social Policy Record: Policy, Spending and Outcomes 2010-2015 relating to families with children under five years of age.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222483","222483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176341","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications for 65-plus Guaranteed Growth Bonds requested the full allowances of (a) £10,000 per bond, (b) £20,000 for both bonds and (c) £40,000 for combined holders.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222470","222470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176342","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was paid in tax relief on private pensions for (a) higher rate taxpayers, (b) additional rate tax payers in each of the last five years up to the most recent period for which records are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222515","222515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176343","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department plans to happen to the ownership of the 65-plus Guaranteed Growth Bonds in the event of a bondholder's death.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222505","222505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176344","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria were used to determine eligibilty for the 65-plus Guaranteed Growth Bonds; and for what reason the qualifying age was set at 65 years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222506","222506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176345","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many higher-rate and additional rate taxpayer purchasers of 65-plus Guarantee Growth Bonds have declared the interest payable on these bonds to HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222608","222608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176346","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of businesses invoicing VAT on goods and services discounted for early payment in cases when the discount is not subsequently applied.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222368","222368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176347","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the cost to businesses of the requirement to double invoice VAT on goods and services which have been discounted for early payment.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222367","222367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176348","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what value of 65-plus Guaranteed Growth Bonds have been sold to applicants from (a) Northern Ireland, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) England.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222448","222448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176349","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average value was of 65-plus Guaranteed Growth Bonds issued to applicants for (a) 1-year and (b) 3-year bonds; and how many applicants applied for both of those bonds.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222447","222447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176350","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222595","222595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176351","2015-02-02","Church Commissioners","2015-01-28","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what discussions the Commissioners have had with Church of England bishops on the laying on of hands during the consecration of (a) female and (b) male bishops; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222446","222446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176352","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department last published data about the extent of deprivation in different parts of the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222450","222450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176353","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage local authorities to protect allotments from development.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222454","222454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176354","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221426, what mechanisms will be put in place to enable the public to hold the city-region Mayor to account other than at election time; and whether he plans to consult the public about those arrangements.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222436","222436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176355","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on ensuring that applications for planning consent make clear who the developer is.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222386","222386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176356","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015, to the hon. Member for Wolverhampton North East to Question 220713, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people residing in outbuildings in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222609","222609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176357","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what arrangements he plans to put in place to allow the public to hold the appointed eleventh leader of the Greater Manchester city-region to account before the anticipated elections in 2017.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222553","222553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176358","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222568","222568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176359","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what protections for residual amenity space are provided by the regulatory regimes for (a) planning, (b) environmental permitting and (b) health and safety.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222538","222538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176360","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of introduction of Florrie's law on total cumulative costs charged to leaseholders in (a) Tower Hamlets, (b) London and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222507","222507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176361","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to reply to the letter dated 22 October 2014 from the right hon. Member for Berwick upon Tweed about planning appeals in Warkworth, Northumberland.","Biography information for Lord Beith","Sir Alan Beith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222509","222509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176362","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have approved planning applications for rabbit farms in each of the last five years for which data is available; and how many such farms were approved by each local authority in that period.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222510","222510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176363","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's communications budget has been for each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222583","222583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176364","2015-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions the Future High Streets Forum has met in the last 12 months; on what dates each such meeting took place; and which of the group's members were in attendance on each such occasion.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222559","222559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176365","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221428, whether the people of Greater Manchester will have a say in determining the salary for the city-region Mayor created by the devolution agreement.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222438","222438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176366","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221428, whether he plans to set an upper salary limit for the city-region Mayor of Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222439","222439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176367","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221428, whether the preliminary equality screening has begun and when the results of that screening will be published.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222437","222437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176369","2015-02-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his Department's communications budget has been for each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222565","222565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176370","2015-02-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222569","222569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176371","2015-02-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220723, whether that advertising campaign was funded from the BBC topslice.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222383","222383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176372","2015-02-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2015 to Question 221249, on broadband, what data has been made available to his Department on where the budget was spent.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222384","222384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176373","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will discuss with the Commonwealth War Graves Commission measures to safeguard overseas war graves from desecration by Islamist extremists.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222360","222360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176374","2015-02-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the cost has been of hiring externally contracted staff at the National Gallery during the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222441","222441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176375","2015-02-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the cost of hiring externally contracted staff at the National Gallery during the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222442","222442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176376","2015-02-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations he has received about plans to hire externally contracted staff at the National Gallery.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222443","222443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176377","2015-02-02","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has been informed by the National Gallery of any proposals to vary the level of the Gallery's services to the public during the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222444","222444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176378","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2015, Official Report, column 687W, whether his Department is carrying out a strategic review of the use and effects of remotely piloted air systems in Afghanistan following the end of combat operations in that country.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222432","222432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176379","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 21 October 2014, Official Report, column 63WS, on the Middle East, how many UK Reaper aircraft are conducting missions in Syria; and whether authorisations have been sought for any missions by those aircraft other than for surveillance.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222433","222433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176380","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his French counterpart concerning the deployment of UK Reapers in support of Operation Barkhane.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222428","222428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176381","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015, to Question 220027, if he will place in the Library a copy of the terms of reference agreed at the meeting of the NATO Reaper MQ-9 Users Group.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222431","222431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176382","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220792, whether any personnel from Squadron 39 are currently embedded with US forces.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222435","222435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176383","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220793, for how long his Department intends to store Reapers in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222434","222434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176384","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220792, whether his Department has identified any defect in the Reapers returned to the UK.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222427","222427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176385","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222570","222570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176386","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222584","222584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176387","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to notify the relatives of service men and women killed in Afghanistan of its plans for a memorial service at St Paul's Cathedral.","Biography information for Lord Murphy of Torfaen","Paul Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222546","222546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176388","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 220012, how many RAF personnel are deployed in Afghanistan; and what the (a) rank, (b) squadron and (c) function is of each RAF officer stationed in that country.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222429","222429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176389","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 9 December 2013, Official Report, column 70W, and with reference to Regulatory Article 1600, published by the Military Aviation Authority on 19 January 2015, whether his Department will fly remotely piloted aircraft systems in the UK outside danger areas or segregated airspace.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222430","222430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176390","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will introduce a compensation scheme for civilian casualties in Iraq.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222465","222465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176391","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the US sought permission from his Department for consolidation at RAF Croughton following that country's European Infrastructure Consolidated Review.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222466","222466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176392","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department plans to inform the families of military personnel killed in Afghanistan of the decision to hold a memorial service at St Paul's Cathedral in March 2015.","Biography information for Lord Murphy of Torfaen","Paul Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222528","222528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176393","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual maintenance and running costs are for each of the golf courses included in his Department's estate.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222514","222514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176394","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many registered voters there were in each parliamentary constituency in Warrington on (a) 17 February and (b) December 2014; and what proportion of the population eligible to vote that figure represented in each constituency on each of those dates.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222387","222387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176395","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of how many and what proportion of students in Warrington North constituency were registered to vote on 1 December 2014.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222403","222403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176396","2015-02-02","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-28","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015, Question 221159, if he will make an assessment of the number of 17 year old attainers who transferred from the household electoral register to individual electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222611","222611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176397","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the total value is of the contract awarded by her Department to the New Schools Network.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222555","222555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176398","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the contract awarded by her Department to the New Schools Network expires.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222556","222556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176399","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the average unit cost of a designated Sure Start Children's Centre.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222557","222557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176400","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what annual funding her Department has allocated the New Schools Network in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222558","222558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176401","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222585","222585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176402","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222571","222571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176403","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222572","222572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176404","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether planning guidance provides for a specific approach to planning for hydraulic fracturing in a) national parks, (b) the Broads, (c) areas of outstanding natural beauty and (d) world heritage sites.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222552","222552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176405","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222586","222586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176406","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many families with children in (a) Halton and (b) the UK are currently in debt to their energy companies.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222549","222549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176407","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information his Department holds about the arrangements by which hydraulic fracturing companies publish evidence of how their commitments under the industry's community engagement charter scheme have been meet each year.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222541","222541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176408","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect of depth limits for hydraulic fracturing on (a) fugitive emissions and (b) safety.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222540","222540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176409","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether he has the power to overrule objections to hydraulic fracturing consents from (a) the Health and Safety Executive, (b) the Environment Agency, (c) Natural England and (d) the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222530","222530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176410","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many families with children in (a) Birmingham, Hall Green constituency, (b) Birmingham and (c) the UK are currently in debt to their energy supplier.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222488","222488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176411","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the Government plans to update the Social and Environmental Statutory Guidance to the Gas and Electricity Market Authority.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222467","222467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176412","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households with children in (a) Denton and Reddish constituency, (b) the North West and (c) the UK are in debt to their energy suppliers.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222468","222468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176413","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to prioritise support for families with children when they fall behind on their energy bills in (a) the North East and (b) Newcastle upon Tyne.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222408","222408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176414","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the payments made under the non-domestic renewable heat incentive scheme have been at the projected lower levels during the summer months since the start of the scheme.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222390","222390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176415","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many inspectors are employed by OFGEM to ensure compliance with the non-domestic renewable heat incentive; for how many such inspectors OFGEM has made budgetary provision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222391","222391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176416","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it is a requirement that an environmental impact assessment be prepared for all hydraulic fracturing developments.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222625","222625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176417","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has the power to overturn a decision on an application for hydraulic fracturing in (a) national parks, (b) the Broads, (c) areas of outstanding natural beauty and (d) world heritage sites.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222626","222626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176418","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what grounds current planning guidance provides for not refusing an application for hydraulic fracturing in (a) national parks, (b) the Broads, (c) areas of outstanding natural beauty and (d) world heritage sites.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222627","222627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176419","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria must be met for a person to be eligible to perform the role of independent well examiner for a hydraulic fracturing development.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222602","222602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176420","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what notice and publicity requirements relate to the planning and environmental permitting process for hydraulic fracturing.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222542","222542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176421","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the number of full-time equivalent staff required by the Environment Agency in order for it to perform its role as a regulator of hydraulic fracturing in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16, (c) 2016-17, (d) 2017-18, (e) 2018-19 and (f) 2019-2020.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222599","222599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176422","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what criteria are used to determine whether a developer is required to undertake a habitats regulation assessment for a proposed hydraulic fracturing project adjacent to a (a) special conservation area, (b) special protection site, (c) site of special scientific interest, (d) area of outstanding natural beauty and (e) Ramsar site.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222603","222603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176423","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what criteria are used to determinte whether a developer of a proposed hydraulic fracturing project is required to undertake a habitats regulation assessment.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222604","222604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176424","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what techniques to minimise methane emissions (a) are and (b) does she plan to be a requirement of environmental permits for hydraulic fracturing.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222605","222605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176426","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's communications budget was in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222497","222497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176427","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for East Londonderry of 4 December 2014 to Question 217167, if she plans to publish the study on the scientific evidence for the welfare of game birds reared in cages.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222501","222501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176428","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222496","222496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176429","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what length of time baseline monitoring of methane in groundwater for hydraulic fracturing developments must take place before consent for such developments may be issued.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222529","222529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176430","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what criteria are used to determine whether a developer is required to undertake a habitats regulation assessment for a proposed hydraulic fracturing project within a (a) special conservation area, (b) special protection area, (c) site of special scientific interest, (d) area of outstanding natural beauty and (e) Ramsar site.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222531","222531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176431","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she has consulted the Committee on Climate Change on the effect of hydraulic fracturing on water scarcity in the next (a) five, (b) 10 and (c) 20 years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222539","222539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176432","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what national standards apply for the baseline monitoring of methane in groundwater for hydraulic fracturing developments.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222533","222533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176433","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what national standards apply for the baseline monitoring of air quality for hydraulic fracturing developments.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222534","222534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176434","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what criteria are used to determine the different categories of groundwater risk; and how the risks posed to groundwater by hydraulic fracturing sites are determined.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222536","222536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176435","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what mechanisms exist to require that information on chemical substances and their maximum concentrations is included in the environmental permit for each hydraulic fracturing development.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222543","222543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176436","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, by what criteria hydraulic fracturing development may be judged a significant risk to groundwater.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222537","222537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176437","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what length of time baseline monitoring of air quality for hydraulic fracturing developments must take place before consent for such developments may be issued.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222535","222535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176438","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what mechanisms exist to require that information on the (a) total daily discharge of hydraulic fracturing fluid into ground and (b) fluid taken off site for disposal is included in the environmental permit for each hydraulic fracturing development.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222544","222544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176439","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the impact of hydraulic fracturing on water scarcity in the next (a) five, (b) 10 and (c) 20 years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222545","222545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176440","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has made to the European Commission on publication of its communication on Building a Sustainable European Food System.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222547","222547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176441","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the government of Burma has taken steps to implement the declaration to end sexual violence which it signed in June 2014.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222511","222511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176442","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222587","222587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176443","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222573","222573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176444","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222518","222518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176445","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220624, what the powers vested in the three treaty Guarantor powers are in relation to the bodies with which they consult, by Article IV of the 1960 Treaty of Guarantor in respect of Cyprus.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222485","222485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176446","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220624, what powers are available to the UN-facilitated settlement process to intervene in respect of the confiscation of property owned by Turkish Cypriots in Vasiliko in order to facilitate oil and gas explortation in Northern and Southern Cyprus.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222486","222486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176447","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the US Commission on International Religious Freedom's Report, Burma: Religious Freedom and Related Human Rights Violations are Hindering Broader Reforms, published in November 2014.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222458","222458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176448","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Venezuelan counterpart on the human rights situation in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222459","222459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176449","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to improve trade between the UK and emerging markets in Latin America; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222460","222460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176450","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met with his Ecuadorian counterpart; what the content of discussions at that meeting was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222461","222461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176451","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met with his Guyanese counterpart; what the content of discussions at that meeting was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222462","222462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176452","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met with his Chilean counterpart; what the content of discussions at that meeting was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222463","222463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176453","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met with his Brazilian counterpart; what the content of discussions at that meeting was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222464","222464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176454","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Egyptian government about the case of Karim Ashraf Mohamed al-Banna.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222392","222392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176455","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of possible Iranian reactions to increased sanctions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222393","222393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176456","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what advice his Department provides to UK citizens employed in academic institutions internationally on (a) countries in which there is a terrorist threat and (b) what to do in the event of a terrorist attack.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222400","222400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176457","2015-02-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who, other than Ministers of the Crown and members of the Diplomatic Service, has been sent from the UK to represent the Government at inaugurations of foreign Heads of State and government since May 2010; and what the cost was of that representation in each such case.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222394","222394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176458","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Iranian counterpart in support of the American-Iranian pastor, Saeed Abedini, who is imprisoned in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222362","222362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176459","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on allegations that rape is being used as a tool by the police in Egypt to suppress activists; and if he will make representations on this matter to his counterpart in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222364","222364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176460","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of Laos about (a) the case of Pastor Sompong Supatto and (b) freedom of religion.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222409","222409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176461","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise at the UN the issue of a co-ordinated response to the threat of Boko Haram in North Eastern Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222410","222410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176462","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the adequacy of his Department's current guidance to NHS trusts on how to monitor hand hygiene levels.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222412","222412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176463","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether decisions on whether to publish documents relating to the contracting of NHS services to private providers (a) may and (b) may not prioritise commercial confidentiality over the public interest; and what the rationale for those prioritisation arrangements is.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222415","222415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176464","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the extent to which commercial insurance companies are capable of covering the risks associated with private health providers carrying out surgery on NHS contracts.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222417","222417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176465","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to reduce the importation and use of artificial sweeteners.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222455","222455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176466","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms are in place for the NHS to recover the costs of performing revision surgery when repairing the damage caused by failed surgery carried out by outsourced private providers.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222416","222416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176467","2015-02-03","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prosecutions have taken place in the UK as a result of horsemeat being sold as beef in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222457","222457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176468","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that UK aid workers who return from work abroad receive effective and accessible healthcare from their local GP.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222363","222363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176469","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue guidance to NHS maternity services to check routinely for tongue-tie routinely in newborn babies.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222378","222378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176470","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many newborn babies were diagnosed with tongue-tie in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222379","222379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176471","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to relevant healthcare professionals on the diagnosis of tongue-tie in infants.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222380","222380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176472","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the provision of infant feeding specialists on the early detection and treatment of tongue-tie in infants.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222381","222381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176473","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effect on mortality rates of the provisions of off-patent drugs outside their licensed indications in cases where research supports the use of those drugs.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222377","222377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176474","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with Public Health England on a national strategy for increasing public awareness of cervical cancer symptoms.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222372","222372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176475","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will launch targeted campaigns on cervical screening in regions where cervical screening rates have fallen below the national average.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222373","222373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176476","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group last met to discuss Translarna; when it will next meet to discuss that drug; and whether approval for its use can be granted before 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222374","222374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176477","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what further discussions his Department has had with (a) NHS England and (b) the Health and Social Care Information Centre on the inclusion of musculoskeletal conditions in the care.data programme.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222473","222473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176478","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of uptake of care plans amongst people with arthritis; and what steps his Department plans to take to widen access to care planning.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222472","222472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176479","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department plans to measure the effect of the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme on access to medicines.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222494","222494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176480","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will conduct a study to determine the effect on access to medicines of the additional allocations made to NHS England as a result of rebate payments under the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222495","222495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176481","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the value of rebate payments from the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme was to (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland in each quarter that scheme has operated.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222493","222493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176482","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff in his Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222519","222519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176483","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with hearing loss are able to access audiology service regardless of where they live.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222489","222489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176484","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with a musculoskeletal condition have a care plan.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222471","222471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176485","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the development of a clinical guideline and quality standard for hearing loss.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222487","222487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176486","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which department or team within NHS England is responsible for the development and implementation of proposals for a national molecular diagnostic testing service in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222475","222475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176487","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England plans to publish full details of the decisions it makes during the prioritisation exercise for new specialised services to be commissioned in 2015-16","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222476","222476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176488","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will work in partnership with charitable organisations to increase awareness of stem cell donation among young people.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222477","222477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176489","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential for mindfulness to improve pain management.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222478","222478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176490","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2015 to Question 221072, if he will conduct a survey of the practice of clinical commissioning groups in respect of capping the total number of Improving Access to Psychological Therapies treatment sessions they offer.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222619","222619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176491","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222588","222588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176492","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222574","222574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176493","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the effectiveness of the individual funding request process for cancer medicines.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222561","222561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176494","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221512, what the delayed discharges referred to in the Answer by local authority area are.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222551","222551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176495","2015-02-04","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) applications to the Cancer Drugs Fund and (b) individual funding requests for cancer medicines were approved in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222562","222562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176496","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of progress on reducing hepatitis C-related liver cancers and mortality since the 2004 Action Plan for hepatitis C.","Biography information for Conor Burns","Conor Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222492","222492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176497","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many practices in (a) Halton and (b) England had vacancies for GPs on 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222550","222550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176498","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2015 to Question 221072, if he will make it his policy to collect data on the number and proportion of patients who have (a) diabetes, (b) anxiety disorder, (c) depression, (d) schizophrenia and (e) personality disorders and are not being treated.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222624","222624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176499","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2015 to Question 221072, what recent assessment he has made of the ability of local authorities to reduce the alcohol dependent population and to help more people recover from alcohol problems.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222622","222622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176500","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2015 to Question 221072, how many and what proportion of opiate users were receiving treatment in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222623","222623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176501","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2015 to Question 221072, if he will make it his policy to collect data (a) on the average time a GP spends with a patient with a mental illness and (b) which may be used to monitor the quality of relationships between doctors and patients in other ways.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222621","222621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176502","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015, to the hon. Member for Barnsley Central to Question 221804, when his Department plans to complete the prevalence survey on children with mental health problems.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222610","222610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176503","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers are involved in the monitoring and investigation of child sex crimes online.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222598","222598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176504","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the contribution of Lord Bates of 28 October 2014, Official Report, column 1083 House of Lords, what the reasons are for the time taken to implement her Department's consultation on mandatory reporting of abuse of children and vulnerable adults.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222631","222631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176505","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222575","222575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176506","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222589","222589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176507","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress operation Nexus has made on tackling offending by foreign nationals.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222491","222491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176508","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff in her Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222520","222520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176509","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how she plans to incorporate the views of charities and children's services into the terms of reference of her Department's consultation on mandatory report of abuse of children and vulnerable adults.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222503","222503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176510","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how she plans to incorporate the views of hon. Members and key stakeholders into the terms of reference of her Department's consultation on mandatory report of abuse of children and vulnerable adults.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222504","222504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176511","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many reports of harassment have been recorded by police forces in England and Wales in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222420","222420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176512","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of safety deposit boxes across the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jenny Willott","Jenny Willott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222397","222397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176513","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with (a) banks, (b) solicitors and (c) other providers on the availability of safety deposit boxes across the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jenny Willott","Jenny Willott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222398","222398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176514","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with suppliers of safety deposit facilities on ensuring that the annual cost of hiring and using such facilities is kept at a reasonable level; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jenny Willott","Jenny Willott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222399","222399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176515","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what further steps she is taking to protect UK citizens from telephone scammers.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222361","222361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176516","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of illegal migration between the UK and the Republic of Ireland in either direction have been detected by Operation Gull in each of the last 10 years; what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Operation Gull; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222365","222365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176517","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many traffic police officers were employed in each police force area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222445","222445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176518","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department allocated to War on Want in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222413","222413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176519","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects War on Want promotes on behalf of her Department.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222414","222414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176520","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many applications for funding more than £5 million she has received for approval for projects in (a) total, (b) Sierra Leone, (c) Liberia, (d) Guinea and (e) Nigeria in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) the financial year to date.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222401","222401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176521","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of UK Official Development Assistance was disbursed to fragile and conflict-affected states in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222395","222395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176522","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Office for National Statistics' revisions to GDP in December 2014 on the Government's ability to achieve the target of 0.7 per cent of gross national income being spent on official development assistance in this financial year.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222396","222396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176523","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's strategic framework for economic development, published in January 2014, what proportion of the £1.8 billion allocated will be spent in (a) this financial year and (b) each of the next three financial years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222402","222402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176526","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Bekou Trust Fund to date; and whether she plans to contribute to it.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222369","222369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176528","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her assessment is of the implications of the current security situation in the Central African Republic for the delivery of humanitarian assistance in that country.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222421","222421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176530","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff in her Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222521","222521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176532","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222590","222590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176534","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222576","222576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176536","2015-02-02","Department for International Development","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what measures her Department has put in place to ensure that funding provided by her Department and spent by foreign governments is used for its intended purposes.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222512","222512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176538","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222577","222577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176540","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222591","222591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176542","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff in his Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222522","222522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176543","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what account he took of the fact that Killarney-Comércio Internacional, Lda is registered as an offshore company before deciding to proceed with the sale to them of the building until recently used as the Lewes Magistrates' Court; what due diligence was carried out into this company and its relationship with (a) Quora and (b) Whitbread Plc prior to the sale; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Baker","Norman Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222469","222469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176544","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what correspondence on what topics he has had with the Council of Europe Commissioner for Human Rights in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222366","222366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176545","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the budget of the education department for HM Prison Wormwood Scrubs was in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222424","222424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176546","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many inmates were enrolled in teaching or training in the art, design and media department in HM Prison Wormwood Scrubs when it was closed down.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222426","222426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176547","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what changes there have been to the budget of the education department at HM Prison Wormwood Scrubs since January 2014.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222425","222425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176548","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the art, design and media department at HM Prison Wormwood Scrubs closed.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222422","222422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176549","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the decision was taken to close the art, design and media department in HM Prison Wormwood Scrubs.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222423","222423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176550","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in which parliamentary constituencies closure of a court has been (a) proposed and (b) decided upon.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222613","222613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176551","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was of the Phillips Review on veterans and the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222554","222554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176552","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015, to Question 221368, what estimate he has made of the potential savings to his Department arising from the proposed closure of Rhyl family court.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222612","222612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176553","2015-02-02","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to her contribution of 27 January 2015, Official Report, column 746, on Second Reading of the Corporation Tax (Northern Ireland) Bill, what plans she has for co-ordination with the Prime Minister and other Cabinet colleagues of a determined effort to sell the benefits of Northern Ireland to the world.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222411","222411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176554","2015-02-02","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff in her Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222523","222523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176555","2015-02-02","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222592","222592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176556","2015-02-02","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222578","222578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176557","2015-02-02","Prime Minister","2015-01-28","To ask the Prime Minister, whether any ceiling was put on the costs of the Iraq Inquiry; and what remuneration has been received by each Committee member.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222484","222484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176558","2015-02-02","Scotland Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many staff in his Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222524","222524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176559","2015-02-02","Scotland Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222579","222579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176560","2015-02-02","Scotland Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222593","222593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176561","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222594","222594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176562","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222580","222580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176563","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff in his Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222525","222525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176564","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving test centres have been (a) closed, (b) opened, (c) reopened having been previously closed in each (i) Scottish and (ii) English local authority area in each of the last five years up to the most recent period for which records are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222516","222516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176565","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date he plans for electric rail passenger services to start operating between (a) Manchester and Liverpool and (b) Liverpool and Wigan.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222490","222490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176566","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passengers flew from (a) Heathrow, (b) Gatwick, (c) Stansted, (d) Liverpool and (e) Manchester airports in each year from 1985.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222480","222480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176567","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to reach a decision on Network Rail's application for a Transport and Works Act Order in connection with the Ordsall Chord project.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222499","222499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176568","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding has been allocated to the electrification of the Hull-Holyhead railway line.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222481","222481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176569","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average amount of carbon emitted by (a) road and (b) rail freight was in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222482","222482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176570","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department applies the World Health Organisation's night noise guidelines for Europe; and whether these guidelines have been broken since May 2010.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222371","222371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176571","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will (a) carry out and (b) publish an equality impact assessment of the introduction of driver-only operation on the Transpennine Express and Northern Rail franchises.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222388","222388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176572","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on passenger safety of the introduction of driver-only operation on the Transpennine Express and Northern Rail franchises; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222389","222389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176573","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average duration of an intercity rail journey between (a) Holyhead and London and (b) Chester and London was in each year from 1985 for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222617","222617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176574","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the amount was of road freight from (a) Ireland to the UK and (b) the UK to Ireland in each year from 1985 for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222615","222615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176575","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many rail passengers were carried between North Wales and London in each year from 1985 for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222616","222616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176576","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to close the Airdrie Driving Test Centre.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222606","222606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176577","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many driving test centres have (a) closed and (b) opened; and how many formerly closed centres reopened in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland, (iii) England, (iv) Wales and (v) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years up to the most recent period for which records are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222607","222607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176578","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passengers  travelled by (a) road and (b) rail from (i) UK to Ireland and (ii) Ireland to the UK in each year from 1985 for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222614","222614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176579","2015-02-02","Wales Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222596","222596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176580","2015-02-02","Wales Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff in his Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222526","222526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176581","2015-02-02","Wales Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222581","222581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176582","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's advertising budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222582","222582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176583","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer from the Minister of State for Care and Support of 23 January 2015 to Question 221072, what estimate he has made of the savings made by his Department as a result of 90,000 people moving off benefits and into work as a result of Improving Access to Psychological Therapy interventions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222620","222620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176584","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to increase cooperation between his Department and the Department of Health in using Improving Access to Psychological Therapies to help those on sickness and disability benefit back to work.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222548","222548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176585","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment criteria the Health and Safety Executive plans to apply in deciding whether its inspections of hydraulic fracturing sites will be unannounced.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222532","222532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176586","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in his Department have been employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222527","222527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176587","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has a target clearance time for a disability living allowance mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222500","222500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176588","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the availability of shared accommodation for people under 35 in receipt of housing benefit.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222474","222474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176589","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what adjustments his Department has made to the number of people reassessed for personal independence payment to reflect the current backlog of claims.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222405","222405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176590","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have undergone a reassessment for personal independence payment before the end of their award period.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222406","222406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176591","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost was of reassessing people with progressive conditions for (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment and support allowance in 2014.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222404","222404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176592","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pertussis vaccine damage claims were made in each year since 2003; and how many were successful in each year.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222407","222407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176593","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Personal Independence Payment new claims: ad hoc statistics, published on 28 January 2015, how many of the 143,000 people disallowed personal independence payment (PIP) claims highlighted in that report were people who were described as not attending an assessment without good reason; what reasons for missing such assessments are permissible; whether the Department or assessment providers adjudicates on reasons for missed appointments; and how many of those people have since reapplied for PIP.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222419","222419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176594","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment claims was (a) disallowed or (b) considered to have been withdrawn due to claimants not returning the PIP2 form in each calendar month since April 2013.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222418","222418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176595","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in how many Jobcentres is a mental health champion employed; and how many mental health champions Jobcentre Plus employs in total.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222449","222449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176596","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have received funeral payments in (a) England, (b) London and (c) Enfield in each of the last 10 years; how much those payments amount to; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222358","222358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176597","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 11 March 2014, Official Report, column 141W, on children: maintenance, what progress he has made on the development of statistics on compliance, collections and enforcement under the statutory child maintenance scheme; and when he will publish these statistics.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222370","222370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176598","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's communications budget was in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222597","222597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176599","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of full-time equivalent staff required by the Health and Safety Executive in order for it to perform its role as a regulator of hydraulic fracturing in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16, (c) 2016-17, (d) 2017-18, (e) 2018-19 and (f) 2019-2020.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222600","222600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176600","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is a requirement that the Health and Safety Executive assess all hydraulic fracturing sites during (a) the exploration phase and (b) all further phases, including decommissioning.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222601","222601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176601","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people aged between 18 and 24 have been unemployed for longer than (a) 6 months, (b) 12 months and (c) 2 years in (i) Tower Hamlets, (ii) London and (iii) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222628","222628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176602","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Bethnal Green and Bow constituency and (b) London have been classified as living in absolute poverty in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222629","222629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176603","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the median income in (a) Tower Hamlets, (b) London and (c) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222630","222630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177246","2015-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to uphold the constitutional importance of judicial review.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907383","907383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/177248","2015-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how the Government is supporting the victims of the sex abuse cases that came to light in 2014.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907381","907381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175916","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 23 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published in July 2013, what progress has been made towards achieving the stated aim of linking professional and business service businesses with the education sector, including through the National Careers Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222126","222126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175917","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 21 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published in July 2013, what progress has been made towards achieving 10,000 higher apprenticeship starts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222127","222127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175918","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 21 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published in July 2013, what steps he has taken to increase the diversity of entry to the professional and business services sector; and what effect those steps have had.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222128","222128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175919","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 21 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published in July 2013, what estimate he has made of changes in the number of higher apprenticeships in the professional and business services sector since the launch of that strategy.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222129","222129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175920","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 21 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published in July 2013, what estimate he has made of changes in the number of higher apprenticeships offered in the professional and business services sector.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222130","222130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175921","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 15 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published, in July 2013, what the outcome was of the report to Government, planned for the third quarter of 2014, on the role of professional bodies and how public confidence can be ensured by demonstrating adherence to the highest professional standards; and if he will publish the actions arising from the report.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222131","222131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175922","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 15 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published in July 2013, how many Growth Vouchers have been (a) issued and (b) used since the launch of that scheme.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222132","222132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175923","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 15 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published in July 2013, what barriers to both the adoption of flexible business models and the development of stronger partnerships between specialist firms have been identified; and what steps have been taken to remove such barriers by the stated deadline of the second quarter of 2014.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222133","222133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175924","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 21 of Growth is our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services, published in July 2013, what estimate he has made of changes in the number of applications to higher apprenticeships in the professional and business services sector.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222134","222134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175925","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the amount of Government support received by the creative industries through fiscal relief on investment and grant programmes; and what proportion such support is of the support given to other sectors included in his Department's industrial strategy.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222145","222145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175926","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of falling oil prices on the ability of businesses to pay salary increases.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222161","222161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175927","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HM Revenue and Customs has taken to encourage people to complete their tax returns by 31 January.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222146","222146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175928","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many trained staff delivering (a) face-to-face and (b) telephone guidance through the Government's Pension Wise scheme will be based in (i) England, (ii) Wales and (iii) Scotland.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222172","222172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175929","2015-02-03","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Citizens Advice Scotland offices in Scotland will deliver pension guidance through the Government's Pension Wise scheme.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222173","222173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175930","2015-01-29","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria he used to determine eligibility for the Pensioner Bonds scheme; and for what reason the qualifying age was set at 65 years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222136","222136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175931","2015-01-29","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any additional resources will be available to HM Revenue and Customs for conducting due diligence on newly-registered pension schemes.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222137","222137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175932","2015-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will delay proposals to build on the green belt in Blaydon constituency until after the publication of Household Projections 2012 to 2037.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222144","222144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175933","2015-01-29","Department for Education","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason she did not publish the applications forms for the Kings Science Academy, Bradford and the Beccles Free School, Suffolk along with the application forms for the other successful Wave 1, 2 and 3 free schools; and if she will publish those application forms.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222135","222135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175934","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with (a) trades unions and (b) Oil and Gas UK on employment levels in the offshore energy sector.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222163","222163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175935","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to enable the seizure of vehicles involved in fly tipping and illegal dumping.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222114","222114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175939","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many project applications have been submitted to the UK Overseas Territories Environment and Climate Fund (Darwin Plus) in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222174","222174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175940","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Gaza Reconstruction Mechanism in fulfilling its objectives to (a) enable the government of Palestine to lead the reconstruction efforts, (b) enable the Gazan private sector, (c) assure donors that their investments in construction work in Gaza will be implemented without delay and (d) address Israeli security concerns related to the use of construction and other dual use material.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222138","222138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175941","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Gaza Reconstruction Mechanism on the humanitarian situation in Gaza.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222139","222139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175942","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to support the Gaza Reconstruction Mechanism.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222140","222140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175943","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health visitors were employed in Pendle constituency in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222142","222142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175944","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will launch a public campaign to stem the rise in the number of people with Type 2 diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222167","222167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175945","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how many diabetes sufferers are not getting the recommended number of annual checks in (a) Lancashire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222168","222168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175946","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges about links between hayfever and dementia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222113","222113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175947","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department last reviewed the effectiveness of public health measures designed to increase the uptake of exercise in adults and children in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222155","222155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175948","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that adults in the UK increase their uptake of exercise to match NHS activity guidelines.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222156","222156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175949","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that children in the UK increase their uptake of exercise to match NHS activity guidelines.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222157","222157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175950","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has made available to pensioners in the UK to increase their uptake of physical activities in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222158","222158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175951","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has made available to children from low-income backgrounds to increase their uptake of physical activities in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222159","222159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175952","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to reduce misdiagnosis of irritable bowel syndrome and bowel cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222112","222112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175953","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to reduce influenza infections in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222115","222115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175954","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that IVF treatment is monitored to prevent genetic defects.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222110","222110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175955","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with his Northern Irish counterpart about the exchange of best practice on the use of technology within the NHS.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222125","222125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175956","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will re-introduce the NHS Diabetes dedicated improvement service.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222169","222169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175957","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many men have had breast reduction surgery in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222118","222118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175958","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable will be for the consultation on mandatory reporting of abuse of children and vulnerable adults.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222170","222170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175959","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the budget will be for the consultation on mandatory reporting of abuse of children and vulnerable adults.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222171","222171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175960","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which organisations tackling violence against women and girls receive central government funding for a telephone helpline; and when the funding for each organisation is due to end.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222166","222166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175961","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015 to Question 221638, how many reports of fraud have been received by Action Fraud in the 12 month period for which figures are available; and how many victims of crime who reported to Action Fraud have received an update on what action has been taken in that period.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222141","222141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175962","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether central government funding for telephone helplines tackling violence against women and girls will be renewed before May 2015.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222164","222164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175963","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when each organisation tackling violence against women and girls receiving central government funding for a telephone helpline will be told whether the funding for that helpline will be renewed.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222165","222165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175964","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Global Learning Programme.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222119","222119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175965","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which schools in Norfolk have registered for the Global Learning Programme.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222120","222120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175966","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which schools in Norfolk are Global Learning Programme Expert Centres; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222121","222121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175967","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many schools have registered for the Global Learning Programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222122","222122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175968","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims of domestic violence have been imprisoned for contempt of court in the last five years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222123","222123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175969","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders who have been part of a restorative justice scheme have reoffended in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222109","222109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175970","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has issued to open prisons on reducing the number of absconders.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222143","222143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175971","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) breathalysed and (b) convicted of driving while under the influence of alcohol in December in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222116","222116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175972","2015-01-29","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that Gibraltar is not excluded from the EU air safety system.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222111","222111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175973","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will hold discussions with the Civil Aviation Authority on requiring airlines operating in UK airspace to have wind shear detection and alert systems fitted to commercial aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222177","222177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175974","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has paid to consultants in preparation for reletting the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises; and what the name of each consultant so paid was.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222176","222176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175975","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was withheld in benefits sanctions from applicants residing in (a) Glasgow North constituency, (b) the city of Glasgow and (c) Scotland in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (v) 2014.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222124","222124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175976","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding has been allocated to universal credit since June 2010.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222162","222162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176012","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the announcement of 12 June 2014 on the £30 million fund to secure the supply of engineers and boost the number of women in the sector, what budget was provided for the developing women engineers strand of that fund in 2014-15; how much has been spent on that strand of work in 2014-15 to date; and what forecast he has made of total spending on that strand of work in 2014-15.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222178","222178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176013","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff in his Department were recruited through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222243","222243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176014","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the implementation of the recommendations on deep offshore underground coal gasification projects in the UK in the Government's 2006 study, Creating the Coalmine of the 21st century.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222206","222206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176015","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship starts there were in the Hendon constituency in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222308","222308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176016","2015-01-29","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the rate of staff turnover was at the Financial Ombudsman Service in the years (a) 2000, (b) 2009, (c) 2010, (d) 2011, (e) 2012, (f) 2013 and (g) 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222284","222284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176017","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding his Department allocated to the Citizens Advice Service in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and what such funding it has allocated for 2015-16.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222336","222336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176018","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many attendances at events by businesses have been facilitated by the Tradeshow Access programme in each (a) year of the present Parliament and (b) of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222352","222352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176019","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many companies have received financial support to date under the Direct Lending scheme; and on what dates such support was provided.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222353","222353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176020","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many companies have received financial support to date under the Passport to Export scheme in each month of the present financial year to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222354","222354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176021","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many companies have been accepted to receive support under the Gateway to Global Growth scheme in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222355","222355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176022","2015-02-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many companies have received financial support under the Tradeshow Access programme in each (a) year of the present Parliament and (b) of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222356","222356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176023","2015-01-29","Cabinet Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of young people aged 16 to 18 years old living in Hendon constituency had a working or educational status classified as unknown in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222309","222309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176024","2015-01-29","Cabinet Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department were recruited through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222244","222244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176025","2015-01-29","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in his Department were employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222252","222252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176026","2015-01-29","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax relief on private pension contributions was paid to (a) additional rate and (b) higher-rate taxpayers in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222297","222297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176027","2015-01-29","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the number of workers using the Construction Industry Scheme; and whether there has been a significant variation in such numbers during the last year.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222272","222272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176028","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make an estimate of potential tax revenues from the development and operation of the deep offshore underground coal gasification projects from licences issued by the Coal Authority in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222207","222207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176029","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Chapter 2.147 of the Autumn Statement 2014 (a) who is handling the review on umbrella companies, (b) who is being consulted and (c) what progress has been made with the consultation to date.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222274","222274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176030","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress his Department is making on preventing companies from deducting both employer and employee National Insurance contributions from their employees' pay packets.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222348","222348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176031","2015-02-02","HM Treasury","2015-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to stop agencies using umbrella companies to manage the payroll function of companies within the construction industry.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222349","222349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176032","2015-01-29","Church Commissioners","2015-01-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what powers parochial church councils possess to convey (a) capital, (b) property and (c) other assets to a local community organisation or charity they are (i) seeking to assist and (ii) whose objections or plan they support.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222327","222327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176033","2015-01-29","Church Commissioners","2015-01-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, how many and which parochial church councils (a) have and (b) have not registered their entitlement to the benefit of recovery of channel repair liability.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222328","222328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176034","2015-01-29","Church Commissioners","2015-01-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, how many court cases have been brought by parochial church councils to recover channel repair liability since the Aston Cantlow judgement by the House of Lords in 2003.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222329","222329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176035","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that the planning system applies equally to (a) Gypsies and Travellers and (b) the settled community.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222343","222343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176036","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221428, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the Greater Manchester devolution agreement and the election of a directly elected city-region mayor before Parliament is dissolved for the 2015 general election.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222345","222345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176037","2015-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will issue planning guidance to ensure that all new developments of 300 homes or larger must be provided with a broadband connection by the developer.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222311","222311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176038","2015-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has for regeneration of the Thames Gateway.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222265","222265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176039","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 219487, what criteria his Department has used to cease funding integration projects and activities since 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222231","222231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176040","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 219487, what funding was provided in financial year 2010-11 for the integration projects and activities listed in the Answer.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222232","222232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176041","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 219487, what criteria his Department has used to allocate funding to integration projects and activities since 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222233","222233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176042","2015-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many staff in his Department were recruited through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222245","222245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176043","2015-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219231, how the spending on child abuse and neglect within the Formula Grant is decided upon.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222183","222183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176044","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 219487, what agreements exist on what the outputs and outcomes will be for each of the organisations and activities funded through his Department's integration budget.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222234","222234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176045","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funds his Department has allocated to the British Muslim Initiative in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222220","222220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176046","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funds his Department has allocated to Middle East Eye in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222221","222221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176047","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funds his Department has allocated to the Cordoba Foundation in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222222","222222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176048","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the written statement of 28 November 2014 by the Minister of State for Housing and Planning, HCWS50, on support for small scale developers, custom and self-builders, when he plans to publish revised planning guidance.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222223","222223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176049","2015-01-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff in his Department were recruited through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222246","222246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176050","2015-01-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what targets he has set for mobile telephone coverage improvements through the MIP local telephone mast project; and when he expects those targets to be met.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222271","222271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176051","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department has spent on the Type 45 programme in each of the last four financial years; and what the projected spend is on that programme in each of the next four financial years.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222281","222281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176052","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department has spent on the aircraft carrier programme in each of the last four financial years; and what the projected spend is on that programme in each of the next four financial years.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222302","222302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176053","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his written statement of 20 January 2015, HCWS210, what progress has been made towards meeting the commitment made in the 2010 Strategic Defence and Security Review to reduce the UK's overall nuclear warhead stockpile ceiling from not more than 225 to not more than 180 by the mid 2020s.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222315","222315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176054","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been paid annually by his Department to (a) AWE Management Ltd and (b) AWE plc under the Atomic Weapons Establishment management and operation contract for each year since 2000.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222312","222312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176055","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Defence Nuclear Safety Regulator's annual assurance report for 2013 will be published; and what the reasons are for the time taken to publish that report.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222313","222313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176056","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the main gate business case for the successor to the Trident Submarine programme will be submitted to his Department's Investment Appraisals Board.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222314","222314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176057","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015 to Question 221805, what estimate he has made of the number of service personnel who have suffered mental illness in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222253","222253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176058","2015-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in his Department were recruited through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222247","222247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176059","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of military veterans in emergency accommodation.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222240","222240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176060","2015-02-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department defines what constitutes a veteran.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222342","222342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176061","2015-02-02","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-27","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what his specific responsibilities are in regards to the Greater Manchester devolution agreement and the appointment and election of a city-region mayor.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222344","222344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176062","2015-01-29","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-27","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what estimate he has made of the number of people on the electoral roll (a) before and (b) after the switch to individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222326","222326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176063","2015-01-29","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-27","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps the Government is taking to increase voter registration in Coventry following the switch to individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222323","222323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176064","2015-01-29","Cabinet Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were on the electoral roll in each parliamentary constituency in Coventry on (a) 17 February and (b) 1 December 2014.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222324","222324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176065","2015-01-29","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-27","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what funding the Government has provided to increase student voter registration following the switch to individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222325","222325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176066","2015-01-29","Cabinet Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Office were recruited through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222248","222248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176067","2015-01-29","Department for Education","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in her Department were employed through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222249","222249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176068","2015-01-29","Department for Education","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 220174, what information her Department holds on children born outside the UK reported to be in private fostering arrangements, who are subsequently placed in residential care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222181","222181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176069","2015-01-29","Department for Education","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2015 to Question 220174, what information her Department holds on the number of new private fostering arrangements of children born outside the UK which have broken down.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222182","222182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176070","2015-01-29","Department for Education","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219299, if she will collect information on the number of children in residential care addicted to narcotics or alcohol.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222184","222184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176071","2015-02-02","Department for Education","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the increase in the schools budget from £35 billion to £39 billion announced in the Spending Review 2010 included Early Years Entitlement funding under the Dedicated Schools Grant.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222230","222230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176072","2015-01-29","Department for Education","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219299, what steps her Department takes when young people living in residential care with substance abuse issues refuse intervention.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222185","222185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176073","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to simplify regulations applying to deep offshore Underground Coal Gasification projects.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222209","222209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176074","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on (a) deep offshore Underground Coal Gasification and (b) developing access rights for that gasification technique following the recommendation in the Smith Commission report on devolving powers on shale gas mineral access rights to the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222211","222211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176075","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department's Working Group on Underground Coal Gasification last met; and what the conclusions were of that meeting.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222204","222204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176076","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he last met the Coal Authority to discuss the potential development of a deep Underground Coal Gasification sector in the UK.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222205","222205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176077","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many staff in his Department were recruited through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222250","222250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176078","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions his Department has had with Ofgem to ensure that reductions in the wholesale price of gas are passed on to consumers.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222216","222216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176079","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will update his Department's estimates of the UK coal resource which could be suitable for deep underground coal gasification development in (a) onshore and (b) offshore locations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222208","222208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176080","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if the Government will make it its policy to include families with children as a vulnerable group in the Social and Environment Statutory Guidance to the Gas and Electric Market Authority.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222303","222303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176081","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many families with children in (a) North Devon constituency and (b) the UK are in debt to their energy companies.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222282","222282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176082","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of houses that have been insulated in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222341","222341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176083","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will meet the National Farmers' Union and the Health and Safety Executive to discuss possible measures to reduce the number of (a) injuries and (b) deaths in the farming sector.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222296","222296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176084","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assistance her Department offers the UK Overseas Territories to identify and tackle the threat that invasive invertebrate pests pose to native plants.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222264","222264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176085","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to continue funding for the next round of the UK Overseas Territories Environment and Climate Fund (Darwin Plus).","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222268","222268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176086","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff in her Department were recruited through employment or recruitment agencies in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222251","222251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176087","2015-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the role that the UK Overseas Territories Environment and Climate Fund (Darwin Plus) plays in delivering on (a) the UK Overseas Territories  Biodiversity Strategy and (b) the UK's international environmental commitments.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222175","222175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176088","2015-02-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to improve the labelling of milk products so that it is easier to identify their country of origin.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222149","222149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176089","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to secure the release of Raif Badawi.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222150","222150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176090","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs within his Department.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222201","222201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176091","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, to what programmes the Government has provided technical assistance to support reform of financial and economic governance in Ukraine; and how much the Government has provided to those programmes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr John Whittingdale","Mr John Whittingdale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222195","222195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176092","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much the Government plans to provide to Ukraine through the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund under each category of expenditure.","Biography information for Mr John Whittingdale","Mr John Whittingdale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222196","222196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176093","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what technical and financial assistance the Government is planning to provide to Ukraine in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr John Whittingdale","Mr John Whittingdale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222197","222197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176094","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his German counterpart on measures to stop the sale of stolen antiquities from Syria and Iraq in the German art and antiquities market.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222199","222199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176095","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the recent conviction of Nabeel Rajab in Bahrain.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222316","222316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176096","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to continue funding for the next round of the UK Overseas Territories Environment and Climate Fund (Darwin Plus).","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222266","222266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176097","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Lebanese counterpart following the terror attacks by the al-Nusra Front in Tripoli.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222276","222276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176098","2015-02-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart regarding the reported relocation of Hamas leader Khaled Meshaal to Turkey; and what steps he is taking to ensure that terrorist groups are not aided by a NATO member country.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222275","222275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176099","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of persecution of Muslims in Russia.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222291","222291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176100","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of persecution of LGBT people in Russia.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222292","222292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176101","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of persecution of LGBT people in (a) China and (b) North Korea.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222293","222293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176102","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of persecution of Christians in (a) China and (b) North Korea.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222294","222294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176103","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the recent call by the Chief of the Atomic Energy Organization of Iran for increased uranium enrichment.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222270","222270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176104","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of persecution of Jewish people in Russia.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222285","222285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176105","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of persecution of Jewish people in (a) China and (b) North Korea.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222286","222286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176106","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of persecution of Muslims in (a) China and (b) North Korea.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222287","222287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176107","2015-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Indonesian counterpart on the use of the death penalty for EU citizens convicted of drug-related offences.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222335","222335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176108","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what revised estimate he has made of the total Cancer Drugs Fund spend for 2015-16, following the re-evaluation of the Cancer Drugs Fund list in December 2014.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222351","222351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176109","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost measured by (a) GP appointments and time and (b) cost of product of issuing prescriptions to people who receive help with prescription costs for emollients such as toothpaste, moisturising lotion and shampoo and conditioner.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222350","222350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176110","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the work of the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation concerning the meningitis B vaccine as an NHS treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222307","222307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176111","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on studies which have been carried out on the efficacy of the drug pemetrexed; if his Department will again make that drug available on the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222304","222304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176112","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide an update of his Department's negotiations with Novartis on finding a cost-effective price for the Bexsero vaccine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222301","222301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176113","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which parliamentary constituencies are (a) completely and (b) partly within the (i) Community Health Trust and (ii) Mental Health Trust coverage area.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222256","222256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176114","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for each hospital trust in England, what the number of nurse shifts covered by bank or agency nurses were in each quarter since 2010; what the average cost was per shift of utilising the services of such bank or agency nurses; and how many nurse vacancies there were in each nursing grade in each quarter.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222263","222263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176115","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the declarations of interest submitted by members of the expert group with responsibilty for updating the UK guidelines on clinical management of drugs mususe and dependence.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222213","222213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176116","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to reduce addiction to prescribed benzodiazepines and z drugs.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222214","222214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176117","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will make an assessment of the implications for its policies of the survey of treatment services provided by local authorities for involuntary tranquilliser addicts conducted by the All Party Parliamentary Group on Involuntary Tranquilliser Addiction.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222215","222215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176118","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that patients prescribed benzodiazepines and z drugs are provided with recent Medicines and Healthcare Regulatory Authority advice on those drugs' addiction potential and the time taken to withdraw safely from taking such drugs.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222212","222212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176119","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of practising doctors in the UK in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222254","222254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176120","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which parliamentary constituencies are (a) completely and (b) partly within the (i) Foundation Trust and (ii) NHS Trust coverage area.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222257","222257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176121","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that medical graduates find employment within the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222200","222200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176122","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase his Department's investment in cancer services; whether NHS England plans to provide increased funding to clinical reference groups to ensure they have sufficient resources to improve specialised services; and if he will create a recognised cancer leadership team to provide support and strategic oversight to NHS England, Public Health England (PHE) and his Department, in conjunction with the introduction of cancer lead roles at PHE and his Department.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222219","222219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176123","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged 18 and under waited more than (a) one month, (b) two months, (c) three months, (d) six months and (e) one year for mental health treatment in each of the most recent five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222239","222239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176124","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the UK Government's response to the detailed opinions issued by EU Member States to the UK's Notification of the draft Standardised Packaging of Tobacco Product Regulations.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222179","222179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176125","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the consultation report and accompanying regulatory impact assessment on standardised packaging for tobacco products.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222180","222180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176126","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that asylum seekers resident in Scotland are able to submit evidence on their claim to offices in Scotland.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222152","222152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176127","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on asylum seekers in Scotland of the recent changes to rules which provide that evidence related to asylum claims must be submitted in Liverpool.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222153","222153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176128","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received about the rule change which means that asylum seekers must submit claims in Liverpool.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222154","222154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176129","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the sale of spyware to individuals across the internet.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222228","222228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176130","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides to police in England and Wales on investigation of a complaint that spyware is being used against an individual.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222229","222229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176131","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of spyware devices sold to residents of England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222227","222227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176132","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which trustees or directors of organisations subject to suspicious activity reports who have subsequently become trustees or directors of other organisations have received public funds in the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222224","222224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176133","2015-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which trustees or directors of organisations which were subject to the closure of their banking facilities have subsequently become trustees or directors of other organisations which have received public funds in the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222186","222186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176134","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken to forensically examine a mobile telephone is from the point of seizure by the police in England and Wales in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222189","222189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176135","2015-02-02","Cabinet Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many reports of the use of spyware against individuals have been made to the police in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222225","222225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176136","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken to forensically examine a computer is from the point of seizure by the police in England and Wales in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222190","222190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176137","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of spyware downloads by residents of Engand and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222226","222226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176138","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests there have been to social media companies under the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 in the last two years; and on how many occasions the information requested was (a) supplied and (b) refused.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222191","222191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176139","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there have been under the Computer Misuse Act 1990 in each year since it entered into force.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222192","222192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176140","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) charged, (b) convicted and (c) sentenced to custody following a conviction involving misuse of social media in the most recent year for which figures are available; and what offences they were (i) charged with, (ii) convicted of and (iii) sentenced for.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222193","222193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176141","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people convicted under sections 2A or 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997 used social media or cyber crime to harass or stalk their victims.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222194","222194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176142","2015-01-29","Attorney General","2015-01-27","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions for summary offences were discontinued as a consequence of delay in obtaining data from (a) social media companies and (b) the forensic examination of computers or mobile phones in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222188","222188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176143","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of its Border Security Assessment being conducted at the level of individual countries rather than on a uniform basis.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222258","222258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176144","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has considered the possibility of varying the terms and conditions attached to a visitor visa on a country-by-country basis or within different parts of large countries.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222259","222259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176145","2015-02-02","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent studies her Department has undertaken of the operation of the visa system in the US; and what assessment she has made of whether a visa system which distinguishes between the level of risk posed by applicants from different countries can operate in the UK.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222260","222260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176146","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to implement in the UK the Commission Implementing Regulation (EU) No 118/2014 of 30 January 2014 amending Regulation (EC) No 1560/2003 laying down detailed rules for the application of Council Regulation (EC) No 343/2003 establishing the criteria and mechanisms for determining the Member State responsible for examining an asylum application lodged in one of the Member States by a third-country national.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222300","222300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176147","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to protect LGBT people from homophobic attacks.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222288","222288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176148","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to protect British Jews from anti-semitic attacks.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222289","222289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176149","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to protect British Muslims from Islamaphobic attacks.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222290","222290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176150","2015-01-29","Home Office","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on when the Independent Police and Complaints Commission plans to publish the results of its investigation into disciplinary matters relating to Ministry of Defence Police officers based at the Atomic Weapons Establishment, Burghfield.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222334","222334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176151","2015-02-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of refuges for women victims of domestic violence that have closed in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222340","222340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176152","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who her Department's top 20 suppliers were on projects in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14; and what the value was of each of those suppliers' contracts in each of those years.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222295","222295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176153","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to continue funding for the next round of the UK Overseas Territories Environment and Climate Fund (Darwin Plus).","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222267","222267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176154","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the report, the Dominion Farms' land grab in Nigeria, published in January 2015, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that projects sponsored by the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition in Africa do not marginalise farmers in Taraba State, Nigeria.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222187","222187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176155","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of financial aid provided to Argentina.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222202","222202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176156","2015-01-29","Department for International Development","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Government's efforts to alleviate food shortages in Eastern Africa.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222203","222203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176157","2015-02-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children born to women serving a custodial sentence were taken into care in the most recent five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222241","222241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176158","2015-02-02","Department of Health","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners are on methadone programmes; and how many such prisoners have been on methadone programmes for more than (a) one month, (b) two months, (c) three months, (d) six months, (e) a year, (f) two years and (g) four years.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222273","222273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176159","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which regions ranked best and worst with regard to prison staff shortfalls in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222317","222317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176160","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department holds on the number of prison staff on detached duty.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222320","222320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176161","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data the Government collects on the recruitment of prison officers and staff.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222321","222321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176162","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received from prison officers and staff regarding morale amongst prison staff and officers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222322","222322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176163","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which 10 prisons sent the highest (a) number and (b) proportion of staff on detached duty to other prisons in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222310","222310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176164","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) sex of the offender (b) offence type and (c) length of sentence was in each case resulting in immediate custody at all courts in the North Wales police force area in each year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222283","222283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176165","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which 10 prisons received the highest (a) number and (b) proportion of detached duty staff from another prison in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222305","222305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176166","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prison officers and staff on detached duty in each month of 2014.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222306","222306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176167","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which department co-ordinates detached duty in the prison service.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222330","222330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176168","2015-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidelines his Department has issued to the Tribunals Service on timescales for appeal hearings at First Tier Tribunals from when the appeal has been submitted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222333","222333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176169","2015-01-29","Prime Minister","2015-01-27","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will establish a Cabinet committee chaired by the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the development of deep offshore underground coal gasification.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222210","222210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176170","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219009, if he will specify the projects comprising the 850 committed route miles of electrified railways referred to in the Answer and the mileage of such railways for each project.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222242","222242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176171","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 220242, on what date he plans for all Class 319 electric trains to start running on the Liverpool to Manchester Victoria via Newton-le-Willows route.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222235","222235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176172","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 220242, by what date he plans for all of the 14 Class 319 electric trains to be refurbished and ready to enter service on the Liverpool to Manchester Victoria via Newton-le-Willows route.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222238","222238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176173","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 220242, what discussions he has had with Network Rail about the time taken to complete electrification of the Liverpool to Manchester Victoria via Newton-le-Willows route, and the effect of the delay to this project compared to the original time estimate on rolling stock provision in the north.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222236","222236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176174","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2015 to Question 220242, what discussions he has had with Northern Rail on the availability of fully trained drivers for the 14 Class 319 electric trains on the Liverpool to Manchester Victoria via Newton-le-Willows route by the time that the refurbished trains are ready for service.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222237","222237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176175","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the criteria are by which he will assess whether the new Traffic Signs Regulations and General Directions have improved safety, accessibility and amenity for pedestrians crossing the road.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222160","222160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176176","2015-02-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the slowdown of activity in the North Sea in recent months on (a) seafarer and (b) helicopter crew employment levels in the offshore oil and gas industry supply chain.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222147","222147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176177","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects regular passenger services to start operating via the Todmorden Curve.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222280","222280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176178","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which franchised train operator has paid the highest level of corporation tax in the financial year 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222279","222279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176179","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which franchised train operator paid the highest amount of corporation tax in each financial year from 2009-10 to 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222278","222278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176180","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on whether Rail North support proposals for the introduction of driver-only operating on the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222347","222347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176181","2015-01-29","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Wales Office regarding the Severn Bridge.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222332","222332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176182","2015-02-02","Department for Transport","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on job numbers of the introduction of driver-only operating on the Northern Rail and Transpennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222346","222346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176183","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent progress his Department has made in sharing data with registered social landlords.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222357","222357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176184","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (b) North Lanarkshire, (c) Scotland, (d) the UK, (e) England, (f) Wales and (g) Northern Ireland received support through the Access to Work scheme in each year from 2010 to the most recent period for which figures are available; and how much was paid out to each category of recipient in each such year.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222331","222331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176185","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have completed the Work Programme to date; and how many of those participants in the Work Programme in (a) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (b) the UK, (c) Scotland, (d) England and (e) Wales stopped claiming either jobseeker's allowance or employment and support allowance in each month since June 2013.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222339","222339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176186","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 18 to 24 year olds claiming (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance who were referred to the Work Programme in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland, (iii) England and (iv) Wales went into a job lasting three to six months in each month since June 2011.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222338","222338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176187","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England and (d) Wales were referred to the Work Programme and went on to get a job lasting three to six months in each year since June 2011.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222337","222337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176188","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made on ensuring his Department processes applications for disability living allowance from young people with diabetes consistently.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222269","222269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176189","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the level of expenditure on unemployment-related benefits to people aged (a) 18 to 24 and (b) 24 to 29 in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland (iii) England, (iv) Wales and (v) Northern Ireland in (A) 2007, (B) 2008 and (C) 2009.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222277","222277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176190","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many outcome payments have been made to contractors involved in the Work Programme in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England and (d) Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222255","222255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176191","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent on Work Programme job outcome fees on (a) Employment and Support Allowance (ESA), Income Related (IR), Work Related Activity Group (WRAG) with three to six months prognosis, (b) ESA (IR) WRAG with 12 months or greater prognosis, (c) ESA (IR) ex-Incapacity Benefit (IB) with three to six months prognosis, (d) ESA (IR) ex-IB WRAG with 12 months prognosis, (e) Voluntary ESA (IR) ex-IB Support Group, (f) Voluntary ESA and (g) ex-IB Support Group claimant groups, in each month since June 2011.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222261","222261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176192","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent on Work Programme attachment fees on (a) Employment and Support Allowance (ESA), Income Related (IR), Work Related Activity Group (WRAG) with three to six months prognosis, (b) ESA (IR) WRAG with 12 months or greater prognosis, (c) ESA (IR) ex-Incapacity Benefit (IB) with three to six months prognosis, (d) ESA (IR) ex-IB WRAG with 12 months prognosis, (e) Voluntary ESA (IR) ex-IB Support Group, (f) Voluntary ESA and (g) ex-IB Support Group, in each month since June 2011 claimant groups.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222262","222262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176193","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people (a) were eligible for and (b) participated in the Work Programme in (i) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (ii) North Lanarkshire, (iii) Scotland and (iv) the UK, in each month since October 2012.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222318","222318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176194","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former incapacity benefit claimants found fit for work after being reassessed for employment and support allowance between October 2010 and March 2014 have found work as a result of the Work Programme in (a) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (b) North Lanarkshire, (c) Scotland, (d) the UK, (e) Engand, (f) Wales and (g) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222319","222319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176195","2015-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many overseas recipients of (a) pension credit, (b) winter fuel allowance and (c) the Christmas bonus there were in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222298","222298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176196","2015-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information his Department holds on how many families with children in Poplar and Limehouse constituency are in debt to their energy companies.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222299","222299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176197","2015-02-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much benefit expenditure was withdrawn through sanctions in each month since May 2010; how many claimants have had benefits withdrawn through sanctions in each of those months; and what the average amount withdrawn through sanctions from a claimant was in each of those months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 222148","222148"
