"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149954","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of (a) men and (b) women were released on Childcare resettlement licence in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 950","950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149957","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of pre-sentence reports have recommended immediate custody for (a) men and (b) women in Crown courts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 951","951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149960","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time served in prison by (a) men and (b) women on mandatory life sentences was for those who were released from prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 952","952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149963","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the expert advisory panel on building safety on revising Advice Note 14 following the increase in unsalable properties in tower blocks.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1103","1103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149966","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people serving suspended sentences were made subject to an electronic monitoring condition, broken down by offence; and on how many occasions was that condition breached in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 942","942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149969","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for International Development of 2 October 2019, Official Report column 1205, when she plans to (a) publish the timescale for informing local authority and civil society partners of and (b) begin supporting those organisations to prepare for that commitment to resettle 5,000 refugees every year post-2020.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1068","1068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149972","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase uptake of the flu vaccine by social care staff.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 844","844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149975","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time served in prison by (a) men and (b) women sentenced for murder was for those who were released from prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 953","953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149977","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of eligible (a) men and (b) women were released on home detention curfew in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 954","954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149978","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of all determinate custodial sentences handed down to (a) men and (b) women were served in prison.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 955","955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149979","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce independent regulation of the media to protect individuals from (a) invasive and (b) unethical journalism.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 934","934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149980","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Hong Kong counterparts on the use of excessive police force against protesters.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 935","935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149981","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the new minimally invasive hip replacement operation will be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1034","1034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149982","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on supporting manufacturers to increase the range of electric cars.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1035","1035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149983","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to publish the names the schools subject to the Asbestos Management Assurance Process.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1024","1024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149984","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support visually impaired people through reducing street furniture.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 974","974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149985","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what programmes are in place to support people with addictions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1036","1036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149986","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will (a) make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the Cambridge University Bennett Institute for Public Policy report entitled Townscapes: The North East and (b) reintroduce the position of Minister for the North East to tackle the decline in North East towns referred to in that report.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 986","986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149987","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he holds statistics on the number of people in the UK who suffer from chronic migraine which affects their quality of life.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1037","1037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149988","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 20 June 2019 to Question 267275 on Offenders: Electronic Tagging, how many events were classed as formal breaches requiring further action.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 943","943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149989","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the recent Cambridge University Bennett Institute for Public Policy report entitled Townscapes, The North East, if she will undertake an assessment of the ability of the two North East Local Enterprise Partnerships to tackle decline in North East towns.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 987","987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149990","2019-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent steps he has taken to support veterans through (a) housing and (b) mental health services.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 975","975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149991","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 03 October 2019 to Question 292174 on Re-offenders: Homicide, how many offenders under statutory supervision have been charged with serious further offences, broken down by offence, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 944","944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149992","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of stem cell therapy treatment to restore sight.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1038","1038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149993","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the 12 week public consultation on trophy hunting imports will commence.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 976","976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149994","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle addiction to prescription drugs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1039","1039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149995","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding her Department has allocated to the President of the 26th Conference of the Parties.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 829","829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149996","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of the recommendations of the Bovine TB Strategy Review published in October 2018.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 977","977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149997","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff her Department have recruited to prepare for the UK hosting of the 26th Conference of the Parties.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 830","830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149998","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to prevent the growth of knotweed along railway lines.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1040","1040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149999","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential benefits to (a) partially sighted and (b) blind people of (i) e-readers and (ii) other digital reading materials; and what steps her Department is taking to increase access to those materials.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 979","979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150000","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what objectives the Government has set for the UK Presidency of the 26th Conference of the Parties.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 831","831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150001","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what her Department’s strategic priorities will be for the 26th Conference of the Parties UN Climate Conference in 2020.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 832","832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150002","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many full time equivalent staff worked on climate change and energy in (a) his Department's UK-based offices and (b) embassies, high commissions and other overseas posts in each year from and including 2010 to 2019.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 833","833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150003","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment has been made of the advantages and disadvantages of appointing the role of President of the 26th Conference of the Parties UN Climate Conference external to the executive.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 834","834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150004","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether she plans to establish an advisory board to support her Department’s preparations for hosting the 26th Conference of the Parties.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 835","835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150005","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of hosting the 26th Conference of the Parties.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 836","836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150006","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of accommodation in Glasgow for the 26th Conference of the Parties.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 837","837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150007","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of using cruise liners to provide accommodation for attendees at 26th Conference of the Parties in Glasgow.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 838","838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150008","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether her Department plans to submit a new Nationally Determined Contribution (NDC) which is separate from the EU's NDC to the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change as required by the Paris Agreement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 839","839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150009","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what executive authority the President of the 26th Conference of the Parties, UN Climate Conference will have over staff within the his Department that are working on climate diplomacy.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 840","840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150010","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the level of energy and climate change policy staffing resources his Department requires to host the COP26 UN Climate Conference in 2020.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 841","841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150011","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings officials in her Department have had with the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change secretariat on the UK hosting the 26th Conference of the Parties.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 842","842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150012","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will publish the names of the organisations that applied for a Brexit Readiness Grant; and how much was awarded to each successful applicant.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 922","922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150013","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether an invitation has been extended to the UNFCCC Secretariat for that Secretariat to visit the UK as part of a fact-finding mission prior to hosting the COP26 UN Climate Conference in 2020.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 843","843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150014","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 3 October to Question 292174 on Re-offenders: Homicide and the Answer of 28 June 2019 to Question 267272 on Homicide, for what reason the figures on the number of offenders convicted of murder, who at the time they committed the offence were being supervised on a life licence between 2016 and 2018 are different from the figures for offenders released from a life sentence for murder who went on to commit another murder while on life licence in the same period.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 945","945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150015","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 3 October 2019 to Question 292174 on Re-offenders: Homicide, how many lifers on licence have been subsequently returned to prison on (a) fixed term recall and (b) standard recall.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 946","946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150016","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to extend the ban on combustible materials on tower blocks to (a) hospitals, (b) care homes, (c) sheltered housing and (d) other high-risk buildings.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1104","1104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150017","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many buildings have received funding from the Government’s £200 million private sector ACM cladding remediation fund.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1105","1105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150018","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's policy paper, Rail network enhancements pipeline: autumn 2019 update, published on 16 October 2019, when he plans to publish the (a) timescales and (b) costs for the development of those schemes.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1053","1053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150019","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding from the public purse has been allocated to the new Office for Veterans Affairs.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 930","930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150020","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the number of specialist prostate care (a) nurses and (b) doctors in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1041","1041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150021","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of remediation of social sector tower blocks with high-pressure laminate cladding and insulation combinations found to be unsafe by the independent expert advisory panel on building safety.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1106","1106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150022","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 30 September to Question 291404, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of local authorities using limited liability partnerships to avoid corporation tax on commercial activity.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1017","1017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150023","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people with psoriasis.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1042","1042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150024","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the diagnostic rate has been of each type of leukaemia in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1043","1043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150025","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason his Department has not encouraged the use of approved automated traffic cone machine, Conemaster, on the strategic road network.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1107","1107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150026","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason Highways England has not responded to Jordan Products Ltd following the meeting of 21 June 2019 on Conemaster.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1108","1108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150027","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of illegally importing firearms into the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1044","1044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150028","2019-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the reliability of algorithms used by local authorities to help make welfare decisions.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 867","867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150029","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to make pyeloplasty for kidney blockages available through the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1045","1045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150030","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of British children trapped in north east Syria.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1109","1109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150031","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department will publish details on the application outcomes of the EU Settlement Scheme at a (a) local authority and (b) parliamentary constituency level.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 848","848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150032","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department will provide data by age on the number of applicants to the EU Settlement Scheme at a (a) regional, (b) local authority and (c) parliamentary constituency level.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 849","849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150033","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will abolish fees for the Blue Badge Scheme.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 988","988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150034","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 2 September 2019 to Question 284794 on Probate: Computer Software, what steps he is taking to ensure applicants can give feedback on their satisfaction with the probate application process after a grant has been issued.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1080","1080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150035","2019-10-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers in the Welsh Government on the potential effect of customs checks on trade across the Irish Sea.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1110","1110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150036","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 7 October 2019 to Question 293525 on Bicycles: Electric Vehicles, what information his Department holds on the geographical distribution of the take up of those incentives; and which local authorities have made an application under that programme.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 984","984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150037","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reduce pool betting duty from 15 per cent to 10 per cent.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 871","871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150038","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many electric car charging points there are in (a) St Helens, (b) the North West and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1062","1062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150039","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to use technology to improve attendance at NHS cancer screenings.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 868","868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150040","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officers from each police force are assigned to the policing operations for (a) Extinction Rebellion protests and (b) protests connected to the UK leaving the EU; and what estimate she has made of the cost of those operations.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1063","1063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150041","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding was provided by his Department through the Deeds of Amendment signed with London and South Eastern Railway Ltd in (a) December 2016 and (b) September 2017.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 991","991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150042","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment basis he has made of the potential effectiveness of implementing the recommendations of the Committee on Standards in Public Life report entitled Local Government Ethical Standards published on 30 January 2019.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1052","1052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150043","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to reform the private rented sector.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 927","927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150044","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions (a) she and (b) officials in her Department have had with the Metropolitan Police on (i) the ban on Extinction Rebellion protests in London, (ii) Police identity checks on people walking across Lambeth Bridge and (iii) the stop and search of people wearing Extinction Rebellion stickers before the implementation of those powers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 971","971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150045","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to reform the regulation of leasehold properties.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 928","928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150046","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to make representations to his Emirati counterpart on (a) recent reports that Ahmed Mansoor has been tortured in al-Sadr prison and (b) Ahmed Mansoor's right to access to healthcare during his hunger strike under UN Standard Minimum Rules for the Treatment of Prisoners.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 859","859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150047","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the extension of eligibility criteria for the Blue Badge scheme on trends in the level of applications to that scheme.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1111","1111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150048","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the outcome of Ilkley Grammar School and the Moorland Trust's application to open a 1,000 place sixth form college under the Free School programme.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 883","883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150049","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it her policy to return British nationals detained in Syria to the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 972","972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150050","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of level of risk to UK nationals detained in Syria and sent for trial in Iraq of (a) torture and (b) the death penalty; if he will make it her policy to oppose the transfer of any UK detainees from Syria to Iraq for trial; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 973","973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150051","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when Highways England will bring forward further measures to tackle congestion on the A27 between Worthing and Shoreham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 819","819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150052","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reverse the fall in the number of health visitors.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 820","820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150053","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will extend the pupil premium to post-16 education to support disadvantaged students in further education.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 989","989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150054","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing a reduced rate bus pass for women born in the 1950s who have had their state pension age changed.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1112","1112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150055","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to evacuate all British children trapped in north east Syria.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 980","980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150056","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his officials have had with representatives of regional authorities in north east Syria on the (a) evacuation and (b) repatriation of British children.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 981","981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150057","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has to repatriate British children trapped in north east Syria.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 982","982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150058","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Israeli Government on conducting a criminal investigation into the alleged shooting by the Israeli Defence Force of a 9 year old Palestinian boy, Abd a-Rahman a-Shteiwi on 12 July 2019.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1015","1015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150059","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions has he had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on the repatriation of British children trapped in north east Syria.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 983","983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150060","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on pet owners of the implementation of the Tenant Fees Act 2019.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1016","1016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150061","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the status is of the cross-Government working group on family support from conception to age two years old; and when the report of that working group will be published.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 821","821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150062","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance he has issued to local authorities on awarding social care contracts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 881","881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150063","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to announce plans for the continued funding of the Adoption Support Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 822","822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150064","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance her Department issues to local authorities on the level of fees charged by social care providers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 882","882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150065","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will increase funding in further education colleges to the level of £5,000 per student.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 990","990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150066","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department’s press release, £100 million crackdown on crime in prison, published on 13 August 2019, what the previously announced £70 million to increase security and stability in prisons was spent on.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1071","1071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150067","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of delivering Midlands Connect.","Biography information for Rachel Maclean","Rachel Maclean","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1113","1113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150068","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was for a GP appointment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1046","1046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150069","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of providing free bus travel for people under 25.","Biography information for Rachel Maclean","Rachel Maclean","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1114","1114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150070","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients were waiting for a diagnostic test in NHS Trusts on 31 March in each year from 2011 to 2019.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1047","1047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150071","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were on the national elective waiting list on 31 March in each year from 2011 to 2019.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1048","1048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150072","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of patients waited more than six weeks for an endoscopy test in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1049","1049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150073","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of patients were seen within four hours in A&E in (a) 2018-19 and (b) each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1050","1050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150074","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many pregnant women have been transported in prisoner transport vehicles in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1019","1019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150075","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions women and men have been transported together in prisoner transport vehicles in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1020","1020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150076","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice,  if he will make it his policy to delay the start of a custodial sentence for pregnant women and new mothers until a place in a mother and baby unit has been made available to them.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1021","1021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150077","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 3 October 2019 to Question 291066 on Collective Bargaining, whether she plans to encourage companies operating in the UK to ensure that workers in other countries in its supply chain are able to engage in collective bargaining.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1115","1115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150078","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 3 October 2019 to Question 291050 on Living Wage, whether she plans to encourage companies operating in the UK to ensure that workers in other countries in its supply chain are paid a living wage.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1116","1116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150079","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question 291409 on Census: Sikhs, what estimate he has made of the number of people among the 20 million that answered no religion or did not answer the optional religious question in the 2011 census who belong to the Sikh ethnic group.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1117","1117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150080","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many contingent workers have been hired through the Public Sector Resourcing framework since its creation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 888","888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150081","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of requiring solar energy systems to be installed on all new dwellings.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1069","1069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150082","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted registered nurseries have been sold to new owners in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1118","1118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150083","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the burning of (a) blanket bog and (b) the peat soils that blanket bog depends on.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1119","1119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150084","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted registered (a) nurseries and (b) childminders have closed for business in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1120","1120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150085","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure compliance with the European Commission's infraction procedure relating to the EU Habitats Directive on the protection and management of blanket bogs in northern England Special Areas of Conservation.","Biography information for Ruth Jones","Ruth Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1121","1121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150086","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the estimated completion date is for the Criminal Justice System Common Platform programme.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 889","889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150087","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the estimated total cost is of the Criminal Justice System Common Platform programme.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 890","890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150088","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will issue guidance on the duties of (a) statutory health providers and (b) local authorities in meeting the care needs of adults with autism.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1018","1018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150089","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effect of anonymous (a) abuse and (b) threats made on Twitter on teenage mental health.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 936","936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150090","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to tackle (a) sexism and (b) racism on Twitter.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 937","937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150091","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of Twitter's appeals process for people that have suffered abuse on Twitter.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 938","938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150092","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on the economy of reducing the working week to 32 hours.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1122","1122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150093","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of amount spent from the public purse on repairs and maintenance at No. 11 Downing Street in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1057","1057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150094","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much has been spent from the public purse on repairs and maintenance at No. 10 Downing Street in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1058","1058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150095","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the running costs of No.10 Downing Street have been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1059","1059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150096","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse has been of repairs to and maintenance of Admiralty House flats in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1060","1060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150097","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse has been of running the Admiralty House flats in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1061","1061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150098","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will provide former employees of Thomas Cook with (a) retraining opportunities and (b) loans to start new businesses.","Biography information for Ms Lisa Forbes","Ms Lisa Forbes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1123","1123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150099","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many overseas drivers have been prosecuted for committing the offence of speeding on UK roads between August 2018 and August 2019.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 818","818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150100","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an estimate of the cost to the public purse of reversing the roll-out of universal credit and returning to the previous system.","Biography information for Jack Brereton","Jack Brereton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1124","1124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150101","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to make clinical commissioning groups in north-west London financially sustainable; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 857","857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150102","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Uganda has abandoned plans to re-introduce an anti-homosexuality Bill imposing the death penalty on homosexuals.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1125","1125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150103","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take in response to reports that the Ugandan Government plans to re-introduce a Bill imposing the death penalty on homosexuals.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1126","1126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150104","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the UK has made to the Ugandan Government on reports that it will re-introduce a Bill imposing the death penalty on homosexuals.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1127","1127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150105","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to safeguard British citizens who identify as LGBT+ who are working and travelling in Uganda following reports that that country's Government plans to re-introduce a Bill imposing the death penalty on homosexuals.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1128","1128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150106","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken since the July 2019 publication of the Clinical Advisory Panel's review of cancer services at Mount Vernon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 858","858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150107","2019-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent from the Continuity of Education Allowance on placements at (a) Eton, (b) Charterhouse, (c) Harrow, (d) Rugby, (e) Shrewsbury, (f) Westminster, (g) Winchester, (h) St Paul's and (i) Merchant Taylors in the last financial year for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1129","1129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150108","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent from the Continuity of Education Allowance on placements at (a) Eton, (b) Charterhouse, (c) Harrow, (d) Rugby, (e) Shrewsbury, (f) Westminster, (g) Winchester, (h) St Paul's and (i) Merchant Taylors schools in the last financial year for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1130","1130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150109","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when she plans to publish the eligibility criteria for companies seeking financial support as part of Operation Kingfisher; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Lidington","Sir David Lidington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 817","817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150110","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of patients referred to the Michael Rutter centre for obsessive–compulsive disorder at the Maudsley Hospital from each (a) nation and (b) region of the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 898","898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150111","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) adults and (b) children who suffer with obsessive compulsive disorder in each (i) nation and (ii) region of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 899","899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150112","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which clinical commissioning groups in England have implemented the NICE guidelines for obsessive compulsive disorder.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 900","900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150113","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the UK remains in alignment with the EU Anti-Tax Avoidance Directive after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1055","1055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150114","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings Ministers in his Department have had on the implementation of sustainable development goals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 891","891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150115","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings officials in his Department have had on the implementation of sustainable development goals in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 892","892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150116","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Solicitors Regulation Authority has a code of conduct for its staff working in the (a) the Investigation and Supervision Unit, (b) Forensic Investigation Unit and (c) Legal and Enforcement Unit.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 957","957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150117","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will ask the Legal Services Board to initiate a review of the consistency of Solicitors Regulation Authority decision-making in relation to (a) supervision, (b) investigations and (c) enforcement in connection with (i) sole practitioners and (ii) firms with no more than four partners, members or directors and which have an annual turnover of no more than £400,000.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 958","958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150118","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Solicitors Regulation Authority.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 959","959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150119","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what key performance indicators exist for staff within the (a) investigation and supervision, (b) forensic investigation and (c) legal and enforcement units of the Solicitors Regulation Authority.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 960","960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150120","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the data on supervision and enforcement outcomes on page 39 of the Solicitors Regulation Authority Annual Report 2017-19, published on 23 May 2019, if he will make an assessment of the value for money represented by the recent exercise of the investigation and enforcement functions of the Solicitors Regulation Authority.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 961","961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150121","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question HL17757 on China: Prisoners, if he will publish the evidence relating to organ harvesting in the People’s Republic of China provided to his Department by (a) the World Health Organisation and (b) other international organisations.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 962","962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150122","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question HL17757 on China: Prisoners, when his Department held its most recent consultation relating to organ harvesting in the People’s Republic of China with (a) the World Health Organisation and (b) other international organisations.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 963","963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150123","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 3 September 2019 to Question 281598 on Organs, what steps the Government plans to take in response to reports of (a) the mistreatment of Falun Gong practitioners and (b) abuses taking place within China’s transplant system.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 964","964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150124","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 2 October 2019 to Question 290776 on Rain Forests: Amazonia, what assessment her Department has made of recent trends in the level of deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 965","965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150125","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 2 October to Question 290776 on Rain Forests: Amazonia, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect of the (a) degradation of carbon sinks and (b) deforestation in the Amazon rainforest on the timeframe for the UK's transition to a net-zero economy.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 966","966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150126","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 7 March 2019 to Question 226643 on Women's Health Taskforce for England, on what dates the Women's Health Taskforce for England has met since February 2019; what the topics of discussion were at each meeting; whether the draft Terms of Reference for the Taskforce have been approved; and whether plans for information and involvement  from (a) the Campaign Against Painful Hysteroscopy and (b) other campaign groups has been considered.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 967","967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150127","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to include outpatient hysteroscopy on the agenda of a future meeting of the Women's Health Taskforce for England.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 968","968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150128","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals there were for (a) rough sleepers and (b) people experiencing other forms of homelessness by (i) local authorities and (ii) local authority children’s services to the National Referral Mechanism in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 969","969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150129","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the (a) adequacy and (b) consistency of (i) local authority and (ii) local authority children’s service referrals to the National Referral Mechanism in relation to the estimates of modern slavery prevalence among rough sleepers in the 15 October 2019 Hestia report Underground Lives: Homelessness and Modern Slavery in London.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 970","970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150130","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that restaurant staff receive 100 per cent of their tips.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1131","1131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150131","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timeframe is for the introduction of National Minimum Standards on disability awareness training for drivers of taxi and private hire vehicles.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 978","978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150132","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 7 October to Question 293726, how many meetings Ministers or officials in his Department have held with Ministers or officials in the Cabinet Office on the National Data Strategy since that strategy was announced.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1132","1132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150133","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 7 October 2019 to Question 293726, how many meetings there have been between officials in his Department and officials in the Cabinet Office on the National Data Strategy over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1133","1133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150134","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what advice she has given to UK-based musicians on transporting instruments into the EU in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 923","923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150135","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 8 October to Question 293725 on Government Chief Data Officer, until what date the objective of appointing a Chief Data Officer by 2020 applies.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1134","1134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150136","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Spanish counterpart on the (a) general and (b) police response to pro-independence demonstrations in Catalonia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1135","1135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150137","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of delaying the proposed introduction in 2020 of charges for Musical Instrument Certificates (MICs) where instruments contain Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Wild Fauna and Flora (CITES)-listed materials.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 924","924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150138","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 7 October 2019 to Question 292999 on Huawei: 5G, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to telecoms networks arising from the delay of a decision on Huawei's involvement in UK 5G.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1136","1136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150139","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to include transitional arrangements for CITES-listed materials in (a) any withdrawal agreement made with the EU and (b) in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 925","925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150140","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to improve electoral accessibility for voters with blindness following the decision of the High Court on 3 May 2019.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1137","1137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150141","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to ensure (a) the continued validity of UK-issued A1 certificates  or (b) that freelance workers are exempted from social security contributions for work undertaken in the EU27 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 926","926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150142","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings he has had with the RNIB since the 3 May 2019 decision of the High Court on electoral accessibility.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1138","1138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150143","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 14 September 2018 to Question 171303, what progress her Department has made in its Ageing Society Mission.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 901","901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150144","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 5 September 2019 to Question 284390 on Public Sector: Computer Software, whether (a) his Department and (b) the GDS is monitoring the number and proportion of public sector computers transitioning from Windows 7 prior to the end of the support date.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1139","1139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150145","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has undertaken an assessment of the adequacy of the evidence available for the purpose of taking a case to the International Court of Justice on the ground that the situation in Burma represents a violation of the UN genocide convention.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1056","1056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150146","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of children who live in households in receipt of benefits who have one or more (a) parent and (b) guardian with a diagnosis of depression or anxiety.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 902","902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150147","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 13 September 2018 to Question 171307, what steps her Department takes to monitor the personal wellbeing of claimants.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 903","903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150148","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) women and (b) men have been sectioned under the Mental Health Act 1983 within 24 hours of their release from prison in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1022","1022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150149","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to keep the issue of anti-abortion clinic protests under review.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1140","1140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150150","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal wellbeing in formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve personal wellbeing in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 904","904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150151","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether her Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies her Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 905","905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150152","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies her department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 906","906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150153","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the past 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 907","907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150154","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies her department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the past 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 908","908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150155","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the past 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 909","909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150156","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies her Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 910","910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150157","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 911","911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150158","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 912","912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150159","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies her Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 913","913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150160","2019-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal well-being in formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 914","914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150161","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department uses Office for National Statistics estimates of personal wellbeing in formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 915","915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150162","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has had made to his Ugandan counterpart on the proposed legislation in that country to impose the death penalty as a punishment for gay sex.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 851","851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150163","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to expedite the development of a GCSE in British Sign Language.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 872","872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150164","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will include data on children with disabilities in the school census.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 873","873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150165","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data his Department collects on the proportion of deaf young people who have completed A-levels.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 874","874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150166","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps the Government is taking to improve human rights in Uganda.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 852","852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150167","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that every deaf child has access to an education, health and care plan.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 875","875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150168","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the progress made in research and response to cystic fibrosis in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 876","876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150169","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that global pharmaceutical companies are required to prioritise patient access to drugs ahead of profit.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 877","877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150170","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department uses ONS estimates of personal wellbeing in formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 916","916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150171","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of reimbursement arrangements for Vertex Pharmaceuticals products for cystic fibrosis in (a) Australia, (b) Germany, and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 878","878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150172","2019-10-21","Wales Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether his Department uses ONS estimates of personal wellbeing in formulating policy; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve personal well-being in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 917","917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150173","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of deaf children have access to radio aids to help them communicate in their early years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 879","879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150174","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to tackle high levels of unemployment among the deaf community.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 880","880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150175","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the recognition of Kosovo as a sovereign state.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1078","1078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150176","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the recognition of Kosovo as a sovereign state in (a) the EU and (b) other major international bodies.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1079","1079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150177","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 9 September 2019 to Question 282187, if he will publish the resource DEL budgets of each work area under the Strategic Objective SO1, Programme Area Building Affordable Homes.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 884","884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150178","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment he has made of the humanitarian effect of the escalation of military activity in Northern Syria; and what steps his Department is taking to help alleviate the humanitarian situation in that region.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 853","853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150179","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, in how many business transactions the Government has intervened in the interests of national security since 2015.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 823","823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150180","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings each Cabinet committee has held since the Prime Minister took office.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1076","1076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150181","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which (a) goods and (b) services he Department has classified as vital for UK national security.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 824","824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150182","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what screening of overseas companies her Department undertakes in relation to national security in advance of foreign direct investment by those companies.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 825","825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150183","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of access for humanitarian supplies in Northern Syria after the recent escalation of military activity in that region; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure humanitarian support is provided to people in that region.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 854","854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150184","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the revenue received by train operating companies for all (a) cross-border rail travel between England and Wales in either direction and (b) cross-border rail travel between England and Scotland in either direction; and how many passenger rail journeys there were between (i) England and Wales in either direction and (ii) between England and Scotland in either direction in the last financial year.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1054","1054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150185","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment he has made of the humanitarian situation in the al-Hol refugee camp in Syria; and what steps her Department is taking to support refugees within that camp.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 855","855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150186","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will make an assessment of the accuracy of reports by the (a) International Committee of the Red Cross and (b) Syrian Arab Red Crescent that Hassekeh city is at risk of  running out of water as a result of damage to the main water station during the recent escalation in military conflict; and what steps will his Department take to ensure adequate water supplies to that region.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 856","856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150187","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's document entitled, Main Estimate 2019-20: Estimates Memorandum, if he will publish the (a) component parts and (b) allocations for the £5,664 million allocated to ring-fenced Capital DEL.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 885","885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150188","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of cases heard by the Grocery Code Adjudicator (a) were successfully proven (b) were unsuccessfully proven and (c) dropped before a decision could be made in each years since the establishment of the Adjudicator.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 860","860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150189","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions (a) he and (b) his officials have had with (i) Ministers and (ii) officials in HM Treasury on the future of the Affordable Homes Programme, ahead of the Budget on 6 November 2019.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 886","886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150190","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he will announce the funding for the next phase of the Affordable Homes Programme.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 887","887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150191","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans the Government has to evacuate British children and their mothers from north east Syria.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1141","1141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150192","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to repatriate the mothers of British children trapped in north east Syria.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1142","1142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150193","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Development on the repatriation of British children from north east Syria.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1143","1143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150194","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with Kurdish authorities on the evacuation of British children from north east Syria.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1144","1144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150195","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 7 October 2019 to Question 292823, whether the budget for the Money and Pensions Service in 2019-20 is 125.6 million; and what comparative assessment he has made of that budget with the combined budget for the Money Advice Service, the Pensions Advisory Service and Pension Wise in each of the five years up to and including 2018-19.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 862","862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150196","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of anti-abortion clinic protests on healthcare professionals, and whether this assessment informed the anti-abortion clinic protest review.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1145","1145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150197","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance he has issued to local authorities on the use of advertisements on their websites.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1026","1026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150198","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effect of anti-abortion protest activity outside clinics on women’s human rights in light of the recent Court of Appeal ruling on the buffer zone around a Marie Stopes clinic in Ealing.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1146","1146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150199","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to continue monitoring anti-abortion clinic protests.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1147","1147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150200","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on what he took the decision to roll local welfare assistance funding into revenue support grant; and what assessment his Department has made of the level of funding required to provide financial assistance to people in financial crisis.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 863","863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150201","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 7 October 2019 to Question 293443, on Public Sector: Redundancy Pay, what recourse is available to public servants who have not had the waiver system applied to their exit payment and wish to challenge that decision.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 864","864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150202","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 7 October 2019 to Question 293443 on Public Sector: Redundancy Pay, how that waiver system will operate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 865","865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150203","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to make it easier for people who cannot take time off work to attend cancer screenings.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 869","869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150204","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 4 October 2019 to Question 290625 on Sentencing, what steps his Department plans to take to alleviate overcrowding in prisons whilst implementing recently announced sentencing reforms.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 866","866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150205","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to update the research on what steps firefighters should take when facing a fire since the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 870","870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150206","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to extend automatic priority need for housing to survivors of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1148","1148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150207","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he will discuss human rights concerns with his Bahraini counterpart during the joint Working Group between Bahrain and the UK on 17 October 2019.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1149","1149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150208","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the risk of an outbreak of African swine fever in the UK; what steps the Government is taking to minimise that risk; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 918","918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150209","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to make whole-life orders mandatory when sentencing people found guilty of the murder of a child; and how many child murderers were released into Hampshire in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1072","1072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150210","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he had with (a) the National Farmers' Union and (b) other relevant bodies before publishing the updated Code of Practice for the welfare of pigs; for what reason that Code applies to England only; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 919","919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150211","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that pork imports do not reach the UK from countries affected by African swine fever.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 920","920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150212","2019-10-21","Attorney General","2019-10-16","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of requests to his Department in relation to a custodial sentence from people in Hampshire fall outside of the unduly lenient sentence scheme.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1073","1073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150213","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what cognisance NHS Improvement took of the oral contribution of the Minister for Health of 27 June 2018, Official Report, column 1002, on irregularities of process that had taken place including at NHS Improvement in respect of the appointment process for the Chair of the Blackpool Trust, Pearse Butler, when NHS Improvement provided advice to that Trust on the permanent appointment of Kevin McGee as the Chief Executive of that Trust and to operate as Chief Executive of both the Blackpool Trust and the East Lancashire Hospitals Trust between June 2019 and September 2019.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 893","893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150214","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect on international student numbers of the decision to restrict UK student visas for foreign graduates to four months after completion of their studies.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 826","826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150215","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provision has been made for international students (a) studying and (b) recently graduated that are resident on their student visa since the previous restriction was made in 2012 who are not currently entitled to remain for two years after graduation to find a job.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 827","827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150216","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department are taking to enable (a) current students and (b) recently graduated students still resident on their student visa to remain for two years after graduation in order to find a job.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 828","828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150217","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what new steps he will take to support improving key roads that are not part of the Major Road Network, outside existing commitments.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1074","1074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150218","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether Kevin McGee will receive fill-time salaries for his each of his positions as Chief Executive of Blackpool Trust and East Lancashire Hospitals NHS Trust.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 894","894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1150221","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the research by the University of Bristol published on 16 September 2019 in Paediatric and Perinatal Epidemiology; and whether he plans update his Department's guidance as a result of that research.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 1075","1075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149187","2019-10-17","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Parliamentary Office for Science and Technology Note No. 599 on Early interventions to reduce violent crime, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the 46 per cent increase in homicides between 2014 and 2018.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 520","520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149188","2019-10-17","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in how many wrongful conviction cases in England and Wales where an individual was exonerated by DNA evidence did the initial conviction involved witness identifications of the defendant.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 521","521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149189","2019-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of introducing mandatory training on memory science for judges; and whether he will introduce mandatory training on memory science for judges.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 522","522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149190","2019-10-17","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with (a) police forces, (b) the Royal College of Policing and (c) Police and Crime Commissioners on (i) the potential benefits of the Self-Administered Interview (SAI) technique and (ii) making the SAI technique standard practice for police forces.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 523","523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149191","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of introducing a mandatory and consistent (a) UK-wide logo and (b) on pack information for compostable food packaging; and what plans her Department has to introduce such a policy.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 524","524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149192","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits for (a) reducing littering and (b) increasing recycling rates by (i) banning food producers from using using the term biodegradable on food packaging and (ii) introducing a standard definition of the term with respect to the time-frame in which products must fully decompose.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 525","525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149193","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to require that specific packaging items must be compostable; and whether she has any plans to do so.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 526","526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149194","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has made an assessment of the potential merits and feasibility of issuing an Interpol Red Notice against US citizen Anne Sacoolas, as a way of securing her extradition to the UK in order to assist Northamptonshire Police in their investigation into the road traffic collision on 27 August 2019 which resulted in the death of Harry Dunn.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 527","527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149195","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government will make an extradition request to the United States of America for the return of US citizen Anne Sacoolas, in order to assist Northamptonshire Police in their investigation into the road traffic collision on 27 August 2019 which resulted in the death of Harry Dunn.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 528","528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149196","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what processes the Government has in place to ensure that special advisers continue to comply with requirements of the national security Vetting Decision Framework subsequent to having previously declared that they have not been involved in actions intended to overthrow or undermine Parliamentary democracy by political, industrial or violent means.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 529","529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149197","2019-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question 290324, when a decision was taken to ensure that the Department's electricity will be supplied solely from renewable resources.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 530","530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149198","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question 290332 and to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question 290324, if he will introduce the same policy as the Department of Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy and switch to an electricity provider that supplies electricity solely from renewable resources within the next 12 months; and for what reason his Department has not already ensured its electricity is supplied solely from renewable resources.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 531","531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149199","2019-10-17","Department for International Trade","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Answer of 7 October 2019 to Question 290330 and to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question 290324, if she will introduce the same policy as the Department of Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy and switch to an electricity provider that supplies electricity solely from renewable resources within 12 months; and for what reason her Department has not already ensured its electricity is supplied solely from renewable resources.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 532","532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149200","2019-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question 291002 and to the Answer of 1 October 2019 to Question 290324, if he will introduce the same policy as the Department of Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy and switch to an electricity provider that supplies electricity solely from renewable resources within the next 12 months; and for what reason his Department has not already ensured its electricity is supplied solely from renewable resources.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 533","533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149201","2019-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will write to her Cabinet colleagues to (a) inform them that her Department is adopting energy suppliers that solely use renewable energy under the Crown Commercial Service energy frameworks for the supply of gas, electricity and liquid fuels and (b) encourage them to adopt similar policies for their Departments.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 534","534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149202","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, which provider supplies energy to his Department; how much CO2 was emitted through his Department’s energy consumption in the latest period for which figures are available; whether the criteria his Department uses to select an energy supplier includes how environmentally friendly the supplier is; and what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce CO2 emissions from its energy use.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 535","535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149203","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to (a) improve rail safety standards, (b) reduce the number of trains which pass through red signals and (c) mitigate the risk of collision when trains pass through red signals.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 536","536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149204","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the objectives of the Entrepreneur Relief scheme are; and what assessment his Department has made as to whether those objectives are being met.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 537","537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149205","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the (a) effect and (b) cost effectiveness of the Entrepreneur Relief scheme on incentivising investment in business.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 538","538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149206","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the Association of Accounting Technicians' proposal for the Government to abolish Entrepreneurs Relief and invest the £3 billion saving in initiatives or reliefs that encourage business start-ups or scale-up activity.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 539","539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149207","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of Turkey's compliance with international law in relation to that country's recent actions in Kurdish occupied northern Syria.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 648","648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149208","2019-10-21","Department for International Trade","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of compliance with arms export licence criteria of weapons sold to Turkey.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 649","649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149209","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the August 2019 British Nuclear Medicine Society's open letter to the Prime Minister on radioisotope delivery, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the costs of radioisotope delivery of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 400","400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149210","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to research conducted by 38 degrees showing that 571 people in Carshalton and Wallington have type 1 diabetes and rely on daily insulin, what assessment his Department has made of the distribution and number of diabetes sufferers in the UK; and what steps his department has taken to secure undisrupted supply of insulin across the UK in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 401","401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149211","2019-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to fulfil the commitment to provide military assistance to Saudi Arabia made in the Written Statement of 23 May 2019, Official Report HCWS716.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 650","650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149212","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with tobacco manufacturers on preventing the smuggling of their product into the UK.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 540","540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149213","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with tobacco manufacturers on the control of their supply chain.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 541","541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149214","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) the accuracy of reports of attacks in Colombia on the headquarters of opposition parties by right wing paramilitary groups and (b) the adequacy of the Colombian’s Government's response to those attacks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 542","542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149215","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to compensate property owners with septic tanks for the expense of (a) upgrading and (b) replacing existing tanks to make their tanks compliant by 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 651","651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149216","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential financial effect on property owners of changes to septic tank regulations which come into force on 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 652","652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149217","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce plastic waste in fast food outlets.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 653","653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149218","2019-10-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he expects construction on the proposed Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre to start; and how much has been allocated from the public purse before construction starts and (a) in total (b) for each of (i) Big Ideas, (ii) Dp9, (iii) Four Communications and (iv) Newgate Communications.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 424","424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149219","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that (a) charities and (b) community interest companies that have contracts with local authorities have an adequate level of unrestricted funding to continue to fulfill their core functions.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 654","654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149220","2019-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an estimate of the cost to the public purse of restoring Local Housing Allowance rates to the 30th percentile.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 456","456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149221","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 8 October 2019 to Question 294108, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the circulation of fake content on Twitter.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 457","457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149222","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the 10 most frequent causes of admission to an NHS hospital; were in the most recent 12 month period for and how many people were admitted for each of those causes, in that time period which data is available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 408","408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149223","2019-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what schemes his Department has introduced to recognise the long service of non-military personnel.","Biography information for David Mundell","David Mundell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 458","458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149224","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that hospitals are used to near capacity before new hospitals are built; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 459","459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149225","2019-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 7 October 2019 to Question 290553 on Sizewell C Power Station, by what framework consumer affordability will be assessed ahead of granting Regulated Asset Base nuclear licences.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 395","395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149226","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average compensation award was for successful child sexual abuse prosecutions which resulted in a criminal compensation order in 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 543","543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149227","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of successful child sexual abuse prosecutions that resulted in a criminal compensation order in 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 544","544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149228","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure safe and adequate levels of staffing across the NHS to protect patient safety.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 460","460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149229","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether she plans to implement in full the EU Directive 2018/0106 on the protection of persons reporting on breaches of European law.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 545","545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149230","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to encourage and support people to enter the nursing profession.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 461","461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149231","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prescriptions for anti-depressants were issued to (a) children aged under 16, (b) teenagers aged 16 to 17 and (c) young people aged 18 to 21 in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 546","546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149232","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to increase the number of medical school places to meet growing demand.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 462","462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149233","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) children under the age of 16, (b) teenagers aged 16 to 17 and (c) young people aged 18 to 21 were prescribed anti-depressants in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 547","547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149234","2019-10-17","House of Commons Commission","2019-10-15","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many complaints under the Independent Complaints and Grievance Scheme which were not previously covered by the scheme have been lodged since the resolution of the House on 17 July 2019.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 548","548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149235","2019-10-17","Cabinet Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to page 31 of the 2013 report entitled Civil Service Reform Plan: One Year On, whether it remains Government policy to appoint all new permanent secretaries on fixed-term tenures; how the civil service implemented that policy; and if he will publish (a) all permanent secretary-level appointments, (b) whether those appointments are fixed-term and (c) when those tenures expire.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 463","463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149236","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to promote the (a) Windrush Helpline and (b) Windrush Compensation Scheme to individuals in (i) India, (ii) Pakistan, (iii) Bangladesh, (iv) Kenya, (v) Singapore, (vi) Malta, (vii) South Africa, (viii) Canada and (ix) Nigeria; and how much has been spent in doing so.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 549","549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149237","2019-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she will publish the terms of reference of her Department's new Serious Case Panel.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 655","655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149238","2019-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether (a) disabled people and (b) representatives from disabled people's organisations will sit on her Department's new independent Serious Case panel.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 656","656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149239","2019-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who will sit on her Department's new independent Serious Case panel.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 657","657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149240","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the merits of (a) splitting Norfolk & Suffolk Foundation Trust into separate trusts and (b) retaining that Trust as a single trust.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 658","658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149241","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with First Group UK on (a) the provision of bus transport in the UK and (b) their plans for the divestment of their UK bus division.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 659","659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149242","2019-10-17","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has plans to extend the provisions of the Bus Services Act 2017 in respect of franchising bus services to local transport authorities other than Combined Authorities.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 660","660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149243","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 8 October 2019 to Question 293577 on Prisons: Fires, how many CPS referrals for prosecution in 2018 involved fire events in prisons.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 550","550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149244","2019-10-17","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report entitled, Missing the safety net, published by Refugee Action, what processes her Department has in place to escalate support for applications that have been delayed beyond her Department's guidelines on the processing of applications; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Sir George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 425","425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149245","2019-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there is a statutory requirement for a (a) military and (b) legal review of the Trident Replacement Decision.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 661","661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149246","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 14 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken to work with partners to develop new models of community funding.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 662","662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149247","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 14 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what plans her Department has to renew its commitment to the Compact.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 663","663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149248","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 14 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken to work with (a) civil society, (b) the Electoral Commission and (c) the charity commission to explore what non-legislative steps could strengthen civil society’s confidence in speaking out.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 664","664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149249","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 15 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken towards convening a cross-government group to work with civil society to establish the principles of effective involvement in the policy-making process.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 665","665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149250","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 15 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken to establish a regular forum for social enterprises to co-ordinate relations with Government.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 666","666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149251","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 15 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what progress her Department has made on working with (a) the Charity Commission and (b) UK Community Foundations to release at least £20 million from inactive charitable trusts to help community organisations.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 667","667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149252","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 15 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what progress her Department has made on working with partners to explore how best to use digital technology to build a stronger and more effective social sector.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 668","668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149253","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 15 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, when her Department plans to provide an update on its approach to support for responsible business.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 669","669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149254","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 15 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken towards establishing a Responsible Business Leadership Group.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 670","670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149255","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 16 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken to support the spread of Citizen Commissioners.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 671","671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149256","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 16 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what progress her Department has made on extending the support offered to public sector teams aspiring to form mutuals to other social sector organisations that wish to deliver public services.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 672","672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149257","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 16 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken towards broadening the range of funding options for community initiatives.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 673","673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149258","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 17 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken towards improving the use of the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 674","674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149259","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 17 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken towards ensuring that the principles of the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 are applied to the whole of government spending and decision-making.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 675","675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149260","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 17 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what progress her Department has made on establishing the potential for the use of social value in grants as well as contracts.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 676","676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149261","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 17 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps her Department has taken on exploring the application of the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 to other areas of public decision-making.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 677","677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149262","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 16 of the Government’s Civil Society Strategy, what steps the Inclusive Economy Unit has taken to follow up the recommendations from the Advisory Group on growing a culture of social impact investment in the UK.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 678","678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149263","2019-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government plans to take to support the automotive industry in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal and exports of UK produced cars become subject to a 10 per cent tariff in line with WTO rules.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 464","464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149264","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the recent increase to the Public Works Loan Board interest rate will apply to existing loans payable by local authorities.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 679","679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149265","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect that increasing the Public Works Loan Board interest rate to 2.8 per cent will have on the (a) number and (b) value of loan applications submitted by local authorities in Wales for capital projects.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 680","680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149266","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many loan applications submitted by Welsh local authorities to the Public Works Loan Board (PWLB) are still viable following the increase to the PWLB interest rate.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 681","681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149267","2019-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it remains his policy to increase (a) female personnel to 15 per cent of intake and (b) Black, Asian and Minority Ethnic personnel to at least 10 percent of total intake by 2020.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 682","682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149268","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to (a) prevent pension phone scams and (b) bring people who undertake pension phone scams to justice.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 683","683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149269","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she had with the Metropolitan police on the revised section 14 notice issued under the Public Order Act 1986 to the Extinction Rebellion autumn uprising event in London on Monday 14 October.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 684","684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149270","2019-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what disability training medical professionals undertaking personal independence payment assessments are required to have in respect to autism.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 685","685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149271","2019-10-17","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to increase women’s rights in developing countries.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 551","551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149272","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many people participated in the National Citizen Service in each local authority area in Surrey in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 552","552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149273","2019-10-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with developers to encourage building on brownfield sites.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 553","553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149274","2019-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support children in conflict zones throughout the world.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 554","554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149275","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps she has taken to expand the size of the Blue Belt.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 555","555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149276","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish a Green Paper on social care.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 686","686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149277","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce waiting times for cervical screening test results.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 556","556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149278","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve detection rates of (a) hepatitis B and (b) hepatitis C.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 557","557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149279","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on recruiting additional GPs in rural locations.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 558","558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149280","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to maintain the level of out-of-hours GP cover in Surrey.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 559","559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149281","2019-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the (a) governance of and (b) humanitarian situation in (i) Uighur and (ii) Xinjiang province, China.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 560","560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149282","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding he is allocating to air ambulance services.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 561","561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149283","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place in the Library data on the number of homeless people (a) in receipt and (b) not in receipt of benefits that have died in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 426","426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149284","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure hospital capacity is increased in line with population growth in the York area.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 562","562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149285","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on anonymous abuse and threats on Twitter.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 465","465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149286","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to undertake a review the exclusion of NHS non-executive directors in protections under the Public Interest Disclosure Act 1998.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 687","687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149287","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to prevent people from establishing anonymous profiles on Twitter.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 466","466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149288","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions officials in her Department have had with their counterparts in the Ministry for Housing, Communities and Local Government on the potential role of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund to (a) reduce and (b) alleviate child poverty.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 563","563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149289","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his Department's consultation entitled, Community pharmacy drug reimbursement reform, published in July 2019, what steps he is taking to undertake an impact assessment of the possible effect of those reforms on the practices of dispensing GPs.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 564","564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149290","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions officials in her Department have had with representatives from Twitter on tackling fake Twitter accounts.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 467","467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149291","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to make it an objective of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund to (a) reduce the level of and (b) alleviate child poverty.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 565","565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149292","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to consult representatives of dispensing GP practices on the proposals in his consultation on community pharmacy drug reimbursement reform.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 566","566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149293","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his 8 May 2019 press release entitled Free meals and activities for 50,000 children over 2019 summer holidays, how much funding he plans to allocate to such projects in summer 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 567","567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149294","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his 8 May 2019 press release entitled Free meals and activities for 50,000 children over 2019 summer holidays, how many unsuccessful bids for that funding were made by organisations based in the North East; what the value of those unsuccessful bids was; and what feedback his Department has given to organisations that made unsuccessful bids.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 568","568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149295","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to ensure the enforcement of UK fishing waters in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 688","688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149296","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 6 February 2019 to Question 215097 on Government Departments: Consultants, how much money has been spent from the public purse on consultancy fees as recorded by the Cabinet Office Spend Analytic Database by each Department since 1 January 2019.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 427","427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149297","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much money was spent from the public purse on the Behavioural Insights Team as recorded by the Cabinet Office Spend Analytic Database by each Department in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 428","428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149298","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using genomics in healthcare for the diagnosis and treatment of blood cancers.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 569","569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149299","2019-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Kuwaiti counterpart on that country's criminalisation of human rights activists; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 409","409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149300","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the effect of UK overseas development assistance on levels of maternal mortality in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 468","468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149301","2019-10-17","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what effect UK overseas development assistance has had on levels of female genital mutilation over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 469","469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149302","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the effect of UK overseas development assistance on levels of contraception prevalence in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 470","470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149303","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the effect of UK overseas development assistance on reducing adolescent birth rates in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 471","471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149304","2019-10-17","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what effect UK overseas development assistance has had on the take up of primary education over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 472","472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149305","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects work to be commenced on the lower level platform lift at Retford station.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 473","473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149306","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which animals will be covered by the ban on trophy hunting imports to the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 570","570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149307","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timeframe is for the ban on trophy hunting imports to come into force.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 571","571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149308","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which countries will be banned from exporting trophies from hunting to the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 572","572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149309","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which countries are allowed to import hunting trophies to the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 573","573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149310","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether animal (a) bones, (b) hands, (c) tails and (d) other parts are included in the ban on hunting trophy imports to the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 574","574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149311","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether imports of trophy hunting can arrive in the UK via other countries to those in which the trophies originated.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 575","575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149312","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to introduce a moratorium on the importation of hunting trophies to the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 576","576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149313","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the import of trophy hunting products by 1 January 2020, without further consultation.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 577","577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149314","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to introduce a bottle deposit scheme to increase the number of plastic bottles reused and recycled.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 429","429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149315","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of high-rise accommodation without a waste shoot that allows for recycling separation on (a) residents’ ability to recycle and (b) UK efforts to tackle climate change; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 689","689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149316","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to make it easier for people who live in high-rise accommodation to recycle.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 690","690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149317","2019-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure consistency between local authorities on the waste that they collect for recycling.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 691","691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149318","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve mental health provision for diabetes patients.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 578","578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149319","2019-10-17","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's Guidance, Anti-knife crime community fund - year 3 (2019-20), last updated on 26 June 2019, when she plans to publish the successful bids for that fund.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 692","692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149320","2019-10-21","Northern Ireland Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of appointing a caretaker devolved government in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 474","474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149321","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of visitor visas were refused in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 579","579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149322","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to widen the scoping criteria for legal aid in family law cases set by the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 580","580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149323","2019-10-21","Ministry of Justice","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure the adequate provision of legal advice in family law cases to reduce the number of litigants in person in the family courts.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 581","581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149324","2019-10-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions officials in his Department have had with representatives of St Helens Council on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 582","582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149325","2019-10-21","Department for Education","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of St Helens Council on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 583","583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149326","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with representatives of St Helens Council on preparations for leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 693","693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149327","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what humanitarian assistance his Department is providing to civilians as a result of Turkey’s military action in the Kurdish controlled territory of northern Syria.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 410","410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149328","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the effect of Turkey’s recent military action in northern Syria on the humanitarian situation in that region.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 411","411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149329","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the number of civilians (a) killed, (b) injured and (c) displaced as result of Turkey’s recent military action in the Kurdish controlled territory of northern Syria.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 412","412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149330","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions her Department has had with representatives of St Helens Council on preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 694","694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149331","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what humanitarian assistance his Department plans to offer to the Kurdistan Regional Government as a result of Turkey’s recent military action in the Kurdish controlled territory of northern Syria.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 413","413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149332","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions he (a) has had and (b) plans to have with his UN Refugee Agency counterparts on the humanitarian situation in the Kurdish controlled territory in northern Syria.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 414","414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149333","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether anti-epileptic drugs are exempted from serious shortage protocols; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the use of such protocols on (a) people with learning disabilities and (b) their families in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 475","475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149334","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 24 July 2019, Official Report, column 1292, how many of those additional police officers will be recruited to (a) the Metropolitan Police and (b) work in Southwark.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 584","584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149335","2019-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's current US dollar contract liability is.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 476","476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149336","2019-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the BBC video report by journalist Fred Scott dated 13 October on three UK orphans in Syria, if she will take steps to return (a) those UK orphans and (b) other UK children in a similar position to the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 585","585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149337","2019-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost was of purchasing nine P-8 Poseidon military aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 477","477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149338","2019-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government's announcement of 15 August 2019 that it would invest £3 billion in purchasing nine Boeing Poseidon P-8A maritime patrol aircraft, what proportion of construction work for the nine aircraft will be carried out in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 478","478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149339","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of anti-epilepsy medications in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 479","479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149340","2019-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent from the public purse on foreign exchange losses in the 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 480","480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149341","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to facilitate the resettlement of (a) vulnerable children and (b) unaccompanied minors from Greek islands.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 415","415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149342","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that Kurdish people in (a) Syria and (b) surrounding regions do not come to harm following the US troop withdrawal from that area.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 695","695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149343","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role Ministers have in the appointment of people to the Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 586","586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149344","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that Kurdish people do not come to harm following the implementation of what Turkish officials are calling the safe zone.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 696","696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149345","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department is in discussion with Greek authorities on additional resettlement places from Greece for (a) unaccompanied minors and (b) migrant children in families.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 416","416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149346","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Ministers have vetoed appointments to the Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 587","587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149347","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is her policy that an individual's support for drugs policy reform is compatible with membership of the Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 588","588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149348","2019-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason universal credit is paid pro-rata when a claimant becomes eligible part way through an assessment period for state pension credit  but not when a claimant becomes eligible for the state pension without state pension credit.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 481","481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149349","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the UK plans to undertake medical evacuations of critically ill children in Greece whose access to adequate and timely healthcare services in that country is obstructed by their migrant status.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 417","417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149350","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the EU Settlement Scheme Statistics dated 22 August 2019, for what reasons 88,900 outstanding applications have yet to be concluded.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 589","589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149351","2019-10-17","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much of the £3.75 million reserved for her Department's March 2019 marketing campaign for the EU settlement scheme was spent on (a) online and (b) offline advertising.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 590","590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149352","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the provision of essential healthcare and mental healthcare for unaccompanied minors in Greece.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 418","418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149353","2019-10-17","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been transferred from Pre-Settled to Settled Status under the EU Settlement Scheme in each month since 1 January 2019.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 591","591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149354","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's funding for voluntary and community sector organisations to support vulnerable and at-risk EEA citizens to apply to the EU Settlement Scheme, what criteria her Department uses to determine whether applicants are (a) vulnerable and (b) at-risk.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 592","592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149355","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the EU Settlement Scheme Statistics dated 22 August 2019, how many of the 88,900 applications that have yet to be concluded have been referred to immigration enforcement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 593","593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149356","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the number of data flow contractual clauses which will need to be arranged by businesses in the UK with businesses in the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 594","594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149357","2019-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Jobcentre staff receive training to identify when a new claimant would be entitled to (a) new-style employment and support allowance and (b) new-style jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 482","482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149358","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number and proportion of economically active people claiming universal claimant in the Vale of Clwyd constituency in August (a) 2018 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 430","430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149359","2019-10-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the British Horseracing Authority on changes to reduce the death rate of horses.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 483","483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149360","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with the office of Wendy Williams on a timetable for taking delivery of the final report of the Windrush lessons learned review.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 697","697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149361","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the matters raised in the joint letter of 1 August 2019 from the British Nuclear Medicine Society and the Royal College of Radiologists to the Prime Minister entitled continued supply of medical radioisotopes in the event of a no-deal Brexit.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 402","402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149362","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make it her policy to produce a long-term plan for the provision of youth services.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 698","698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149363","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to increase funding for local authorities to deliver (a) the provision of youth workers on a long-term basis and (b) other core youth work.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 699","699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149364","2019-10-21","Ministry of Defence","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to place the order for the first fleet solid support ships; and how many of those ships he plans to order.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 396","396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149365","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the joint letter of 1 August 2019 from the British Nuclear Medicine Society and the Royal College of Radiologists to the Prime Minister entitled continued supply of medical radioisotopes in the event of a no-deal Brexit, if the NHS will allocate additional funding to NHS trusts to cover increased costs incurred for the supply of medical isotopes in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 403","403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149366","2019-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Prime Minister's proposed EU exit deal, what assessment his Department has made of the economic effect on businesses in Northern Ireland of the imposition of checks on both the North-South and East-West border.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 404","404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149367","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the joint letter of 1 August 2019 from the British Nuclear Medicine Society and the Royal College of Radiologists to the Prime Minister entitled continued supply of medical radioisotopes in the event of a no-deal Brexit, if his Department will respond to the concerns raised in that letter about the timely delivery of medical radioisotopes to the North of England, the South West of England, Wales, Scotland and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 405","405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149368","2019-10-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to her Department's News story of 10 July 2019, Review launched into statutory guidance for local authorities on providing youth services,  what steps she plans to take to actively involve the views of young people in need of such services.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 700","700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149369","2019-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Prime Minister's proposed EU exit deal, when his Department last met with representatives of Northern Irish industry to discuss the effect on that industry of the imposition of a North-South and an East-West border.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 419","419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149370","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to respond to the letter to the Prime Minister of 12 September 2019 from the hon. Member for Birmingham Northfield and other hon. Members and Peers on Prime Minister Netanyahu's announcement that he intends to annex the Jordan Valley to Israel.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 420","420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149371","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Sri Lankan counterpart on the status of Tamil people in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 431","431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149372","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the UK Government is taking to support the protection of human rights of Tamil communities in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 432","432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149373","2019-10-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on reviewing the EU-Turkey refugee agreement; and what steps he is taking to ensure the safety of refugees in Turkey and the surrounding region.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 484","484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149374","2019-10-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital Media Culture and Sport, whether she has made an assessment of the implications for her policy on commencing Part 3 of the Digital Economy Act 2017 of the 26 September 2019 research by the BBFC in its role as designated age-verification regulator; and when she plans to lay the BBFC guidance on age-verification arrangements.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 595","595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149375","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of people hold a UK passport; and what her estimate is of the number and proportion of UK citizens who do not hold a passport.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 596","596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149376","2019-10-21","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of UK citizens aged over 17 who (a) hold and (b) do not hold a full or provisional UK driving licence.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 597","597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149377","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) findings, (b) conclusions and (c) recommendations of the report entitled, Duty of care: midwives' experience of the NHS charging regime, published on 9 September 2019 by Maternity Action; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 598","598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149378","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effect on mental health of anonymous (a) abuse and (b) threats made on Twitter.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 485","485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149379","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have had with the (i) Academy of Royal Colleges, (ii) Royal College of General Practitioners and (c) Royal College of Midwives on those organisations' call for the NHS overseas visitors charging regime to be suspended pending an independent review of its impact on individual and public health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 599","599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149380","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 8 October 2019 to Question 294115 on Children: Social Media, if he will make an assessment of the effect on children's mental health of anonymous (a) abuse and (b) threats made on Twitter.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 486","486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149381","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 30 April 2019 to Question 246493 on Health Services: Foreign Nationals, whether the review document shared with Deighton Pierce Glynn setting out the findings of his Department’s December 2017 review of the functioning of the NHS (Charges to Overseas Visitors) (Amendment) Regulations 2017 was shared with any other party during the 2018 judicial review of that policy.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 600","600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149382","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether (a) local authorities or (b) Government will bear the cost of producing a local electoral identity document.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 701","701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149383","2019-10-17","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) volume of passenger data which will be transferred from Virgin and Stagecoach to new West Coast Partnership operator First/Trenitalia before the start of the new franchise in December 2019 and (b) effect of the level of data transferred on the quality of passenger service under that new franchise.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 601","601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149384","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps he is taking to integrate nutrition into his Department's programmes in Rwanda; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 421","421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149385","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment he has made of the humanitarian situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 422","422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149386","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the representatives of large companies on their ability to assess the employment status of their workers for the purpose of IR35 rules; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 423","423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149387","2019-10-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in Makerfield constituency have (a) opted out after being auto-enrolled into a workplace pension and (b) saved more than the auto-enrolment minimum contribution.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 602","602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149388","2019-10-17","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the credit ratings of UK rolling stock companies (a) Porterbrook, (b) Angel Trains, (c) Eversholt Rail and (d) Rock Rail and the costs at which those companies can respectively secure finance.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 603","603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149389","2019-10-17","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect Operation Brock will have on congestion levels on the Kent (a) road network and (b) economy.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 604","604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149390","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 7 October 2019 to Question 292911 on Dietary Supplements: Expenditure, in what situations and to treat which illnesses are the probiotics listed in that Answer prescribed.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 605","605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149391","2019-10-17","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent updates he has had from the Civil Aviation Authority on their assessment of the safety of the Boeing 737 Max airliners.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 606","606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149392","2019-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether her Department has plans to review the traffic light system limits on seismic disturbance.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 702","702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149393","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding his Department plans to make available to (a) healthcare in the North East of England, (b) healthcare in Sunderland and (c) the South Tyneside and Sunderland Hospital Trust in the next five years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 607","607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149394","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to make funding available to South Tyneside and Sunderland Hospital Trust  for infrastructure expenditure.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 608","608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149395","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the findings of the Cruelty Free International and SOKO Tierschutz investigation of contract animal testing facility the Laboratory of Pharmacology and Toxicology in Germany.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 609","609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149396","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hate crimes were recorded in each category in (a) 2010 and (b) the most recent period for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 433","433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149397","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 25 March 2019 to Question 236341, Health Services: Foreign Nationals, what the total sum was that NHS trusts (a) charged to and (b) recovered from patients not covered by the EHIC scheme under the NHS overseas visitors charging regime in (i) England, (ii) Scotland and (iii) Wales in each financial year from 2015-16 to 2019-20.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 610","610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149398","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to inspect UK contract animal testing laboratories with reference to the recent findings of the Cruelty Free International and SOKO Tierschutz investigation of the contract animal testing facility Laboratory of Pharmacology and Toxicology in Germany.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 611","611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149399","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the supply of Lisdexamphetamine.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 703","703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149400","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any Government Departments or agencies (a) have sponsored and (b) are sponsoring any research at the Laboratory of Pharmacology and Toxicology contract animal testing facility in Germany.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 612","612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149401","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure there will be an adequate supply of Lisdexamphetamine in the event of the UK’s departure from the EU on 31 October 2019 without a deal.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 704","704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149402","2019-10-17","Department for Transport","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the (a) adequacy of the arrangements for the transfer of passenger data between rail franchises and (b) effect a shortfall in the transfer of data has on the quality of passenger service.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 613","613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149403","2019-10-21","Home Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on whether animals housed at the Laboratory of Pharmacology and Toxicology in Germany have been exported from the UK.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 614","614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149404","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent from the public purse on voter ID pilot schemes.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 434","434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149405","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on the local economy of his Department's decision to not support a finance package for Sirius Minerals' Woodsmith Mine project.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 615","615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149406","2019-10-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost to Sirius Minerals PLC of the decision by his Department not to support a finance package for that company's Woodsmith Mine project.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 616","616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149407","2019-10-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the revised Joint Spatial Plan for South Gloucestershire allows the building of affordable homes in the Filton and Bradley Stoke area.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 617","617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149408","2019-10-21","Cabinet Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the evaluation of Voter ID Pilots 2019, published in July 2019, if he will publish the cost data from all pilot authorities.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 618","618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149409","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of reducing pool betting duty to 10 per cent.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 487","487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149410","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 4 March 2019 to Question 226730 on Burma: Human Trafficking, what assurances he has received from his Burmese counterpart that the upgrades to the women and children health ward at Sittwe General Hospital in Burma will also be beneficial to the Rohingya community.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 705","705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149411","2019-10-21","Department for International Development","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 4 March 2019 to Question 226730 on Burma: Human Trafficking, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Ministry of Health in Burma on reported apartheid practices at Sittwe General Hospital in that country.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 706","706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149412","2019-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what policies are in place to ensure that staff of his Department based in Burma do not use Burmese military owned companies to provide goods and services.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 707","707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149413","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to (a) encourage and (b) support people to enter the nursing profession.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 708","708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149414","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that adequate levels of staffing are maintained throughout the NHS to protect patient safety.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 709","709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149415","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received on the loyalty penalty in the mortgage market; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 435","435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149416","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to attract more people to work in the NHS.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 710","710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149417","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to help tackle the loyalty penalty in the mortgage market.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 436","436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149418","2019-10-21","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the loyalty penalty in the mortgage market.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 437","437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149419","2019-10-17","Department for Education","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress the Government has made on introducing a Takaful-based university fee funding structure.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 438","438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149420","2019-10-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the supply of Agomelatine.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 711","711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149421","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care what steps he is taking to ensure the adequacy of the supply of Agomelatine in the event that the UK leaves the EU on 31 October 2019 without a deal.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 712","712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149422","2019-10-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children and teenagers that have benefitted from social prescribing services since July 2018.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 713","713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149423","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many formal complaints the Financial Conduct Authority has received from consumers in relation to the (a) sale and (b) distribution of Exchange Traded Notes that reference cryptoassets.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 488","488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149424","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many formal complaints from consumers the Financial Ombudsman Service has (a) received and (b) upheld in relation to the (i) sale and (ii) distribution of Exchange Traded Notes that reference cryptoassets.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 489","489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149425","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many consultation responses the Financial Conduct Authority has received in opposition to the proposals in the consultation entitled, CP19/22 prohibiting the sale to retail clients of investment products that reference cryptoassets.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 490","490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149426","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Financial Conduct Authority’s proposed ban of cryptoasset investment products for retail investors on (a) Revolut and (b) other challenger banks that offer products linked to cryptoassets.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 491","491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149427","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the recommendations of the Cryptoassets Taskforce's 2018 report in relation to enabling innovators in the financial sector that play by the rules to thrive.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 492","492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149428","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether issuers of Exchange Traded Notes are required to comply with (a) the EU Prospectus Directive, (b) Listing Rules for the NASDNAQ and (c) Nordic Growth Markets.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 493","493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149429","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK’s status as a FinTech hub of the proposals by the Financial Conduct Authority to ban the sale of cryptoasset investment products for retail investors.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 494","494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149430","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK’s status as a FinTech hub of innovative Exchange Traded Notes  issuers (a) remaining and (b) establishing operations in the UK.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 495","495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149431","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of companies in the Financial Conduct Authority’s (FCA) Regulatory Sandbox that would be affected by the FCA’s proposed ban on the sale to retail clients of investment products that reference cryptoassets.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 496","496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149432","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the evidential basis was for the Financial Conduct Authority statement in its consultation that Exchange Traded Notes that reference cryptoassets present risks to investors that are similar to Contract for Difference products which reference cryptoassets.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 497","497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149433","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason the Financial Conduct Authority's cost benefit analysis in its consultation entitled CP19/22: Restricting the sale to retail clients of investment products that reference cryptoassets did not include the benefits of Exchange Traded Notes that reference cryptoassets.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 498","498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149434","2019-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-10-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to UN General Assembly's First Committee on International Disarmament and International Security 2018 joint statement on the impact of explosive weapons in populated areas, whether the UK will become a signatory to that statement before the end of 2019.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 439","439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1149435","2019-10-17","Treasury","2019-10-15","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the Financial Conduct Authority’s compliance with (a) section 138I of the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 and (b) the powers under Article 42 of the Markets in Financial Instruments Regulation in relation to the proposed ban on the sale to retail clients of investment products that reference cryptoassets.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2019/20 499","499"
