"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48696","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect on the number of people subject to improved incentives to work of the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196519","196519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48697","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has issued to jobcentres on how claimant commitments should take into account the caring responsibilities of single parents.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196496","196496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48698","2014-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, columns 103-4W, on state retirement pensions, if he will assess whether a woman born on 6 April 1981 who was in continuous employment from her 21st birthday until her state pension age as derived in line with the practice outlined in the Pensions Bill, had worked consistently in contracted-in employment for 30 hours a week in a role which paid the National Minimum Wage, had average female life expectancy, in line with the most recent ONS population projections, and was subject to any other assumptions used in the Impact Assessment which accompanied the Pensions Bill, would receive a different level of pension at the point of retirement under the Single Tier mechanism than they would have expected under the current pension system; and what the difference in the level of pension would be.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196652","196652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48699","2014-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of jobseeker's allowance claimants were subject to sanctions in each county in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196651","196651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48700","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research he has commissioned on the number of single parents on jobseeker's allowance who have been sanctioned; what the reasons are for such sanctions; and what the proportion of such sanctions that have been overturned is.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196501","196501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48701","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which Minister in his Department has responsibility for assessing the effect of his Department's policies on the welfare of children.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196502","196502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48702","2014-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to make it easier to report benefit fraud allegations.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196633","196633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48703","2014-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to increase understanding of pensions and retirement planning amongst women.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196632","196632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48704","2014-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what happens to a Remploy worker personal budget if the full amount is not used by the individual within 18 months.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196631","196631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48705","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department uses to measure the performance of each Jobcentre Plus office.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196736","196736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48706","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what budget is allocated to each Jobcentre Plus office to reimburse jobseekers' travel expenses; and how each such budget is decided.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196735","196735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48707","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department uses a working assumption for the timescale for a work capability assessment report to be processed by Atos.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196745","196745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48708","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in which circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196606","196606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48709","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many businesses in Skipton and Ripon constituency will be issued with staging dates for automatic enrolment between 1 April 2014 and 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Julian Smith","Julian Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196597","196597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48710","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many representations he has received opposing the removal of customer access phones from Jobcentre Plus offices; which Jobcentre Plus offices serving constituents of Ogmore constituency have been affected by the removal of customer access phones from such offices; and how many people in Ogmore constituency are being serviced by each such Jobcentre Plus office.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196609","196609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48711","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of businesses in Skipton and Ripon constituency have not yet met their staging date for automatic enrolment for workplace pensions.","Biography information for Julian Smith","Julian Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196596","196596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48712","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken was between an application being made and benefit paid for (a) attendance allowance, (b) bereavement benefits, (c) carer's allowance, (d) disability living allowance, (e) employment and support allowance, (f) jobseeker's allowance, (g) maternity benefits, (h) housing benefit, (i) council tax benefit and (j) pension credit in the most recent period for which figures are available in (i) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (ii) Scotland and (iii) the UK.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196601","196601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48713","2014-04-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that the staging dates for automatic enrolment for workplace pensions are being effectively communicated to businesses in Skipton and Ripon constituency.","Biography information for Julian Smith","Julian Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196671","196671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48714","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people currently receiving a UK state pension and living in the UK who would move abroad if pensions were up-rated for all UK pensioners living overseas.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196561","196561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48715","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 April 2014, Official Report, columns 218-9W, on social security benefits, when he expects to make available the requested data.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196518","196518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48716","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants in the work-related activity group in (a) Scotland, (b) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (c) North Lanarkshire and (d) the UK (i) successfully and (ii) unsuccessfully appealed against the imposition of a sanction in (A) the two years prior to December 2012 and (B) each year since December 2012 including the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196528","196528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48717","2014-04-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions were applied to jobseeker's allowance claimants in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Dundee in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim McGovern","Jim McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196554","196554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48112","2014-04-28","Attorney General","2014-04-10","To ask the Attorney General, what levels of stock the Law Officers' Departments hold of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196196","196196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48113","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196195","196195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48114","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many small businesses in High Peak constituency have received support from the Regional Growth Fund.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196243","196243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48115","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses were registered in High Peak constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196244","196244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48116","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who made the decisions and on what basis were the decisions made on how many shares would go to each priority investor, each institutional investor and each retail investor in respect of the privatisation of Royal Mail.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196282","196282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48117","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much in cash terms and what proportion of total university funding came from (a) domestic tuition fees, (b) foreign student fees, (c) public funding and (d) external sponsorship in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196285","196285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48118","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff in the Hull Official Receiver's office have been offered voluntary redundancy terms.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196333","196333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48119","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many directors of each Official Receiver's office were disqualified in the year ending 31 March 2014.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196336","196336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48120","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many disqualification reports were submitted by each Official Receiver's office in the year ending 31 March 2014.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196334","196334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48121","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the monetary value to the wider economy of a bankruptcy restriction order or undertaking.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196337","196337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48122","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many statements of fact were submitted by each Official Receiver's office in the year ending 31 March 2014.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196338","196338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48123","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will (a) publish and (b) provide to the recognised trade unions, a detailed cost analysis for the closure of Hull Official Receiver's office.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196339","196339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48124","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what facilities his Department has identified to allow (a) company directors, (b) bankrupts and (c) others to be interviewed locally after the closure of the Hull Official Receiver's office.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196343","196343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48125","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the annual (a) total cost and (b) cost per (i) female and (ii) male employee of maternity and paternity leave.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196413","196413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48126","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196457","196457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48127","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received on illegal pump imports into the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196444","196444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48128","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Insolvency Service paid for fruitless payments in respect of individual and corporate insolvencies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196416","196416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48129","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) location, (b) number of staff including remote workers and (c) number of full-time equivalent staff was of each Official Receiver's office.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196417","196417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48130","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the potential cost of buying out the lease for the Hull Official Receiver's office.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196418","196418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48131","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on which date authority was given for the closure of the Hull Official Receiver's office; and who gave such authority.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196419","196419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48132","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what negotiations took place with trade unions prior to the decision to close the Hull Official Receiver's office; and on what dates those negotiations took place.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196420","196420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48133","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to ensure that the Official Receiver's statutory duties are completed in Hull and the East Riding of Yorkshire once the Hull Official Receiver's office is closed.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196421","196421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48134","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what review was undertaken of the Hull Official Receiver's office before his Department's decision to close that office; what the timescale for that review was; and what evidence was collected in that review.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196422","196422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48135","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what alternative office accommodation was sought in the Hull area to reduce the operating costs of the Hull Official Receiver's office.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196430","196430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48136","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people of Latin American ethnicity in (a) the UK, (b) England and Wales, (c) London, (d) each London borough and (e) Streatham constituency.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196454","196454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48137","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans his Department has to ensure that the Latin American community is better recognised in official statistics.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196455","196455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48138","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196458","196458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48139","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions the Office for National Statistics has had with EU counterparts about differences in the way projected growth is estimated.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196291","196291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48140","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196197","196197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48141","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196218","196218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48142","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many VAT431NB claims have been submitted in each of the last 32 quarters.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196287","196287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48143","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many VAT431C claims have been submitted in each of the last 32 quarters.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196288","196288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48144","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to reduce the amount of stamp duty paid by first-time home buyers.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196306","196306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48145","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the loss to the public purse as a result of illicit, illegal and smuggled tobacco in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196391","196391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48146","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196467","196467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48147","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average cost is of recovery of £1 of debt by HM Revenue and Customs debt management staff.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196353","196353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48148","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the staffing levels at HM Revenue and Customs debt management collectors were in (a) debt management telephony centres, (b) field force, (c) debt collection intervention teams, (d) debt technical offices and (e) late stage intervention in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196351","196351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48149","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average commission paid across Government is of recovery of £1 of debt by private debt collection agencies.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196352","196352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48150","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had on the future of the Landfill Communities Fund.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196355","196355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48151","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the performance of projects funded by the Landfill Communities Fund; what plans he has for the future of the fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196348","196348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48152","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the value of Landfill Community Fund grants to projects in (a) Dudley North constituency, (b) Dudley Borough, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196349","196349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48153","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average annual (a) cost of employing HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) debt management collectors and (b) value of interventions undertaken by individual HMRC debt management collectors are in (i) debt management telephony centres, (ii) field force, (iii) debt collection intervention teams, (iv) debt technical offices and (v) late stage intervention.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196354","196354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48154","2014-04-28","Church Commissioners","2014-04-10","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what levels of stock the Church Commissioners hold of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196198","196198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48155","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196199","196199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48156","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to ensure continuity in local authority provision of youth services during commissioning processes to tender those services.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196224","196224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48157","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the planning system gives priority to creating additional school places.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196238","196238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48158","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average number of people on a waiting list for an allotment for every 100 plots available in England.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196308","196308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48159","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average length of time a person has been on a waiting list for an allotment in each year since 2010 in England.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196309","196309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48160","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been self-built in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196286","196286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48161","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate has he made of the proportion of youth services commissioned by local authorities from (a) in-house bids from directly-funded providers, (b) voluntary organisation and (c) private-sector companies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196256","196256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48162","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people of no faith are consulted and listened to when formulating policy on faith and communities.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196267","196267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48163","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications he has (a) received and (b) approved for the disposal of allotment sites in each year since 2010 in England; and in what local authority each such site was located.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196310","196310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48164","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people on a waiting list for an allotment in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196311","196311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48165","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to help older people with their housing needs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196350","196350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48166","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funds his Department has allocated (a) for identifying troubled families and (b) in performance payments for turning those families around to each local authority participating in the Troubled Families Programme to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196481","196481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48167","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to give local authorities greater powers to deal with the consumption of legal highs in a public place; and what support he is providing to councils who wish to put by-laws in place to prevent such consumption.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196379","196379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48168","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of his Department's staff excluding non-departmental public bodies were (a) women in top management posts women, (b) women, (c) black and minority ethnic and (d) disabled.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196415","196415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48169","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will direct the Leasehold Advisory Service to co-operate with the Leasehold Knowledge Partnership and the Campaign Against Retirement Leasehold Exploitation on providing advice to leaseholders.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196396","196396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48170","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will direct the Leasehold Advisory Service to cease carrying advertising for or links to the services of Benjamin Mire or Trust Property Management.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196397","196397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48171","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to appoint a new chariman to the Leasehold Advisory Service.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196398","196398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48172","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196459","196459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48173","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196460","196460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48174","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he has made an assessment of the recommendations contained in the Association of Business Recovery Professionals publication entitled Level Playing Field: SMEs, taxpayers, and the Football Creditors Rule.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196373","196373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48175","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ratify the Hague Convention for the Protection of Cultural Property in the Event of Armed Conflict and its two Protocols.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196240","196240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48176","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196200","196200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48177","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to prevent or reduce nuisance telephone calls.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196456","196456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48178","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196201","196201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48179","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) associated costs and (b) utility of the Trident Alternatives Review.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196225","196225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48180","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when Ministers in his last met their counterparts from (a) Norway, (b) Finland and (c) Sweden.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196262","196262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48181","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Latvia, (b) Lithuania and (c) Estonia about strengthening defence and security relationships with those countries.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196264","196264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48182","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether military training given to the Burmese Army by UK advisers advises soldiers to refuse orders that could result in human rights abuses.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196319","196319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48183","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the service complaints investigation teams there are in each branch of the armed forces; what their qualifications are; what training is provided to them; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196362","196362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48184","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many equal opportunities investigation officers there are in each branch of the armed forces; what their qualifications are; what training is provided to them; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196361","196361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48185","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of readiness to defend its Overseas Territories in the event of attack.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196321","196321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48186","2014-04-28","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-04-10","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what levels of stock his Office holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196202","196202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48187","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196203","196203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48188","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to promote the reputation and status of youth work.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196223","196223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48189","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been removed from their parents by social services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jeremy Browne","Mr Jeremy Browne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196237","196237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48190","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures are in place to check whether the decision made by Somerset County Council on safeguarding children are fair in their treatment of parents.","Biography information for Mr Jeremy Browne","Mr Jeremy Browne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196246","196246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48191","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what resource is available to parents who believe that Social Services departments are behaving unreasonably in pursuing their children's safeguarding activities.","Biography information for Mr Jeremy Browne","Mr Jeremy Browne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196247","196247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48192","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the performance of the children and families department in Somerset County Council.","Biography information for Mr Jeremy Browne","Mr Jeremy Browne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196248","196248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48193","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the merits of requiring all schools in the UK to fly the Union flag.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196305","196305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48194","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to deal with emotional neglect of children.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196374","196374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48195","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196461","196461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48196","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what mechanisms his Department has put in place to ensure that (a) schools, (b) nurseries and (c) learning establishments receiving any funds or endorsement from his Department teach evolution and do not teach that creationism is scientifically valid.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196449","196449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48197","2014-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196462","196462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48198","2014-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Answer of 14 January 2013, Official Report, column 481W, on biofuels, is biomass feedstock origin recorded in the renewable energy planning database; and what his policy is on the use of biomass feedstock sourced from outside the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196358","196358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48199","2014-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the costs associated with supporting new nuclear power stations in England and Wales will be levied on energy consumers in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196414","196414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48200","2014-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his Answer of 16 January 2014, Official Report, columns 994-5, whether his Department is seeking to promote first or second generation biomass and biofuels; and whether his Department has made a sustainability assessment of both forms.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196359","196359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48201","2014-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information his Department holds on the incidence of power cuts by (a) county and (b) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196271","196271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48202","2014-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to ensure that the renewable heat incentive scheme is targeted on households most in need of help with their energy bills.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196236","196236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48203","2014-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196204","196204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48204","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196205","196205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48205","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what date cage trapping and shooting of badgers was implemented alongside the free-shooting of badgers in the pilot badger cull in Somerset in 2013; and on what date free shooting had started in that cull.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196191","196191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48206","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how soon the cage trapping and shooting of badgers was implemented alongside the freeshooting of badgers after the commencement of the pilot badger cull in Gloucestershire in 2013; and what authorisation from the Department was required.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196192","196192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48207","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to (a) protect and (b) police the shell fisheries industry in the Wash area.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196277","196277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48208","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations his Department has received from bodies supporting (a) hydraulic dredging and (b) hand-raking methods of cockle fishing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196276","196276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48209","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of prong collars on the welfare of dogs.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196297","196297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48210","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, Official Report, column 1005, what assessment he has made of how the farming and forestry improvement scheme might help those affected by flooding.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196340","196340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48211","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196463","196463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48212","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has in place to be executed in the event of further Russian aggression on the Ukrainian border.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196320","196320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48213","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure UK embassies, high commissions and consulates are promoting trade with the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196322","196322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48214","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Icelandic counterpart on strengthening UK-Icelandic business relations.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196325","196325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48215","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to take steps against Spain other than to appeals to the Government should incursions on the UK border continue.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196316","196316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48216","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the effects of delays in the organisation of the referendum in Western Sahara on the security situation in that region.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196298","196298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48217","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on human rights in Western Sahara.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196299","196299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48218","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to condemn the Russian annexation of Crimea in addition to steps taken with the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196300","196300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48219","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives from the European Commission on European sanctions on Russia.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196301","196301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48220","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Russian counterpart on the situation in Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196302","196302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48221","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for the UK of international sanctions against Russia.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196303","196303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48222","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Burma on protecting Burmese soldiers who refuse orders which could result in human rights abuses.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196328","196328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48223","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in North Korea on freedom of religion.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196307","196307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48224","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Iranian authorities about the persecution and detention of members of the Bahá'í faith in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196289","196289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48225","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his German and US counterparts on securing the unconditional release of Pastor Saeed Abedini from prison in Iran.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196290","196290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48226","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Latvia, (b) Lithuania and (c) Estonia about strengthening defence and security relationships with those countries.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196265","196265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48227","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Norway, (b) Finland and (c) Sweden about the security situation in the Scandinavian region.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196263","196263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48228","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196206","196206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48229","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the role independent pharmacies play in relieving pressures on other health and welfare services; and what steps he has taken to disseminate best practice.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196239","196239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48230","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what authority the Health and Social Care and Information Centre requires for the disclosure to other bodies of identifiable hospital episode statistics data.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196232","196232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48231","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196208","196208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48232","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the ratio of GPs to patients is in each clinical commissioning group area in England.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196193","196193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48233","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate has he made of the cost to the economy of untreated mental illness.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196255","196255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48234","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of dementia awareness training in the health and social care sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196253","196253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48235","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that numbers of community children's nurses meet future demand; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196251","196251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48236","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children of what age have spent three months or more continuously in hospital in each local health authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196252","196252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48237","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS funding is allocated to (a) mental and (b) physical health care.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196254","196254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48238","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on NHS service provision for seriously ill children and their families of the specialist senior nurses posts funded by the charity Well Child.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196249","196249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48239","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure NHS staff have the appropriate training to communicate effectively and compassionately with patients at difficult times in the diagnosis and treatment process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196260","196260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48240","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on diagnosis rates of brain tumours in the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196261","196261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48241","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to increase public understanding of the services offered by independent pharmacies.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196241","196241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48242","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria his Department use to define illness as mental as opposed to physical.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196245","196245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48243","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will consider creating the role of bereavement midwives to work exclusively with parents who have experienced the death of their baby shortly before, during or after birth; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196273","196273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48244","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that information on bereavement support and services is made available to parents who have suffered the loss of a baby.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196274","196274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48245","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the sufficiency of access to imagery scanning for diagnosing brain tumours; and if he will issue revised guidance on when to refer a patient for a scan with the aim of raising diagnosis rates and decreasing mortality rates.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196258","196258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48246","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage international collaboration in research and the sharing of best practice on quality of life for patients diagnosed with brain tumours.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196259","196259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48247","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the benefits of all expectant mothers being assigned one specific midwife for the duration of their pregnancy in ensuring (a) continued care, (b) correct information being received and (c) prevention of stillbirth.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196272","196272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48248","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the sufficiency of access to information about support and services for people diagnosed with a brain tumour; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196257","196257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48249","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward from 42 weeks the period for inducing labour in at risk expectant mothers.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196280","196280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48250","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for individual (a) benzodiazepine drugs and (b) antidepressants were dispensed in the community in 2013.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196292","196292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48251","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the medicinal use of cannabis.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196293","196293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48252","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many warfarin patients attending anti-coagulant clinics had to wait for a prescriber to administer vitamin K in the most recent year for which information is available; what the average waiting times for those patients was; and how many of those patients had to go to accident and emergency because a prescriber was not available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196283","196283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48253","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason no formal minutes were taken of the meeting of the national advisory group to the Keogh Mortality Review of 5 July 2013.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196294","196294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48254","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage investment in antibiotic resistance research and development.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196284","196284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48255","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department collects on referrals to services providing independent mental health advocacy under the Mental Health Act 2009; what annual reporting processes he has put in place in relation to those referrals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196327","196327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48256","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he is satisfied with the current levels of recruitment to midwifery; and what steps he is taking to encourage recruitment of midwives.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196275","196275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48257","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the performance of cancer services against statements 11 and 12 in the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence Breast cancer quality standard.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196367","196367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48258","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what methods of data collection his Department uses to measure the performance of services against each of the 13 statements in the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence Breast cancer quality standard.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196365","196365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48259","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the overall performance of cancer services against the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence Breast cancer quality standard.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196363","196363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48260","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reduction of avoidable harm by better medicines reconciliation for hospital patients with Parkinson's.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196344","196344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48261","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that future iterations of the Cancer Patient Experience Survey enable the responses of patients with primary and secondary cancer to be analysed separately.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196364","196364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48262","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had on the potential for Patient Reported Outcome Measures to be used to measure improvements in outcomes for breast cancer patients.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196366","196366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48263","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the online system for members of the public to compare hospitals on the basis of safety indicators will include information on cases in which patients with conditions such as Parkinson's have not received their medication on time; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196342","196342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48264","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve reporting of instances in which the medication regimes of hospital patients with Parkinson's are disrupted through delays or errors in medicines reconciliation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196360","196360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48265","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what pharmaceutical companies supplied the Government's stockpile of Tamiflu.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196368","196368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48266","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times NHS England has discussed parity of esteem between mental and physical health at board meetings in the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196389","196389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48267","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England's review of Tier 4 Children and Adolescent Mental Health Services provision will be complete.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196387","196387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48268","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the polypill.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196388","196388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48269","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions officials in his Department have had with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) on the development of NICE's highly specialised technologies programme since 1 January 2014; what the content of those discussions was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196411","196411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48270","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196464","196464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48271","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who will have responsibility for cervical screening under the forthcoming Public Health England commissioning framework.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196446","196446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48272","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of teenage pregnancy co-ordinators in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196447","196447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48273","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made over the last 12 months on delivering the Prime Minister's pledge that cancer patients will have access to innovative radiotherapy techniques from April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196472","196472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48274","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the increase in demand for child and adolescent mental health following the launch of the MindEd e-portal; and what steps it is taking to accommodate that increase.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196448","196448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48275","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect that new public health structures are having on community obstetrics and gynaecology (a) workforce planning and (c) continuing professional development.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196445","196445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48276","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 120W, on haemolytic uraemic syndrome, what discussions NHS England has had with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) since 1 January 2014 on NICE's appraisal of eculizumab; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196426","196426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48277","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his policy that recommendations of the Francis Report should apply to mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196480","196480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48278","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of the report of the Independent Commission on Mental Health and Policing commissioned by the Metropolitan Police Commissioner.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196478","196478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48279","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that health professionals are trained in the identification and notification of (a) all special educational needs and (b) educational needs related to cerebral palsy in children under two years of age.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196404","196404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48280","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 31 March 2014, Official Report, column 491W, on medical treatments, what technology appraisals were conducted by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence in the last five years; what the most plausible cost per quality adjusted life-year for each such appraisal was; what the estimated eligible patient population was for each appraised indication; on which appraisals end-of-life criteria were applied in each final appraisal determination; and on which date each such appraisal was (a) initiated and (b) concluded.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196429","196429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48281","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) ensuring that assessments of treatments by NICE conducted through (a) normal technology appraisals and (b) highly specialised technology appraisals is consistent in its (i) engagement with stakeholders and (ii) wider methodological approaches.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196428","196428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48282","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (NICE) assesses the cost-effectiveness of an intervention when the data available are uncertain; what assessment NICE has made of the average range around the most-plausible cost-per-QALY in its technology appraisals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196424","196424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48283","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 120W, on haemolytic uraemic syndrome, for what reasons it was felt that further advice was needed on the overall cost implications, benefits and affordability of eculizumab; when it was first concluded that such further advice was needed; for what reasons the seeking of that advice was delayed until the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence took on responsibility for assessing highly specialised technologies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196427","196427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48284","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she intends to take in response to the judgment in the High Court of 9 April 2014 by Lord Justice Popplewell on asylum support; and by what date she plans to set out that response.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196385","196385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48285","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of cigarettes, (b) volume of roll-your own tobacco and (c) value of the (i) cigarettes and (ii) tobacco smuggled into the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196390","196390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48286","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what powers advocates will have during the pilot advocate scheme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196476","196476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48287","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the pilot advocate scheme will begin.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196477","196477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48288","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish the terms of reference for the trial advocate scheme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196473","196473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48289","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will consider extending the trial advocate scheme to unaccompanied children.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196474","196474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48290","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the pilot scheme for advocates will be independent of local authorities.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196475","196475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48291","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in what circumstances she uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools she uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196465","196465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48292","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have received (a) redundancy payments and (b) pension enhancements since 2010; and what the cost of each such type of payment is.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196317","196317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48293","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure police officers record all crimes they deal with.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196323","196323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48294","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was claimed by Police and Crime Commissioners in expenses in 2013-14.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196324","196324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48295","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will introduce legislative proposals to protect police dogs by recognising them as an extension of their handler as a police officer.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196315","196315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48296","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of violent crimes were committed by non-British nationals in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196304","196304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48297","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of rural crime; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196281","196281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48298","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Israeli citizens were found to be working in the UK without an appropriate visa in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196266","196266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48299","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have arrived in the UK under the Syrian refugee programme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196250","196250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48300","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what levels of stock her Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196209","196209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48301","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's total budget for assisted voluntary returns projects is for the current financial year, and what has been the total budget for such projects in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196222","196222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48302","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers there were, by country of origin, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196226","196226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48303","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers, by country of origin, have been waiting for a decision on their application for asylum for (a) one and (b) more than five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196227","196227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48304","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many rejections of asylum seekers, by country of origin, there have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196228","196228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48305","2014-04-28","House of Commons Commission","2014-04-10","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what levels of stock the House of Commons Commission holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196210","196210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48306","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what levels of stock her Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196211","196211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48307","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much support her Department is giving to the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196345","196345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48308","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department measures the effect of support for the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196346","196346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48309","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department gives to small-scale food producers in areas supported by the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196347","196347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48310","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to her Answer of 5 March 2014, Official Report, column 871, on Pacific Islands, how much support, and under what categories her Department gave indirectly to Pacific Island countries in 2013-14.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196375","196375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48311","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Agreed Conclusions of the 58th Session of the Commission on the Status of Women, if she will support the inclusion of a specific target on women's full, equal and effective participation in all fields and leadership at all levels of decision-making within the post-2015 development framework.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196376","196376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48312","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what conditions are placed on recipients of support from the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196357","196357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48313","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department gives to the World Economic Forum's New Vision for Agriculture.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196356","196356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48314","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to introduce individual case reviews following the introduction of the Transforming Rehabilitation agenda into magistrates' courts in England and Wales.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196371","196371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48315","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to introduce specialisations in magistrates' courts in England and Wales following the introduction of the Transforming Rehabilitation Agenda.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196372","196372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48316","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance he has given magistrates in England and Wales on the introduction of the risk of serious recidivism tool into the National Probation Service following the introduction of the Transforming Rehabilitation model in England and Wales.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196370","196370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48317","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to introduce training for magistrates and legal advisers following the introduction of the Transforming Rehabilitation Agenda in England and Wales.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196369","196369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48318","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 3 of the Sexual Offences (Amendment) Act 2000 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196331","196331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48319","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 3 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196332","196332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48320","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 1 or section 2 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, where the offence was not committed against a child under the age of 16 years, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196329","196329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48321","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 30 to 41 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003, where the offence was committed against an adult, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196330","196330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48322","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many inmates committed suicide in prison between 2010 and 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196326","196326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48323","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 160 of the Criminal Justice Act 1988 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196442","196442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48324","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 1 of the Protection of Children Act 1978 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196441","196441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48325","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 3 to 4, 9 to 12, 14 to 20, 25 to 26, 47 to 50, 52 to 53, 57 to 59, 61 and sections 66 to 67 where the offence was committed against a child under the age of 16 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196443","196443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48326","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what circumstances he uses a calculation of the (a) value of preventing a fatality, (b) willingness to pay and (c) cost-per-quality adjusted life year approach to quantify the value of a policy intervention; what other tools he uses to quantify the benefit of a policy intervention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196466","196466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48327","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 126 to 129 of the Mental Health Act 1983 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196450","196450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48328","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to Section 1 of the Infanticide Act 1938 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196451","196451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48329","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions under the Hunting Act 2004 there were in 2013; how many of those prosecutions were successful; and what offences these prosecutions involved.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196479","196479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48330","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2014, Official Report, columns 649-50W on judges: housing, when he expects the review of the spend on judges' lodging to be completed.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196453","196453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48331","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in each prison have (a) started and (b) completed the Ibaana programme since it was introduced.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196380","196380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48332","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Judicial Conduct Investigations Office (a) started and concluded its investigation into Benjamin Mire; and what steps that Office subsequently took.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196400","196400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48333","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners were recorded as having caught hepatitis B while in prison in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196381","196381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48334","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether Benjamin Mire was shown the report of the Judicial Conduct Investigations Office into his conduct.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196401","196401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48335","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, under what circumstances the Judicial Conduct Investigations Office report on Benjamin Mire can be made public.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196402","196402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48336","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vaccinations for hepatitis B were given in prisons in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196382","196382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48337","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what timescale Benjamin Mire would have been removed from his appointment to the property tribunal following the conclusion of the report on the Judicial Conduct Investigations Office had he not resigned from that post.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196403","196403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48338","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what security breaches associated with the Prisons ICT Academy programme there have been since 1 January 2014; when these first came to the attention of Ministers; what the (a) nature of and (b) the outcome of their investigation was; and what illegal activities by prisoners were uncovered.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196383","196383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48339","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what rules his Department has in place on the (a) proven and (b) alleged criminal actions of potential bidders for the Transforming Rehabilitaiton programme.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196384","196384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48340","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of (a) domestic and (b) sexual abuse were reported by victims attending a police station in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196377","196377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48341","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when and for what reasons Benjamin Mire left his judicial appointment on the property tribunal.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196399","196399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48342","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of crimes reported in a police station in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196378","196378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48343","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners were recorded as having hepatitis B at the time of their induction into prison in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196386","196386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48344","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 1 of the Indecency with Children Act 1960 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196436","196436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48345","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence of murder, kidnapping or infanticide contrary to the common law of England and Wales in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196437","196437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48346","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 5 of the Sexual Offences Act 1967 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196438","196438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48347","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 145 of the Nationality, Immigration and Asylum Act 2002 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196440","196440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48348","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 54 of the Criminal Law Act 1977 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196439","196439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48349","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196212","196212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48350","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether prisoners at HM Prison Manchester have access to (a) library books on specialist subjects and (b) educational courses.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196234","196234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48351","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many packages of books delivered to HM Prison Manchester were found to contain drugs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196235","196235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48352","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many law firms were permitted to resubmit their tenders to the then Legal Services Commission bid for a contract to provide publicly funded immigration services in the 2010 tender round after the deadline set out in the tender rules.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196221","196221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48353","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make provision for construction of secure accommodation at Wrexham Magistrates' Court to replace accommodation at Wrexham Police Station due to be closed by North Wales Police in 2016.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196270","196270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48354","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions (a) HM Courts Service and (b) his Department has had with North Wales Police about future cell provision at Wrexham Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196268","196268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48355","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will ensure that criminal cases continue to be considered at Wrexham Magistrates' Court over the next five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196269","196269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48356","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 4 of the Asylum and Immigration (Treatment of Claimants etc.) Act 2004 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196431","196431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48357","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 5 of the Domestic Violence, Crime and Victims Act 2004 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196432","196432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48358","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 170 of the Customs and Excise Management Act 1979 in relation to goods prohibited to be imported under section 42 of the Customs Consolidation Act 1876 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196433","196433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48359","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to section 4(3) of the Misuse of Drugs Act 1971, where the person to whom controlled drugs were supplied or offered to be supplied was a child, in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196434","196434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48360","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of an offence contrary to sections 1, 2 and 6 of the Child Abduction Act 1984 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196435","196435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48361","2014-04-28","Leader of the House","2014-04-10","To ask the Leader of the House, what levels of stock his Office holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196213","196213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48362","2014-04-28","Northern Ireland Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what levels of stock her Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196214","196214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48363","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what levels of stock No. 10 Downing Street holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196215","196215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48364","2014-04-28","Prime Minister","2014-04-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what role the National Security Council plays in the long-term strategic planning and development of security policy.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196229","196229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48365","2014-04-28","Prime Minister","2014-04-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the ability of the National Security Council to foster collective decision-making across Government.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196231","196231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48366","2014-04-28","Prime Minister","2014-04-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what meetings he plans to have with representatives of the Sikh community on events surrounding the storming of the Golden Temple in Amritsar in 1984 and subsequent massacres.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196312","196312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48367","2014-04-28","Scotland Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196216","196216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48368","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to improve the performance of London Midland commuter trains.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196279","196279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48369","2014-05-01","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency meets the deadline of 1 November 2014 for enabling payment for vehicle tax discs by direct debit.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196296","196296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48370","2014-05-01","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency will include small and medium-sized enterprises in the procurement process for its contract to manage direct debit payments for vehicle tax discs.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196295","196295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48371","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require landowners and service suppliers to install manhole covers that have resistance abrasion values to prevent slipping and injury.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196318","196318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48372","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the level of funding per head of the population for transport in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196230","196230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48373","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196217","196217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48374","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will open discussions with his French counterpart to ensure crews on ferries operating between the UK and France are paid under British or French minimum wage regulations.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196313","196313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48375","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the prevalence of the practice of logbook lending.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196314","196314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48376","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect a hydrogen transport system would have on air quality in (a) London and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196341","196341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48377","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguard operations room staff have applied for posts in the restructured coastguard service.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196407","196407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48378","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to enable hydrogen fuel to compete equally as a viable part of the transport mix.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196408","196408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48379","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguard operations room staff in Liverpool have left the service in the last two years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196409","196409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48380","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how often and when each coastguard station has been under-staffed in the last two years.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196410","196410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48381","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguard operations room staff have applied for voluntary redundancy.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196406","196406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48382","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy that the compensation consultation and trial scheme in relation to High Speed 2 should be published by the end of 2014.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196393","196393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48383","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguard operations room staff have applied for both new posts in the new coastguard structure and voluntary redundancy.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196405","196405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48384","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish details of who considered the proposals for a property bond in relation to High Speed 2; and what the reasons were for rejecting that proposal.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196394","196394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48385","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the safeguarding directions in relation to High Speed 2 were last updated; and if he will publish the maps relating to that update.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196395","196395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48386","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish a list of responses to the Environmental Statement in Advance of Second Reading of the High Speed Rail (London - West Midlands) Bill.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196392","196392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48387","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support the hydrogen fuelling market; and when he expects to have completed them.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196452","196452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48388","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of increases in passenger numbers (a) nationally and (b) on the West Coast Main Line over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196423","196423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48389","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received about the implications of the proposed EU Package Travel Directive on insolvency protection for consumers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr John Whittingdale","Mr John Whittingdale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196425","196425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48390","2014-04-28","Wales Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196219","196219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48391","2014-04-28","Women and Equalities","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what levels of stock the Government Equalities Office holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196207","196207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48392","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of extending the triple lock guarantee to all British pensioners resident abroad; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196233","196233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48393","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what levels of stock his Department holds of (a) stationery, (b) printer cartridges, (c) treasury tags and other fasteners and (d) other office consumables.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196220","196220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48394","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish on the government website an up-to-date impact assessment for universal credit.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196194","196194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48395","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of Capita on processing medical assessment reports for personal independence payments.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196278","196278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48396","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of British pensioners resident abroad whose pensions have been frozen.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196242","196242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48397","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from charities and community organisations on the removal of warm phones from Jobcentre Plus offices.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196471","196471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48398","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average caseload was for a Jobcentre Plus advisor in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196468","196468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48399","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Youth Contract in the 20 designated areas of high youth unemployment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196469","196469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48400","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department is monitoring the progress and effect of the EU Youth Guarantee.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196470","196470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48401","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many job vacancies there are in (a) London, (b) the London Borough of Hounslow and (c) Brentford and Isleworth constituency.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196412","196412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48494","2014-04-30","Department for Education","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to other government departments on implementing the Government's commitment to give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child when considering new policy or legislation.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903755","903755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48608","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of links between tobacco smuggling and organised crime.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903701","903701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48899","2014-04-29","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of how much the reduction in the additional rate of income tax to 45 per cent will be worth each year for a person earning £1 million a year.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903727","903727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48900","2014-04-29","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to reform the Business Premises Renovation Allowance following HM Revenue and Customs' recent consultation.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903732","903732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48901","2014-04-29","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential funds that will accrue to the public purse from the Europe for Citizens Programme.","Biography information for Michael Connarty","Michael Connarty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903731","903731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48902","2014-04-29","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of fiscal policy on the number of young people claiming jobseeker's allowance for over 12 months since May 2010.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903723","903723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48903","2014-04-29","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of how much the reduction in the additional rate of income tax to 45 per cent will be worth each year for a person earning £1 million a year.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903730","903730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48904","2014-04-29","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of sustained low interest rates on incentives to save; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903726","903726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48905","2014-04-29","HM Treasury","2014-04-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal steps he is taking to help pensioners on low incomes.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903728","903728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49171","2014-04-30","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he plans to take to ensure that a higher proportion of young people from disadvantaged backgrounds participate in the National Citizen Service.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903762","903762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49172","2014-04-30","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress he has made on developing the role of the Crown Commercial Service; what savings to the public purse he expects to accrue from commercial reform of government procurement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903760","903760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49173","2014-04-30","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to promote digital government.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903757","903757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/49174","2014-04-30","Cabinet Office","2014-04-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to maintain the level of youth services provision.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903759","903759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47877","2014-04-28","Attorney General","2014-04-09","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions have taken place under the Obscene Publications Act 1959 for the offence of providing unrestricted access to hardcore pornography online, as set out in the 2005 Crown Prosecution Service guidelines, disaggregated by year.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196000","196000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47878","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, what progress his Department has made in establishing the effect of school reporting metrics on the prestige of higher apprenticeships as a destination.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195984","195984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47879","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, what progress his Department has made in increasing the number of higher apprenticeships in the professional and business services sector.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195989","195989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47880","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, what progress his Department has made in (a) developing a clearing house for professional and business services higher apprenticeship applicants and (b) helping small and medium-sized enterprises access this talent pool.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195985","195985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47881","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, what web-based initiatives have been set up to link professional and business services businesses with the education sector.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195990","195990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47882","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, what engagement plan for disseminating high value opportunity programme opportunities has been developed; and what opportunities have been identified within the professional and business services sector.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195986","195986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47883","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, what progress his Department has made in increasing the diversity of entry to the professional and business services sector.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195987","195987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47884","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, what progress his Department has made in piloting new approaches to improving business and skills system engagement and sharing of good practice.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195991","195991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47885","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, what progress his Department has made in the development of the growth voucher scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195988","195988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47886","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, how many further education colleges have engaged with business as a condition of achieving chartered status.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195992","195992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47887","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, what progress his Department has made in encouraging bodies to find innovative ways of improving employability of young people within the national curriculum.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195993","195993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47888","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, if the new envoy network has been convened through UK Trade & Investment; and what progress his Department has made in orchestrating a mission programme.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195994","195994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47889","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, whether his Department is on course to run at least two professional and business services dedicated trade missions each year; and what such missions have taken place since the Strategy was published.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195995","195995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47890","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Growth is Our Business: A Strategy for Professional and Business Services published in July 2013, whether UK Trade & Investment has produced the marketing plan and collateral.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195996","195996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47892","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to reduce the regulatory burden on small businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196014","196014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47893","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research and development into the commercial application of robotics his Department funds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196017","196017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47894","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether information included in the registry of company beneficial ownership information will be available for free.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196058","196058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47895","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether information included in the registry of company beneficial ownership information will be cross-checked against data held by (a) passport authorities, (b) vehicle licensing authorities, (c) electoral registers and (d) other databases.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196059","196059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47896","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the registry of company beneficial ownership information will contain a description of how the beneficial owner exercises control over (a) a company, (b) names of the chain of companies that demonstrate a person is the beneficial owner and (c) any other means by which a person exercises control over a company.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196061","196061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47897","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that exporters of intangible goods can access the resources of UK Export Finance.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196127","196127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47898","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the student loan default rate is for students and graduates of (a) Bristol, (b) Cambridge, (c) Durham, (d) Exeter, (e) Leeds, (f) Manchester and (g) Oxford Universities.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196099","196099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47899","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value of bilateral trade in agricultural goods and services between the UK and Israel was in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196116","196116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47900","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research his Department has commissioned into the effects of reducing funding to further, higher and adult education.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196108","196108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47901","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 8W, on employee ownership, what estimate he has made of how many people will apply to be an employee shareholder under the Shares for Rights Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196146","196146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47902","2014-04-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 8W, on employee ownership, how many companies have applied to participate in the Shares for Rights Scheme to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196147","196147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47903","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people of pensionable age in Brighton, Kemptown constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196005","196005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47904","2014-04-28","Cabinet Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of young people in (a) Brighton, Kemptown constituency and (b) East Sussex who have been unemployed for longer than 12 months in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196004","196004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47905","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to reduce taxation on small businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196013","196013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47906","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department made of the annual level of fraud involving the existing one pound coin in order to inform the decision to introduce a new style coin.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196039","196039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47907","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the likely change in annuities in 12 months' time for the average 65-year-old (a) man and (b) woman.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196040","196040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47908","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what change there has been in the total amount of gift aid claimed by charities between 2008 and 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196042","196042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47909","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the increase in ISA limits announced in the 2014 Budget allow those with current ISAs to take advantage of the new limit between the present time and March 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196043","196043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47910","2014-04-28","HM Treasury","2014-04-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the future of HM Revenue and Customs' centres in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195975","195975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47911","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will include Peterborough in the areas involved in his Department's proposals for dealing with rogue private rented sector landlords; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195997","195997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47912","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to help shops in (a) Brighton, Kemptown constituency and (b) East Sussex with their business rate bills; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196009","196009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47913","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the amount of housing proposed on what had been designated Green Belt land in 2010 in adopted and emerging Local Plans.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196045","196045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47914","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made on reducing the number of empty homes in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) the West Midlands, (d) Worcestershire and (e) Worcester.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196072","196072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47915","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will impose a moratorium on processing all planning applications submitted by UK Coal Production Ltd until that body has demonstrated it can meet its obligations on restoration and section 106 contributions.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196068","196068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47916","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent research his Department has undertaken on retaliatory evictions in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196063","196063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47917","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the wishes of the local people and decisions of the local council are given priority in appeal decisions by the Planning Inspectorate.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196030","196030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47918","2014-04-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 13 February 2014, Official Report, column 800W, on Business Improvement Districts: Birmingham, when he expects to publish the report on the Business Improvement District for Sparkbrook and Springfield, or to reach a decision on that matter.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196137","196137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47919","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many schools will benefit from his broadband rollout for schools.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196097","196097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47920","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the average time taken to grant planning permission for mobile telephone base stations in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196025","196025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47921","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to Law Commission Report No. 336 published on 28 February 2013, what progress his Department has made on reforming the electronic communications code.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196024","196024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47922","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which research studies used by his Department in formulating policy on fixed odds betting terminals (a) have and (b) have not received industry funding or support; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196046","196046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47923","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations he has received from the charity sector about the effect of gambling addiction; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196003","196003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47924","2014-04-28","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what services are available in Brighton, Kemptown constituency to assist people with gambling problems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196002","196002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47925","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on (a) armed forces recruitment and (b) armed forces recruitment marketing in 2012-13.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196069","196069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47926","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of armoured fighting vehicles which will be (a) returned to the UK, (d) destroyed or (c) sold by the time of the main withdrawal from Afghanistan; and what the costs associated with each of those categories are to date.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196076","196076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47927","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he last discussed the Nuclear Non-proliferation Treaty with his counterparts from the Permanent Members of the UN Security Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196027","196027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47928","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason an Apache helicopter had to make an emergency landing outside Aberdeen during Exercise Joint Warrior.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196036","196036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47929","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many suitably qualified and experienced RAF personnel his Department has required for aircraft maintenance in each location in each of the last three years; and how many such posts were vacant in each location in each such year.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196037","196037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47930","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many suitably qualified and experienced RAF personnel involved in aircraft maintenance have been required by his Department in each of the last three years; and how many such posts were vacant in each such year, by location.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196115","196115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47931","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the names and causes of death of all UK service personnel who died in the course of or in connection with operations in Northern Ireland between 1969 and 2007.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196154","196154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47932","2014-04-28","Ministry of Defence","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons an Apache helicopter had to make an emergency landing outside Aberdeen during exercise joint warrior.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196114","196114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47933","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish statutory guidance on careers advice.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196107","196107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47934","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 April 2014, Official Report, column 205W, on primary education: admissions, and of 6 March 2014, Official Report, column 904W, on academies, regarding primary school admissions from nursery schools, if he will make it his policy to reject the Chief Schools Adjudicator's recommendation to issue further guidance for admission authorities and instead amend the admissions code to enable primary schools to create all-through primary schools that include the years prior to reception.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196101","196101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47935","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2014, Official Report, columns 789-90, on special educational needs, when he expects the special educational needs (SEN) gateway will be available for all parents of SEN children.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196031","196031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47936","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 191W, on special edcuational needs, which local authorities will trial the First-Tier Tribunal (Special Educational Needs and Disability) pilots.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196028","196028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47937","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2014, Official Report, column 789-90W, on special educational needs, what support his Department is providing to Nasen.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196029","196029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47938","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools suspended pupils for (a) bullying and (b) cyber-bullying between 2004 and the latest date for which information is available.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196060","196060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47939","2014-04-28","Department for Education","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support he plans to give schools which have no kitchen facilities and are unable to build such facilities because of financial constraints, and which cannot have meals delivered from other local schools, to enable them to provide free school meals for infant children; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196056","196056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47940","2014-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to encourage the use of smart meters; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196001","196001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47941","2014-04-28","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many tonnes of carbon dioxide were displaced by onshore wind electricity generation in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Scotland and (d) Wales in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196079","196079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47942","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the geographical spread in the UK of the bacterium melissococcus plutonius.","Biography information for Simon Reevell","Simon Reevell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196047","196047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47943","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote the health of (a) domestic and (b) wild rabbits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196010","196010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47944","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on renegotiating overseas fishing agreements with Guinea-Bissau and other countries along the West African coast.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196130","196130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47945","2014-04-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on implementing a regional wildlife enforcement strategy in the Horn of Africa and addressing the illegal trade in shark fins.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196129","196129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47946","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Israel regarding plans for the creation of a new settlement in the Old City of Hebron.","Biography information for Fiona O'Donnell","Fiona O'Donnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196143","196143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47947","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made any recent representations to the government of Uzbekistan regarding the imprisonment of the journalist, Salidzhon Abdurakhmanov.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196144","196144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47948","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Pakistan government on the case of Shafqat Emmanuel and Shagufta Kausar who have been sentenced to death for allegedly sending a text message regarding the prophet Mohamed.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196041","196041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47949","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) Palestinians and (b) Jews displaced from their country of origin in the Middle East since 1984.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195958","195958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47950","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with UK companies to encourage them to take part in construction and development projects in the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195961","195961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47951","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Colombian government on human rights and the deaths of striking agricultural workers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195962","195962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47952","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage businesses in the fishing sector to operate in the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195963","195963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47953","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage businesses in the construction sector to build houses in the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195964","195964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47954","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to help workers in the oil industry to seek employment in the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195965","195965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47955","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2014, Official Report, columns 161-2W, on Syria, on what basis the Women's International League for Peace and Freedom was selected as the recipient of £200,000.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195973","195973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47956","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 139W, on Burma, what commitments the Burmese immigration minister made on conduct of the census.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195982","195982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47957","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the country of origin was of each special mission to the UK that has been refused since 4 March 2013; and what were the grounds for each refusal.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196034","196034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47958","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he would refuse to consent to a special mission on (a) human rights grounds and (b) where the person in question has been the subject of a UK judicial arrest warrant, European Arrest Warrant or similar judicial process.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196032","196032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47959","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the country of origin was of each special mission to the UK since 4 March 2013; and whether any person travelling on a special mission to the UK has been the subject of (a) an arrest warrant or (b) a criminal investigation conducted by SO15 since 4 March 2013.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196033","196033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47960","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the written statement of 4 March 2013, Official Report, columns 55-6WS, on special mission immunity, how many special missions have been (a) consented to and (b) refused under the pilot process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196035","196035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47961","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much the UK contributed towards the funding of the United Nations and International Monetary Fund in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196109","196109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47962","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made on establishing a date for a third round of negotiations for the Geneva Conference on Syria.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196110","196110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47963","2014-04-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK Government Ministers have visited Lesotho since 2010.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196122","196122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47964","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NICE has to further assess photodynamic therapy treatments for the treatment of cancers.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196123","196123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47965","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the use of photodynamic therapy for cancer.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196124","196124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47966","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which cancers the NHS treats with photodynamic therapy.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196125","196125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47967","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals provide photodynamic therapy for the treatment of cancers.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196126","196126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47968","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what role he envisages for Health and Wellbeing boards in supporting people into employment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196092","196092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47969","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how (a) morbid obesity and (b) obesity affects the development of osteoarthritis.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196093","196093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47970","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of cancer patients have access to intensity modulated radio therapy at (a) Brighton University Hospitals Trust and (b) Southampton University Hospitals Trust.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196087","196087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47971","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what level of body mass index a patient with anorexia nervosa must have to be admitted to in-patient care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196064","196064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47972","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Cystic Fibrosis Trust's report, Hope for more: Improving access to lung transplantation and care for people with cystic fibrosis, what estimate he has made of the donor lung utilisation rate for transplantation; and what measures he has identified as having the greatest potential to increase utilisation.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196084","196084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47973","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of existing arrangements for donor lung allocation for people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196085","196085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47974","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the psychological support available to individuals with cystic fibrosis after lung transplantation.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196086","196086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47975","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many courses of IVF treatment patients can access in each clinical commissioning group area in each English region.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196090","196090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47976","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Child and Adolescent Mental Health Service beds for young people suffering from eating disorders there are; and what their occupancy levels were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196066","196066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47977","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to allow people to view their medical records online; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196077","196077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47978","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish research carried out by his Department on the (a) provision of IVF cycles by clinical commissioning groups and (b) criteria used by clinical commissioning groups to determine the number of cycles to which each woman is entitled.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196065","196065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47979","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients with suspected cancer see a specialist within two weeks in the area served by the Coastal West Sussex clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196062","196062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47980","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will provide funding to meet any shortfall in funding of the National Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196048","196048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47981","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England about future funding of the National Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196050","196050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47982","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that recent progress in the diagnosis and treatment of pancreatic cancer informs NHS practice.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195977","195977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47983","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that all patients receive innovative radiotherapy treatment where clinically indicated.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195978","195978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47984","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many midwives there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195971","195971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47985","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Announcement of 16 May 2012, how many and what proportion of health visitors have been given enhanced training to identify the early signs of postnatal depression.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195974","195974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47986","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that efficiency savings are not introduced too quickly and that the resulting stress on staff is kept to a minimum.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195967","195967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47987","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage the retention of experienced NHS staff.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195968","195968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47988","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in Northern Ireland on access to cancer drugs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195969","195969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47989","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women now have access to a named midwife; how many women each named midwife looks after; and what proportion of women get one-to-one midwifery care in labour.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195970","195970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47990","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cochlear operations there were in each of the last five years; and what the ages were of the patients who had those operations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195959","195959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47991","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage children and pregnant women to eat more eggs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195960","195960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47992","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which former directors in his Department have been promoted to new roles at NHS England in the last four years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196044","196044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47993","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research the Health Protection Agency has funded on male fertility and sperm counts in the last five years; and if he will publish the findings of such research.","Biography information for Simon Wright","Simon Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195983","195983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47994","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) correspondence and (b) representations from lawyers representing tobacco companies (i) ministers and (ii) civil servants of his Department have received since the announcement of the Chantler Review on 28 November 2013; and from which law firms and tobacco companies in each such case.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196098","196098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47995","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health visitors there are in post; what change there has been in the number in post since May 2010; how many new health visitors are required in order to reach his target of 4,200 new health visitors by April 2015; how many student health visitors are undergoing health visitor training; when they are due to finish training and begin practice; what his regional targets are for the 4,200 new health visitors; and what proportion of health visitors are currently in post in each such region.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196100","196100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47996","2014-04-28","Department of Health","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow children under two months to become an organ donor.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196138","196138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47997","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police forces failed to meet her Department's deadline of 4 April 2014 for handing over to the Independent Police Complaints Commission any evidence relating to the Hillsborough disaster.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196052","196052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47998","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make a comparative assessment of the sources, reliability and mutual compatibility of the statistics on the number of human trafficking victims from Albania given in parliamentary written answers and in the annual reports of the National Crime Agency.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196038","196038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/47999","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time is between the expiry of a visa and (a) the person voluntarily leaving the country and (b) the forcible removal of the visa holder.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196067","196067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48000","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many family visit visa applications to the UK were made between June 2013 and December 2013; and how many such applications were (a) granted, (b) refused, (c) withdrawn, (d) lapsed and (e) given the right to appeal.","Biography information for Margaret Beckett","Margaret Beckett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196070","196070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48001","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria are used to decide in which countries to have UK consular and visa offices.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196075","196075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48002","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from Lesotho applied for UK visas in each of the last 12 years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196074","196074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48003","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police forces (a) handed over evidence relating to the Hillsborough disaster and (b) contacted the Independent Police Complaints Commission to inform it that they did not have any evidence relating to the Hillsborough disaster.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196026","196026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48004","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the budgets for criminal justice and emergency services will be devolved to Police and Crime Commissioners; and what the total budget is that Police and Crime Commissioners will inherit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196088","196088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48005","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the code governing detention of teenagers under the Police and Criminal Evidence Act will be redrafted to ensure that 17 year olds in custody are treated as teenagers by the police.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196089","196089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48006","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the overseas aid budget is being used to help combat the spread and treatment of HIV and Aids; and in which countries.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196112","196112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48007","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of levels of violence against women in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196071","196071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48008","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects her Department has in Lesotho.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196073","196073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48009","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many UK construction companies are involved in development projects in the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195966","195966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48010","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many visits she made to the Jordan Valley in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196106","196106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48011","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the report of Parliamentary Ombudsman into the complaint raised by a constituent of the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion regarding her Department's oversight of CDC Group Investments published in February 2014 and her letter of 19 November 2013 to the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion stating that she would reply in full after the publication of the Ombudsman's report, when she plans to make that full reply.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196113","196113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48012","2014-04-28","Department for International Development","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to ensure developing countries can access UK satellite technology to monitor local agricultural land and environmental risks; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196128","196128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48013","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 2 April 2014, Official Report, column 703W, on translation services, how much was spent on interpreters in courts in each court in Lancashire in 2011, 2012 and 2013; which languages were interpreted; and how much was spent on interpreting each language.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196153","196153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48014","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has issued to magistrates on consideration of breach applications following the introduction of the Transforming Rehabilitation agenda in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196021","196021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48015","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the Supreme Court's judgment in Summers v Fairclough Homes that exaggerated or fabricated personal injury claims might be struck out in exceptional circumstances; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196051","196051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48016","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost to the (a) public purse and (b) prison service is of processing a complaint by a prisoner against a prison officer.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196053","196053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48017","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many child sex offenders were in prison in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196054","196054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48018","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints were made by imprisoned child sex offenders against (a) prison officers and (b) prison staff in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196055","196055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48019","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions there have been for the offence of causing serious injury by dangerous driving since its introduction in 2012; and what the average length of sentence handed out by the courts for that offence is.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196057","196057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48020","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to ensure that there will not be delays in the delivery of court reports to magistrates' courts in Wales and England following the introduction of the Transforming Rehabilitation agenda.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196020","196020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48021","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has issued to magistrates in Wales and England on the implications of the Transforming Rehabilitation agenda for the functioning of the courts.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196019","196019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48022","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is adequate staffing in magistrates' courts to ensure the efficient and speedy provision of information to the bench.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196023","196023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48023","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what effect the introduction of the Transforming Rehabilitation agenda in magistrates' courts in England and Wales will have on report writing slots.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196022","196022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48024","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people residing in Preston constituency are (a) being monitored by an electronic tag (b) subject to a suspended sentence order and (c) subject to a community order.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196141","196141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48025","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason each foreign national in prison awaiting deportation who is beyond the end of their sentence is yet to be deported.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196095","196095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48026","2014-04-28","Ministry of Justice","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the UK Government has agreed to provide the government of Nigeria in financial support as part of the prisoner transfer agreement with the country signed on 9 January 2014; and what the benefits for the UK are of that agreement.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196094","196094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48027","2014-04-28","Home Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many 17 year olds have been held in police custody in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196091","196091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48028","2014-04-28","Leader of the House","2014-04-09","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will introduce and consult upon proposals for the Standards Committee to be replaced by a body consisting of a majority of lay members with representation of more than three hon. Members without voting rights.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196096","196096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48029","2014-04-28","Northern Ireland Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, on how many occasions she has met with representatives of Praxis Care in the last 12 months; when she last visited a Praxis residential facility; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196082","196082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48030","2014-04-28","Northern Ireland Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many officials from her Department attended the recent Crown Court trial of John Downey in an official capacity; which representatives of the British-Irish Inter-Governmental Secretariat attended that trial in an official capacity; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196081","196081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48031","2014-04-28","Northern Ireland Office","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of her progress in discharging her responsibilities under section 75 of the Northern Ireland Act 1998 in respect of (a) HM Revenue and Customs, (b) the Driver and Vehicle Agency and (c) the UK Border Agency.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195999","195999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48032","2014-04-28","Prime Minister","2014-04-09","To ask the Prime Minister, what matters in respect of (a) Pakistan's possession of nuclear weapons and (b) the prospects of Pakistan joining the Nuclear Non-proliferation Treaty he discussed at his April 2014 meeting with his Pakistani counterpart.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196132","196132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48033","2014-04-28","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 8 April 2014, Official Report, column 193W, on electoral register, if the Electoral Commission will introduce public awards for electoral registration officers who have set best practice in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196133","196133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48034","2014-04-28","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 8 April 2014, Official Report, column 193W, on electoral register, for what reasons the Electoral Commission had previously organised voter registration drives for overseas voters but had not organised such drives for UK citizens who reside in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196134","196134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48035","2014-04-28","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 8 April 2014, Official Report, column 193W, on electoral register, if he will place a copy of the responses from electoral registration officers on whether or not they carried out a personal canvass of all non-responders in the Library and on the internet.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196135","196135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48036","2014-04-28","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 8 April 2014, Official Report, column 193W, on electoral register, for what reasons the Electoral Commission does not collect data on the number of attainers registered as part of its monitoring of  electoral registration officers.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196136","196136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48037","2014-04-28","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-04-09","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the voter registration rate was for 18 year olds in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196131","196131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48038","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much he estimates will have to be spent protecting the High Speed 2 track on phase 1 and phase 2 against the effects of mining subsidence; and whether that sum is included in the overall projected cost.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196117","196117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48039","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the Government invested in highway and infrastructure construction in the North West in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196111","196111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48040","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many referrals have been made to him where a local planning authority is minded to approve an application for planning permission against the advice of HS2 Ltd; and what his decision has been on each such referral.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195981","195981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48041","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the Competition Commission's inquiry into the car insurance industry to report.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195976","195976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48042","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many consultation requests from local planning authorities under the safeguarding directions for Phase One have been received by HS2 Ltd since 9 July 2013; and from which local planning authorities such consultation requests have been received.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195980","195980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48043","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many High Speed 2 consultation requests are EIA development as defined in the Town and Country Planning (Environmental Impact Assessment) Regulations 2011; and how many recommendations for refusal of the grant of planning permission are (a) EIA and (b) non-EIA development.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 195979","195979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48044","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the modal shift from car to railway use as a result of eliminating the weekday minimum fare resulting from the use of the Network Rail card; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196008","196008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48045","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage the interoperability of smart tickets on local bus services outside London where more than one bus company runs the service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196006","196006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48046","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with cities outside London on interoperability of smart tickets between rail and bus services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196007","196007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48047","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Transport for London (TfL) about the use of other smart ticket systems in the TfL area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196015","196015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48048","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to ensure that the benefits of Crossrail are shared with passengers using London Victoria, London Bridge and London Blackfriars railway stations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196016","196016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48049","2014-04-28","Department for Transport","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) EIA and (b) non-EIA development recommendations HS2 Ltd has made for conditions to be imposed on planning permission to protect the High Speed 2 project.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196049","196049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48050","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide a simple route for people to donate their universal benefits back to the state; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196078","196078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48051","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the effect of using Wolverhampton as a redistribution centre for all mail relating to processing benefit claims, payments and appeals on (a) time taken to process and (b) the reliability of the claims process.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196080","196080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/48052","2014-04-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-04-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times the date set for the implementation of the personal independence payment programme has changed since that policy was introduced.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 196083","196083"
