"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19195","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on whether any UK doctors or psychologists have worked in any US detention centres or offered assistance regarding the detention and interrogation of prisoners suspected of terrorism since 2001.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174951","174951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19231","2013-11-08","Northern Ireland Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Minister of Justice in Northern Ireland on disappeared persons; and what steps she is taking to locate their remains.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174779","174779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19232","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many members of the Garda Siochana have been seconded to work in police forces in Great Britain in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174781","174781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19233","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Police Service of Northern Ireland officers have been seconded to work in police forces in Great Britain since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174782","174782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19234","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many present adult claimants of disability living allowance live within the catchment of each personal independence payment consultation centre serving South and East England; and what the longest journey in miles is to each such centre.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174783","174783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19235","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which of the 21 personal independence payment consultation centres serving South and East England cannot be reached within (a) 90 minutes and (b) 60 minutes by public transport from all parts of their catchment area.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174784","174784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19236","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which of the 21 personal independence payment consultation centres serving South and East England are not wheelchair-accessible.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174785","174785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19237","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which of the 21 personal independence payment consultation centres serving South and East England are not on a bus route.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174786","174786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19238","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which of the 21 personal independence payment consultation centres serving South and East England do not have parking available for clients within 50 metres of the centre.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174787","174787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19239","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, under what circumstances those attending personal independence payment centres have their transport costs paid.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174789","174789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19240","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) policies and (b) statutory obligations each school governing body is required to keep under review.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174790","174790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19241","2013-11-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the statement of 5 November 2013, Official Report, on sporting legacy, how many of the projects listed by the Minister are operating within Wales.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174791","174791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19242","2013-11-08","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the EU regulation on periodic roadworthiness tests for motor vehicles and the inclusion of caravans within that regulation.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174792","174792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19243","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is providing to people in refugee camps on the border between Cameroon and the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174793","174793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19244","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent reports she has received on the humanitarian situation in eastern Cameroon; and what assessment she has made of the potential threat presented by Seleka forces to the humanitarian effort in eastern Cameroon.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174794","174794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19245","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of British nationals present in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174795","174795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19246","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the conflict in (a) Bossangoa and (b) the Central African Republic as a whole; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174796","174796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19247","2013-11-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what targets his Department has been set by the Prime Minister for savings on the cost of average dual fuel energy bills following the conclusion of the review of green levies.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174802","174802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19248","2013-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what total amount in salary, fees and expenses was paid by his Department to Sir Michael Lyons for his work on the Lyons Inquiry into Local Government.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174801","174801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19249","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2013, Official Report, columns 618-9W, on separated people: finance, when each of the seven voluntary and third-sector projects established in March 2013 under the Help and Support for Separated Families Innovation Fund will start working with customers directly.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174807","174807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19250","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the provisional teacher training allocations published by his Department on 1 November 2013, how many places from each accredited providers initial teacher training allocations are for (a) each phase, (b) each secondary subject, (c) core provision and (d) School Direct provision.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174808","174808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19251","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the provisional teacher training allocations published by his Department on 1 November 2013, how many places have been allocated to (a) higher education institutions, (b) school-centred initial teacher training, (c) School Direct fee-paying, (d) School Direct salaried, (e) other types of provision, (f) primary phase, (g) secondary phase and (h) each individual secondary subject.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174809","174809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19252","2013-11-11","Cabinet Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new jobs created in the private sector in the last 12 months were (a) unpaid workfare or internships, (b) through zero-hour contracts, (c) part-time, (d) part-time working 16 hours or less per week, (e) part-time working eight hours or less per week, (g) paid at the level of the minimum wage and (h) jobs transferred from public sector organisations.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174810","174810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19253","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2013, Official Report, column 642W, on asylum, what the total number of complaints made against the Commercial and Operational Managers Procuring Asylum Support Service project was.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174811","174811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19254","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions the ministerial oversight group for universal credit has met in the last 12 months; and when that group is scheduled to meet again.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174812","174812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19255","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what amounts have been paid to date to each (a) IT service provider and (b) consultant in relation to the universal credit programme.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174813","174813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19256","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether Ministers of his Department have attended meetings of the ministerial oversight group on universal credit in the last 12 months.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174814","174814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19257","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance he has issued to schools regarding education on the effects of legal highs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174815","174815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19258","2013-11-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) the public, (b) trades unions, (c) businesses and (d) consumer groups are consulted about ongoing negotiations for a transatlantic trade and investment partnership.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174816","174816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19259","2013-11-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to keep Parliament informed of developments in the negotiations for a transatlantic trade and investment partnership.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174817","174817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19260","2013-11-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will give consideration to making a super-complaint to the Office of Fair Trading regarding the fairness of (a) supply and (b) pricing in the UK concrete and cement market.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174820","174820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19261","2013-11-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will commission a commemorative campaign medal for veterans of Dunkirk who were left behind by Operation Dynamo.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174821","174821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19262","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the amount of tax revenue lost to the public purse owing to tax avoidance in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174822","174822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19263","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff have been made redundant and subsequently re-employed by NHS organisations on a (a) permanent basis and (b) fixed-term contract basis since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174823","174823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19264","2013-11-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the President of Sri Lanka on accreditation for UK journalists wishing to attend the upcoming Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174824","174824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19265","2013-11-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any minister or official has agreed or taken any steps to restart talks with Spain on the sovereignty of Gibraltar under the Brussels Process or any other bilateral process.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174826","174826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19266","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the Notice of Concern from the Deputy Inspector General of the US Department of Defense dated 22 October 2012 regarding the visit to BAE Systems in Samlesbury in connection with the Joint Strike Fighter Programme.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174797","174797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19267","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the Notice of Concern from the Deputy Inspector General of the US Department of Defense dated 20 November 2012 regarding the visit to Honeywell Aerospace in Yeovil in connection with the Joint Strike Fighter Programme.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174798","174798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19268","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what design features are incorporated into the Queen Elizabeth Class aircraft carriers to allow for shipborne rolling vertical landing.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174799","174799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19269","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the ability of the Queen Elizabeth Class carriers to conduct shipborne rolling vertical landing operations with the Joint Strike Fighter in moderate to heavy seas.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174800","174800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19270","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive about the effect of the decision of the Supreme Court in R (on the application of Reilly and another) v Secretary of State for Work and Pensions in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174803","174803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19271","2013-11-08","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which local authorities have used the powers given to them in February 2011 to implement local bans on parking on pavements.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174804","174804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19272","2013-11-08","Cabinet Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow regulators to introduce fairness to customer criteria when assessing complaints.","Biography information for Lord Watts","Mr Dave Watts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174805","174805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19273","2013-11-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the cost to energy companies of the Energy Company Obligation since 1 January 2013.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174806","174806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19274","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis currently accessing the Motability Scheme are in receipt of the higher rate mobility component of disability living allowance; and how many such people lease a (a) car, (b) scooter and (c) powered wheelchair.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174827","174827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19275","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis are currently accessing the Motability Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174828","174828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19276","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of ongoing management costs incurred by his Department under a national contract for the administration of the Nursery Milk Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174829","174829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19277","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what benefit monies remain unclaimed for (a) the UK and (b) each region of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174830","174830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19278","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect a pharmacy-led national minor ailments scheme would have on the number of people attending accident and emergency services with minor ailments; what consideration he has given to the creation of such a scheme; what assessment he has made of the minor ailments schemes currently run by pharmacies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Kevin Barron","Mr Kevin Barron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174889","174889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19279","2013-11-08","Wales Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's length bodies are paid less than the living wage; and how many direct employees of his Department are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174909","174909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19280","2013-11-08","Prime Minister","2013-11-06","To ask the Prime Minister, whether there were discussions of any potential security risks prior to the invitation of Councillor Abdul Aziz to attend a recent event at No. 10 Downing Street.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174910","174910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19281","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that the proposed newly-merged Swansea Magistrates' Court will address the specific needs of people in the county borough of Neath Port Talbot taking account of remoteness, low incomes and digital exclusion.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174899","174899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19282","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons he is proposing to close Neath Port Talbot Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174900","174900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19283","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether access to a railway line is available at (a) RAF Warminster, (b) RAF Lyneham, (c) Ashchurch, (d) Donnington and (e) Warminster; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174911","174911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19284","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how far it is to the nearest motorway access point from (a) RAF Warminster, (b) RAF Lyneham, (c) Ashchurch, (d) Donnington and (e) Warminster; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174912","174912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19285","2013-11-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Ambassador of Thailand about the charges against UK citizen Andy Hall.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174831","174831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19286","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many agency workers are employed at (a) RAF Warminster, (b) RAF Lyneham, (c) Ashchurch, (d) Donnington and (e) Warminster to maintain and monitor short term storage of A&B vehicles in accordance with AESP2300-A-401-031; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174913","174913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19287","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on road safety of the divergence of the UK's maximum speed limit from that of other European Union Member States.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174832","174832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19288","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of School Direct allocations for academic year 2013-14 have been filled; and what proportion of School Direct allocations for academic year 2014-15 he expects to be filled.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174890","174890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19289","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much rental income was earned from buildings at each defence support group site in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174914","174914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19290","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the cost-effectiveness of an innovation fund to assist the development of autism services.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174833","174833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19291","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the determination of the number of student commissions for healthcare workers by local education and training boards is based on consistent and accurate data.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174903","174903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19292","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what budget the National College for Teaching and Leadership has set for promotion and advertisement of (a) core allocation and (b) School Direct routes for entry in academic year 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174891","174891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19293","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made on how the NHS is complying with National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines on diagnosing and managing adults with autism.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174834","174834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19294","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 1265W, on defence support group, whether his Department has developed a business case for the sale of Defence Support Group Ashchurch; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174915","174915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19295","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Health Education England is taking to ensure that reductions in commissioned student places by local education and training boards do not affect the viability of education and training courses for healthcare workers.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174904","174904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19296","2013-11-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Royal Parks about their decision to introduce charges for people wanting to play sport on the section of Hyde Park known as the Old Football Pitches.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174892","174892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19297","2013-11-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he intends to publish the results of the research project on the provision of food aid in the UK.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174893","174893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19298","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effects on the small business sector of the expiry of the doubling of small business rate relief in March 2014.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174836","174836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19299","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data (a) his Department and (b) Health Education England (i) commission and (ii) use to calculate the number of student commissions for healthcare workers by local education and training boards.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174905","174905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19300","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which defence support group sites have the capacity to inspect and test nuclear biological and chemical clean air supply in military vehicles; what training is required for staff to carry out such work; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174916","174916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19301","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effects of freezing business rates in 2014-15 for hereditaments with a rateable value of between (a) £6,001 to £18,000 and (b) £6,001 to £25,000 in London.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174837","174837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19302","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the level of intellectual property infringement in the UK furniture industry; and if he will bring forward legislative proposals to create a criminal offence of deliberate registered design infringement.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174895","174895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19303","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 22 April 2013, Official Report, column 1265W, on defence support group, whether a contamination survey has found evidence of asbestos at Defence Support Group Ashchurch; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174917","174917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19304","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2013, Official Report, column 779W, on military decorations: World War II, how many applications have been received to date from next of kin; what progress his Department has made in processing applications from next of kin to date; what the average processing time is for applications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174906","174906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19305","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the determination of the number of student commissions for health care workers by local education and training boards takes full account of the many health care workers now employed outside the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174896","174896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19306","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Health Education England is taking with its counterparts in Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland to ensure UK-wide assessment of need in the commissioning of student places for the education and training of healthcare workers.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174907","174907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19307","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2013, Official Report, column 147, on NHS accountability, when he expects to respond to the report from the Joint Overview and Scrutiny Committee regarding the deficit for Croydon's Primary Care Trust in financial year 2010-11; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174838","174838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19308","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Pakistani government on the Pakistani arrest warrant issued for Councillor Abdul Aziz.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174897","174897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19309","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the living wage; and how many direct employees of his Department are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174908","174908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19310","2013-11-08","Northern Ireland Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much the Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission spent on (a) salaries, (b) travel and (c) subsistence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174898","174898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19311","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations he has received from (a) the Mayor of London and (b) the London Borough of Bromley regarding the Bromley London Borough Council (Crystal Palace) Act 1990; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174839","174839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19312","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Tewkesbury of 15 April 2013, Official Report, column 285W, on MOD Ashchurch, what recent estimate he has made of the costs of (a) physical movements, (b) extra training, (c) redundancy payments and (d) any other items of expenditure as a result of moving operations carried out at Ashchurch; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174918","174918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19313","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that an England-wide assessment of need is made in the commissioning of student places for the education and training of healthcare workers.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174902","174902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19314","2013-11-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he or the Prime Minister has received in favour of the Prime Minister attending the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in Sri Lanka; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174840","174840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19315","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Tewkesbury of 15 April 2013, Official Report, column 285W, on MOD Ashchurch, if he will place in the Library the report of the review of the vehicle basing options and greater efficiencies from relocating facilities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174919","174919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19316","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a card to establish the right to use NHS services.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174841","174841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19317","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much in total tax receipts the Exchequer has received from non-UK resident landlords in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174844","174844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19318","2013-11-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information he holds on how many post offices have transferred to the locals model; and what assessment he has made of whether the Government's targets on transformation will be met in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174854","174854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19319","2013-11-08","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2013, Official Report, columns 612-3W, on cross country railway line, what proportion of the total network grant was paid by Network Rail to the franchised train operating company on the (a) Cross Country, (b) Greater Anglia, (c) Great Western and (d) West Coast railway line in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174847","174847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19320","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department measures Work Programme customer satisfaction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174855","174855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19321","2013-11-08","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2013, Official Report, columns 612-3W, on cross country railway line, what leasing costs the franchised train operating company on the (a) Cross Country, (b) Greater Anglia, (c) Great Western and (d) West Coast railway line paid to rolling stock companies in each year since 2009-10; and to which rolling stock company each such payment was made.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174848","174848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19322","2013-11-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many overseas trips, and at what total cost, her Department made in each year since 2010; and what the costs of (a) flights, (b) internal travel, (c) hotel accommodation and (d) subsistence were of each trip.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174856","174856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19323","2013-11-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many overseas trips, and at what total cost, his Department made in each year since 2010; and what the costs of (a) flights, (b) internal travel, (c) hotel accommodation and (d) subsistence were of each trip.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174857","174857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19324","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many overseas trips, and at what total cost, her Department made in each year since 2010; and what the costs of (a) flights, (b) internal travel, (c) hotel accommodation and (d) subsistence were of each trip.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174858","174858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19325","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many overseas trips, and at what total cost, his Department made in each year since 2010; and what the costs of (a) flights, (b) internal travel, (c) hotel accommodation and (d) subsistence were of each trip.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174859","174859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19326","2013-11-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many overseas trips, and at what total cost, his Department made in each year since 2010; and what the costs of (a) flights, (b) internal travel, (c) hotel accommodation and (d) subsistence were of each trip.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174860","174860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19327","2013-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to require environmental impact assessments for fracking in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174849","174849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19328","2013-11-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects to make an announcement on an F-35 Joint Strike Fighter Aircraft Main Gate 4 decision.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174861","174861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19329","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people had their driving licences revoked in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174862","174862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19330","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will end aid to India following the recent launch of an Indian space mission to Mars.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174850","174850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19331","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average age has been at which people have passed their driving test in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174863","174863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19332","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people hold (a) provisional and (b) full driving licences in (i) Ribble Valley constituency, (ii) Lancashire and (iii) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178464","178464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19333","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the effect on cancer services in England is of Welsh-registered patients seeking access to those cancer medicines not approved in Wales by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence or the All Wales Medicines Strategy Group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174851","174851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19334","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve rural road safety.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178465","178465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19335","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimates his Department has made of (a) the average length of time and (b) the average cost of learning to drive in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178466","178466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19336","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claiming (a) employment and support allowance, (b) income support and (c) incapacity benefit were engaged in permitted work in (i) 2008, (ii) 2009, (iii) 2010, (iv) 2011, (v) 2012 and (vi) January to October 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178467","178467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19337","2013-11-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will discuss with the Board of Royal Mail Group Ltd on the possibility of offering dividend reinvestment plans to promote continued investment by small shareholders.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178469","178469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19338","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what he expects the effect on the NHS to be of the development of a prostate cancer test which will distinguish between slow growing and more aggressive forms of the condition.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178470","178470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19339","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arms lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174969","174969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19340","2013-11-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which of the National Portfolio Organisations funded by Arts Council England received (a) over £50 million, (b) £30-£50 million, (c) £20-£30 million, (d) £10-£20 million, (e) £5-£10 million, (f) £1-£5 million, (g) less than £1 million in 2012-13.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174871","174871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19341","2013-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will offer support to Portsmouth and neighbouring authorities to help those affected by the job losses announced by BAE systems.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174872","174872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19342","2013-11-08","Attorney General","2013-11-06","To ask the Attorney General, how many direct employees and contracted workers of the Law Officers' Departments and its arms lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174970","174970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19343","2013-11-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many direct employees and contracted workers of her Department and its arms lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174973","174973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19344","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children who routinely smoke cigarettes in (a) England, (b) London and (c) Hendon constituency.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174881","174881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19345","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many direct employees and contracted workers of her Department and its arms lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174981","174981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19346","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arms lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174982","174982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19347","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the levels of child obesity in (a) England, (b) London and (c) Hendon constituency.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174882","174882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19348","2013-11-08","Northern Ireland Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many direct employees and contracted workers of her Department and its arms lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174983","174983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19349","2013-11-08","Scotland Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arms lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174984","174984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19350","2013-11-08","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arms lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174985","174985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19351","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what planning applications have been made in relation to the Ashchurch site in each year since 2005; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174875","174875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19352","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what planning applications have been made in relation to Defence Support Group Donnington in each year since 2005; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174876","174876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19353","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what next steps were agreed with Syria's neighbours following the London 11 meeting in October.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174884","174884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19354","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions Ministers in his Department have had with the governments of Yemen and Saudi Arabia on child executions in those countries.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174922","174922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19355","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the intention of the new Iranian regime to engage with the International Atomic Energy Agency on its nuclear programme.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174885","174885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19356","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the approach taken by President Rouhani in the E3+3 talks.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174886","174886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19357","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will set out the role of the Defence Infrastructure Organisation and Logistic Commodities and Services in planning for any closure of Ashchurch; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174877","174877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19358","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Burma regarding the lack of citizenship for the Rohingya community and the incitement of inter-communal violence affecting Muslim communities in Rakhine.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174923","174923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19359","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many vehicles held by his Department offer Nuclear, Biological and Chemical protection; which Defence Support Group sites are able to provide inspection and testing capability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174878","174878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19360","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent terrorist attacks in Borno State, Nigeria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174887","174887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19361","2013-11-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information his Department holds on the number of people who pay their energy bills by direct debit in each (a) region and (b) constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174924","174924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19362","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of fit for work capability assessments have been overturned on appeal in (a) each Welsh county and (b) each constituency in Wales in each year between 2008 and 2012.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174932","174932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19363","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many vehicles back loaded through the reverse supply chain to the UK from Afghanistan are compliant for use on UK roads; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174879","174879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19364","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recorded accidents there were at (a) Donnington, (b) Warminster and (c) Ashfield by (i) Defence Support Group staff and (ii) agency workers in the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174880","174880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19365","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to ensure that organisations currently being paid by the Government to provide services to victims of human trafficking will be free to comment on current provisions and policies as part of the consultation on draft legislation on modern-day slavery without prejudice to their future contractual relationship with the Government.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174925","174925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19366","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people were placed on the Future Jobs Fund programme in Vale of Clwyd constituency in each month of that programme's existence.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174934","174934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19367","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which organisations which currently provide services under contract to his Department to provide care for victims of trafficking have been contacted by officials in his Department in the last quarter.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174926","174926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19368","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people there were on jobseeker's allowance for 12 months or more in each constituency in Wales in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174935","174935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19369","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether organisations which currently provide services under contract to his Department to provide care for victims of trafficking have been instructed or advised by officials in his Department not to comment on the policies and practice of his Department.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174927","174927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19370","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of people required to maintain the second proposed aircraft carrier whilst it is baseported; and what estimate he has made of such number if that carrier is mothballed.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174936","174936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19371","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking with the Department for International Development to ensure that the UK's response to the problems in Kachin State is comprehensive.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174920","174920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19372","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the transfer of deep maintenance work from Plymouth to Portsmouth.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174937","174937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19373","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the capability of Jama'atu Ansarul Muslimina Fi Biladis Sudan within Nigeria and the region.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174921","174921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19374","2013-11-08","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who is responsible for track and infrastructure maintenance on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174938","174938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19375","2013-11-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to his Answer to the hon. Member for Penistone and Stocksbridge, of 10 October 2013, Official Report, column 280 on bovine tuberculosis, on the basis of what evidence he stated that some of the badgers that have been shot have been desperately sick; and how many and what proportion of the badgers that have been shot to date have (a) undergone a post-mortem sufficient to test for TB infection and (b) been found to have advanced TB.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174928","174928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19376","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2013, Official Report, column 268W, on Afghanistan, how many fluent Pashto speakers her Department currently employs in Afghanistan; what the total annual cost to her Department is of such employees; and how many such fluent Pashto speakers are employed in the Helmand region of Afghanistan.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174939","174939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19377","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he has made in promoting governance reform of the International Monetary Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174962","174962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19378","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2013, Official Report, column 268W, on Afghanistan, how many commercial flights currently run each week; when flight services began from the Bost Airfield; and how many local businesses have used the airfield for commercial flights to date.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174940","174940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19379","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people with an annual income of less than £7,592 paid class 1 national insurance contributions in 2012-13; and what the total value of those contributions was.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174930","174930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19380","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2013, Official Report, column 268W, on Afghanistan, whether the airfield has been used to transport any freight from the local area to other regions of Afghanistan.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174941","174941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19381","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Work Programme in (a) Vale of Clwyd constituency and (b) North Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174931","174931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19382","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department records the nationality of new claimants of universal credit in Hammersmith and Fulham; and if his Department will publish all data it records on the nationality of such claimants.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174963","174963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19383","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the process is for closing a free school.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174952","174952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19384","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of free schools he expects to fail.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174953","174953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19385","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the framework for the monitoring visits of free schools carried out by his Department in their first year of operation; and who is responsible for resourcing improvements required.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174955","174955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19386","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS Trusts have failed to meet their referral to treatment targets since May 2010; and in what months each such failure occurred.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174965","174965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19387","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the number of independent financial advisers trading without professional indemnity insurance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174957","174957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19388","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on how many people currently employed by banks operating in the UK are paid (a) the national minimum wage for apprentices, (b) the national minimum wage for full-time equivalents and (c) the national living wage.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174958","174958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19389","2013-11-11","Attorney General","2013-11-06","To ask the Attorney General, how many people in the Cleveland Police area were prosecuted for breaches of anti-social behaviour orders in (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013 to date.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174966","174966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19390","2013-11-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will take steps to encourage energy companies to continue with discounts for customers who pay their bills by direct debit.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174959","174959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19391","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how many NHS trusts are currently prescribing nabiximols (Sativex).","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174960","174960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19392","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide additional funding to NHS Trusts in the North East to develop resilience to increased pressures on accident and emergency departments during winter.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174967","174967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19393","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people currently claiming (a) working tax credit and (b) child tax credit were non-UK nationals at the point of being issued a National Insurance number.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174961","174961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19394","2013-11-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on giving claimants a choice between remaining on the higher rate mobility of disability living allowance and taking responsibility for attending all NHS medical appointments personally and not having this allowance and giving this responsibility to the NHS.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174968","174968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19395","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the UK Border Force's submission to the Government's Red Tape Challenge on General Aviation.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175016","175016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19396","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the UK Border Force will be represented on the Challenge Panel which will oversee the Civil Aviation Authority's changes to the regulatory system for general aviation.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175017","175017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19397","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174989","174989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19398","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs Notice 701/7, relating to VAT reliefs for disabled people, has been promulgated with the (a) Defence Infrastructure Organisation and (b) Reserve Forces and Cadets Association for applications on future adaptation projects.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174988","174988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19399","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has a complete list of UK-registered private planes.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175018","175018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19400","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many private flights are undertaken each year in UK airspace.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175019","175019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19401","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many trainees (a) started the School Direct programme in 2012-13 and (b) having started that programme, did not achieve Qualified Teacher Status.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175010","175010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19402","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to apply automatic penalties for under-recruitment to School Direct places in the present academic year.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175011","175011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19403","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he expects to publish his evaluation of the School Direct programme.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175012","175012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19404","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average length of time is for approval of local plans submitted by local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175021","175021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19405","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to announce a decision on Solihull Metropolitan Borough Council's local plan.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175022","175022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19406","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools recruited through School Direct in 2012-13 for trainees to start in 2013.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175013","175013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19407","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of modern technology and digital media on levels of mental health in children and adolescents.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175014","175014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19408","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many post-graduate certificate in education courses have closed since 2010; and how many teacher trainees were accepted in 2009-10 onto courses that have closed since 2010.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175023","175023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19409","2013-11-08","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the most recent findings are of the Rail Delivery Group with regard to workforce planning and the creation of apprenticeships for the rail industry.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175015","175015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19410","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many School Direct candidates were declined by partner Initial Teacher Training providers after they had been selected by a school.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175024","175024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19411","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of schools that recruited through School Direct in 2012-13 for trainees to start in 2013 were (a) not rated Outstanding in their most recent Ofsted inspection and (b) not partnered with lead schools that were rated Outstanding by Ofsted in their most recent inspection.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175025","175025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19412","2013-11-08","Cabinet Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174990","174990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19413","2013-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174991","174991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19414","2013-11-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 her Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174992","174992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19415","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174993","174993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19416","2013-11-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2013-11-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Office (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174994","174994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19417","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174995","174995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19418","2013-11-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174996","174996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19419","2013-11-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174997","174997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19420","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174998","174998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19421","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174999","174999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19422","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 her Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175000","175000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19423","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 her Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175001","175001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19424","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175002","175002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19425","2013-11-08","Northern Ireland Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 her Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175003","175003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19426","2013-11-08","Scotland Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175004","175004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19427","2013-11-08","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175005","175005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19428","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175006","175006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19429","2013-11-08","Wales Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175007","175007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19430","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many telephone lines with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843 his Department (i) operates and (ii) sponsors; how many calls each number has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175008","175008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19431","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of visits to GPs per year by people who have (a) undergone and (b) not undergone mindfulness interventions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175038","175038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19432","2013-11-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the decision by the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority (NDA) to extend for a further five years the top tier management contract of Nuclear Management Partners for Sellafield; and what discussions his Department held with the NDA in respect of the contract extension prior to it being agreed.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175049","175049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19433","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what instructions his Department has given to Ofsted inspectors in respect of the inspection of wellbeing in schools since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175028","175028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19434","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service complaints made in the (a) Royal Naval Reserve, (b) Royal Air Force Reserve and (c) Territorial Army in each of the last three years achieved resolution at each level of the process, by level.","Biography information for Glenda Jackson","Glenda Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175039","175039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19435","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the comparative criminal penalties for illegal bird killing in (a) the Cyprus Sovereign Base Areas and (b) the Republic of Cyprus.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175029","175029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19436","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service complaints made in the (a) Royal Naval Reserve, (b) Royal Air Force Reserve and (c) Territorial Army in each of the last three years failed to meet the timeline for settlement.","Biography information for Glenda Jackson","Glenda Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175040","175040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19437","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the amount consumers spend on bank fees and charges.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175051","175051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19438","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many commercial fishing licences have been sold for the waters of Ascension Island in 2013; and what the flag state is of each vessel which has purchased one of those licences.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175030","175030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19439","2013-11-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with the Office for Nuclear Regulation on its programme of stakeholder engagement; and whether (a) any Ministers or officials of his Department and (b) officials from other bodies responsible for aspects of nuclear regulation have been invited to attend such stakeholder meetings since the stakeholder forum was inaugurated.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175052","175052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19440","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that UN Resolution 2016 is upheld, particularly with reference to ensuring that the culture of impunity surrounding sexual violence ends.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175031","175031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19441","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service complaints made in the (a) Royal Naval Reserve, (b) Royal Air Force Reserve and (c) Territorial Army were made in the last three years; and what the average processing time was for such complaints.","Biography information for Glenda Jackson","Glenda Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175041","175041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19442","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take to improve the speed and management of armed forces service complaints; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Glenda Jackson","Glenda Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175042","175042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19443","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussion he has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills and (b) BAE Systems Ltd in respect of innovative ways to protect the collective skill base of the workforce at the Portsmouth Dockyard by diversification into marine energy technology systems and other related low carbon energy systems.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175053","175053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19444","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps have been taken in the last 12 months to strengthen the sustainability of the commercial fishery in Ascension Island.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175032","175032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19445","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the case for introducing secure excise duty revenue protection systems for cigarettes and hand-rolling tobacco.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175054","175054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19446","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the incidence of attention deficit hyperactivity disorder over the last 20 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175043","175043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19447","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what role her Department plays in meeting the cost of any budget overruns in the St Helena Air Access Project.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175033","175033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19448","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of teachers in each Government office region underwent their initial teacher training within that region.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175055","175055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19449","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the cost of restructuring the shipbuilding agreement with BAE Systems.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175044","175044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19450","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate (a) the total cost of the contract for the three offshore patrol vessels, (b) the unit cost of the vessels and (c) when each vessel will enter service.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175045","175045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19451","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that individuals who develop long-term conditions will be able to access insurance products to cover the sum of the social care cap.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175056","175056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19452","2013-11-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many applications for Darwin Plus funding were received in the (i) first and (ii) second application rounds; and what the total financial value was of applications received in each round.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175034","175034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19453","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects to appoint the new chief nuclear inspector.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175057","175057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19454","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether ocean patrol vessels will be equipped with (a) Scanter 4100 air search radar and (b) a hanger capable of housing a Merlin helicopter.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175046","175046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19455","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the forthcoming regulations and national eligibility criteria for social care will account for individuals of working age with moderate care needs.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175058","175058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19456","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) declare rape an illegal weapon of war, (b) insist that all incidents of rape are recorded and that reparations are given to survivors and (c) promote the international humanitarian law methods of war procedures.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175035","175035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19457","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on UN Security Council Resolution 2122 on Women, Peace and Security.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175036","175036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19458","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the report published by Public Health England on 31 October 2013, what steps he plans to take to mitigate the hazards to health of householders from exposure to radon gas transported to homes in methane gas streams obtained from the hydraulic fracturing of shale reserves.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175073","175073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19459","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his proposed rural fuel discount extension will apply to road fuel gases as well as to conventional automotive fuels.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175037","175037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19460","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the current salaries paid to (a) each board member and (b) the 10 highest paid senior executives of the Green Investment Bank (GIB); and if he will provide details of (i) how the salaries were benchmarked before being agreed and (ii) what bonus options were included in each contract for GIB senior executives.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175074","175074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19461","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list each of the contracts currently placed by his Department to develop a replacement for the Trident nuclear submarine which is covered by commercial confidentiality restrictions on disclosure of contract details.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175095","175095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19462","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the secondary and tertiary economic impact on the travel to work areas for the Portsmouth Naval shipyard prior to his announcement on reforms in UK shipbuilding priorities on 6 November 2013; and if he will publish copies on his departmental website.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175075","175075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19463","2013-11-08","Wales Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many people in Wales receive carer's allowance.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175096","175096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19464","2013-11-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the percentage incremental increase in (a) radioactivity and (b) volume of radioactive waste earmarked for a national geological disposal facility if 16GW of new nuclear generating capacity is added in the nuclear new build programme; and if he will set out the basis for the calculation in each case.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175076","175076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19465","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the living wage.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175097","175097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19466","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police information notices have been issued by Sussex Police in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175065","175065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19467","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average (a) weekly and (b) monthly value is of (a) an education support allowance, (b) a jobseeker's allowance and (c) an income support claim.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175098","175098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19468","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she has issued on police information notices and circumstances in which they are appropriate.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175118","175118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19469","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been issued with a police information notices by Sussex Police in each of the last three years which led to a subsequent charge of harassment.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175119","175119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19470","2013-11-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to pages 14-15 of the report Review of the Potential Public Health Impacts of Exposures to Chemical and Radioactive Pollutants as a result of Shale Gas Extraction, published by Public Health England on 31 October 2013, what assessment he has made of the hazards to human health of radon in the methane gas streams obtained by the hydraulic fracturing of shale which is delivered to homes within less than 3.8 days of extraction.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175077","175077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19471","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to assist UK businesses seeking amendment of Commission Regulation 900/2008 to correct the anomalies in the test methodology as set out in article 2(3)b of that Regulation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175101","175101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19472","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence was submitted by his Department as part of the call for evidence by the Youth Select Committee on its report on a curriculum for life.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175066","175066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19473","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the suspension of the Terms of Business Agreement with BAE Systems during the construction of the offshore patrol vessels means there will be no mechanisms by which BAE can claim costs for a lack of work.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175080","175080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19474","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how he proposes to respond to the Youth Select Committee report on a curriculum for life.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175121","175121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19475","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions BAE Systems has written to his Department to notify it of a (a) Key Industrial Capability Trigger Event and (b) Key Industrial Capability Notice under the terms of the 2009 Terms of Business Agreement.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175081","175081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19476","2013-11-08","House of Commons Commission","2013-11-06","To ask the hon. Member for Aberdeen North, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many written questions were tabled on each sitting day between 25 June 2009 and 30 October 2009.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175102","175102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19477","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions his Department has been served with a Key Industrial Capability notice by BAE Systems under the terms of the 2009 Terms of Business Agreement; and what the cost to the public purse of each such occasion was.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175082","175082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19478","2013-11-08","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the use of inland waterways for freight movements.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175103","175103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19479","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the monthly costs of running HM Prison the Verne as an immigration removal centre; and what the detention capacity of HM Prison the Verne will be after it is converted into an immigration removal centre.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175067","175067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19480","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the number and locations of individuals held in prison solely for immigration purposes as part of the quarterly immigration statistics.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175068","175068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19481","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2013, Official Report, column 794W, on jobseeker's allowance, what (a) number and (b) proportion of unemployed people have been signposted to local voluntary and community sector organisations by his Department by (i) region and (ii) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175083","175083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19482","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the £80 million of targeted funding for low carbon vehicle technologies made available through the Office for Low Emission Vehicles will be spent on researching the safety implications of such vehicles.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175069","175069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19483","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of higher education institutions with an Outstanding Ofsted rating have been granted a smaller core allocation for initial teacher training for academic year 2014-15 than in 2012-13.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175070","175070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19484","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people reported poor (a) mental and (b) physical health in (i) May 2010 and (ii) the most recent period for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175060","175060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19485","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of initial teacher training allocated places for academic year 2014-15 have been granted to lead institutions with an (a) Outstanding, (b) Good, (c) Requires improvement and (d) Inadequate Ofsted rating.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175071","175071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19486","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of initial teacher training allocated places for academic year (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14 were granted to lead institutions with an (a) Outstanding, (b) Good, (c) Requires improvement and (d) Inadequate Ofsted rating.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175072","175072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19487","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funds have been allocated to each Portas Pilot; what the total amount of these funds which currently remain unallocated is; if he will list the total amount of funds which have been allocated to town teams; and what the amount of these funds which currently remain unallocated is.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175087","175087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19488","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with anxiety disorder in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175062","175062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19489","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the age of onset of depression over the longest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175063","175063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19490","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of materialism on levels of mental health.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175064","175064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19491","2013-11-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households in Barrow and Furness constituency have received finance under the Green Deal since January 2013; and what the total amount of such finance was.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175089","175089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19492","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the EU's capacity-building mission in Niger.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175105","175105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19493","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many firms in Barrow and Furness constituency were subject to the national insurance holiday for new firms in each year it has been in operation.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175090","175090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19494","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to restrict the import of new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175106","175106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19495","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the total value of business rates levied in Barrow and Furness constituency was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175091","175091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19496","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the forthcoming regulations governing the eligibility criteria for social care will incorporate and adequately account for fluctuating conditions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175117","175117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19497","2013-11-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to improve the equitable sharing of benefits from genetic resources in accordance with the 2010 Nagoya Protocol.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175107","175107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19498","2013-11-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the number of households using pre-payment electricity meters in (a) Wirral, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175093","175093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19499","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue excise duty has been foregone on (a) cigarettes and (b) hand-rolling tobacco in each year since 2010-11 due to fraud and smuggling.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175122","175122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19500","2013-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department paid Sir Michael Lyons in (a) salary, (b) fees and (c) related expenses for his work on the Lyons Inquiry into Local Government in 2007.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175108","175108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19501","2013-11-11","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian consequences of government air strikes in Sudan's Darfur region in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175094","175094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19502","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department paid Sir Michael Lyons in (a) salary, (b) fees and (c) related expenses for his work on the Public Sector Relocation Review in 2007.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175109","175109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19503","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to appoint new members of the board of the Office for Nuclear Regulation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175124","175124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19504","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will give the annual results for the (a) depression register for adults number 18 plus or (b) depression prevalence for adults 18 plus (percentage) for each year in which data are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175125","175125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19505","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2013, Official Report, column 116W, on migrants: detainees, how many individuals held in prisons solely for immigration purposes had been held for (i) less than six months, (ii) between six and 12 months, (iii) between one and two years and (iv) longer than two years; and if she will provide a breakdown of the prisons in which individuals held solely for immigration purposes were held.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175110","175110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19506","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he intends to publish forecasts of child poverty during the present Parliament.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175111","175111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19507","2013-11-12","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 30 November 2012, Official Report, column 543W, on judges: county courts, what the identity of each county court was in relation to each judge in respect of which any direction was provided authorising the judge to sit pursuant to section 5(3) of the County Courts Act 1984 between 1 January 2007 and 1 November 2013.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175116","175116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19508","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of children who will be living in households with incomes below 60 per cent of contemporary median net disposable household income (a) before and (b) after housing costs in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15, (iii) 2015-16 and (iv) 2016-17.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175113","175113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19509","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the variations in local temperatures as a result of differing topography in relation to the cold weather payment.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175126","175126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19510","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with representatives of the dairy industry on future options for the Nursery Milk Scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175114","175114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19511","2013-11-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to abolish the time restraints on a family provision claim in the circumstances of an intestacy death.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175115","175115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19512","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish (a) the recorded average temperatures used for the calculation of cold weather payments at the weather station at Mona, Ynys Môn, for each week of the last five years and (b) the average temperature at Bethesda, Arfon, for each week of the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175127","175127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19513","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the difference in recorded temperatures between the weather station at Mona, Ynys Môn and Bethesda in Arfon constituency in relation to the cold weather payment.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175128","175128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19514","2013-11-11","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when (a) he was made aware of the French military manoeuvres which took place in the South West on 5 November 2013, (b) HMNB Devonport was advised of the plans of the French army and (c) Devon and Cornwall Constabulary was informed that the French military were undertaking manoeuvres in the UK and would need an escort.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175134","175134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19515","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of (a) the costs of a new national procurement process for the Nursery Milk Scheme and (b) the costs to business of the adoption of an e-voucher scheme for providing nursery milk.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175135","175135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19516","2013-11-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many national governing bodies have been set a specific target for raising female participation in return for Sport England's 2013 to 2017 Whole Sport Plan investment.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175129","175129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19517","2013-11-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations he has received on the banning of Chinese lanterns.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175131","175131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19518","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the number of School Direct trainees recruited for the 2013-14 academic year for each subject, by the government region of the lead institution.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175136","175136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19519","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many domestic homicide reviews have been undertaken since April 2011; and in how many such cases (a) the perpetrator had an alcohol misuse problem or was drinking at or around the time of the fatal attack and (b) was known to health services as having a mental health problem.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175130","175130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19520","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the overall (a) School Direct allocation, (b) Core allocation (postgraduate), (c) Core allocation (undergraduate) and (d) Core allocation (School Centred Initial Teacher Training) has the National College for Teaching and Leadership calculated will need to be filled in academic year 2014-15 in order for the overall recruitment target to be met.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175137","175137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19522","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-PSNI officers have been deployed in Northern Ireland in each of the last three years; and from which constabulary each such officer was deployed.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174780","174780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19523","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the costs of assessing transport to personal independence payment assessment centres are borne by Atos under their contractor or paid separately by his Department.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174788","174788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19524","2013-11-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with Lord Marland on human rights in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174825","174825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19525","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that objective 5 contained in the Annual Reports of Her Majesty's Courts and Tribunals Service 2012-13, to reduce the number of cases coming before courts and tribunals, is appropriately balanced against the other objectives of that body.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174901","174901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19526","2013-11-08","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she was informed of the Royal Parks' intention to introduce charges for people wanting to play sport on the section of Hyde Park known as the Old Football Pitches.","Biography information for Baroness Jowell","Dame Tessa Jowell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174894","174894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19527","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time is for taxi drivers to receive Disclosure and Barring Service checks; and how many and what proportion of applicants who work as taxi drivers have to wait more than (a) two and (b) three months (i) in each region, (ii) in each police force area and (iii) nationally for such checks.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174842","174842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19528","2013-11-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding the (a) Royal Opera House, (b) Southbank Centre, (c) National Theatre, (d) English National Opera, (e) British Museum, (f) Natural History Museum, (g) Imperial War Museum, (h) National Gallery, (i) Royal Museums Greenwich, (j) National Museums Liverpool, (k) National Portrait Group, (l) Science Museum Group, (m) Tate Gallery, (n) Wallace Collection, (o) Museum of Science and Industry Manchester, (p) Sir John Soane's Museum, (q) Horniman Museum and Gardens, (r) Geffrye Museum, (s) Royal Armouries and (t) British Library received or is forecast to receive from (i) her Department, (ii) Arts Council England and (iii) the National Lottery in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174843","174843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19529","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to use staff who process housing benefit for district and unitary councils to process universal credit.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174852","174852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19530","2013-11-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people received shares in Royal Mail Group Ltd at the recent flotation; how much was retained due to the difference in the £750 worth of shares applied for and the £749.10 given in shares; and what happened to the amount retained.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 178468","178468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19531","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with Ministers and officials in other departments regarding the effect of the introduction of universal credit with regard to (a) staffing levels at local authorities which currently process housing benefit, (b) redundancy costs for those staff and (c) whether those staff could process universal credit.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174853","174853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19532","2013-11-08","Cabinet Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174971","174971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19533","2013-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174972","174972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19534","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174974","174974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19535","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174975","174975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19536","2013-11-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174976","174976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19537","2013-11-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174977","174977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19538","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174978","174978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19539","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174979","174979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19540","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many direct employees and contracted workers of her Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174980","174980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19541","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a detailed stockholding assessment has been carried out for the storage of military vehicles following withdrawal from (a) Afghanistan and (b) Germany; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174873","174873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19542","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many direct employees and contracted workers of his Department and its arm's lengths bodies are paid less than the rate defined by the Living Wage Foundation as a living wage; and how many direct employees are on zero hours contracts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174986","174986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19543","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what activities his Department carries out at Ashchurch; and which other Ministry of Defence sites have been identified as having (a) the capacity, (b) the area of land and (c) the skills mix to replicate each such activity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174874","174874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19544","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions Ministers in his Department have had with other Security Council members on Iran's reported contravention of UN Security Council Resolution 1747.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174883","174883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19545","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what number and proportion of claimants of jobseeker's allowance have been sanctioned in (a) each Welsh county and (b) each constituency in Wales in the latest year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174933","174933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19546","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of financial sanctions on members of the government of Zimbabwe and individuals associated with them.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174888","174888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19547","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has for staffing levels at the Tax Credit Office in Preston following the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174942","174942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19548","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has plans to regulate and license shisha bars and cafes.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174943","174943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19549","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether UK aid to UNRWA is used to fund UNRWA political lobbyists.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174929","174929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19550","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who is responsible for buying out existing contracts at a failed free school.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174954","174954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19551","2013-11-11","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has (a) to replace class 142, 143 and 144 railbuses and (b) to make such buses compliant with the Disability Discrimination Act.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174956","174956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19552","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department has spent on the promotion of five a day for mental health in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174987","174987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19553","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many private flights arriving in the UK are not checked on arrival by UK Border Force staff.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175020","175020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19554","2013-11-11","Department for Education","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applicants to School Direct in 2012-13 had a UK undergraduate degree that was (a) first class, (b) second class, upper division (2.1), (c) second class, lower division (2.2), (d) third class and (e) ordinary degree (pass).","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175026","175026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19555","2013-11-11","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate she has made of the number of young people in young offenders' institutions and specialist children's homes; and if she will distinguish those who are jailed on human trafficking offences.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175027","175027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19556","2013-11-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department first obtained a copy of the report the PBO model at Sellafield: Performance to 31 May 2013, commissioned by the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority from KPMG; and what factors underpinned the decision of his Department not to make a copy of this report available to (a) the Public Accounts Committee PAC and (b) the National Audit Office prior to the PAC hearing on assurance of reported savings at Sellafield held on 4 November 2013.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175050","175050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19557","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate how much the contract overruns in the Aircraft Carrier Alliance cost the public purse to date.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175047","175047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19558","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which equipment programmes currently have a cost overrun risk ratio of 90 per cent for the public purse and 10 per cent for the contractor.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175048","175048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19559","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Royal Navy vessels will use gas turbine parts from Kawasaki Heavy Industries.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175120","175120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19560","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the need for a weather station in Arfon to better record local temperatures in relation to the cold weather payment.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175099","175099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19561","2013-11-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with other EU member states and the European Commission regarding the draft Regulation amending Commission Regulation (EC) No 900/2008 to correct the anomalies in the test methodology for assessing the content of milk fat in whey protein as set out in article 2(3)b of that Regulation.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175100","175100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19562","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the agreement in principle for three offshore patrol vessels with BAE Systems.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175078","175078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19563","2013-11-08","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Heads of Terms signed with the Aircraft Carrier Alliance.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175079","175079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19564","2013-11-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of EU sanctions against Belarus.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175104","175104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19565","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications for funds under the Mayoral High Streets Fund (a) have been received, (b) have been approved, (c) have been rejected and (d) are currently outstanding; and what total amount of funds remains unallocated under the High Streets Fund.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175084","175084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19566","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications for funds under the High Street Support Scheme (a) have been received, (b) have been approved, (c) have been rejected and (d) are currently outstanding; and what total amount of funds remains unallocated under the High Street Support Scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175085","175085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19567","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to question 171111, how many shares in the Royal Mail are being sold to (a) foreign and (b) domestic shareholders; and how many shares were purchased in each region.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175059","175059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19568","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications for funds under the High Street Innovation Fund (a) have been received, (b) have been approved, (c) have been rejected and (d) are currently outstanding; and what total amount of funds remains unallocated under the High Street Innovation Fund.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175086","175086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19569","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many working days were lost owing to (a) anxiety, (b) depression and (c) stress in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175061","175061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19570","2013-11-11","Home Office","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total number of claims made by businesses in relation to the August 2011 riots under the Riots (Damages) Act 1886 is; how many such claims have been settled; how many such claims have been rejected; how many such claims remain outstanding; what total sum has been paid to busineses under the Act in relation to the August 2011 riots; and what the total amount claimed by businesses to date is.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175088","175088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19571","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department has spent on promoting free winter influenza vaccinations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175092","175092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19572","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish an update on his Department's plans to develop and test an arrears segmentation approach in respect of child maintenance arrears combining a client's willingness and ability to pay with other available data sources, and using the client's history of paying in order to test different communications messages and the effect it has on payment behaviour.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175123","175123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19573","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has spent on administering the UK Guarantees Scheme to date.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175112","175112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19574","2013-11-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to ban the use of Chinese lanterns.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175132","175132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19575","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to discourage people from taking out multiple payday loans.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 175133","175133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19716","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that provision of NHS services will not be open to legal challenge as a result of the proposed transatlantic trade and investment partnership.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174818","174818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19717","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS will be exempt from any competition and investment provisions agreed as part of a transatlantic trade and investment partnership.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174819","174819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19718","2013-11-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many small businesses are in receipt of 100 per cent small business rate relief.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174835","174835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19719","2013-11-12","Department for Transport","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the injury rate in accidents on the A15 north of Lincoln was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174845","174845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19720","2013-11-11","HM Treasury","2013-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress he has made in encouraging the American government and Congress to approve the quota and governance reforms agreed by the International Monetary Fund Board of Governors in December 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174964","174964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19807","2013-11-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on compensation for people with mesothelioma.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901037","901037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19808","2013-11-12","House of Commons Commission","2013-11-06","To ask the right hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what committees of the House are consulted before displays or exhibitions take place in Westminster Hall.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174846","174846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19003","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to work with NHS bodies, local authorities, police and other agencies to (a) prevent people with mental health problems becoming victims of crime and (b) support people with mental health problems who are victims of crime.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174564","174564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19004","2013-11-07","Department for Transport","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the personal injury rate on the A428 has been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174565","174565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19005","2013-11-07","Department for Transport","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how long the average journey time on the A428 from St Neots to Cambridge has been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174566","174566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19006","2013-11-07","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what role the Principal of Kings Science Academy, Bradford had in the appointment of (a) Dr Waheed Hussain and (b) other governors of the school.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174567","174567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19007","2013-11-07","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Kings Science Academy, Bradford received an independent valuation before awarding a contract for lease of land from a company owned by Mr Alan Lewis.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174568","174568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19008","2013-11-07","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission an urgent independent inquiry on why Action Fraud did not investigate allegations of fraud at Kings Science Academy, Bradford, referred to it by the Department for Education in April 2013, until October 2013.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174569","174569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19009","2013-11-07","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons his Department did not enquire for at least six months about the progress of a police investigation into fraud allegations at Kings Science Academy, Bradford, referred to Action Fraud by his Department in April 2013.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174570","174570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19010","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Health Education England takes with its counterparts in Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland to ensure that assessment of need in the commissioning of student places for the education and training of health care workers takes place on a UK-wide basis.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174571","174571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19011","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether all A & B vehicles back-loaded through the reverse supply chain to (a) RAF Warminster, (b) RAF Lyneham, (c) Ashchurch, (d) Donnington and (e) Warminster are held in short-term storage to comply with AESP 2300-A-401-031; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174572","174572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19012","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many A & B vehicles were back-loaded through the reverse supply chain to (a) RAF Warminster, (b) RAF Lyneham, (c) Ashchurch, (d) Donnington and (e) Warminster from Afghanistan in 2012 and 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174573","174573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19013","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which recommendations in Professor John Perkins' review of engineering skills published in November 2013 he has accepted; and what arrangements he is making for their implementation.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174582","174582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19014","2013-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department gives local planning authorities on asking people to state their sexual orientation when completing their responses to Joint Core Strategy or Local Plan consultation documents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174583","174583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19015","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse to 1 April 2017 of the Employee Shareholder legislation up to 1 April 2017; how many companies will make use of this legislation by 1 April 2017; and what estimate he has made of the number of employee shareholders by 1 April 2017.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174584","174584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19016","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the powers available of Police and Crime Panels when considering complaints made against Police and Crime Commissioners; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174585","174585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19017","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish the financial notice to improve letter sent by his Department to Kings Science Academy in May 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174586","174586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19018","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons Action Fraud informed his Department that it was not taking any further action into allegations of fraud at the Kings Science Academy, Bradford.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174588","174588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19019","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what early intervention measures he has introduced to reduce young offending since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174589","174589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19020","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of young offenders aged over 16 have gone into full-time education upon leaving custody in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174590","174590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19021","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much individual covered vehicle storage space is available at (a) RAF Warminster, (b) RAF Lyneham, (c) Ashchurch, (d) Donnington and (e) Warminster; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174575","174575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19022","2013-11-07","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will take steps to include British Sign Language within the modern foreign language group of subjects in the national curriculum.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174577","174577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19023","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the frequency is of the regular visual inspection of A & B vehicles stored at (a) RAF Warminster, (b) RAF Lyneham, (c) Ashchurch, (d) Donnington and (e) Warminster; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174578","174578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19024","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many A & B vehicles are currently (a) stored under cover in an unheated hangar and (b) outside in the open at (i) RAF Warminster, (ii) RAF Lyneham, (iii) Ashchurch, (iv) Donnington and (v) Warminster; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174579","174579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19025","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any (a) Defence Council Instructions, (b) Standard Operating Procedures and (c) local regulations issued in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011 and (iii) 2012 override AESP2300-A-401-031; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174580","174580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19026","2013-11-07","Department for Transport","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of undiagnosed obstructive sleep apnoea on road safety.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174594","174594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19027","2013-11-07","Department for Transport","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many deaths caused by road traffic accidents in each of the last five years were attributable to the driver having undiagnosed obstructive sleep apnoea.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174595","174595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19028","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when young people in Stirling constituency who are currently in receipt of disability living allowance will be re-assessed for personal independence payment.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174597","174597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19029","2013-11-07","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of animals used in experiments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174598","174598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19030","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet representatives from the Hibu Shareholders Action Group to discuss reported misconduct by the board of Hibu; whether the Financial Conduct Authority plans to investigate that reported misconduct; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174599","174599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19031","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of dispensing drugs to patients with long-term conditions on a 28-day prescription cycle.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174600","174600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19032","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many days (a) under-16 year olds and (b) under-18 year olds spent on adult mental health wards in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174601","174601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19033","2013-11-11","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the value of the drug Chlortalidone in treating hypertension; and on what grounds the decision to withdraw Chlortalidone from the NHS was made.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174591","174591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19034","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether financial or other penalties will be imposed on those companies contracted to carry out the assessment process for the personal independence payment as a result of the delay to the national rollout.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174602","174602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19035","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on his Department's expenditure plans of the delay in the national rollout of the personal independence payment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174603","174603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19036","2013-11-07","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Scottish Government on tackling terrorism in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174616","174616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19037","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his most recent estimate is of the amount of revenue foregone as a result of illegal fuel being transported over the border between Northern Ireland and the Irish Republic.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174626","174626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19038","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that Portsmouth Dockyard has the capability to supply power to two aircraft carriers in dock simultaneously.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174617","174617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19039","2013-11-07","Department for Transport","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assurances on access he can provide to existing and potential future open access operators in light of the new East Coast Mainline schedule of rail franchise replacement and extension.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174618","174618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19040","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England will introduce a tariff for stereotactic ablative radiotherapy.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174627","174627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19041","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence about health technology assessment methodologies for appraising cancer medicines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174619","174619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19042","2013-11-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on maximising the tourism benefits of the stages of the Giro d'Italia being held in Northern Ireland in 2014.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174620","174620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19043","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has put in place to monitor the number of people who carry the abnormal prion protein which causes variant Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174628","174628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19044","2013-11-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many staff in his Department (a) were disciplined and (b) had their employment terminated as a result of a poor sickness record in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174629","174629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19045","2013-11-07","Northern Ireland Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which victims' groups she has met since her appointment.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174623","174623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19046","2013-11-07","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in his Department (a) were disciplined and (b) had their employment terminated as a result of a poor sickness record in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174630","174630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19047","2013-11-07","Northern Ireland Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what meetings she has had with foreign direct investors in Northern Ireland since her appointment.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174624","174624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19048","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans that screening of the abnormal prion protein which causes variant Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease will be introduced.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174631","174631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19049","2013-11-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress his Department has made on the creation and implementation of Shariah-compliant student loans for those potential students who cannot make use of the traditional loan system as a result of their religious convictions; and when he expects such a system to be fully operable.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174636","174636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19050","2013-11-07","Department for International Development","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the UK plans to vote against further World Bank loans to Argentina (a) in December 2013 and (b) for the foreseeable future.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174625","174625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19051","2013-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on how many Palestinians receiving United Nations Relief and Works Agency aid are surviving refugees from 1948.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174632","174632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19052","2013-11-07","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Romanian and Bulgarian nationals who choose to live in the UK have the means to support themselves and their families.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174637","174637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19053","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many visits were made to a GP in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174639","174639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19054","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the rate of mortgage default was in each (a) region, (b) local authority area, (c) parliamentary constituency and (d) town in the latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174640","174640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19055","2013-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will take steps to ensure that specific funds are directed to the uplands in the reformed CAP.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174604","174604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19056","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions his Department has overruled the Schools Playing Fields Advisory Panel since September 2012; and what the reason for each such case was.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174647","174647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19057","2013-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will take steps to ensure that CAP funding is restricted to those who are active farmers.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174605","174605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19058","2013-11-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of licence applications for the export of strategic goods and items are currently processed by his Department's Export Control Organisation within 60 days.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174641","174641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19059","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted inspection reports on mainstream schools in the past year have commented on the quality of specialist education support services for deaf children.","Biography information for Lord Bruce of Bennachie","Sir Malcolm Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174648","174648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19060","2013-11-07","Department for Transport","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) traffic volume and (b) accident rate was on the A428 in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174606","174606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19061","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of disability living allowance living in areas other than Wales, the Midlands and East Anglia received notification that they would be reassessed for personal independence payment before the announcement of the delay to the national rollout.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174642","174642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19062","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timescale was for decisions for terminally ill people who applied for disability living allowance under the Special Rules process from 1 January to 1 October 2013.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174643","174643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19063","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the number of people who carry the abnormal prion protein which causes variant Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174633","174633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19064","2013-11-07","Attorney General","2013-11-05","To ask the Attorney General, in how many cases criminal charges have been (a) considered and (b) brought against undercover police officers for suspected offences committed while they were undercover in the last three years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174607","174607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19065","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timescale is for decisions for people with terminal illnesses who apply for personal independence payments under the Special Rules procedures.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174644","174644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19066","2013-11-07","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how her Department checks the accreditation process for detainee custody officers who work as overseas escorts during the enforced removal of foreign nationals from the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174608","174608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19067","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what appointment procedure and external scrutiny took place when the Senior Responsible Officer, PCT Estate Programme, at his Department became a non-executive director of NHS Property Services; and what salary he receives.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174650","174650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19068","2013-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Palestinians who were born and live in the West Bank and Gaza are considered by his Department to be refugees.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174634","174634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19069","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in his Department (a) were disciplined and (b) had their employment terminated as a result of a poor sickness record in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174645","174645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19070","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's total spending on research programmes for motor neurone disease is (a) for the duration of the current Parliament and (b) in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174651","174651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19071","2013-11-07","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has introduced realistic scenario-based training replicating situations and safe restraint techniques for use on board aircraft for overseas escorts undertaking enforced removals of foreign nationals from the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174609","174609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19072","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what restrictions have been imposed by the Spanish government on the movements of NATO military aircraft and warships in (a) the vicinity of Gibraltar and (b) transit between Spain and Gibraltar in the last 12 months; and what recent steps he has taken to have such restrictions lifted.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174635","174635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19073","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in which Jobcentre Plus (a) districts and (b) offices lone parent advisers operate.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174652","174652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19074","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many removal directions served on immigration detainees have been cancelled and reset in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174610","174610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19075","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on the Support for Mortgage Interest scheme in (a) 2007-08, (b) 2008-09, (c) 2009-10, (d) 2010-11, (e) 2011-12 and (f) 2012-13.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174653","174653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19076","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many lone parent advisers were working for Jobcentre Plus in (a) 2008, (b) 2009, (c) 2010, (d) 2011 and (e) 2012,","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174654","174654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19077","2013-11-21","Department for Transport","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions HS2 Ltd has had with (a) relevant local authorities and (b) Lichfield District Council on the relocation of residents and those properties affected by High Speed 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174593","174593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19078","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what fire safety arrangements were in place at Campsfield House Immigration Removal Centre at the time of the fire on 18 October 2013; whether working sprinklers were in place; and whether a roll call of detainees and employees was held after evacuation of the building.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174611","174611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19079","2013-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost to each local authority in England of recouping rent arrears owed by council house tenants since 1 April 2013.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174655","174655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19080","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many administrative reviews have been (a) requested and (b) completed following a refusal of an application made outside the UK for a visa to enter the UK for each of the last five years for which information is available.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174612","174612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19081","2013-11-08","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) nurses and (b) doctors were working in hospitals in Merseyside in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174656","174656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19082","2013-11-18","Department for Transport","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how his Department calculated the contingency sums included in the estimated costs for the (a) construction of and (b) rolling stock for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Frank Dobson","Frank Dobson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174613","174613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19083","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many of her Department's staff do not speak English as their first language.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174657","174657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19084","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made in investigating claims that the UK Border Agency asked lesbian, gay, bisexual and transgender asylum seekers to prove their sexuality.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174658","174658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19085","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the pilot offering employment and support allowance applicants the option to have their work capability assessments audio recorded will end; and when an evaluation report of this pilot will be published.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174659","174659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19086","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the risk register associated with his Department's consultation on transforming rehabilitation.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174660","174660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19087","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time taken between a decision to award a benefit and the start of payments.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174662","174662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19088","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time is between an application for (a) disability living allowance and (b) personal independence payment and the setting of a date for an assessment.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174663","174663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19089","2013-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on the development of social tariffs to help low income households with the cost of water.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174671","174671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19090","2013-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on the continuation of the Air Quality Grants programme.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174672","174672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19091","2013-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he intends to publish his Department's response to the Local Air Quality Management delivery in England consultation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174673","174673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19092","2013-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of people who pay lower water bills as a result of the WaterSure tariff.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174674","174674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19093","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many on-site exploratory salvage and marine operations have occurred in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174675","174675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19094","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many vessels (a) worldwide and (b) in UK territorial waters are active concerns for the Salvage and Marine Operations unit.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174676","174676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19095","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much income tax did not accrue to the Exchequer from taxpayers resident in Scotland due to changes in the base rate in (a) 2011-12 and (b) 2012-13; and what estimate he has made of such figures in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174677","174677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19096","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to prevent companies erroneously claiming that sales were made in Ireland and not the UK for the purposes of calculating corporation tax.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174678","174678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19097","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency; and if he will publish the results of that assessment.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174680","174680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19098","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will seek to renegotiate international tax agreements to prevent companies paying tax in Ireland on profits and sales made in the UK.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174699","174699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19099","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions have been issued to jobseeker's allowance claimants in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174710","174710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19100","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the net effect on revenue collected by HM Revenue and Customs of taxation agreements between the UK and Ireland.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174700","174700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19101","2013-11-07","Ministry of Defence","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) UK contractors, (b) UK civilians, (c) MOD personnel, (d) Ministry of Defence Police, (e) RAF personnel and (f) GCHQ personnel work at NSA Menwith Hill.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174711","174711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19102","2013-11-07","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the annual budget is of each police constabulary in the South West.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174712","174712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19103","2013-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Swansea Magistrates' Court is able to absorb the transferred case load from the proposed closure of the Neath Port Talbot Magistrates' Court; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174701","174701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19104","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to reconfigure general, non-specialist, paediatric services in (a) Stafford and (b) England.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174720","174720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19105","2013-11-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2013, Official Report, column 371W, on renewable energy, if he will set out the form he envisages the provision for cancellation will take; and under what circumstances the provision for cancellation will be applied.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174664","174664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19106","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff who work for the East and North Herts NHS Trust earned between (a) £50,000 and £66,000, (b) £67,000 to £99,000 and (c) £100,000 or more in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174713","174713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19107","2013-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effects of the proposed closure of the Neath Port Talbot Magistrates' Court on the ability of those in remote valley communities to travel to court hearings.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174702","174702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19108","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS organisation has overall responsibility for regional and national critical care infrastructure.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174721","174721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19109","2013-11-07","Department for International Development","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects her Department funds to support job and employment creation (a) generally, (b) for young people and (c) for women.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174722","174722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19110","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what revenue will be forgone by the Exchequer from taxpayers resident in Scotland due to changes in the income tax threshold by 25 December 2013.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174714","174714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19111","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and (b) Public Health England on the Quality and Outcomes Framework.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174665","174665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19112","2013-11-07","Wales Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice regarding the proposed closure of the Neath Port Talbot Magistrates' Court; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174703","174703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19113","2013-11-07","Department for International Development","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to make it easier for small, UK-based development charities to obtain support and match funding for their work.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174723","174723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19114","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department gives on the best size of maternity units in England in terms of the number of births handled each year.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174715","174715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19115","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in Luxembourg about tax avoidance schemes involving that country.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174704","174704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19116","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the acceptable safe travel time for women in labour.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174716","174716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19117","2013-11-07","Department for International Development","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's top 20 contractors, by value, were on projects in (a) 2010-11 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174724","174724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19118","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct Public Health England to prioritise the development of a Quality and Outcomes Framework indicator that would award points to GPs who advise, prescribe and recommend appropriate guidance and support for obese and overweight patients.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174666","174666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19119","2013-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions (a) he and (b) HM Courts and Tribunals Service (HMCTS) have had with local individuals and organisations on the proposed closure of the Neath Port Talbot Magistrates' Court prior to the publication of the HMCTS impact assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174705","174705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19120","2013-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the value of export business gained by UK companies through the direct work of UK Embassies and High Commissions.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174725","174725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19121","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he will take to incentivise GPs to advise, prescribe and recommend appropriate guidance and support for obese and overweight patients.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174667","174667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19122","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many residents in Scotland paid the 20p income tax rate in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174668","174668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19123","2013-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what comparative assessment he has made of the growth in UK exports to (a) countries where a diplomatic mission has been maintained and (b) countries with no UK diplomatic mission.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174726","174726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19124","2013-11-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support export growth to countries where the UK does not maintain a permanent diplomatic mission.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174727","174727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19125","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much Sir Michael Lyons was paid in (a) salary, (b) other fees, (c) related expenses and (d) total for his work on the Public Sector Relocation Review published on 15 March 2013.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174669","174669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19126","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to monitor access to insulin pump therapy in (a) Stafford and (b) England.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174728","174728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19127","2013-11-07","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will extend the public consultation on the future of Neath Port Talbot Magistrates' Court in order to consult upon specific proposals to (a) re-open the Port Talbot Magistrates' Court, (b) use the County Court at Neath, (c) adapt the Port Talbot Police Station and (d) adapt the Neath police station or Crown Building in Windsor Road in Neath; and for what reasons those proposals were not considered in the initial consultation.","Biography information for Dr Hywel Francis","Dr Hywel Francis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174706","174706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19128","2013-11-07","Department of Health","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff who work for the East and North Herts Clinical Commissioning Group earned (a) between £50,000 and £66,000, (b) between £67,000 and £99,000 and (c) £100,000 or more in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174729","174729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19129","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many enquiries were received by the Employer Checking Service in each month in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174681","174681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19130","2013-11-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with water companies on the use of their concessionary schemes to protect community groups from unaffordable surface water drainage charges.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174670","174670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19131","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will implement a same-day checking service for employers.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174682","174682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19132","2013-11-07","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of revenue foregone by the Exchequer from taxpayers resident in Scotland due to changes in the income tax threshold in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174707","174707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19133","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the benefit sanctions introduced under the Jobseekers (Back to Work) scheme 2013.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174691","174691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19134","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Answer dated 29 October 2013, Official Report, columns 455-7W, on employment and support allowance, how many sustained job outcomes had been achieved by claimants on the Work Programme in each ICD disease code by February 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174683","174683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19135","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue the Exchequer has received in income tax payments from non-UK resident landlords in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174692","174692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19136","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on proposals to merge the International Monetary Fund and the World Bank.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174730","174730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19137","2013-11-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people currently in receipt of disability living allowance will be re-assessed for the personal independence payment in the three months from 7 October 2013 in the postcode areas highlighted in the Quick Guide to Personal Independence Payments, updated on 28 October 2013.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174708","174708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19138","2013-11-08","Ministry of Justice","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many decisions subject to an appeal to the Immigration and Asylum Chamber of the First-tier tribunal have been withdrawn by the Home Department within five days of the appeal date in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174694","174694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19139","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the number of illegal immigrants currently in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174731","174731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19140","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many food banks there were in the UK in (a) 2007 and (b) 2010; and how many there were on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174695","174695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19141","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the consultation Support for Mortgage Interest launched in December 2011.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174684","174684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19142","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on securing the adoption of the International Monetary Fund Special Drawing Right as the principal reserve assets in the international monetary system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174732","174732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19143","2013-11-08","Department for Education","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer to the hon. Member for Coventry South of 6 September 2013, Official Report, column 550W, on schools: playing fields, if he will publish the title of the document, including the page reference, from which the figure of 2,540 was drawn.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174696","174696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19144","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will attend the Third Global Forum on Human Resources for Health between 10 and 13 November 2013.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174686","174686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19145","2013-11-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with Post Office Limited on the progress of the Post Office Locals Transformation plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174733","174733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19146","2013-11-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people claiming jobseeker's allowance were sanctioned resulting in the loss of benefit in each constituency in the UK (a) in 2012-13 and (b) to date in the current financial year.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174697","174697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19147","2013-11-08","HM Treasury","2013-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the total liability of non-UK resident landlords to the Exchequer; and what proportion of this figure was collected by HM Revenue and Customs in the most recent tax year.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174687","174687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19148","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many offences involving a knife have been committed in (a) Liverpool, Walton constituency and (b) Liverpool city region in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174734","174734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19149","2013-11-08","Home Office","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will record numbers of those people leaving the UK.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174740","174740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/19150","2013-11-08","Department for International Development","2013-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what courses her Department provides to staff for learning a second language other than English.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 174688","174688"
