"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428037","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Enterprise Investment Scheme, Venture Capital Trust, tax relief or Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme have offered low-risk investment opportunities in energy generation; and what his Department's definition of low-risk is in this context.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16164","16164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428038","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with its UN and EU member counterparts on the reform of Standard Industrial Classification codes in order more accurately to measure the growth of the video games industry.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16136","16136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428039","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs is investigating VAT fraud conducted by online traders operating from outside the EU; and what action his Department is taking to prevent the possibility of such fraud taking place.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16173","16173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428040","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions the Government has had with (a) Amazon and (b) eBay on VAT fraud conducted by online traders operating from outside the EU; and what safeguards his Department has put in place to prevent such fraud.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16174","16174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428041","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average duration of a claim for tax credits was in Salford in the most recent (a) three and (b) six  months for which data is available.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16175","16175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428042","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total on-flow and off-flow for tax credits was for claimants in Salford in the most recent (a) three and (b) six months for which data is available.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16176","16176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428043","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the relationship between household income and (a) taxi and (b) bus use.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16196","16196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428044","2015-11-17","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that all staff in HM Revenue and Customs authorised to cancel late-filing penalties are authorised to provide the person concerned with written confirmation of that cancellation.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16209","16209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428045","2015-11-17","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that all staff in HM Revenue and Customs authorised to cancel late-payment penalties are authorised to provide the person concerned with written confirmation of that cancellation.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16210","16210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428046","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether there are alternative mechanisms for tax credits claimants to inform his Department of changes to their childcare arrangements other than the tax credits helpline.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16204","16204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428047","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average (a) export and (b) import tariffs paid by the UK to countries with whom the EU has a Free Trade Agreement was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16267","16267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428048","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many individuals have had financial sanctions imposed on them for expected involvement in terrorism in each of the last five years; and how many of those individuals are British (a) citizens and (b) residents.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16285","16285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428049","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure companies or individuals suspected of funding ISIL through oil trades do not operate or transfer money through the UK financial system; and what steps she has taken to assess whether such steps have been effective.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16278","16278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428050","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which of his Department's projects have received funding under the  European Regional Development Fund 2007 to 2013; what the location is of each such project; and how much each such project received.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16269","16269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428051","2015-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the starter homes policy on access to (a) home ownership and (b) affordable rented accommodation in (i) London and the South East and (ii) England.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16244","16244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428052","2015-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assistance his Department plans to give to local authorities to ensure that they are able to provide new affordable housing to people on low incomes.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16242","16242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428053","2015-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the extension of Right to Buy on affordable housing supply.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16243","16243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428054","2015-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to take to provide further guidance to local authorities on preventing people who apply to those authorities for accommodation from continuing to sleep rough.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16178","16178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428055","2015-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Local Government Transparency Code 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16106","16106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428056","2015-11-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Ministry of Justice press release, Prison building revolution announced by Chancellor and Justice Secretary, published on 9 November 2015, what plans the Government has to ensure that redevelopment of prison sites in central London includes an element of social housing.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16108","16108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428057","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in the Lancashire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16154","16154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428058","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in the Greater Manchester Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16155","16155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428059","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in the Merseyside Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16156","16156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428060","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change was in the number of firefighter posts in the Cheshire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16160","16160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428061","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change was in the number of firefighter posts in the Cumbria Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16161","16161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428062","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the level of resources necessary for trading standards to fulfil the additional duties set out under the Energy Performance of Buildings (England and Wales) (Amendment) (No. 2) Regulations 2015 and (b) alternative arrangements for enforcing those regulations; and what discussions his Department has had with local authority trading standards and professional groups representing trading standards on the effect that those duties will have on their resourcing.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16309","16309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428063","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Universal Service Obligation on broadband download speed for all properties will be achieved by 2016.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16303","16303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428064","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to develop a UK games archive to preserve computer and online games and the creative process which is part of their development as part of the UK's cultural identity.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16137","16137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428065","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to coordinate additional support for and recognition of the importance to modern British culture of the video games industry from (a) the BFI, (b) Arts Council of England and (c) other public agencies.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16138","16138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428066","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations his Department has received on including art and design within the curriculum for STEM subjects.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16139","16139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428067","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with VisitEngland on fiscal support for the Great Places Fund; and what the outcome of those discussions was.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16193","16193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428068","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to (a) maintain and (b) increase real terms funding for marketing of domestic tourism after 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16197","16197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428069","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what total amount of funding has been allocated to the Superconnected Cities project.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16226","16226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428070","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much of the funding for Superconnected Cities has been allocated to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16227","16227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428071","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will allocate additional funding to the Superconnected Cities fund for those applications in the most recent round that were unsuccessful.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16228","16228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428072","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has for funding for voucher offers under the Superconnected Cities fund that were not taken up.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16229","16229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428073","2015-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the armed forces compensation scheme tariffs were last reviewed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16211","16211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428074","2015-11-17","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what account he has made of the adequacy of tariffs in the armed forces compensation scheme for former service personnel with an employment-related mental illness.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16212","16212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428075","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the Trident missile renewal programme on international nuclear disarmament and non-proliferation.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16101","16101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428076","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on integrating the Eurofighter Typhoon aircraft with (a) Storm Shadow missiles, (b) Meteor missiles, (c) the DASS radar system and (d) other avionics.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16102","16102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428077","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Eurofighter Typhoon aircraft have been exported in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16103","16103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428078","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the announcement by BAE Systems on jobs, related to production of the Eurofighter Typhoon on 12 November 2015, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs that will be lost which are related to the production of that aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16104","16104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428079","2015-11-18","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the announcement by BAE Systems on jobs, related to production of the Eurofighter Typhoon on 12 November 2015, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs in each production location that will be lost which are related to the production of that aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16105","16105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428080","2015-11-17","Department for Education","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to take steps to promote the STEAM agenda in schools to support the development of skills for careers in creative digital sectors.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16084","16084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428081","2015-11-17","Department for Education","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that guidance on changes to the disabled students' allowance is easily accessible to (a) parents and (b) schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16132","16132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428082","2015-11-17","Department for Education","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the contribution of art subjects to ensuring people develop the skills needed for a career in the creative digital economy.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16097","16097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428083","2015-11-17","Department for Education","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a computer games studies qualification within the education curriculum.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16098","16098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428084","2015-11-17","Department for Education","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance has been issued to headteachers on the application of the Prevent programme in schools.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16172","16172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428085","2015-11-18","Department for Education","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which (a) primary and (b) secondary schools had more than (i) five, (ii) seven and (c) 10 per cent of pupils defined as children in need in the most recent year for which figures are available; and how many such pupils there were at each of those schools.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16199","16199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428086","2015-11-18","Department for Education","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2730, what progress she has made on establishing a school on the site of the former East Ham police station.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16203","16203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428087","2015-11-17","Department for Education","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions have taken place with teaching unions on the application of the Prevent programme in schools.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16165","16165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428088","2015-11-18","Department for Education","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in need whose primary assessment of need was abuse or neglect were within 12 months of a previous referral in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16283","16283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428089","2015-11-18","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of children in need (a) applied to and (b) entered university in the most recent years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16284","16284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428090","2015-11-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many children in families on the troubled families programme were classified as in need in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16260","16260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428091","2015-11-17","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of the funding of £500 million for shared schooling in Northern Ireland is expected to come from her Department's budget.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16298","16298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428092","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect on investor confidence in the UK electricity generation market following the recent announcements surrounding the Renewables Obligation closure and reductions in feed-in tariffs.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16308","16308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428093","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with other Government departments and in Cabinet Committees and sub-committees on the resilience and security of the UK's electricity supply.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16292","16292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428094","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with the Scottish Government on the resilience and security of the energy supply in Scotland.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16293","16293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428095","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the implications for the security of electricity supply for winter 2015-16 of the announced closure of Longannet, Ferrybridge and Eggborough power stations.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16294","16294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428096","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent steps she has taken to continue to ensure the security of the electricity supply in the UK.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16295","16295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428097","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions her Department has had with National Grid on its Winter Outlook Report 2015-16, published in October 2015.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16296","16296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428098","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with National Grid after it gave its notification of inadequate system margin on 5 November 2015.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16297","16297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428099","2015-11-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of UK withdrawal from the EU on the importation of electricity from the Republic of Ireland into Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16272","16272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428100","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to support the development of domestic oil purchasing syndicates.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16277","16277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428101","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to (a) promote the installation of domestic solar photovoltaic systems and (b) provide funding streams for such installations.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16253","16253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428102","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if her Department will bring forward plans to invest in energy storage, including pump storage hydro, to increase security of electricity supply.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16236","16236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428103","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the probability of the UK not being able to rely on electricity interconnectors to the continent as in previous years because of French and Belgian supply being limited until 2020 due to the closure of old fossil fuel plant and nuclear reactors in those countries.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16182","16182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428104","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on security of energy supply of failures this winter in the operation of those major coal power stations which are due to close in spring 2016.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16183","16183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428105","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the probability of the UK having to export electricity across the interconnectors to the continent at times of peak demand during winter 2015-16.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16184","16184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428106","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect of the National Grid's assumption of electricity supply from interconnectors increasing from 0GW to 1GW of electricity at the same time as electricity margins on the continent shrink on the UK being able to import electricity at times of peak demand.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16185","16185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428107","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans her Department has to increase electricity generation in 2015-16 and 2016-17.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16186","16186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428108","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether COBR has a role in considering resilience issues relating to security of energy supply.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16198","16198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428109","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of proposed changes to feed-in tariffs on the solar industry in Scotland.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16217","16217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428110","2015-11-18","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average time taken is for customers to switch their domestic energy supplier.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16157","16157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428111","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of developing zero subsidy Contracts for Difference auctions for the electricity supply market; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16074","16074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428112","2015-11-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many times the National Grid has used the demand side balancing reserve in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16075","16075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428113","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average household bill for water was in (a) Enfield North constituency, (b) Enfield, (c) Greater London and (d) the UK in (i) 2010 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16085","16085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428114","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's priorities are for the Clean Growth Committee; what role she will have on that committee; and whether that committee will consider her Department's air quality consultation.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16221","16221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428115","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on cleaning rivers and waterways in each of the last five years; and what estimate she has made of the level of such funding in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16219","16219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428116","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to review the Pet Animals Act 1951.","Biography information for Jim Dowd","Jim Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16208","16208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428117","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish the cost benefit analysis of the year 1 and 2 badger cull pilots; for what reasons the roll-out to Dorset of the badger culls went ahead prior to the publication of that cost benefit analysis; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16192","16192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428118","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the cost of (a) completing the network of Marine Conservation Zones and (b) creating a blue belt around British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16220","16220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428119","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on the recording of food crime as an identifiable category of crime in police databases.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16222","16222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428120","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding for the 25 year plan on biodiversity; and what estimate she has made of the costs of implementing that plan.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16223","16223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428121","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with HM Treasury on the removal of the fuel duty escalator for liquefied petroleum gas as part of government proposals to reduce emissions from road transport.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16248","16248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428122","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of ancient woodland is located within (a) national parks and (b) areas of outstanding natural beauty; and what proportion of that woodland has site of special scientific interest status.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16224","16224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428123","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce in the rest of the UK the General Licence Restriction Order for the protection of birds in use in Scotland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16252","16252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428124","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evaluation she made of the potential effect on delivering sustainable development (a) on the Government Estate and (b) in the UK of the planned reduction in her Department's expenditure.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16256","16256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428125","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the net present value of a phase-out of the use of lead ammunition for sports shooting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16255","16255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428126","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the objectives of the National Wildlife Crime Unit are beyond March 2016.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16257","16257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428127","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which of her Department's projects have received funding under the  European Agricultural Guarantee Fund 2007 to 2013; what the location is of each such project; and how much each such project received.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16270","16270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428128","2015-11-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which of her Department's projects have received funding under the  European Marine Fisheries Fund 2007 to 2013; what the location is of each such project; and how much each such project received.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16271","16271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428129","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the cost of protection and conservation of UK coastlines has been over the last five years; and what the projected cost of such protection and conservation will be over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16304","16304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428130","2015-11-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the value to tourism and to the national economy of the UK coastline.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16305","16305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428131","2015-11-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has to protect and conserve the UK's coastlines.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16291","16291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428132","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer about the level of funding for the (a) Food Crime Unit and (b) Food Standards Agency.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16299","16299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428133","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what work his Department is undertaking with authorities in China to support the welfare of animals.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16262","16262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428134","2015-11-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with his counterparts in (a) China, (b) Vietnam and (c) South Korea about the dog meat trade in those countries.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16263","16263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428135","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to develop a comprehensive strategy to combat ISIL and simultaneously prioritise the protection of civilians in Syria.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16289","16289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428136","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessments her Department has made of the effect of the relocation of the Visa and Entry Clearance Office from Dakha to New Delhi on people from Bangladesh applying for a visa to enter the UK.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16231","16231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428137","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the Government's Visa and Entry Clearance Office in Dakha, Bangladesh is being relocated to New Delhi, India.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16230","16230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428138","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress made by Montserrat in meeting the Prime Minister's ambition for a public register of beneficial ownership since June 2013.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16079","16079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428139","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the time taken for the Turks and Caicos Islands to respond to his Department's consultation on a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16080","16080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428140","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Indian government on re-opening border crossings to Nepal since discussions were held between the British and Indian ambassadors to Nepal on border blockages on 30 October.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16083","16083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428141","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will ensure that any agreement on a central registry of beneficial ownership in the Turks and Caicos Islands will include access for the public with legitimate reason.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16076","16076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428142","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the time taken for Montserrat to respond to his Department's consultation on a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16081","16081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428143","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure consistent and comprehensive communications by travel insurance companies with UK nationals in Sharm el-Sheikh, Egypt.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16095","16095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428144","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions the Government has had with (a) the Egyptian authorities, (b) airlines and (c) other national and international bodies on changes to the allocation of slots for flights arriving and leaving Sharm el-Sheikh airport.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16093","16093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428145","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress made by the Turks and Caicos Islands in meeting the Prime Minister's ambition for a public register of beneficial ownership since June 2013.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16078","16078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428146","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the former Emir of Qatar, Sheikh Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani, is a diplomat at Minister-Counsellor rank in the Qatari embassy to the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16072","16072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428147","2015-11-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what advice and information his Department has distributed to UK nationals in Sharm el-Sheikh, Egypt since 28 October 2015 on staying in that resort; and if he will place copies of such documents in the Library.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16094","16094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428148","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was allocated to fund influenza vaccinations for clinical staff in the independent and voluntary sector in 2014-15; and how much of that funding was spent on (a) residential, (b) domiciliary and (c) other community care services.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16099","16099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428150","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the circumstances in which patients over a particular age can be automatically marked as Do Not Resuscitate; and whether medical staff must follow a particular procedure to check with elderly patients upon admission to hospital or their relatives whether they wish to be resuscitated.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16241","16241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428151","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will carry out an assessment after the November Spending Review of local authorities' capacity to meet their new duties under the Care Act 2014 following changes to local authority funding.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16245","16245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428152","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to monitor the number of local authorities charging carers for the support they receive to help them in their caring role.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16238","16238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428153","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding the Government plans to provide for research on diffuse intrinsic pontine glioma brain tumours.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16225","16225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428154","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy on charging carers for the support they receive in their caring role of an increase in the number of councils charging carers.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16237","16237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428155","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what decision his Department has made on the use of the £6 billion of funding allocated for the implementation of phase 2 of the Care Act 2014 now that the implementation of that phase has been postponed.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16246","16246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428156","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will create a database for local authorities on best practice in meeting their new duties under the Care Act 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16247","16247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428157","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimates his Department have made of the proportion of the total number of influenza vaccinations administered by private providers in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16281","16281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428158","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how cancer indicators for clinical commissioning groups ratings will be established and employed.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16261","16261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428159","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting times for therapeutic services through referral pathways was for sexual assault referral centres which do not directly provide therapeutic services for children under 18 in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16273","16273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428160","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what care pathways are in place at each sexual assault referral centre; and what the average waiting time is for access to those pathways for (a) adults and (b) children under 18.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16274","16274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428161","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have received the influenza vaccination at (a) a hospital, (b) a GP surgery, (c) a pharmacy, (d) a supermarket and (e) another facility in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16279","16279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428162","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time taken that children who have experienced abuse wait to receive support from therapeutic services.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16275","16275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428163","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current average waiting time is for therapeutic services at each sexual assault referral centre for (a) adults and (b) children under 18.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16276","16276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428164","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many influenza vaccinations (a) have been and (b) he expects to be administered for this winter.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16280","16280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428165","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many one-stop shops of medical experts for the assessment of children with disabilities are in place; and where those one-stop shops are located.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16264","16264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428166","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GP appointments and A&E visits each year for self-treatable conditions which could have been treated at home or with advice from a pharmacist; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16254","16254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428167","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what system of accountability NHS England will establish for clinical commissioning groups' work on improving one year cancer survival rates from June 2016.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16202","16202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428168","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in what way his Department will hold clinical commissioning groups responsible for making improvements along the cancer pathway including (a) early diagnosis and (b) supporting people beyond treatment.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16201","16201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428169","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure early access for the immuno-oncology treatment nivolumab for both lung cancer and melanoma.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16191","16191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428170","2015-11-18","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue a response to Early Day Motion (a) 162, Closures of abortion clinics and (b) 172, Buffer zones around abortion centres.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16218","16218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428171","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of delayed discharges from NHS hospitals due to the absence of community social care provision by local authorities in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16207","16207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428172","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that any new system of appraisal for cancer medicines will include in its remit appraisal for drugs which treat conditions with small patient populations.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16188","16188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428173","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential future effect of immuno-oncology treatments and funding of such treatments through the NHS budget.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16189","16189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428174","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential for immune-oncology treatments to treat mesothelioma effectively.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16190","16190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428175","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce variations in the quality of at-home care given by carers' agencies across the UK.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16177","16177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428176","2015-11-17","Department of Health","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure to new medicines on the Cancer Drugs Fund list on patients with chronic myeloid leukaemia.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16187","16187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428178","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the most recent national security direction under section 94 of the Telecommunications Act 1984 was made; and what the number of UK citizens was from whom data was collected under that direction.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16310","16310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428179","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times action has been taken against a service provider for non-compliance with a warrant served under the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 since 2001.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16311","16311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428180","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has provided the Intelligence and Security Committee with copies of any national security directions made under section 94 of the Telecommunications Act 1984.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16312","16312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428181","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has paid out any financial compensation on national security directions made under sections 94 of the Telecommunications Act 1984 in the last 30 years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16313","16313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428182","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, by what process her Department identified the areas of policy within its responsibility proposed for reservation in Annex B of the publication Powers for a Purpose: Towards a lasting devolution settlement for Wales, published on 27 February 2015.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16150","16150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428183","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons the matters within her Department's responsibility in Schedule 1 of the draft Wales Bill have been designated as reserved.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16145","16145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428184","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times she has (a) met and (b) corresponded with a minister of the Welsh Government on the draft Wales Bill in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16146","16146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428185","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Tier 4 visas have been issued to students entering the UK to study English as a foreign language as their principal area of study in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16213","16213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428186","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to renew funding of the National Wildlife Crime Unit after March 2016.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16200","16200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428187","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse of provision of (a) accommodation and (b) support services for asylum seekers was in Gloucestershire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16171","16171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428188","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of crimes committed by people with gambling problems.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16206","16206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428189","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many suspicious activity reports relating to (a) the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 and (b) the Terrorism Act 2000 have been submitted to the National Crime Agency in the last financial year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16286","16286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428190","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many investigations have been commenced by the National Crime Agency into human trafficking, in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16287","16287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428191","2015-11-18","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of online child abuse were referred from the National Crime Agency to individual police forces in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16288","16288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428192","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much she expects to be top-sliced from the (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17 police grant; and from what areas that funding will be top-sliced.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16232","16232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428193","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures her Department has established to safeguard 16 and 17 year olds who are victims of sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16240","16240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428194","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the evidential basis which shows that cannabis is harmful, cited in the Government response to the epetition, We demand the British Government reschedule cannabis.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16250","16250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428196","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many decisions on further submissions related to asylum claims that are outstanding have been waiting for longer than (a) one year, (b) two years and (c) three years for a decision.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16091","16091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428197","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's current service standard is for the time taken to process further submissions related to an asylum claim.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16090","16090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428198","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of private hire vehicles illegally plying for hire.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16087","16087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428199","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on introducing a statutory definition of plying for hire in the taxi and private hire vehicle industry.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16088","16088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428200","2015-11-17","Home Office","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many private hire vehicle drivers have been arrested in (a) London and (b) the UK for offences related to plying for hire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16086","16086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428201","2015-11-17","Department for International Development","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of protests at border crossings between Nepal and India on the supply of (a) fuel, (b) medicine and (c) blood to Nepal.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16082","16082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428202","2015-11-17","Department for International Development","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to improve the reliability and collection of data on nutrition in countries in Asia and Africa.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16107","16107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428203","2015-11-17","Department for International Development","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the Syrian people in establishing a framework for post-conflict reconstruction.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16290","16290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428204","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations his Department has received on manorial rights in Cumbria in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16259","16259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428205","2015-11-18","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to abolish the feudal system of land tenure in England and Wales.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16258","16258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428206","2015-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times he has (a) met and (b) corresponded with a minister of the Welsh Government on the draft Wales Bill in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16149","16149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428207","2015-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what number of cases is handled by the National Probation Service in (a) each region of England and (b) each month in each such region.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16117","16117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428208","2015-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what process his Department identified the areas of policy within its responsibility proposed for reservation in Annex B of the publication Powers for a Purpose: Towards a lasting devolution settlement for Wales, published on 27 February 2015.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16151","16151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428209","2015-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release, Prison building revolution announced by Chancellor and Justice Secretary, published on 9 November 2015, whether the Government plans to consult on proposals to sell prison estates to property developers.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16109","16109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428210","2015-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release, Prison building revolution announced by Chancellor and Justice Secretary, published on 9 November 2015, what discussions he has had with prison and probation staff on the planned closure of prisons in central London.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16110","16110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428211","2015-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release, Prison building revolution announced by Chancellor and Justice Secretary, published on 9 November 2015, what plans he has for relocating prison populations in prisons in central London that are planned for closure.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16111","16111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428212","2015-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release, Prison building revolution announced by Chancellor and Justice Secretary, published on 9 November 2015, which prisons the Government plans to sell to property developers; and what estimate he has made of the value of land on each of those sites.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16112","16112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428213","2015-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many probation officers have been employed by the National Probation Service since its establishment in each month in that period, and for each such month in each region of England.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16114","16114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428214","2015-11-17","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons the matters within his Department's responsibility in Schedule 1 of the draft Wales Bill have been designated as reserved.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16142","16142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428215","2015-11-17","Prime Minister","2015-11-13","To ask the Prime Minister, on what date he wrote to the Commander of the at-sea Trident nuclear submarine giving guidance on the use of Trident ballistic missiles after he assumed the office of Prime Minister in 2010; and on what date he sent a message superseding the message given to the at-sea Commander of Trident by Gordon Brown while he was Prime Minister.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16251","16251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428216","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure consistent and comprehensive communications by tour companies and airlines with UK nationals in Sharm el-Sheikh, Egypt.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16092","16092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428217","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November to Question 13665, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the proposal from High Speed UK on high speed rail.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16073","16073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428218","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2015 to Question 5604, when he expects to provide a full response to the Law Commission's report on a statutory definition of plying for hire for the taxi and private hire industry.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16089","16089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428219","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total number of passengers travelling independently through flight-only sales or independent bookings that have been affected by recent restrictions on UK-bound flights from Sharm el-Sheikh airport; and what steps the Government has taken to support those passengers.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16096","16096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428220","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the increase in (a) traffic and (b) HGV traffic on the A303 at Chicklade in each year to 2030.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16235","16235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428221","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with HM Treasury on the removal of the fuel duty escalator for liquefied petroleum gas as part of government proposals to reduce emissions from road transport.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16249","16249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428222","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the expected cost of dualling the A303 from Wylye to Mere.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16234","16234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428223","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the expected level of increased traffic (a) noise, (b) pollution in Chicklade as a result of the dualling of the A303 at Stonehenge.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16233","16233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428224","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to improve access to buses for blind and partially-sighted people.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16194","16194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428225","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the value of economic output lost as a result of industrial action in the transport sector in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16180","16180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428226","2015-11-18","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the time the DVLA takes to process reapplications for a driving license after a suspension of that license for medical reasons.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16314","16314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428227","2015-11-17","Department for Transport","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 15131, what discussions the Government has had with Heathrow Airport on the mitigation measures proposed for Heathrow expansion in the Airport Commission's final report; what information the Government has received from Heathrow Airport in response to those discussions; and what account the Government will take of the response from Heathrow Airport in reaching a final decision.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16307","16307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428228","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to extend occupational pensions to include widows from same sex married couples in the same way as widows from other married couples are currently included.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16179","16179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428229","2015-11-18","Women and Equalities","2015-11-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with civil society organisations on the findings of the research study into pregnancy and maternity discrimination in the workplace, Pregnancy and Maternity-Related Discrimination and Disadvantage - First Findings: Surveys of Employers and Mothers, published by the Equality and Human Rights Commission in partnership with the Department for Business, Innovations and Skills on 24 July 2015.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16159","16159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428230","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) what the total value of payments is and (b) how many payments have been made from the Flexible Support Fund to assist with childcare costs in (i) each region and (ii) each constituency in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16115","16115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428231","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants claimed support for childcare costs in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16205","16205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428232","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department will provide a definition of the term vulnerable group for the purposes of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill; and with whom his Department will consult on that definition.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16181","16181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428233","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by what process his Department identified the areas of policy within its responsibility proposed for reservation in Annex B of the publication Powers for a Purpose: Towards a lasting devolution settlement for Wales, published on 27 February 2015.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16153","16153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428234","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the matters within his Department's responsibility in Schedule 1 of the draft Wales Bill have been designated as reserved.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16144","16144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428235","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training has been given to Jobcentre Plus staff on the application of benefit sanctions in circumstances where a parent is unable to comply with conditions for benefit because of lack of suitable childcare.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16116","16116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428236","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times he has (a) met and (b) corresponded with a minister of the Welsh Government on the draft Wales Bill in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16147","16147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428237","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which of his Department's projects have received funding under the  European Social Fund 2007 to 2013; what the location is of each such project; and how much each such project received.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16268","16268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428238","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what procedures his Department follows when a jobcentre client requests a food bank voucher for the fourth time in any given year.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16265","16265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428239","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what procedure his Department follows in investigating cases of discrepancies between statements in disability benefit claimant questionnaires and assessor reports.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16266","16266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428240","2015-11-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether all types of credit union account are eligible for the receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16282","16282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428241","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's current targets are for processing benefit payments.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16239","16239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428242","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-compliant cases the Child Support Agency has closed under its 1993 and 2003 statutory schemes' closing process.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16300","16300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428243","2015-11-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of outstanding cases handled by the Child Support Agency were classed as non-compliant before the implementation of the 1993 and 2003 statutory schemes' closure process.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16301","16301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427434","2015-11-16","Attorney General","2015-11-10","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2015 to Question 12365, what savings have resulted from the police-led prosecution initiative in each year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15710","15710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427436","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to maintain the current level of skills funding for 16 to 18 year olds up to May 2020.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15729","15729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427438","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the contribution international students studying in the UK make to British soft power overseas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15732","15732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427458","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what level of spending will be required from (a) the Government, (b) other public sector bodies and (c) private employers to create three million quality apprenticeships by 2020.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15786","15786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427460","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the Government spent on each infrastructure project in Easington constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15769","15769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427462","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing three-year funding plans for further education colleges.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15809","15809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427464","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to publish the report of the Cutting Red Tape programme.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15840","15840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427466","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what account was taken of the results of the 2011 Workplace Employment Relations Survey on workplace union representatives in the healthcare sector in bringing forward proposals to cap union facility time in the Trade Union Bill.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15794","15794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427468","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of whether the UK  has enough qualified IT specialists to meet the IT requirements of businesses in the UK.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15945","15945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427471","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department plans to include measures as part of the National Action Plan on Business and Human Rights to promote ethical practices of UK businesses operating abroad.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15924","15924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427473","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what restrictions are in place to monitor mobile pubs on bicycles.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15962","15962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427475","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many full-time equivalent UKTI staff in his Department were based in (a) India and (b) Gujarat in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16042","16042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427477","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department made of the financial viability of the Redcar coke ovens and blast furnace as a standalone operation without South Bank coke ovens.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16043","16043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427480","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from further education colleges on withdrawal of ESOL Plus Mandation Funding.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15989","15989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427482","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish a Digital Transformation Plan.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15944","15944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427484","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what impact assessment his Department has conducted on withdrawal of ESOL Plus Mandation funding and its effects on further education colleges in (a) Greater London and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15990","15990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427486","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when post-16 education in Warrington is planned to be reviewed under the area review process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15997","15997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427488","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on the ability of the Office for Nuclear Regulation to carry out its safety and security regulatory functions in full of the guidance set out in the Legislative and Regulatory Reform (Regulatory Functions) (Amendment) Order 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16001","16001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427490","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what targets he has set for the creation of numbers of apprenticeships between now and 2020.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16053","16053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427492","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value of trade was between the UK and Israel in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15858","15858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427494","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the number of people who would be worse off financially if the threshold for student loan repayments were not index-linked in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b )Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16060","16060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427496","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what change there has been in the number of part-time higher education students in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15877","15877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427498","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the level of awareness among potential students of the availability in England of loans for part-time higher education study.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15878","15878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427500","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has to ensure that GOV.UK is accessible by Welsh speakers in the Welsh language.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16059","16059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427502","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to tackle cyber attacks originating in Russia and China.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15963","15963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427505","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when his Department introduced the Welsh Language Scheme; when that scheme was last updated; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of that scheme.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15926","15926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427507","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of student loan outlay that will never be repaid by graduates (a) undertaking full-time higher education and (b) undertaking part-time higher education.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15959","15959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427516","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the funding offer for the Pioneer Communities Project was withdrawn; and what the basis was for the withdrawal.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15763","15763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427517","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions took place between his Department and the Department for Education about the allocation of funds to the Pioneer Communities Project.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15764","15764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427518","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit claimants in Salford have been in continuous receipt of tax credits for (a) one, (b) two, (c) three and (d) four or more years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15719","15719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427519","2015-11-18","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average duration of a claim for tax credits was in Salford in the most recent (a) 12 and (b) 24 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15720","15720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427520","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on recipients of the expiry of the Business Rates Reoccupation Relief scheme at the end of March 2016.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15716","15716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427521","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on recipients of the expiry of the Small Business Rate Relief scheme at the end of March 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15717","15717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427522","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to improve trade relations with Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15702","15702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427523","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure that uncertainty about the outcome of the EU referendum does not affect inward investment in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15705","15705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427524","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of small firms likely to be affected by the expiry of the Small Business Rate Relief scheme at the end of March 2016.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15707","15707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427525","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government plans to take in response to the Sixth Report of the Public Accounts Committee, HM Revenue and Customs performance in 2014-15, HC 393.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15953","15953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427526","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the staff budget for HM Revenue and Customs was in each year since 1997-98.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15954","15954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427527","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the budget was for staff answering calls to tax offices in each year since 2007-08.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15955","15955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427528","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of fiscal support for the offshore oil and gas sector on (a) employment and (b) pay rates in that sector since 2010-11.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15797","15797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427529","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to support international efforts to improve tax transparency and accountability.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15968","15968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427530","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the number of people who will become higher rate taxpayers as a result of the provisions of Clause 24 of the Finance Bill 2015 (restriction to Landlords' interest deductibility) in each year between 2017-18 and 2020-21.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15898","15898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427531","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the annual additional taxation receipts arising from restrictions to Landlords' interest deductibility from inception of Clause 24 of the Finance Bill 2015 in April 2017 through to its full effects coming into force in 2020-21.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15897","15897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427532","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the number of people who will be subject to personal allowance restriction on incomes over £100,000 as a result of Clause 24 of the Finance Bill 2015 (restriction to Landlords' interest deductibility) in each year between 2017-18 and 2020-21.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15899","15899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427533","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects to make a decision on City Deals for (a) Edinburgh, (b) Aberdeen and (c) Inverness.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15900","15900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427534","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, in cases where a person has registered a donation to a charity for gift aid but ended the year below the income threshold for income tax, whether it is the policy of HM Revenue and Customs to reclaim the gift aid from the (a) donor or (b) charity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15811","15811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427535","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much gift aid has been (a) requested and (b) reclaimed from (i) donors and (ii) charities in circumstances in which people making registered charitable donations for gift aid ended the year below the income tax threshold in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15812","15812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427536","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the number of people that will be subject to the provisions of the High Income Child Benefit Tax Charge as a result of Clause 24 of the Finance Bill 2015 (restriction to Landlords' interest deductibility) in each year between 2017-18 and 2020-21.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15895","15895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427537","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many decommissioning relief deeds relating to decommissioning activity in the UK Continental Shelf have been signed to date; and what the total value of such deeds is to the (a) public purse and (b) decommissioning industry.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15803","15803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427538","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which companies have signed decommissioning relief deeds with his Department.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15802","15802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427539","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what process the Treasury determines whether an item of public spending should trigger a consequential payment to the devolved administrations under the Barnett formula.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15788","15788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427540","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department agreed a grant to the Wave Trust to fund the Pioneer Communities Project; and how much that grant was for.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15761","15761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427541","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria were attached to the granting of a grant to the Wave Trust to fund the Pioneer Communities Project.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15762","15762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427542","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of (a) the number of people in receipt of the carer's credit and (b) the total cost of the carer's credit scheme in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15934","15934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427543","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) complaints and (b) investigations into complaints made by civil servants against special advisers in his Department (i) have been made in each of the last five years and (ii) are currently ongoing.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15935","15935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427544","2015-11-16","HM Treasury","2015-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what Support for Mortgage Relief provisions are available to customers of Northern Rock Asset Management.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15843","15843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427545","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people from (a) other EU countries and (b) non-EU countries who were deemed homeless have been returned to their home countries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15937","15937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427546","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many hostel places for the homeless there were in (a) London and (b) each London borough on 1 October in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15938","15938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427547","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much was spent on returning people from (a) other countries and (b) non-EU countries who were deemed homeless to their home countries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15936","15936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427548","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many planning applications for the erection of telephone masts have been rejected by local authorities in (a) the UK, (b) Cheshire and (c) Eddisbury constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15875","15875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427549","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of codes of conduct protecting officers of local authorities from bullying and intimidation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15879","15879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427550","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to reduce barriers to officers of local authorities reporting bullying and intimidation by those in senior positions within their local authority.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15880","15880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427551","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authority staff report bullying and intimidation each year.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15881","15881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427552","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the document, Fixing the Foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, Cm 9098, when he will intervene in local authorities that do not produce local plans.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16038","16038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427553","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many 16 and 17 year olds presented as homeless to (a) Ashfield District Council and (b) Broxtowe Borough Council in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15784","15784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427554","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many children have been registered as homeless in (a) Ashfield and (b) Broxtowe in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15781","15781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427555","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what powers are available to local authorities to restrict the use of fireworks.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15782","15782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427556","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many complaints about (a) natural gas or (b) inadequate safeguards to detect natural gas have been lodged with councils in the last year.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15771","15771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427557","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people who are at high risk from carbon monoxide poisoning.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15772","15772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427558","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made by the Ministerial Working Group on Preventing and Tackling Homelessness.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15838","15838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427559","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the building of bungalows and other homes accessible to people with limited mobility.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15795","15795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427560","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the risks of carbon monoxide poisoning.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15903","15903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427561","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the rate of suicide among members of the fire service; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce such numbers.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15952","15952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427562","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the level of financial reserves of local authorities.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15709","15709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427563","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the time taken to (a) implement broadband roll-out and (b) tackle non-spots on people and businesses in (i) St Helens North constituency, (ii) Merseyside and (iii) the UK.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15706","15706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427564","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of his Department's expected DEL underspend in 2015-16; what his Department's current forecast for AME expenditure is in 2015-16; and what that forecast was at the time of the (a) Summer Budget 2015 and (b) March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15785","15785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427565","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of his Department's expected DEL underspend in 2015-16; what his Department's current forecast for AME expenditure is in 2015-16; and what that forecast was at the time of the (a) Summer Budget 2015 and (b) March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15779","15779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427566","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to increase the accessibility of defibrillators for sports clubs.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15886","15886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427567","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made reforming the Electronic Communications Code.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15874","15874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427568","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of homes and businesses that will not benefit from the roll-out of superfast broadband in each of the 11 Cheshire parliamentary constituencies.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15873","15873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427569","2015-11-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to implement the family test; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15847","15847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427570","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 14296, where in Europe Tata Steel is licensed and has an exclusive right to manufacture Super Bainite Steel; from which countries Tata may not export Super Bainite steel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15941","15941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427571","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether General Sir Nicholas Houghton sought permission under departmental directive 2014DIN03-024 on Contact with the media and communicating in public to discuss the Trident nuclear weapons system in advance of the recent television interview on the Andrew Marr on Sunday programme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15998","15998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427572","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value of weapons owned by his Department was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15991","15991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427573","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the reliability of the power and propulsion systems of the Type 45 Destroyer.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15927","15927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427574","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to ensure the full participation of the Northern Ireland Executive and people in memorialising UK servicemen and civilians who have died in conflict.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15857","15857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427575","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether there has been any recent change to the guidance given to senior personnel in the armed forces on the public comments on political matters which they may make.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16054","16054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427576","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel from 13 and 39 Squadron have not taken their full entitlement to annual leave over the last two years.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15892","15892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427577","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Typhoon aircraft are unable to fly because parts of them have been removed for use in other aircraft.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15767","15767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427578","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the prevalence of (a) the indicators of mental disorders including stress, depression, fatigue and post traumatic stress disorder and (b) the provision of support by service providers or others to personnel in 13 and 39 Squadrons.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15894","15894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427579","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many referrals for treatment for post traumatic stress disorder from 13 and 39 Squadron service personnel there have been over the last two years.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15893","15893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427580","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to provide additional support for ex-servicemen and women and their families.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15830","15830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427581","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues about providing more comprehensive support for ex-servicemen and women and their families.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15831","15831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427582","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to table a new statutory instrument relating to the Veterans Advisory and Pensions Committees and to change their title to reflect their new role.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15947","15947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427583","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many L86A1-SA-80 light support weapons have been returned from the Middlesex North West London Army cadet force to his Department's Donnington barracks since 2003.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15703","15703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427584","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has been provided with a copy of the US President's Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board report of 15 February 1990, entitled The Soviet 'War Scare', by the US administration.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15747","15747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427585","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place in the Library a copy of the 1984 Joint Intelligence Committee paper JIC(84)(N)45, entitled Soviet Union: concern about a surprise NATO attack.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15748","15748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427586","2015-11-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the expected cost of HMS Artful was when it was commissioned.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15753","15753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427587","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve the skills of and training for school staff working with autistic children.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15737","15737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427588","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of establishing a national pay scale for teaching assistants.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15738","15738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427589","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what impact assessment her Department (a) has carried out or (b) plans to carry out on the effects that changes to National Insurance and occupational pension scheme contributions will have on special educational needs schools budgets.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15905","15905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427590","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations she has received from heads of special educational needs schools on the increase in costs from national insurance and pension scheme contributions.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15906","15906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427591","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will provide more funding to special educational needs schools in (a) Greater London and (b) Enfield.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15907","15907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427592","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment her Department has made of the merits of providing additional funding to schools to offset the cost of (a) National Insurance and (b) occupational pension scheme contributions.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15908","15908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427593","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many parents in Ashfield have been fined for a child's unauthorised absence from school in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15780","15780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427594","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what involvement her Department has had in the grant originally made available to the Pioneer Communities Project that was administered through her Department.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15787","15787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427595","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of resources available to (a) primary and (b) secondary school children requiring educational psychology services in each of the next five years; and how much such support will be made available during each of the next five years.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15890","15890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427596","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the ease of access of play opportunities for children with disabilities and complex needs.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15995","15995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427597","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average length of time was for the process of fostering a child in each constituent part and county of the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15862","15862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427598","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to expedite the process for fostering a child.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15861","15861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427599","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to tackle racism in secondary schools.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15889","15889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427600","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the breadth of physical activity opportunities beyond sport available to children (a) in and (b) out of school.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15976","15976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427601","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will assess the effect on the ability of the Office for Nuclear Regulations to carry out its functions of the provisions of the Regulators' Code requiring regulatory agencies to consider how they might support or enable economic growth for compliant businesses they regulate.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15833","15833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427602","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what provisions she plans to make for onshore wind projects that have achieved everything technically, been granted planning permission, and have grid connection contract but are outside the grace period and are contracts for difference (CFD); and whether she plans a CFD for those projects.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15837","15837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427603","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she plans to (a) launch a public consultation on her Strategy to Maximise Economic Recovery of North Sea oil and gas reserves, and (b) lay the final version of that strategy before Parliament.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15796","15796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427604","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the change in the number of jobs in the solar sector that will be lost as a result of the Government changes to the feed-in tariff in (a) Barnsley East, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15950","15950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427605","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure homes are adequately heated over the winter and protect against deaths due to the cold weather.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15923","15923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427606","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department has taken to assess the impact of hydraulic fracturing in (a) national parks and (b) other environmentally sensitive areas.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15971","15971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427607","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13044, what assessment she has made of reasons for the delays in constructing reactors in China as requested in that question.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15972","15972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427608","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to prevent shale gas drilling at the surface in areas of the greatest environmental value.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15722","15722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427609","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with European counterparts on progress they have made in tackling the waste of imperfect food.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15698","15698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427610","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the economic effect of the England Coast Path on each area through which opened sections of that path pass.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15736","15736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427611","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with supermarkets on reducing the amount of food that is wasted because it is not considered aesthetically appealing to customers.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15759","15759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427612","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) her Department and (b) each of its arm's length bodies has spent on staff redundancies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15760","15760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427613","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what cost was incurred by her Department as a result of the withdrawal of the CAP-D programme in March 2015.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15726","15726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427614","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evidence her Department has received on the potential effect on the sport of shooting that would result from the phase out of the use of lead ammunition for sport shooting in England.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16008","16008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427615","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings her Department has had to ascertain whether birds of prey predate on other birds of prey in order to inform her policies on bird conservation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15965","15965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427616","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the animal welfare benefits of the proper use of non-toxic alternatives to lead ammunition for sports shooting; and what comparative assessment she has made of the policies adopted in other countries and their effect on animal welfare.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16007","16007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427617","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the recent figures on household food waste published by the Waste and Resources Action Programme; and what steps her Department is taking to reduce domestic food waste.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16046","16046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427618","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions the Government with the EU on charges for quarry spaces and pest control.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15964","15964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427619","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 14616, what estimate her Department has made of the number of signatories to the (a) Cortauld Commitment 3, (b) Electrical and Electronic Equipment Sustainability Action Plan, (c) Hospitality and Food Service Agreement and (d) Sustainable Clothing Action Plan in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16039","16039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427620","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evidence her Department has received on the welfare effect of lead ammunition in sports shooting and hunting.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16006","16006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427621","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the need for increased quarrying capacity to meet the stone demand for new house building.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15913","15913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427622","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will estimate the number of households affected by food insecurity in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) South Yorkshire and (d) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15956","15956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427623","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on implementing those aspects of the Floods and Water Management Act 2010 applicable to smaller reservoirs.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15790","15790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427624","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to take further steps to implement those aspects of the Floods and Water Management Act 2010 applicable to smaller reservoirs.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15791","15791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427625","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that non-target species such as domestic pets are not caught in snares.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15836","15836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427626","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether snares are used to trap animals on land owned by her Department; and what records her Department keeps of animals caught in such snares.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15832","15832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427627","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to encourage Chinese investors to invest in the UK dairy industry.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15770","15770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427628","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions her Department has had with the British Veterinary Association on the control of bovine TB.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15789","15789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427629","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the target date is for completion of the England Coast Path.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15800","15800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427630","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that snare operators are (a) aware of and (b) complying with the Code of Good Practice on the Use of Snares, published in 2005.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15839","15839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427631","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of partial restrictions on the use of lead ammunition for reducing the incidence of lead poisoning; and what comparative assessment she has made of the effectiveness of that policy and those in place in other jurisdictions.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15974","15974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427632","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to inform consumers about the lead content of game meat shot with lead ammunition.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15975","15975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427633","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much game meat has entered the human food chain from licensed hunting activities on land owned by Government Departments or agencies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15977","15977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427634","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on the use of lead ammunition on land owned by the Government.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15978","15978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427635","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average household bill for water was in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in (i) 2010 and (ii) 2015.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16048","16048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427636","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what preparations her Department is making to support the agricultural economy in the Northern Ireland in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15824","15824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427637","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evidence her Department has recently received about wildlife mortality caused by lead poisoning resulting from the use of lead ammunition in sports shooting.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15979","15979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427638","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the report by the National Audit Office, The economic regulation of the water sector, HC487; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure that customers benefit from water companies' unexpected financial gains.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16047","16047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427639","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of levels of compliance with the Environmental Protection (Restriction of the Use of Lead Shot) (England) Regulations 1999 (as amended).","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15980","15980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427640","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a ban on snares.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15826","15826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427641","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the level of deposition of lead gunshot in wetland and terrestrial habitats.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15981","15981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427642","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what study her Department has made of the experience of other countries in reducing lead poisoning through regulation of the use of lead ammunition and the use of non-toxic alternatives.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15982","15982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427643","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to respond to the final report of the Lead Ammunition Group.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15983","15983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427644","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she received the final report of the Lead Ammunition Group; and what discussions she has had with the Chair and other members of that Group since that date.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15985","15985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427645","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish a cost to benefit analysis of the badger cull.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16049","16049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427646","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the relative costs and effectiveness of alternatives to lead ammunition for sports shooting.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15986","15986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427647","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Government has spent in England on (a) cattle testing for TB, (b) compensation as a result of a test for bovine TB, (c) surveillance activity associated with bovine TB by the Veterinary Laboratories Agency and Animal Plant Health Agency, (d) Tuberculin supply and (e) research connected to bovine TB in each year since 2010-11; and what the total expenditure was on measures to prevent bovine TB in each such year.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16050","16050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427648","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent on measures to improve air quality in each year since 2010-11; how much funding has been allocated to air quality improvement in the 2015-16 financial year; and what estimate she has made of the funding needed until 2020 to bring air pollution levels to within legal limits.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16051","16051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427649","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the sale of UK produce to new global markets.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16002","16002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427650","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce public exposure to lead in the food chain.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15988","15988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427651","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish a financial assessment and analysis of the effectiveness of badger culling in the first three quarters of 2015.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15888","15888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427652","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the change in the bee population over the summer of 2015.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15859","15859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427653","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to Resolution 11.15 adopted by the Eleventh Conference if the Parties to the Convention on the Conservation of Migratory Species of Wild Animals in November 2014, what assessment she has made of the extent and type of poisoning risk from lead ammunition in the UK.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16061","16061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427654","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding has been (a) allocated and (b) spent as part the Illegal Wildlife Trade Challenge Fund to date.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16063","16063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427655","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how her Department plans to implement the Guidelines to Prevent the Risk of Poisoning to Migratory Birds adopted by the Eleventh Conference if the Parties to the Convention on the Conservation of Migratory Species of Wild Animals in November 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16062","16062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427656","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons the Rural Payments Agency was not able to make advance basic payments from 16 October 2015.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15883","15883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427657","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what role the National Wildlife Crime Unit will play as part of the UK's commitment to Action on the Illegal Wildlife Trade from March 2016.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16064","16064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427658","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many CITES prosecutions have been brought in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16065","16065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427659","2015-11-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in which towns and cities the Government intends to create pocket parks; and what the estimated cost will be to (a) his Department and (b) the Government of this programme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16029","16029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427660","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to reducing light pollution in the next five financial years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16030","16030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427661","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the cost of maintaining flood defences in each year of this Parliament.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16031","16031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427662","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent on flood defences in Dartford in the last 12 months; and what such spending is planned in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16033","16033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427663","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with (a) the property and mortgage industries and (b) local authorities on the effect of Japanese knotweed on property values.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16032","16032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427664","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has plans to encourage the planting of trees to enhance the visual amenity of farmland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15860","15860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427665","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the area of land occupied by solar panel arrays that was previously arable land usable for economically farmed fruits or vegetables.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15882","15882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427666","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation for religious minorities in Burma.","Biography information for John McNally","John Mc Nally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16034","16034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427667","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to assist African governments in reversing the number of animals thought to be at risk of extinction.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16055","16055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427668","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to support the Russian government since the crash of Airbus 321 in Egypt.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15887","15887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427669","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he or his Ministers have had with their Egyptian counterparts on (a) the reconstruction and repair of churches and other Christian property and (b) the granting of licences for new churches in Egypt.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15865","15865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427670","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the UK's contribution to the EU Strategy on Citizen Security in Central America and the Caribbean is for 2014-15.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15773","15773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427671","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of Equitorial Guinea on human rights and freedom of speech in that country.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15774","15774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427672","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to raise the security, humanitarian access, freedom of movement and citizenship rights of ethnic groups with the Burmese government.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15804","15804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427673","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Development on contributing to the European Commission's North Africa Trust Fund.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15912","15912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427674","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many full-time equivalent consular staff were based in (a) India and (b) Gujarat in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16041","16041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427675","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the conflict in Central African Republic.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15967","15967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427676","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise the issue of minority rights during the visit of Prime Minister Modi of India; and if he will specifically raise (a) Sikh political prisoners in India and (b) the case of Bapu Surat Singh Khalsa.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15966","15966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427677","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department plans to take to facilitate a transition in Burma from dictatorship to democracy.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15731","15731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427678","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent people migrating illegally from Haiti to the Turks & Caicos islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15733","15733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427679","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to use the upcoming Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting to prioritise the strengthening of diplomatic and economic ties with Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15734","15734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427680","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of steps taken by (a) his Department and (b) the Burmese government to stop the use of child soldiers in that country.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15743","15743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427681","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the freedom of elections in Burma in November 2015 and the fairness of the outcome of that election as reflected in the distribution of seats in that country's parliament.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15739","15739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427682","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of steps taken by (a) his Department and (b) the Burmese government to prevent sexual violence in conflict in Burma.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15742","15742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427683","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of (a) disqualifications of parliamentary candidates, (b) disenfranchisement of ethnic groups and (c) inaccuracy and omissions from the voter lists in elections in Burma in November 2015.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15740","15740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427684","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department has provided to the EU election observation mission overseeing elections in Burma in November 2015.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15745","15745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427685","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to meet the new President of Burma; and if he will raise the issue of human rights abuses of ethnic groups in that country with the President.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15741","15741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427686","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will provide a list of diplomats at Minister-Counsellor rank serving in the Qatar embassy to the United Kingdom (a) currently and (b) for each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15765","15765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427687","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Bangladesh on the murder of Faisal Arefin Dipon.","Biography information for John McNally","John Mc Nally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15778","15778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427688","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of Russian airstrikes on (a) ISIL/Daesh targets on (b) non-ISIL/Daesh targets in Syria to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15711","15711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427689","2015-11-16","Cabinet Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what data is collected on the number of people who have primary breast cancer twice.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15723","15723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427690","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his officials have had with the MBC Project in Boston, USA, on secondary breast cancer research.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15724","15724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427691","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether (a) officials of his Department, (b) representatives of NHS bodies or (c) researchers funded by his Department will be attending the San Antonio Breast Cancer Symposium in November 2015.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15725","15725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427692","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce and prevent incidences of pneumococcal pneumonia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15693","15693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427693","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the effect of the changing criteria for the Adult Dependent Relative Visa on recruitment and retention of health professionals.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15696","15696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427694","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many female inpatient mental health beds there were on (a) Saturday 7 November 2015 and (b) Sunday 8 November 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15708","15708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427695","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information is recorded by the Cancer Registry on secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15754","15754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427696","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information is recorded for primary and secondary breast cancer by the Cancer Registry on (a) diagnosis dates, (b) stage at diagnosis, (c) age and (d) gender of person at diagnosis.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15755","15755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427697","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to improve cancer outcomes for men.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15758","15758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427698","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of support services available to carers and parents when a child is diagnosed with autism.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15735","15735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427699","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will have age-related macular degeneration by 2050.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15921","15921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427700","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what powers local authorities have to restrict the growth of e-cigarette outlets.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15961","15961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427701","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether assessing eye health is part of GPs' standard patient health assessment.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15922","15922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427702","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time for access to talking therapies is in (a) Warrington and (b) the North West; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16040","16040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427703","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the new junior doctors' contract on patients' safety.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15970","15970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427704","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) healthy adults, (b) pregnant women and (c) children who regularly consume game meat shot with lead.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16011","16011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427705","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what level of lead consumption his Department has defined as safe; and what evidence his Department has received on the mean level of lead in (a) game meat and (b) game meat shot with lead ammunition.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16009","16009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427706","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the safe level of consumption of game killed with lead ammunition for (a) healthy adults, (b) pregnant women and (c) children.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16010","16010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427707","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of Public Health England's report, Sugar reduction: the evidence for action, published in October 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15960","15960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427708","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spends on treating age-related macular degeneration each year.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15918","15918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427709","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of medical research spending is directed toward eye disease.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15919","15919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427710","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the likely annual cost to the NHS of treating age-related macular degeneration by 2050.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15920","15920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427711","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve oral health as part of the childhood obesity strategy.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15909","15909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427712","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve children's oral health in England through (a) diet and (b) other methods.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15910","15910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427713","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that NHS staff can report patient safety incidents quickly and efficiently.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15911","15911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427714","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will encourage participation by NHS organisations and local authorities in Self Care Week.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15949","15949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427715","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2015 to Question 11782, what discussions he has had with the professional regulators regarding the level of mental health training offered as part of the mandatory training course for (a) student doctors, (b) student nurses and (c) midwives.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15842","15842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427716","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has conducted into the likelihood of people who get primary breast cancer twice getting secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15806","15806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427717","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the (a) cost and (b) effectiveness of stem cell transplants and tyrosine kinase inhibitor therapies as treatments for chronic myeloid leukaemia.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15807","15807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427718","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure improved outcomes for patients who undergo stem cell transplantation in the last five years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15768","15768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427719","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the review of national radiotherapy capacity commissioned by NHS England.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15814","15814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427720","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of claims management companies on the number of unmeritorious claims brought forward in clinical negligence cases.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15815","15815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427721","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of introducing a fixed recoverable cost regime in clinical negligence cases on the number of claims brought by claims management companies and litigants in person.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15816","15816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427722","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the costs to his Department associated with unmeritorious claims resulting from changes to a fixed cost recoverable scheme for clinical negligence.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15817","15817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427723","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the propriety of his Department overseeing the consultation on a fixed recoverable cost regime in clinical negligence cases when it is the defendant in most such cases.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15818","15818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427724","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the incentives for defendants in clinical negligence cases to encourage early admissions and settlements.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15792","15792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427725","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that claimant lawyers can continue to pursue low-value claims in clinical negligence cases in a fixed recoverable cost regime.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15793","15793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427726","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) men and (b) women by (i) age and (ii) incident have been diagnosed with secondary breast cancer in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15756","15756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427727","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the new contract with junior doctors on recruitment in the NHS.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15810","15810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427728","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) amount and (b) proportion of the grants awarded by the National Institute for Health Research have been related to mental health in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15841","15841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427729","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of a seven-day elective service in the NHS on the number of hours worked by NHS staff; and if he will publish any such assessment.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15884","15884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427730","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of a seven-day elective service in the NHS on the number of NHS staff available (a) Monday to Friday and (b) on a weekend; and how he estimates staffing levels will change.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15885","15885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427731","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent research his Department has commissioned or conducted on the health effects of e-cigarettes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15866","15866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427732","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Royal College of Nursing on links between the consumption of carbonated drinks and the incidence of heart failure.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15867","15867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427733","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been prescribed Viagra for medical purposes other than that for which it is usually prescribed in the last three years; and what those other purposes have been.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15870","15870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427734","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Royal College of Nursing on the treatment of prostate cancer by high doses of radiotherapy on the first 20 days of that treatment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15869","15869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427735","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice his Department makes available on the prevention of loss of hearing amongst older people.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15868","15868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427736","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make a comparative assessment of the number of recorded MRSA infections recorded in (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust, (b) Nottingham University Hospitals NHS Trust and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15933","15933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427737","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions bed occupancy rates were (a) 85, (b) 90, (c) 95 and (d) 100 per cent in each hospital trust in Nottinghamshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15932","15932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427738","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the possible effect of reductions in accident and emergency opening hours  on public health and medical treatment standards.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15931","15931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427739","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the effectiveness of arrangements for delivering community health services to patients who reside outside the clinical commissioning group area in which their GP is based.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15929","15929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427740","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients are registered with GPs who are based outside the clinical commissioning group area in which the patient resides.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15930","15930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427741","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each hospital trust has paid consultants in waiting list initiative payments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15854","15854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427742","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average length of clinical time spent on duty each week by a hospital consultant was in 2014-15.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15855","15855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427743","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking with the College of Emergency Medicine to help attract middle-grade and senior doctors to local hospitals.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15852","15852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427744","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include physical activity as a top-tier issue of public health when outlining the annual remit of Public Health England for 2016-17.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15987","15987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427745","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NHS England to publish the first and second quarter figures for Cancer Drugs Fund notifications and individual Cancer Drugs Fund requests for 2015-16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15850","15850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427746","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the National Institute for Health Research.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15940","15940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427747","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2015 to Question 10091, what the implications for his policies are of the decision by NHS England to remove (a) the pancreatic cancer drug Abraxane and (b) 22 other drugs and indications from the Cancer Drugs Fund List.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15851","15851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427748","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to implement the family test; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15848","15848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427749","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current status is of the draft NHS Research and Development Strategy which was consulted on last year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15849","15849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427750","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of a seven-day elective service in the NHS on patient (a) care and (b) safety; and if he will publish any such assessment.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15999","15999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427751","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there are differences in the (a) definition and (b) recording of secondary breast cancer in ICD-10 compared with the Cancer Registry.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15992","15992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427752","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the progress of the Breakthrough Generations study towards secondary breast cancer diagnosis.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15993","15993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427753","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with the Royal Colleges the potential side effects of osteoporosis drugs on (a) jaw and (b) general bone health.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15996","15996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427754","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to fully integrate physical activity into the care pathways of all long-term conditions where it has a proven beneficial effect.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15984","15984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427755","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on the devolution of abortion legislation to the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16069","16069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427756","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with organisations representing women in (a) Scotland, (b) England and (c) Wales on the devolution of abortion legislation to the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16068","16068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427757","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges on the devolution of abortion legislation to the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16067","16067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427758","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 14774, what data his Department holds on the number of voluntary carers in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16045","16045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427759","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that Alzheimer drugs for use at home cost less than £2,100 per year.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16071","16071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427760","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will undertake a review of the causes of stillbirths and neonatal deaths in the UK so as to better understand how maternity practice can be improved.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15872","15872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427761","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16013","16013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427762","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of her Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps she has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16021","16021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427763","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the reduction in the number of English language testing centres on the number of international students entering the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15825","15825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427764","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to implement the family test; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15845","15845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427765","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to respond to the IPCC's proposals on governance reform as set out in its Annual Report and statement of accounts 2014-15, HC 286.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15856","15856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427766","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make available the name, date and description of each counter-terrorism operation in the UK which has resulted in one or more convictions in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15928","15928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427767","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will hold discussions with the government of the Irish Republic on the number of refugees likely to be settled in the Irish Republic who would be eligible to subsequently move to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16056","16056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427768","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with Amnesty International and the Committee Against Torture on recent and proposed changes to the legislation on asylum seekers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15863","15863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427769","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of domestic violence were recorded in each county and constituent part of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15864","15864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427770","2015-11-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of further restrictions on the use and sale of fireworks.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15783","15783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427771","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the wearing of masks at demonstrations in public spaces.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15775","15775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427772","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department has allocated to work on the strategic communications plan for making (a) young and (b) other people aware of the blanket ban on legal highs proposed in the Psychoactive Substances Bill.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15805","15805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427773","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-EU workers hold visas to work on IT projects in the UK.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15946","15946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427774","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many official Royal British Legion Remembrance events have received logistical police support other than wreath laying in a ceremonial capacity in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15957","15957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427775","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy that police officers be assigned to support all Royal British Legion Remembrance parades.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15958","15958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427776","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people attempting to enter the UK without valid papers were detained at UK border controls at Calais and returned to the French authorities in the last 12-month period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15757","15757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427777","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to publish an updated action plan on violence against women and girls.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15728","15728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427778","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when and by what method she informed South Wales Police of the errors in calculating the police funding formula.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15697","15697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427779","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy that the Common Travel Area be maintained in the event that Great Britain and Northern Ireland leave the EU.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15721","15721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427780","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 14380, what (a) number or (b) proportion of referrals under the UNHCR VPR scheme translate into arrivals.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15714","15714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427781","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the average cost to a local authority of taking in a Syrian refugee under the UNHCR VPR scheme in year (a) one, (b) two, (c) three, (d) four and (e) five; and how much additional central government funding has been made to local authorities to help meet those costs per refugee for each of those years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15715","15715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427782","2015-11-16","House of Commons Commission","2015-11-10","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, for what reasons a fire safety contract with Norland Managed Services, London has been awarded outwith the Restoration and Renewal project for the Palace of Westminster.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15695","15695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427783","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's summary of its work in Indonesia 2011-15, published in June 2013, how many hectares of natural forest have been saved since the programme to protect forests in that country started.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15712","15712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/427784","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 9 November 2015 to Question 14770, when she plans to publish the contribution the UK will make to the World Food Programme for 2016.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15713","15713"
