"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844108","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which local authorities are taking part in the postal vote pilots for the local government elections in May 2018; and what specific measures are to be piloted in each such local authority area.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128448","128448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844109","2018-02-21","Department for International Development","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on health outcomes of the time taken to grant exit permits for Palestinians in Gaza seeking medical treatment elsewhere in the Occupied Palestinian Territory or abroad; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128449","128449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844110","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Government of Israel on the approval of permits for Palestinians seeking medical treatment outside Gaza in 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128450","128450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844111","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Government of Israel on WHO reports on the number of Palestinian patients who have died while awaiting permits to travel outside Gaza for medial treatment.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128451","128451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844112","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, hat estimate he has made of the cost to (a) Government and (b) local authorities of filling in potholes in England in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128452","128452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844113","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of filling in potholes in England in 2016.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128453","128453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844114","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to (a) Government and (b) local authorities of filling in potholes in England in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128454","128454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844115","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport,  what estimate he has made of the cost to (a) Government and (b) local authorities of filling in potholes in England in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128455","128455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844116","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of repairing all potholes on public roads.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128456","128456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844117","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an estimate of the cost of damage to cars caused by potholes in England each year.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128457","128457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844118","2018-02-21","Department for International Development","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent estimate she has made of the number of humanitarian and development items that have been delayed in entering or denied entry to Gaza by the Israeli authorities in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128458","128458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844119","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average annual running cost is of a Type 23 frigate.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128459","128459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844120","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average annual running cost is of a Type 45 destroyer.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128460","128460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844121","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether there is a standard service level agreement for contracted-out occupational health services provided on behalf of Her Majesty's Prison and Probation Service.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128461","128461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844122","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the estimated average annual running cost is of a Type 31e frigate.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128462","128462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844123","2018-02-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-02-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will introduce a charge of 25p for disposable cups on the parliamentary estate; what assessment the Commission has made of the potential merits of the recommendations made in the reports of the Environmental Audit Committee on plastic bottles and coffee cups, HC339 and HC 657, published on 22 December 2017 and 5 January 2018 respectively; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128463","128463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844124","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether there was a standard service level agreement for contracted out occupational health services on behalf of HM Prison and Probation Service at the time those services were contracted out to a third party service provider in July 2017.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128464","128464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844125","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he has plans to introduce variations in the standard service level agreement for contracted out services for Her Majesty's Prison and Probation Service Occupational Health service.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128465","128465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844126","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many open cases were transferred to the third party service provider HML when that company's contract started July 2017.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128466","128466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844127","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what date will standard service level agreements for occupational health services for personnel of Her Majesty's Prison and Probation Service come into effect with its third party service provider.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128467","128467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844128","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he will make available additional funding for Sheffield children's services to tackle that local authority's overspend in 2017-2018.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128468","128468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844129","2018-02-22","Department for International Development","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which multilateral projects in the Gaza Strip her Department helps fund; and how much is disbursed from the public purse for each such project.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128469","128469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844130","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress his Department has made on its proposals for leasehold reform for people currently living in leasehold properties.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128470","128470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838918","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, if he will take steps to establish an India-UK social security totalisation agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127480","127480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838919","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the findings of the Financial Services Authority's investigation into Midas Financial Solutions (Scotland) Limited in October 2012.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127481","127481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838920","2018-02-20","Attorney General","2018-02-08","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Crown Prosecution Service is taking as a result of the  BBC Panorama documentary, Undercover: Britain’s immigration secrets, broadcast on 4 September 2017.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127482","127482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838921","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment the Government has made of the potential effect on the provision of education when Ofsted inspections do not occur routinely due to a school going through the process of converting to academy status.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127483","127483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838922","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which (a) completed and (b) ongoing public sector contracts in (i) Bethnal Green and Bow, (ii) Tower Hamlets and (iii) Greater London involved Carillion in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127484","127484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838923","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decommissioning of oil platforms on the economy in north east of Scotland.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127485","127485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838924","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will hold discussions with representatives of the Scottish Government on the effect of her policies on WASPI women in Scotland.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127486","127486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838925","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the continuation of Officer Training Corps and University Air Squadrons in universities.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127487","127487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838926","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to help ensure access for humanitarian aid to Yemen.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127488","127488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838927","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to help tackle modern slavery in developing countries.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127489","127489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838928","2018-02-20","Scotland Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his Department has made an assessment of the economic contributions  of Ministry of Defence contracts to the shipbuilding industry in Scotland.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127490","127490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838929","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of withholding tax for dividends and royalties in tax treaties on levels of investment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127491","127491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838930","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he had with the Secretary of State for International Development on the priorities for negotiations on the tax treaty with Lesotho.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127492","127492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838931","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of Exchequer on the (a) process of negotiation and (b) ratifying the UK’s tax treaties with (i) Lesotho and (ii) Columbia.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127493","127493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838933","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the extension of the deadline for installing SMETS1 meters from July 2018 to September 2018 on (a) the supply chain for installing smart meters, and (b) progress towards the 2020 smart meters roll-out target.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127494","127494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838934","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure the maintenance of safety standards for smart meter installations as a result of the Government's incentive schemes for increasing the number of installations of those meters.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127495","127495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838935","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the number and proportion of smart meters which are operating in dumb mode.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127496","127496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838936","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Data Communication Company charging statement, published on 12 January 2018, for what reasons there is a 30 per cent increase in annual charges per household by 2020-21.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127497","127497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838937","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of of deployment of (a) solar rooftop and (b) solar farm in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127498","127498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838938","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the change in the level of investment in renewable energy in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127499","127499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838939","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that fewer plastic bottles (a) are incinerated, (b) go to landfill and (c) littered on land or at sea.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127500","127500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838940","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to incentivise producers of packaging to use recycled plastic in their products.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127501","127501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838941","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will give the Environment Agency regulatory control over how the revenue from Packaging Recovery Notes is spent.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127502","127502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838942","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage registered social landlords to apply for the Affordable Homes Grant to build new sites for Travellers.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127503","127503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838943","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the trend in the number of specialist teachers for deaf children in (a) Yorkshire and (b) Wakefield district since 31 December 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127504","127504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838944","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of consultant lobbyists registered under the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-Party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127505","127505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838945","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will review the the fees for the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-Party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014 in consultation with representatives from (a) public affairs and lobbying trade associations, (b) civil society groups and (c) transparency campaigners.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127506","127506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838946","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the UN on the effectiveness of the UN Verification and Inspection Mechanism for Yemen.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127507","127507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838947","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2018 to Question 123544, on Department for International Development: Procurement, what the centrally-managed contract is; and what the value of that contract is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127508","127508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838948","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2018 to Question 123544, on Department for International Development: Procurement, what the cross-government contracts are; and with which other Departments those contracts are shared.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127509","127509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838949","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2018 to Question 123226, on Carillion, how often ministers and officials of his Department meet strategic suppliers; and what is discussed at such meetings.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127510","127510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838950","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2018 to Question 123545, on Department for Work and Pensions: Procurement, what those contracts are for; and what the value of each such contract is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127511","127511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838951","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2018 to Question 123543, on Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport: Procurement, what those four contracts are for; and what the value of each such contract is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127512","127512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838952","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2018 to Question 123538, on Department for Transport: Procurement, what those contracts are; and what the value is of each such contract.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127513","127513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838953","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2018 to Question 123547, on Department of Health and Social Care: Procurement, what those contracts are; and what the value of each such contract is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127514","127514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838954","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2018 to Question 123549, on Ministry of Justice: Procurement, what those contracts are; and what the value of each such contract is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127515","127515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838955","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether trades unions and other employee organisations were consulted on the establishment of Gov Facility Services Limited.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127516","127516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838956","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether employees of Gov Facility Services Limited are covered by TUPE regulations.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127517","127517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838957","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether Gov Facility Services Limited is classified as an arms-length body of his Department; and who is planned to sit on the board of directors of that body.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127518","127518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838958","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the amount of financial liabilities was which was taken on by his Department when forming Gov Facility Services Limited.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127519","127519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838959","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the transparency document entitled HMRC policy meetings with tobacco stakeholders: October to December 2017, if he will publish the minutes of the meetings between HMRC officials and such stakeholders which took place on 16 October, 17 October, 3 November and 8 December 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127520","127520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838960","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to comments made by the Permanent Secretary to the Cabinet Office at the London School of Economics on  24 January 2018, which 600 Government buildings will be closed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127521","127521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838961","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on the national institute for obesity research policy unit's research into the causes of childhood obesity; and what the timetable is for that unit's findings to be provided to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127522","127522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838962","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the minimum salary threshold for granting visas to overseas doctors with offers of employment in UK hospitals; and will she make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127523","127523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838963","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will add (a) consultant and (b) non-consultant, non-training and medical staff posts in (i) general medicine, (ii) pathology, (iii) psychiatry, (iv) surgery and (v) anaesthetics to the United Kingdom Shortage Occupation list.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127524","127524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838964","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times the Contingencies Fund has been used since 2010; and how much was used from that fund on each such occasion and for what purpose.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127525","127525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838965","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department is making on its review of air weapons.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127526","127526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838966","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the timetable is for the publication of the Student Loans Company's annual report for 2016-17.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127527","127527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838967","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward proposals for there to be a requirement for local authorities to work collaboratively with the UK Accreditation Service in order to avoid the duplication of inspections of dog breeders.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127528","127528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838968","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many disabled students allowance awards have been made to students in higher education in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127529","127529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838969","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will immediately suspend the use of medical procedures involving vaginal mesh implants.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127530","127530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838970","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on how many people who have contacted the Modern Slavery Helpline and Resource Centre have been referred to (a) Government and (b) non-government support organisations since 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127531","127531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838971","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has considered the potential merits of acquiring the capabilities currently being examined by the US Army's Squad-Multipurpose Equipment Transport (SMET) programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127532","127532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838972","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to increase the production of electricity from offshore wind.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127533","127533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838973","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure services which support children who have experienced sexual abuse receive adequate funding.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127534","127534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838974","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prevent UK residents from registering the ownership of UK land overseas in order to avoid capital gains tax.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127535","127535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838975","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether police officers appointed as wildlife crime officers hold a range of other responsibilities.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127536","127536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838976","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for the Cabinet Office of 15 January 2018, on Carillion, if she will place the annual reports of the 14 pension schemes forming part of the Carillion Group in the Library.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127537","127537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838977","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of times a multi-academy trust has withdrawn sponsorship of agreeing in principle to sponsor a school in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127538","127538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838978","2018-02-20","Department for International Trade","2018-02-08","To ask the secretary of state for international trade whether he has made an assessment as to whether the telecommunications interception equipment licensed to Honduras on 17 August 2017 and 19 December  2016 has been used by the authorities in their recent surveillance-led crack down against dissidents following November's disputed election; and whether he plans to revoke licences for strategic goods to that country.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127539","127539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838979","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the number of early years teachers.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127540","127540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838980","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment was made of passenger satisfaction, reliability, capacity, and the number of commuter services which serve Newport, Severn Tunnel Junction, and Caldicot train stations before the most recent decision to extend the Great Western Franchise was made.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127541","127541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838981","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will meet representatives of (a) the Scout Association and (b) other uniformed youth groups to discuss how his Department can support such organisations in taking forward the recommendations of the December 2016 Casey review into opportunity and integration.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Mrs Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127542","127542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838982","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children in receipt of the early years pupil premium achieved a good level of development in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127543","127543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838983","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to publish a maritime skills strategy.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127544","127544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838984","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse is of the delayed completion by more than three months of Government IT projects since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127545","127545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838985","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the additional cost to the public purse was of delays of more than three months in the completion of Government IT projects in each Department since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127546","127546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838986","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to help inform children and their parents on the safe-guarding dangers of gaming apps; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127547","127547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838987","2018-02-20","House of Commons Commission","2018-02-08","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will take steps to ban the use of single-use plastic straws on the Parliamentary Estate.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127548","127548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838988","2018-02-20","Department for International Trade","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the key potential economic benefits for UK (a) businesses and (b) consumers of the UK agreeing trade agreements with other countries after leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127549","127549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838989","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's consultation, eligibility for free school meals and the early years pupil premium under Universal Credit, which closed on 11 January 2018, what estimate he has made of the number of children who will be eligible for free school meals (a) if the proposals set out in the recent consultation are fully implemented and (b) five years after the proposals have been fully implemented.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127550","127550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838990","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to simplify save as you earn schemes and share incentive plans to encourage more people to save.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127551","127551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838991","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to seek EU State Aid approval to renew the Enterprise Management Incentive scheme; and whether he plans to undertake a review of the limits of that scheme.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127552","127552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838992","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage the sale of food closer to its source of production.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127553","127553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838993","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will provide additional compulsory training on religion and freedom of religion or belief for diplomats and Government officials working in countries where violations of those freedoms are most prevalent.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127554","127554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838995","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has held recent round-table meetings on freedom of religion or belief with interested stakeholders; if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127555","127555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838996","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what safeguards are in place to ensure that level two apprenticeship opportunities are not reduced under the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127556","127556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838997","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to protect the number of apprenticeships available with non-levy paying small employers in England.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127557","127557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838998","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of the establishment of wholly-owned companies to manage NHS properties on behalf of NHS Foundation Trusts with proposals set out in the Government response to the Naylor Review, published on 30 January 2018.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127558","127558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838999","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 9 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, what funding will be made available for the training and development of the estates and facilities workforce; and whether that funding will come from existing budgets.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127559","127559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839000","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans there are to extend access to accredited training and development in the development of high quality business cases as set out in the Government’s response to the Naylor Review, published on 30 January 2018, to other NHS organisations.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127560","127560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839001","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that sustainability and transformation partnerships are held accountable for the successful delivery of approved capital developments given those partnerships are not legal entities.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127561","127561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839002","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that effective biosecurity measures are in place to protect flora in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127562","127562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839003","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how his Department is promoting land-based colleges in rural areas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127563","127563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839004","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister for Housing, Communities and Local Government on relieving financial pressures on the NHS as a result of business rates.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127564","127564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839005","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2018 to Question 126148, on Coca Cola and Mars UK, on what dates those meetings took place.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127565","127565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839006","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2018 to Question 126164, on British Soft Drinks Association, on what dates each of those meetings took place.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127566","127566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839007","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he plans to take to increase the availability of food that is low in sugar content in vending machines on his Departmental estate.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127567","127567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839008","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase the use of virtual courts in criminal proceedings.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127568","127568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839009","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with retailers to limit the promotion of high sugar food and drink products.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127569","127569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839010","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how may people have appeared in court proceedings via video link from (a) police stations and (b) prisons since 2000; and what the demographic breakdown was of the defendants involved.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127570","127570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839011","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2018 to Question 126149, what steps he is taking to initiate discussions with representatives from social media companies on restricting junk food adverts available to children.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127571","127571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839012","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of virtual court processes on the court experience of defendants.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127572","127572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839013","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will hold discussions with the Secretary of State for Education on improving the health of pupils through increased participation in sport.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127573","127573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839014","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with representatives of cycling organisations in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127574","127574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839015","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the potential benefits of cycling for public health.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127575","127575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839016","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the sum accrued to the public purse from tax on the sale of energy drinks in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127576","127576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839017","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken in the last 12 months to encourage cycling.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127577","127577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839018","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will withdraw the diplomatic papers of Sri Lanka's Defence Attache to the UK and expel him following reports of that attache making death threats to protesters.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127578","127578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839019","2018-02-20","Department for International Trade","2018-02-08","To ask the secretary of state for International Trade, whether he sought assurances from the Government of Honduras that the telecommunications interception equipment licensed to Honduras would not be used in internal repression.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127579","127579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839020","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps his Department has taken to tackle obesity levels in children in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127580","127580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839021","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2018 to Question 125455, on Courts: ICT, what performance related measures are applied to the PwC contract for the delivery of digital courts reform.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127581","127581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839022","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2018 to Question 125455, on Courts: ICT, whether access to justice will be used as a criterion to assess the performance of contractors other than PwC for the delivery of digital courts reform contracts.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127582","127582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839023","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with whom was the new Behavioural Insights Crown Commercial Services framework developed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127583","127583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839024","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, who the suppliers are of the new Behavioural Insights Crown Commercial Services framework.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127584","127584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839025","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2018 to question 121556, on Asylum, what steps her Department plans to take with the Department for Work and Pensions to ensure refugees are not left destitute following a successful asylum application.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127585","127585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839026","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers do not have access to free classes in English as a second language.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127586","127586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839027","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have access to 10 hours a week of free classes in English as a second language.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127587","127587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839028","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the minimum necessary standard of spoken and written English for a refugee to integrate in the UK.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127588","127588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839029","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the minimum total teaching time in English as a second language that is required to allow asylum seekers to achieve adequate standards of spoken and written English.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127589","127589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839030","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions Minsters of his Department have had with the Equality and Human Rights Commission on the effect of the revised definition of Traveller in PPTS 2015 in relation to local planning authorities’ policy provision.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127590","127590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839031","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department takes to validate the PAYE data it receives from HMRC on the amounts paid to claimants of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127591","127591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839032","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the workforce are paid (a) weekly, (b) less frequently than weekly but more frequently than monthly and (c) monthly.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127592","127592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839033","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Anti-Slavery Commissioner on the greatest challenges to his effective work; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127593","127593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839034","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Government news story of 2 February 2018 entitled Government harnesses advances in Behavioural Insights with new framework, what the evidential basis is for the sum of £16 million cited.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127594","127594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839035","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of levels of mortality linked to outdoor air pollution exposure at local authority level.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127595","127595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839036","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to improve measurement of PM2.5 particles across the UK.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127596","127596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839037","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department will work with the Ministry for Housing, Communities and Local Government to provide guidance to local councils on ensuring air quality monitors record fine particulate matter, PM2.5.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127597","127597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839038","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the most recent data from indicator 3.01 in the Public Health Outcomes Framework to be published by Public Health England.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127598","127598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839039","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much money was raised for the public purse from the sale of each court since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127599","127599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839040","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has contingency plans for the event of Capita being unable to fulfil its contractual obligations with schools in (a) Brighton and Hove and (b) other areas; what assessment he has made of the total value of contracts between schools and Capita; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127600","127600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839041","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2017 to Question 108876, on Sentencing: Females, if he will provide that same information by the offence categories used in his Department's offender management statistics.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127601","127601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839042","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2018 to Question 125504, on Amey, what was meant by the statement that the maintenance contract with Amey will be reset; and whether any changes to the contract with that company have been made.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127602","127602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839043","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent correspondence he has had with the Mayor of London on penalty charges on TfL roads; and if he will place a copy of that correspondence in the Library.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127603","127603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839044","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Written Statement of 2 February 2018, HCWS445, on energy policy; if he will publish a list of the items that the £2,275,000 is planned to be spent on.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127604","127604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839045","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support his Department is providing for the (a) reskilling and (b) retraining of employees in the coal sector as result of its policy to phase out unabated coal by 2025.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127605","127605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839046","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the spending from the public purse to date on the smart meter roll-out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127606","127606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839047","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125605, what funding his Department has allocated to (a) reduce the number of 11-16 year olds who participate in gambling activities and (b) support those aged 11-16 who have been identified as problem gamblers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127607","127607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839048","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statement from the Under-Secretary-General for Humanitarian Affairs and Emergency Relief Coordinator to the UN Security Council, published on 7 December 2017, on the humanitarian situation in South Sudan, what representations he has made to the Government of South Sudan on allowing unhindered access for humanitarian organisations.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127608","127608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839049","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to use his position on the UN Human Rights Council during the Council session on 13 March to speak about the human rights and humanitarian situation in South Sudan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127609","127609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839050","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to review the effectiveness of legislation on medical negligence compensation.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127610","127610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839051","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what financial support is available from the Government for hospitals that are placed in special measures.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127611","127611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839052","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many affordable housing units have been completed by type of unit and region in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127612","127612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839053","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to introduce penalties for local planning authorities that fail to introduce a five-year land supply.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127613","127613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839054","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's recently advertised roles which are paid, except in circumstances where the successful applicant already receives a salary for full-time work paid for from public funds, what proportion of applications are from people employed in the public sector which (a) do not pay a salary to those already in receipt of a full-time salary from public funds, (b) are unpaid and (c) are paid irrespective of an applicant's existing public-sector pay.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127614","127614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839055","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's recently advertised roles which are paid, except in circumstances where the successful applicant already receives a salary for full-time work paid for from public funds, what assessment he has made of the effect of that policy on protected characteristics under the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127615","127615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839056","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to extend the scope of Office for Low Emission Vehicles grants to include e-bikes and e-cargo bikes.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127616","127616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839057","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the deployment of Egyptian troops to Eritrea on Eritrea-Ethiopia relations.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127617","127617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839058","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 4.7 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, how guidance issued by NHS Improvement can be applied to the primary care estate.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127618","127618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839059","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from VAT on vehicles and other supplies to disabled people in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127619","127619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839060","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 4.9 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, when the comprehensive dataset on the primary care estate will be completed and available for enquiries.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127620","127620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839061","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the School Direct route into teaching.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127621","127621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839062","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from VAT on residential conversions and renovations in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127622","127622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839063","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 4.10 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review published in January 2018, how estates expertise will be enabled at the local level.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127623","127623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839064","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received the reduced rate for domestic fuel and power in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127624","127624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839065","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of tuition fee costs on teacher training applications.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127625","127625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839066","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received the reduced rate of VAT on energy saving materials in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127626","127626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839067","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 4.11 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, how the development of (a) local capacity and (b) local support has been delivered.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127627","127627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839068","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what psychological support is provided by her Department to victims of torture seeking asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127628","127628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839069","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph of 4.13 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review published in January 2018, if he will publish the evaluations of the small number of sustainability and transformation partnerships that have been assessed by the group of strategic estatesadvisers.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127629","127629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839070","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many non-repayable bursaries the Government has allocated to support trainee teachers in the last year; and what the value was of those bursaries.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127630","127630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839071","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 4.14 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, what arrangements his Department has put in place for the (a) governance and (b) accountability for the Strategic Estates Planning service.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127631","127631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839072","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 4.22 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, what steps the Property Board takes to improve the quality of business cases.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127632","127632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839074","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to prevent the establishment of wholly owned companies to manage estates and property management which have been progressed but whose business case does not meet the standards of the published checklist.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127633","127633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839075","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment has he made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the recruitment of teachers in England.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127634","127634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839076","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 5.5 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, what the timetable is for the prioritised capital investment plans covering whole sustainability and transformation partnerships footprints to be (a) completed and (b) published.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127635","127635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839077","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money was accrued to the public purse from Capital Gains Tax paid on residential property in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127636","127636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839078","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding he has allocated to the (a) establishment and (b) operation of the NHS Property Board.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127637","127637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839079","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 5.11 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, what steps he is taking to ensure that business cases will have the full support of sustainability and transformation partnerships.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127638","127638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839080","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving Euratom on medical treatments provided by the NHS.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127639","127639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839081","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 5.12 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, what steps he has taken to (a) renegotiate and (b) replace PFI schemes.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127640","127640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839082","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Smaller Brewers received relief from excise taxes in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127641","127641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839083","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of state school teachers in England were recruited from EU countries.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127642","127642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839084","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 6.28 of the Government Response to the Naylor Review, published in January 2018, how much of the £8 billiion of operating costs is directly linked to (a) PFI and (b) other external contracts.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127643","127643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839085","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps the Government has taken to encourage professionals into teaching.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127644","127644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839086","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to direct Community Health Partnerships to return the dividend paid from Local Improvement Finance Trust contracts to local health economies.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127645","127645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839087","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to improve the retention rate of teachers in England.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127646","127646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839088","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers have left the profession by (a) gender and (b) age in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127647","127647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839089","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money his Department has spent on advertising for teacher recruitment in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127648","127648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839090","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of statutory rights of occupiers of social housing to succeed to a tenancy on the death of the previous sole or joint tenant.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127649","127649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839091","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people have been removed from social housing because they did not have succession rights to remain following the death of the previous sole or joint tenant in each year since 2012 .","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127650","127650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839092","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the cost to the public purse was of tenants living in social housing who do not have succession rights appealing local authority decisions in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127651","127651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839093","2018-02-20","Wales Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many meetings (a) he and (b) his officials have held with the Welsh Government on the Swansea Bay tidal lagoon since 6 December 2017; and when and where such meetings took place.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127652","127652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839094","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have been provided with alternative social housing as a result of being removed from existing social housing for which they are no longer eligible following the death of the previous tenant.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127653","127653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839095","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to raise awareness of the link between mental health issues and the use of social media in young people.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127654","127654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839096","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support he offers to Credit Unions; and what steps his Department is taking to encourage their use.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127655","127655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839097","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of offering financial incentives to encourage people to buy an electric car; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127656","127656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839098","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department has offered to Haiti in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127657","127657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839099","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government’s planned clean air strategy will include a commitment to reaching WHO limits for particulate matter.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127658","127658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839100","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will include a target on reducing premature deaths from air pollution in its new clean air strategy.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127659","127659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839101","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the next round of funding for railway safely projects to be allocated to the closure of level crossings.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127660","127660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839102","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the next phase of level crossing closures.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127661","127661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839103","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of housing units for rent or sale built by Network Rail or its contractors since 2013.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127662","127662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839104","2018-02-20","Wales Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether he has made representations to the Secretary of State for Transport on the railway safety implications of the cancellation of rail electrification programmes in and to Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127663","127663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839105","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of units for rent or sale for commercial use built by Network Rail or its contractors since 2013.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127664","127664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839106","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many housing units for rent or sale his Department estimates Network Rail or its contractors will have built by 2020.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127665","127665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839107","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of units for rent or sale for commercial use which will be built by Network Rail or its contractors by 2020.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127666","127666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839108","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of his Department's property portfolio in terms of financial value has been sold or leased for (a) housing for rent or sale and (b) commercial property since 2013.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127667","127667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839109","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of his Department's property portfolio in terms of financial value is planned to be sold or leased for (a) housing for rent or sale and (b) commercial property by 2020.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127668","127668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839110","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of housing units for rent or sale and designated as affordable housing which have been built by Network Rail or its contractors since 2013; and what the average cost of those units has been.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127669","127669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839111","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of housing units for rent or sale and designated as affordable housing which are planned to be built by Network Rail or its contractors by 2020; and what information his Department holds on the average cost of those units.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127670","127670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839112","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on how many local authorities have signed confidentially agreements with HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127671","127671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839113","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many current asylum applicants' claims have taken more than 182 days to process.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127672","127672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839114","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to review the effectiveness of the new Sports Governance guidelines over the next 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127673","127673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839115","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to  the Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125493 on Faith Schools; what discussions his Department has had with local authorities on the effect of the removal of the cap on the distribution of (a) school admissions and (b)catchement areas.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127674","127674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839116","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125493 on Faith Schools, what assessment he has made of whether allowing faith schools greater freedom to discriminate on the grounds of faith conflicts on the Government's proposals to strengthening equalities legislation.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127675","127675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839117","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect the Government's hostile environment policy on the ability of asylum seekers to claim asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127676","127676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839118","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the terms and conditions of the contracts held between his Department and Carillion have been changed following their transfer to new companies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127677","127677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839119","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of staff hours in his Department which have used on assessing and dealing with the effects of Carillion entering liquidation and the transfer of contracts formerly held by that company.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127678","127678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839120","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to his Department's updated Departmental Plan, published on 29 January 2018, whether he intends to publish a consultation on reform of Society Lottery regulation.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127679","127679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839121","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the General Data Protection Regulation, what steps he is taking to support manufacturers to track appliances sold to customers to enable effective product corrective action.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127680","127680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839122","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to include a target to reduce premature deaths from air pollution in the new clean air strategy.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127681","127681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839123","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to include a commitment to reaching World Health Organisation limits for particulate matter in the new clean air strategy.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127682","127682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839124","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether universal credit recipients who have received a provisional offer of employment but are undergoing security checks prior to being approved for the role must continue applying for other employment opportunities.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127683","127683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839125","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has had discussions with the Gambling Commission on tackling sexual harassment and sexist practices at gambling industry events; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127684","127684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839126","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to made an assessment of the effectiveness of  the Starting Well, oral health preventative programme.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127685","127685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839127","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of children who have been admitted to A&E due to dental problems.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127686","127686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839128","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the most common reason is for children being admitted to A&E.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127687","127687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839129","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the review of S4C.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127688","127688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839130","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for the people undertaking the review of S4C to report back to him.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127689","127689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839131","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the planned level of funding for S4C from the public purse is for financial year 2018-17.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127690","127690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839132","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases of sepsis there were in each region of England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127691","127691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839133","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of devolving broadcasting to Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127692","127692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839134","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress he has made on the public consultation on the deregulation of commercial radio.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127693","127693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839135","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of proposals in its consultation on the deregulation of radio on the use of the Welsh language in radio in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127694","127694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839136","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of deregulation of commercial radio on levels of locally produced content.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127695","127695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839137","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with lung disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127696","127696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839138","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what financial benchmarks his Department plans to use to inform its consideration, based on an assessment by the Infrastructure and Projects Authority, of the financial resilience of (a) Third Energy UK Gas Limited and (b) other companies proposing to carry out hydraulic fracturing operations.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127697","127697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839139","2018-02-20","Department for International Trade","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if his Department will publish the name of the company that it licensed to supply two batches of surveillance and telecommunications interception equipment to Honduras in 2017.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127698","127698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839140","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons her Department has not yet responded to the North and Midlands Independent Monitoring Board for Short-term Holding Facilities, Annual Report 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127699","127699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839141","2018-02-20","Department for International Trade","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department took to comply with criterion two of the consolidated EU and national arms export licensing criteria before issuing arms export licences for exports to Honduras in 2017.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127700","127700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839142","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has undertaken an equality impact assessment of the planned changes to Support for Mortgage Interest; how many SMI claimants are (a) pensioners and (b) disabled people; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127701","127701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839143","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125704, on Mortgages: Interest Payments, by what date her Department plans to have contacted all claimants of support for mortgage interest to offer the new support for mortgage interest loan.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127702","127702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839144","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much each NHS Trust in the North-West accrued from parking charges in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and what proportion of each NHS Trust's income that figure represents.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127703","127703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839145","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to Figure 9 of the Defence Equipment Plan 2017, what the identified savings were from each of the programmes which formed part of the Equipment Support Projects Review that contributed to (a) savings delivered and (b) total forecast savings.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127704","127704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839146","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to bring forward legislative proposals to repeal charges on toll bridges established under 19th Century Acts of Parliament; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127705","127705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839148","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of domestic abuse cases reported to her Department resulted in a prosecution in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127706","127706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839149","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nursing posts are currently vacant in (a) Warrington and (b) the North-West.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127707","127707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839150","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to Figure 9 of the Defence Equipment Plan 2017, how the £677 million of financial benefits delivered under the Submarine Enterprise Performance Programme were achieved.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127708","127708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839151","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have appealed against their original personal independence payment assessment; and how many of those appeals were successful.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127709","127709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839152","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence,with reference to Figure 9 of the Defence Equipment Plan 2017, what estimate he has made of the (a) gross savings and (b) net savings within the identified Total Forecast Savings in that plan.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127710","127710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839153","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the roll-out of personal independence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127711","127711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839154","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to establish a sugar policy to provide equity in the sugar market for producers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127712","127712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839155","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department last reviewed the provisions of the Vagrancy Act 1824.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127713","127713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839156","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to repeal the Vagrancy Act 1824.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127714","127714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839157","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to figure 9 of The Defence Equipment Plan 2017, which weapons systems in the Complex Weapons pipeline were included in the programme to develop families of weapons utilising the principles of commonality, modularity and re-use that he estimates will deliver £1.2bn savings over 10 years from 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127715","127715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839158","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many rough sleepers have been (a) arrested and (b) prosecuted under the Vagrancy Act 1824 in (i) England and (ii) Wales in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127716","127716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839159","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much revenue support has been provided by his Department to (a) Baker Dearing Educational Trust, (b) New Schools Network and (c) Studio Schools Trust in each financial year since 2009.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127717","127717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839160","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to Question 122221 tabled on 11 January 2018 by the hon. Member for Oxford West and Abingdon.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127718","127718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839161","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the research his Department has (a) conducted and (b) commissioned into Basic Income schemes since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127719","127719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839162","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, at what age a person with dementia is eligible for benefit entitlement as a result of that condition.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127720","127720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839163","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library a copy of the revised guidance issued to staff as a result of the changes to universal credit announced in Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127721","127721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839164","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of UK Visas and Immigration's practice of returning important personal documents including (a) passports and (b) birth certificates by standard post.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127722","127722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839165","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is to present to Parliament, the secondary legislation required to enable Collective Defined Contribution pensions.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127723","127723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839166","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what evidence his Department submitted to the OECD's report on Sustainable Access to Innovative Therapies.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127724","127724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839167","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2018 to Question 123536 on Ministry of Defence Procurement, if he will publish the name of each supplier.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127725","127725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839168","2018-02-20","Scotland Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the future viability of the Scottish component of the British Transport Police pension fund when it is transferred to the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127726","127726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839169","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether all banks and financial service firms are required to have a written policy on domestic abuse.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127727","127727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839170","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to take urgent steps in primary legislation to create a statutory definition of cross border hiring whereby a journey must begin or end in the licensing authority area for which the vehicle, driver and operator are licensed; and if he will support this by the introduction of statutory England-wide guidance setting out minimum licensing standards; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127728","127728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839171","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department issued to (a) banks and (b) the financial service sector on responding to cases has of domestic abuse in which the perpetrator and victim have a joint bank accounts.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127729","127729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839172","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals for a definition of plying for hire.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127730","127730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839173","2018-02-20","Scotland Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the effect of the merger of the Scottish component of the British Transport Police into Police Scotland on cross border policing; and what estimate he has made of the cost of cross border activities as a result of that merger.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127731","127731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839174","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2018 to Question 108783 on Taxis, on what date in the New Year the working group plans to report.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127732","127732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839175","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's Response to the Work and Pension Committee’s Fourteenth Report of Session 2016–17, Child Maintenance: Government Response to the House of Commons, HC 354, how many employees within the Child Maintenance Service have received specialist domestic abuse training.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127733","127733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839176","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to decision of the UN to freeze Libyan Assets, agreed by EU Directive and adopted by the UK, whether he has made an estimate of the value of assets frozen (a) at the time the assets were frozen and (b) the current value of those assets.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127734","127734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839177","2018-02-20","Scotland Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the effect on cross border policing of the proposed merger of British Transport Police (Scotland) with Police Scotland.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127735","127735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839178","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether (a) specialist, (b) face to face and (c) ongoing training on domestic abuse is provided to employees working in its frontline services.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127736","127736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839179","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will proscribe Antifa; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127737","127737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839180","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has held with his counterparts in the EU on tensuring the security and retention of frozen Libyan assets.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127738","127738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839181","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Ambassadors and High Commissioners have left posts with his Department and subsequently been re-appointed as an official or consultant since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127739","127739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839182","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on including the Dartford Crossing in his Department’s Air Quality Plan as a result of the reclassification of that crossing as an urban road in 2017.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127740","127740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839183","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons his Department's Air Quality Action Plan concluded that no road in Dartford would be over the limit value for air pollution this year.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127741","127741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839184","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which road in Dartford was identified in his Department’s Air Quality Action Plan to be over the limit value for air pollution in 2017.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127742","127742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839185","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 7 February 2018, Official Report, column 1566, on Local Government Finance, if he will encourage local authorities in Dorset to budget for 2018-19 on the basis that they will not be subject to negative revenue support grant in 2019-20; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127743","127743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839186","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on fuel supplies for back-up generators in Gaza; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127744","127744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839187","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued to GPs to promote participation in sport to their patients.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127745","127745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839188","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons contracted out facilities management to (a) Carillion (b) Amey.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127746","127746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839189","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which road in Dartford was identified in his Department’s Air Quality Action Plan to be over the limit value for air pollution in 2017.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127747","127747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839190","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many recorded breaches of contracts by (a) Carillion and (b) Amey there were in financial year 2016-17.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127748","127748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839191","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking improve health provision for communities in (a) the West Bank and (b) Gaza.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127749","127749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839192","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the size of his Department's estate was in square metres of floor space for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127750","127750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839193","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the current size of the Government estate is, by Department, in square metres of floor space.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127751","127751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839194","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the size of the Government estate was, by Department, in square metres of floor space in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127752","127752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839195","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the publication of the results of the 2016 public enquiry into the Hope Valley line improvements.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127753","127753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839196","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for Network Rail's design work on the improvements to the Hope Valley line be concluded.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127754","127754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839198","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the monthly civilian staff cost to his Department was for (a) payroll and (b) non-payroll staff, including (i) contingency and (ii) consultancy staff in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127755","127755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839199","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government has made an assessment of the (a) efficacy and (b) experiences of Designated Safeguarding Leads in schools in advance of the introduction of Designated Mental Health Leads in schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127756","127756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839200","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-payroll staff were employed by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127757","127757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839201","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the potential financial merits of including in the Hope Valley improvement scheme an increase in express trains from Sheffield to Manchester from 2 to 4 trains an hour.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127758","127758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839202","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of the Hope Valley line improvement scheme on economic growth in the area.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127759","127759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839204","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for a decision to be made on the funding for the Hope Valley Line improvement scheme.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127760","127760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839205","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for new rolling stock to be introduced on the Midland Mainline.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127761","127761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839206","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) children and (b) adults spent time in a police station as a place of safety due to a mental health condition in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127762","127762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839207","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for hybrid trains to begin running on the Midland Mainline.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127763","127763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839208","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many attendances at emergency departments for self-harm per 100,000 people there were in 2016-17; and how many of those attendancies received a psychological assessment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127764","127764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839209","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) planned and (b) actual administration budget spending for each Department has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127765","127765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839210","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many in-patient eating disorder beds there have been for (a) adults and (b) children in each year since 2010 in England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127766","127766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839211","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many formal complaints (a) mental health services and (b) the NHS received in each region in each month of each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127767","127767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839212","2018-02-20","Prime Minister","2018-02-08","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she discussed the disqualification of candidates from Hong Kong elections with the Government of China during her recent visit to that country.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127768","127768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839213","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to Question 117720, tabled by the right hon. Member for Westmorland and Lonsdale on 5 December 2017.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127769","127769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839214","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to respond to Question 123846, tabled by the right hon. Member for Westmorland and Lonsdale on 19 January 2018.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127770","127770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839215","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the status of  LGBT+ rights in Bermuda.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127771","127771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839216","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department first become aware of detainee welfare concerns at Brook House Immigration Removal Centre.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127772","127772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839217","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of what led to concerns about detainee welfare at Brook House Immigration Removal Centre.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127773","127773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839218","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who are (a) survivors of sexual and gender-based violence and (b) otherwise recognised as vulnerable under the Adults at Risk policy have been brought to immigration detention centres since 12 September 2016.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127774","127774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839219","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Bermudian counterpart on same-sex marriage legislation.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127775","127775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839220","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of asylum seekers who received therapy or counselling from the NHS during 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127776","127776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839221","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2018 to Question 123744, on Home Office: Contracts, if her Department will publish its monitoring of the financial performance of strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127777","127777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839222","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications have been open for a period of two years or longer prior to 6 February 2018.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127778","127778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839223","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2018 to Question 121751, what steps her Department plans to take to monitor the effectiveness of those arrangements.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127779","127779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839224","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to carry out post-removal monitoring of refugees sent back to Sudan to (a) ensure their safety and (b) collect data on any adverse consequences for them of their return.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127780","127780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839225","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons her Department removed the simple payment method in March 2018 for benefit claimants without a bank account.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127781","127781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839226","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the reasons were for the decision that the voucher scheme would give universal credit claimants £100 a time rather than the monthly paid benefit payable under the simple payment method.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127782","127782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839227","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce drink and drug abuse among mental health service users.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127783","127783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839228","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the incidence of drink and drug abuse among pregnant women.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127784","127784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839229","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps are being taken to ensure that students are educated on issues of privacy and personal security on social media.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127785","127785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839230","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of non-Arab Darfuri asylum seekers who had their asylum claims rejected in 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127786","127786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839231","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the danger to non-Arab Dafuris sent to Khartoum after having their asylum claims rejected in the UK.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127787","127787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839233","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government is in the process of drafting asylum seeker returns and readmission arrangements for Sudan.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127788","127788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839234","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment has been made of whether there has been any water contamination as a result of fracking in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127789","127789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839235","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of services to check people for skin cancer.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127790","127790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839236","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to improve the level of average weekly earnings in Yorkshire and Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127791","127791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839237","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how his Department monitors the observance of guidance on support to the tobacco industry in its overseas posts; what assessment he has made of compliance with that guidance by those posts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127792","127792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839239","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will set out all instances where assistance was provided to the tobacco industry by UK overseas posts since December 2013.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127793","127793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839240","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what percentage of young people who were eligible for free school meals in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England were in education, employment or training after completing Key Stage 4 in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127794","127794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839241","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how he monitors observance by UK overseas posts of the revised guidance on support to the tobacco industry published in December 2013.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127795","127795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839242","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to monitor adherence to the revised guidance to UK overseas posts on support to the tobacco industry, issued in December 2013, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127796","127796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839243","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of young people in (a) Ashfield, constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England who were eligible for free school meals at age 15 achieved two or more A levels or equivalent qualifications by the age of 19 in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127797","127797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839244","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many terminally ill personal independence payment claimants were assessed as fit to work; and how many and what proportion of those claimants were considered as ineligible for the enhanced daily rate in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127798","127798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839245","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what percentage of young people eligible for free school meals at 15 in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England entered higher education by the age of 19 in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127799","127799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839246","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125090 on Travellers: Caravan Sites, how many local planning authorities development plan documents were found to be consistent with planning policy for Traveller Sites.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127800","127800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839247","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for his Department to make a decision any investigation into the proposed takeover of GKN Plc by Melrose Industries in the interests of National Security.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127801","127801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839248","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what percentage of young people eligible for free school meals at 15 from (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England entered higher education at a Russell Group university in each of the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127802","127802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839249","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 124116 on Children: Daycare, how many of the callers to the childcare service helpline successfully completed their application for Tax-Free Childcare.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127803","127803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839250","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department has issued on  30 hours free childcare provision to parents whose job circumstances change in the rolling three-month period.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127804","127804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839251","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps the Government has taken to tackle the misuse of Fentanyl.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127805","127805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839252","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the top ten drugs bought by the NHS from EU countries were by (a) volume and (b) price.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127806","127806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839253","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government taking to help alleviate the humanitarian situation in Afrin.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127807","127807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839254","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the amount of (a) public and (b) private funding was invested in (i) new and (ii) existing ports infrastructure was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127808","127808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839255","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the the adequacy of levels of (a) public and (b) private investment in UK ports infrastructure in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127809","127809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839256","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to publish (a) regulations and (b) guidance on goat racing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127810","127810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839257","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on rates of (a) employment and (b) training for UK-based seafarers.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127811","127811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839258","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on annual rates of freight tonnage traffic handled at UK ports.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127812","127812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839259","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the shipping industry of the UK (a) remaining and (b) becoming part of (i) the single market and (ii) a customs union with the European Union.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127813","127813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839260","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on the ports sector in the UK of (a) remaining or (b) becoming part of (i) the single market or (ii) a customs union with the EU.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127814","127814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839261","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on the maritime services sector of the UK (a) remaining or (b) becoming part of (i) the single market or (ii) a customs union with the EU.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127815","127815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839262","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the answer of 30 January 2018 to Question 124845, on Energy: Prices, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of energy price caps on (a) consumers (b) employment and (c) investment in (i) Canada, (ii) the US, (iii) Spain and (iv) New Zealand; and if his Department will publish that assessment.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127816","127816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839263","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the Government plans to respond to the ninth report of the Women and Equalities Committee's report, Building for Equality: Disability and the Built Environment of Session 2016-17, HC 631, published on 25 April 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127817","127817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839264","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill on employment in energy projects in the counties and regions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127818","127818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839265","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of implementation of proposals in the draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill on a (a) a rise and (b) fall in wholesale energy costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127819","127819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839266","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timescale is for the introduction of the Faecal Immunochemical Test to the bowel screening programme.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127820","127820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839267","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how mainstream schools are held to account for the use of SEND funding; and whether the Government plans to ring-fence that funding.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127821","127821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839268","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department takes to ensure that learners on SEND support in mainstream settings are prioritised by school leadership.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127822","127822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839269","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that SEND is a fundamental part of strengthening Qualified Teacher Status.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127823","127823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839270","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve career progression opportunities for special educational needs coordinators and SEND specialists; and whether he plans to include those roles in his Department's consultation, Strengthening qualified teacher status and career progression, published on 15 December 2017.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127824","127824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839271","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the usage of the Severn Tunnel Junction will be considered when the (a) Cross Country and (b) Great Western franchise agreements are drawn up.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127825","127825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839272","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to issue (a) regulations and (b) guidance on ferret racing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127826","127826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839273","2018-02-20","Prime Minister","2018-02-08","To ask the Prime Minister, how many times she met with (a) Alan Milburn in his capacity as Chair or (b) Baroness Gillian Shephard in her capacity as Deputy Chair of the Social Mobility Commission during their tenure at that Commission.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127827","127827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839274","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the number of insecure jobs in (a) the North West and (b) Liverpool Walton constituency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127828","127828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839275","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the number of self-employed people who earn below the national living wage in (a) the North West and (b) Liverpool Walton constituency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127829","127829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839276","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the increase in the number automated jobs on the potential merits of introducing a universal basic income.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127830","127830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839277","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the automation of jobs on (a) women, (b) BAME people, (c) disabled people and (d) people from lower socio-economic backgrounds.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127831","127831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839278","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Liverpool Walton constituency are employed on zero-hour contracts.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127832","127832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839279","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the liquidation of Carillion on schools in Liverpool Walton constituency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127833","127833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839280","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125090, how many local planning authorities have had their development plan documents assessed and found to be inconsistent with planning policy for Traveller sites.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127834","127834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839281","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all schools teach awareness of violence against women and girls.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127835","127835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839282","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of unqualified teachers in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in Liverpool Walton constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127836","127836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839283","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125090, what training planning inspectors tasked with examining development plan documents receive with regard to the assessment of the accommodation needs of Gypsies and Travellers.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127837","127837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839284","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the public sector pay cap on the recruitment and retention of staff in schools in (a) the UK, (b) the North West and (c) Liverpool Walton constituency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127838","127838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839285","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of Sure Start children’s centres on the school readiness of children in Liverpool Walton constituency.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127839","127839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839286","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of people from lower socio-economic backgrounds applying to university.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127840","127840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839287","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on which websites Army recruitment advertisements have been placed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127841","127841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839288","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) total and (b) disaggregated spend was on each website where army recruitment advertisements have been placed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127842","127842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839289","2018-02-20","Cabinet Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings he has had with the Social Mobility Commission since his appointment.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127843","127843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839290","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total spend was on army recruitment advertising via (a) Facebook, (b) Snapchat and (c) Twitter in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127844","127844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839291","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent to boost posts on the Army Jobs Facebook page in each of the last three years; and what the target audience was for each of those posts.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127845","127845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839292","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded incidents of domestic violence there were in (a) Leigh constituency and (b) Wigan Borough in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127846","127846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839293","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to introduce a new pension scheme for members of the armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127847","127847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839294","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will review the rules of the Armed Forces Pension Scheme relating to widows who remarried prior to 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127848","127848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839295","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consultation is planned to engage businesses and other stakeholders on the development of proposals for a new environmental enforcement agency to ensure good governance after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127849","127849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839296","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 123021, what information his Department holds on the number of staff who will be recruited to Companies House in 2018-19; and what plans he has to increase recruitment to that organisation after the next 12 months.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127850","127850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839297","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to introduce automated verification systems in Companies House to check the accuracy of the register of beneficial ownership for companies; and how much it costs to maintain the public register each year with regards to staff, IT and any associated overheads.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127851","127851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839298","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the Government plans to supply molybdenum-9, used for the manufacture of technetium-99 generators after the UK leaves Euratom.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127852","127852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839299","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Israeli Government on the demolition of EU-funded structures in the village of Abu Nuwar in the West Bank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127853","127853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839300","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish a list of current suppliers of molybdenum-99 located in countries that are not members of Euratom.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127854","127854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839301","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to ensure the continued supply of molybdenum-99 after UK leaves Euratom.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127855","127855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839302","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have been (a) convicted and (b) fined under the Money Laundering Regulations 2007 by offence since 2010.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127856","127856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839303","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost of the Thameslink project at London Bridge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127857","127857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839304","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much money from the public purse has been spent on the Thameslink project to improve the infrastructure to all rail lines that run (a) into and (b) out of London Bridge Station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127858","127858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839305","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to provide funding (a) directly and (b) indirectly to (i) Bridge International Academies and (ii) its parent or subsidiary companies.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127859","127859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839306","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 2 February 2018 to Question 125487, whether local authorities have discretion to not provide a free school meal to a child in (a) reception (b) year 1 and (c) year 2 because of their age.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127860","127860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839307","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate her Department has made of the funds allocated to Bridge International Academies and its parent or subsidiary companies in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127861","127861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839308","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential improvement the performance of Southeastern rail services on completion of the Thameslink project at London Bridge Station; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127862","127862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839309","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 1 February 2018 to Question 125414, on Communication Trust, what estimate his Department has made of the number of speech, language and communication needs specialists jobs that may be at risk as a result of his Department's decision to not renew that contract.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127863","127863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839310","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on the review of the Care Quality Commission (Registration) Regulations 2009.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127864","127864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839311","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the answer of 1 February 2018, to Question 125414, on Communication Trust, for how many consecutive years his Department has had contracts with The Communications Trust related to speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127865","127865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839312","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January to Question 123732, if he will list (a) those local authorities that have informed his Department that they have commissioned hair strand tests for drug and alcohol use from Trimega and (b) the reasons why each local authority commissioned such tests.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127866","127866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839313","2018-02-20","Women and Equalities","2018-02-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what overseas visits officials in the Government Equalities Office have undertaken in 2017; how many officials took part in each such visit; and what the (a) cost, (b) purpose and (c) outcome of each such trip was.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127867","127867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839314","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of eligible employees of his Department use childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127868","127868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839315","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of eligible employees of his Department use childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127869","127869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/839435","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to co-ordinate cross-Whitehall working to increase social mobility in response to the recommendations of the Social Mobility Commission report, State of the Nation 2017: Social Mobility in Great Britain.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903981","903981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/837764","2018-02-08","Department for Transport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government has plans to introduce a diesel vehicle scrappage scheme for people on low incomes.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 126795","126795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/837966","2018-02-08","Department for Transport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government plans for the Severn Bridge toll to be removed entirely.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 126996","126996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838176","2018-02-07","Northern Ireland Office","2018-02-07","What recent assessment she has made of the strength of the Northern Ireland economy.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903764","903764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838177","2018-02-07","Northern Ireland Office","2018-02-07","What recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on ensuring that people in England who were victims of terrorism perpetrated by paramilitary groups based in Northern Ireland are able to access legal aid.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903766","903766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838178","2018-02-07","Northern Ireland Office","2018-02-07","What discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on city deals in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903768","903768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838201","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Health, what clinical guidance advises on (a) at what stage of pregnancy anaesthetic is applied to a fetus before an abortion procedure and (b) for which kind of abortion procedures anaesthetic is applied.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127099","127099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838202","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much parents with no recourse to public funds must pay to establish that their children are UK nationals.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127100","127100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838203","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase funding for the national NHS ophthalmic services contract for adults and children with learning disabilities and for people who are homeless.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127101","127101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838204","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to support people with dementia after they retire from work; and what assessment he has made of the connection between retirement and the onset of dementia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127102","127102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838205","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps he is taking to ensure that the Red Sea supply route to Yemen is protected from hostile attacks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127103","127103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838206","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to introduce the Princes Trust to young people to help them acquire employment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127104","127104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838207","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to support (a) Nigeria and (b) Syria in response to the water crises in those countries.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127105","127105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838208","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of the number of primary school-age children who are self-harming.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127106","127106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838209","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of deaths recorded in secure inpatient mental health units in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127107","127107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838210","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on staffing levels in (a) secure adult inpatient mental health units and (b) Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services Tier 4 inpatient units for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127108","127108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838211","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what records her Department holds on complaints to the police about the display of Hezbollah flags at the Al-Quds Day rally in London on 18 June 2017.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127109","127109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838212","2018-02-20","Scotland Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment his Department has made of the contribution to the economy of (a) Dumfries and Galloway and (b) Scotland of the Port of Cairnryan.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127110","127110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838213","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of whether cancellation charges incurred by subcontractors and SMEs after 15 January 2018 working on public contracts secured by Carillion will be paid.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127111","127111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838214","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions his Department has had with internet service providers on the continued high search result rankings of secondary ticketing websites on the internet.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127112","127112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838215","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of extending the 12-month time period within which a child maintenance agreement within a consent order cannot be overruled by the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127113","127113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838216","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department plans to respond to the report published by the Independent Commission on Dormant Assets.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127114","127114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838217","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department hold on the number of people over the age of 65 who were re-admitted to hospital within (a) one week, (b) two weeks, (c) one month, (d) three months and (e) six months of discharge from hospital to a social care setting in each of the years for which data is available.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127115","127115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838218","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions since 2015 he has used his powers under Schedule 6, Paragraph 3 of the Town and Country Planning Act 1990 to determine a planning application appeal which would otherwise be determined by a person appointed by the Secretary of State.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127116","127116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838219","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions he has been asked to confirm a local planning authority's decision to revoke planning permission under Section 97 of the Town and Country Planning Act 1990; and on how many such occasions he (a) confirmed and (b) overturned that decision in each year since 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127117","127117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838220","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the cost to the public purse is for initiatives aimed at preventing female genital mutilation overseas since 2016; and which countries have received that funding.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127118","127118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838221","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse is for using the US non-governmental organisation Polaris to set up a helpline for victims on modern slavery; and how many times the helpline has been used since its establishment.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127119","127119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838222","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of credibility interviews for Tier 4 visa applications that have taken place since 2010.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127120","127120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838223","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) import extradition requests her Department received from and (b) export extradition requests her Department made to non-category 1 and 2 countries in each year since 2016; and how many of each such requests were (i) granted and (ii) refused.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127121","127121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838224","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many export extradition requests her Department received from Category 2 territories in each year since 2016; and of those requests how many (a) were certified, (b) were approved by district judges at extradition hearings and (c) faced extradition.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127122","127122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838225","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many immigration advisers were registered with the Office of the Immigration Services Commissioner (OISC) in each year since 2016; how many complaints the OISC received about immigration advisers registered with them in each of those years; how many complaints resulted in a OISC reported wrongdoing on the part of the adviser; and in how many such cases the OISC (a) took action against the adviser and (b) referred the complaint.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127123","127123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838226","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many import extradition requests from Category 2 territories were passed to the International Criminality Unit of the Home Office in each year since 2016; how many such requests she authorised to be sent to Category 2 territories for hearing in courts in those territories; and in how many of those cases the court ordered extradition.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127124","127124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838227","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding for stem cell research was allocated by the National Institute for Health Research and Blood and Transplant Research Unit in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127125","127125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838228","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) registered care home and (b) nursing home places there were in (i) England and (ii) Greater London in each year since 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127126","127126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838229","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of a cessation of drift net salmon fishing in 2018 on heritage fishing in North Shields.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127127","127127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838230","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional costs have been incurred on PFI contracts for police buildings that are used to train firearms officers in (a) the Metropolitan police and (b) other police forces in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127128","127128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838231","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Get Britain Cycling, published by the All Party Parliamentary Cycling Group in 2013, if his Department will ensure that cycling infrastructure receives adequate funding in line with the recommendations in that report.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127129","127129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838232","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies have had their financial statements rejected by Companies House as unsuitable for filing in each year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Nigel Mills","Nigel Mills","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127130","127130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838233","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to consult further with (a) further education colleges and (b) other stakeholders on proposals contained in the Government's Careers Strategy.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127131","127131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838234","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to provide financial support for Sheffield City region to fund non-statutory concessions for bus travel.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127132","127132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838235","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the level of the lone parent work allowance.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127133","127133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838236","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will make an assessment of the adequacy of the current level of the lone parent work allowance.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127134","127134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838237","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he is taking steps to ensure that evidence of the absolute and relative health risks of heat-not-burn tobacco products is independently reviewed.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127135","127135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838238","2018-02-20","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union of 31 January, Official Report, column 833, on the Government’s EU Exit Analysis, whether the document referred to has been classified as a market access assessment by his Department.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127136","127136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838239","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many student nurses from outside the UK have received bursaries in the last four years.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127137","127137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838240","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to update the Reinsurance (Acts of Terrorism) Act 1993 to enable insurance companies to pay compensation to businesses after terrorism attacks when there is no damage to property.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127138","127138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838241","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of terrorism insurance in compensating businesses after an act of terror.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127139","127139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838242","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce legislation to update the Reinsurance (Acts of Terrorism) Act 1993 to enable insurance companies to pay compensation to businesses after terrorism attacks when there is no damage to property.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127140","127140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838243","2018-02-20","Department for International Trade","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2018 to Question 125208, how many (a) staff and (b) contracted staff were involved in (i) replicating agreements and (ii) negotiating with counterparties and what experience of negotiating each of those staff had for each agreement listed on the European Commission’s website.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127141","127141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838244","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to provide medical support for people affected by recent military action between Turkish Government forces and Kurds.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127142","127142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838245","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with the management Heathrow Airport on the planned length of the third runway there.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127143","127143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838246","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, under which of the grounds set out in Regulation 32 (Use of the negotiated procedure without prior publication) his Department justified the extension of Virgin Rail’s West Coast contract by direct award rather than through a competitive tendering process.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127144","127144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838247","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Government of the Republic of Ireland on steps to ensure the revival of Wild Atlantic Salmon stocks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127145","127145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838248","2018-02-20","Department for Transport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department received legal advice in relation to Regulation 32 (Use of the negotiated procedure without prior publication) to enable a direct award of Virgin Rail’s contract extension for the West Coast Main Line rather than awarding it through a competitive tendering process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127146","127146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838249","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of men dying as a result of prostrate cancer.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127147","127147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838250","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) residential care homes and (b) nursing homes have closed since 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127148","127148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838251","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding has been allocated to the Forced Marriage Unit in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127149","127149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838252","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted for drink driving in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127150","127150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838253","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of the offence of causing serious injury by dangerous driving since 2010; and how many such people were imprisoned for the maximum amount stipulated for the offence.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127151","127151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838254","2018-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to establish within his Department and each service of the Armed Forces improved provision for confidential access to mental health support.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127152","127152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838255","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Security of 19 December 2017, Official Report, column 1008, how her Department differentiates between members of the political and military wings of Hezbollah, and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127153","127153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838256","2018-02-20","Department for Education","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will discuss with Stonewall its proposals for an inclusive maths curriculum.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127154","127154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838257","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the capacity of local police forces in London to investigate burglaries.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127155","127155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838258","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the cost implications for the public purse of not including an appeals process to an expert independent body on the level of a cap on energy prices in the draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill; and what the evidential basis is for not including such an independent appeals process.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127156","127156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838259","2018-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications of the Government's proposed household energy price cap for the smart meter roll-out.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127157","127157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838260","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average response times and (b) total hours flown were for helicopters at each of the bases of the National Police Air Service in each fiscal year since that service was created.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127158","127158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838261","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding was allocated by each Police and Crime Commissioner area for the running of the National Police Air Service in each fiscal year since that service was created.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127159","127159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838263","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police road pursuits of vehicles were abandoned due to a lack of air support in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127160","127160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838264","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government will introduce a fiat digital currency.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127161","127161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838265","2018-02-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of the National Lottery on the effect on lottery tickets sales of the price change of National Lottery tickets since that price change was made in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127162","127162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838266","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department took to minimise risk in response to the National Audit Office report on The Home Office's oversight of forensic services, published in January 2015.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127163","127163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838267","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of awarding universal credit to prisoners who are nearing completion of their sentence before they leave prison.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127164","127164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838268","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions her Department has had with the Ministry of Justice on the merits of awarding universal credit to prisoners who are nearing completion of their sentence before they leave prison.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127165","127165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838269","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether NHS mental health and health trusts are required to inform his Department of their capacity to admit patients with very specific mental health needs to places where appropriate care is available; and whether his Department issues guidelines to such trusts on the maximum distance from a patient's home and families such patients can be so placed.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127166","127166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838270","2018-02-20","HM Treasury","2018-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the reasonableness of the levels of interest which banks apply to homeowner loans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127167","127167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838271","2018-02-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that refuge services currently in receipt of funding from his Department do not close at the end of the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127168","127168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838272","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent of expansion of Hezbollah's weapons arsenal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127169","127169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838273","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how the decision will be made on assessing whether a child defendant has the ability to effectively participate in court proceedings via a video link rather than in person; and what adjustments are made for a child appearing before a court via video link.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127170","127170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838274","2018-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political and security situation in Cameroon; and what steps his Department is taking to help protect human rights in that country.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127171","127171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838275","2018-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average caseload of a caseworker at the Criminal Cases Review Commission has been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127172","127172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838276","2018-02-20","Department for International Development","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to hold discussions with the South Sudan Leaders Forum to encourage better representation of young people in South Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127173","127173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838277","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to mitigate the costs to business of the implementation of the EU Medium Combustion Plant Directive.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127174","127174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838278","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of patient access to community transport for the purposes of attending hospital appointments in rural areas.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127175","127175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838279","2018-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Table 5.9 of the Office for Budget Responsibility' report Welfare Trends, published in January 2018, that more than 300,000 self-employed workers will lose an average of over £3,000 a year under universal credit.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127176","127176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838280","2018-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding for flood defences has been allocated to each constituency in England and Wales since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127177","127177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838283","2018-02-20","Home Office","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the Community Security Trust's Antisemitic Incidents Report 2017.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127178","127178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/838284","2018-02-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether it is the policy of NHS England to require a person to provide photographic ID to register with a GP.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127179","127179"
