"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990382","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his October 2018 policy paper, The future of healthcare: our vision for digital, data and technology in health and care, what support his Department will provide to health and social care organisations to enable them to spend money wisely on technology.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181266","181266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990383","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the October 2018 policy paper, The future of healthcare: our vision for digital, data and technology in health and care, what assessment his Department has made of the level of technical fluency of leaders in the NHS; and what steps he plans to take to recruit leaders with the technical fluency needed to be a competent customer.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181267","181267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990384","2018-10-23","Treasury","2018-10-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer,  whether the Government has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that payday lenders make individual assessments of the effect on people who have (a) gambling and (b) mental health problems of taking out a loan.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181174","181174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990385","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-resident parents at the time of their annual review had their child maintenance calculated from income that was earned more than two years from the date of that assessment.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181324","181324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990386","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps HMRC is taking to ensure that records on the income of Child Maintenance Service non-resident parents are kept up to date.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181325","181325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990387","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit payday loan companies from advertising their services on television.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181175","181175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990388","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the October 2018 policy paper, The future of healthcare: our vision for digital, data and technology in health and care, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of national IT programmes; and whether he has concluded that any of those programmes should be cancelled.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181268","181268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990389","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174798, how many children and young people have been admitted to A&E in London in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181326","181326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990390","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to (a) ensure that the new asylum seeker accommodation contracts will deliver accommodation of a good standard and (b) support people to make a successful transition from asylum-seeking to refugee status.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181327","181327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990391","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that local authorities are empowered and funded to support asylum seekers and newly recognised refugees.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181328","181328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990392","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to support local authorities during the transition to new asylum accommodation contracts.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181329","181329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990393","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions will be in the new asylum accommodation contracts to ensure that successful asylum applicants do not become destitute when they leave dispersal accommodation.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181330","181330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990394","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding his Department has provided to support newly-recognised refugees in London when they have moved out of asylum dispersal accommodation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181331","181331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990395","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the NHS Long-Term Plan will ensure that every patient with secondary breast cancer has access to a tailored health and wellbeing event that includes psychological support and opportunities to meet other people with secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181332","181332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990396","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to expand the Controlling Migration Fund in London to support newly recognised refugees find and sustain suitable accommodation.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181333","181333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990397","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers are living in London as at October 2018.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181334","181334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990398","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of asylum seekers registered to attend English for Speakers of Other Languages classes in London (a) six months and (b) 12 months after arriving in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181335","181335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990399","2018-10-23","Cabinet Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much of the £1.9 billion awarded to the National Cyber Security Centre in 2016 has been spent to date; and on what such funds have been spent.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181336","181336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990400","2018-10-22","Attorney General","2018-10-18","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions he has agreed to (a) review and (b) reconsider his consent to prosecution; and on how many of those occasions he withdrew his consent in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181269","181269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990401","2018-10-22","Attorney General","2018-10-18","To ask the Attorney General, how many times he has been asked to consent to a prosecution; and in how many of those cases he (a) granted and (b) refused consent in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181270","181270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990402","2018-10-22","Cabinet Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many registered users of Gov.UK verify there were at February 2018.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181337","181337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990403","2018-10-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people affected by the errors in the calculation of employment and support allowance made by her Department in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181178","181178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990404","2018-10-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what (a) financial support and (b) other resources his Department has provided to Cancer Alliances for long-term planning for breast cancer care.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181271","181271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990405","2018-10-23","Home Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the annual budget for the National Crime Agency's International Corruption Unit has been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181272","181272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990406","2018-10-23","Home Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the annual budget for the National Crime Agency's Financial Intelligence Unit has been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181273","181273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990407","2018-10-23","Attorney General","2018-10-18","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions have been made by the Crown Prosecution Service under (i) Section 330 and (ii) Sections 327-329 of the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181274","181274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990408","2018-10-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the value of underpayments to recipients of employment support allowance in South Yorkshire since 2011.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181338","181338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990409","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the value of underpayments to recipients of employment support allowance in Barnsley since 2011.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181339","181339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990410","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of employment support allowance in South Yorkshire have been underpaid since 2011.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181340","181340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990411","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of employment support allowance in Barnsley have been underpaid since 2011.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181341","181341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990412","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of strike action on Arriva Rail North; and what financial assessment he has made of the effect of that strike action on the franchise.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181275","181275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990413","2018-10-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people calculated to have been underpaid employment and support allowance payment in South Yorkshire have been refunded a backdated payment in full.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181342","181342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990414","2018-10-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people calculated to have been underpaid employment and support allowance in Yorkshire have been refunded a backdated payment in full.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181343","181343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990415","2018-10-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people calculated to have been underpaid employment and support allowance payment in South Yorkshire have been refunded a backdated payment in full.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181344","181344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990416","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of whether Arriva Rail North has met the obligations and provisions of its franchise.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181276","181276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990417","2018-10-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people calculated to have been underpaid employment and support allowance payment in Barnsley have been refunded a backdated payment in full since 2011.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181345","181345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990418","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of universal credit in (a) South Yorkshire and (b) Barnsley receive less money under universal credit compared with their previous benefit entitlement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181346","181346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990419","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of recipients of universal credit in (a) South Yorkshire and (b) Barnsley receive less money under universal credit compared with their previous benefit entitlement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181347","181347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990420","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what adjustments his Department has made to the provisions of the Arriva Rail North franchise in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181277","181277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990421","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the maintenance of access to insulin after the the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181348","181348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990422","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the (a) availability and (b) provision of (i) flu and (ii) pneumonia vaccines for people eligible for free vaccinations.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181349","181349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990423","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the provisions of the Northern Rail franchise to protect the operator against falling passenger numbers.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181278","181278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990424","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of UK expatriates living in South Africa that will be affected by the motion passed in the Parliament of South Africa on 1 March 2018  to confiscate land without compensation from white farmers.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181215","181215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990425","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what adjustments he has made to the provisions of the Northern Rail franchise that provide protection to the operator against falling passenger numbers.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181279","181279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990426","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the value was of the subsidy his Department provided to Arriva Rail North in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181280","181280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990427","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to protect the operator against falling passenger numbers on Northern Rail.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181281","181281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990428","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of the franchise competitions for (a) Southeastern, (b) East Midlands Trains and (c) West Cost trains.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181282","181282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990429","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the contribution in premiums to the public purse from First Transpennine in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181283","181283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990430","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason access to the alternative remedies package has been limited only to applicants authorised by the Prudential Regulatory Authority to take deposits.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181284","181284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990431","2018-10-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the recent Court of Appeal judgement in the case of the Palestine Solidarity Campaign and Jacqueline Lewis against the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the new Institutions for Occupational Retirement Provision Directive will be applied to the local government pension scheme in January 2019.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181285","181285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990432","2018-10-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library the assessments his Department has made of trends in the incidences of human rights abuses in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia over the last three years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181350","181350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990433","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on access to alternative remedies package funds the employment of senior people historically connected to RBS GRG unit will have.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181286","181286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990434","2018-10-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of (a) service personnel in each of the services and (b) officials in his Department stationed in Saudi Arabia have delivered training to Saudi Armed forces in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181351","181351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990435","2018-10-23","Department for International Trade","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on UK consumer and food standards regulations which meet the US Trade Priorities and Accountability Act definition of an unjustified (a) sanitary or (b) phytosanitary restriction and (c) an unjustified technical barrier.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181352","181352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990436","2018-10-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department has had with his counterparts in other EU member states on (a) the right to work, (b) access to social security and (c) accessing UK based pensions in the EU if the UK leaves the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181353","181353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990438","2018-10-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to extend Equality Act 2010 to include people with episodic and fluctuating mental health conditions.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181354","181354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990439","2018-10-23","Cabinet Office","2018-10-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2018 to Question 179329 on Cybercrime: Industry, whether the new minimum cyber security standard will apply to suppliers with existing contracts.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181355","181355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990440","2018-10-23","Treasury","2018-10-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many representations for additional funding he has received from the National Cyber Security Centre in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181356","181356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990441","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to make audio visual recording facilities available for personal independence payment and employment and support allowance assessments.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181287","181287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990442","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to encourage retailers to introduce plastic-free supermarket aisles.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181357","181357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/991143","2018-10-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how HMRC determines which full year income records are classed as complete for a taxpayer in order to calculate child maintenance payments.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181590","181590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989396","2018-10-17","Scotland Office","2018-10-17","What recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Scottish economy.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907026","907026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989397","2018-10-17","Scotland Office","2018-10-17","What recent assessment he has made of the effect of the freeze on fuel duty on low income families in Scotland.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907027","907027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989398","2018-10-17","Scotland Office","2018-10-17","What recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Scottish economy.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907029","907029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989399","2018-10-17","Scotland Office","2018-10-17","What recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Scottish economy.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 907034","907034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989447","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the amount spent on re-surfacing roads in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180633","180633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989448","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of trends in A Level results in (a) Coventry South, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180634","180634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989449","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of trends in GCSE results in (a) Coventry South, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180635","180635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989450","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the effect of long-term homelessness on mental health.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180636","180636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989451","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) Secretary of State for Health and Social Care and (b) Chancellor of the Exchequer on the cost of parking at hospitals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180637","180637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989452","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the effects of loneliness on physical and mental health in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180638","180638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989453","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with headteachers in (a) Coventry South, (b) Coventry and (c) the West Midlands on schools the increase in funding of teachers' pay as set out in the 2018 School Teachers' Review Body report.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180639","180639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989454","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government received information following the inspection of Barzeh by the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons at any time in the six months before missile strikes were initiated against that location on 14 April 2018.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180698","180698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989455","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2018 to Question 161049 on Waste Management, when the Resources and Waste Strategy will be published.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180850","180850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989456","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department supports local authorities to promote recycling by businesses.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180845","180845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989457","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether local authorities are responsible for monitoring the extent of recycling undertaken by businesses.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180846","180846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989458","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many civilian casualties there were in the attack by the Chadian army on the town of Kouri Bougoudi in September 2018; and what representations he has made to his Chadian counterpart on that attack.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180671","180671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989459","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish details of the accommodation used by London-based Ministers and officials of his Department when visiting the UN General Assembly in New York in September 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180672","180672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989460","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many representations his Department has received since his reference to the Soviet Union when speaking about the EU at the Conservative party conference on 30 September 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180673","180673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989461","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if will publish a ranked list of the reasons for fixed-period exclusions of pupils in secondary schools in (a) the North East and (b) England in the last two years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180725","180725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989462","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department (a) holds a list of Government controlled companies which only produce financial reports as small companies and (b) monitors the risk to the taxpayer of undisclosed contingent liabilities in Government controlled companies.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180828","180828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989463","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) legal fees and (b) directors’ emoluments in relation to IMS Ltd since that company ceased trading in July 1991.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180829","180829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989464","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent in relation to IMS Ltd since it ceased trading; and what steps he takes to monitor the reasonableness of those costs.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180830","180830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989465","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the merits of restricting the sale of  paracetamol and aspirin to behind the counter to reduce the number of deaths by self-poisoning.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180815","180815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989466","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of audiologists specialising in paediatrics that will be needed up to 2020.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180851","180851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989467","2018-10-22","Cabinet Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will undertake a review of the (a) reasons and (b) extent of increases in postal and proxy vote applications in constituencies in (i) Northern Ireland and (ii) England in advance of any changes required to the system for such applications for the next General Election.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180655","180655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989468","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the revenue to the public purse from the introduction of the three per cent surcharge on buy to let properties between April 2016 and April 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180656","180656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989469","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the EU Mortgage Credit Directive on the cost of mortgages.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180624","180624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989470","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the advice on the efficacy of e-cigarettes as a stop smoking aid between Public Health England’s document entitled Stop smoking options: guidance for conversations with patients and NICE’s document entitled Stop smoking interventions and services guidance.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180852","180852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989471","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to publish the ten-year plan on the development of Maritime and Royal Marine activity in the High North by the end of October 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180661","180661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989472","2018-10-22","Department for International Development","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on (a) producers and (b) workers in developing countries.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180726","180726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989473","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of higher rate tax relief claimed by people with personal pensions in each of the last ten years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180657","180657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989474","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in which local authority areas the £39 million is being spent in reducing parental conflict through evidence-based interventions; over what time periods that money is being spent; whether there are plans to make service universal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180660","180660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989475","2018-10-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an estimate of the level of funding required to cancel the debts of claimants transferred from legacy benefits to universal credit.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180650","180650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989476","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 176323 on Teacher's Pensions, what proportion of the projected rise in employer contribution costs is due to the change to the Scape discount rate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180747","180747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989477","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Indian counterpart on the seven Indians in the Orissa region who have been in prison on murder charges for 10 years awaiting an appeal hearing.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180658","180658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989478","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Chinese counterpart on a reported increase in forced organ harvesting.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180659","180659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989479","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason his Department has reduced the validity of biometric residence permits issued to people granted indefinite leave to remain from 10 to six years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180715","180715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989480","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of (a) civilian casualties, (b) damage to property, community facilities and infrastructure by RAF strikes in Mosul in 2016-17.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180811","180811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989481","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 178358 on the London to Brighton Railway line, what the timetable is for a decision on the options his Department is considering to simplify the Brighton mainline fare structure.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180823","180823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989482","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the funding allocated for substance misuse services in England by (a) local authority and (b) in total in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180687","180687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989483","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the funding allocated for alcohol treatment services in England by (a) local authority and (b) in total in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180688","180688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989484","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the funding allocated for drug treatment services in England by (a) local authority and (b) in total in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180689","180689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989485","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to increase local authority funding for substance misuse services as a result of changes in the cost of prescribing buprenorphine.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180690","180690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989486","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the financial effect on substance misuse services of the changes in the cost of prescribing buprenorphine.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180691","180691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989487","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on the financial effect of the increase in the cost of prescribing buprenorphine on the provision of substance misuse services.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180692","180692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989488","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it is the Government's policy to move away from using coal to generate electricity in the UK; and what assessment his Department has made of the effect of higher gas prices on the level of electricity generation from (a) coal and (b) gas.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180812","180812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989489","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has allocated additional funding to substance misuse services as a result of the increase in the cost of prescribing buprenorphine.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180693","180693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989490","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many medically-staffed alcohol in-patient detoxification beds there are in (a) England, (b) London and (c) Suffolk.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180694","180694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989491","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to increase the number of neurology consultants.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180628","180628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989492","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 174137 on Vacancies: West Midlands, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of vacancies on (a) Find a Job and (b) Universal Jobmatch for (i) permanent and (ii) contract positions since 2013.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180841","180841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989493","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when her Department plans to lay before Parliament its draft regulations on the managed migration of claimants to universal credit.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180749","180749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989494","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the managed migration of claimants to universal credit will (a) include a roll-out schedule and (b) allow for (i) pauses and (ii) reviews to ensure that the system is ready to manage the projected number of claimants.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180750","180750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989495","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the potential effect on vulnerable claimants of moving three million people manually on to universal credit; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180751","180751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989496","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department plans to provide to vulnerable claimants moving to universal credit under managed migration; and what steps she is taking to ensure those claimants do not lose income as a result of that transition.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180752","180752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989497","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect on vulnerable claimants of the roll-out of universal credit under (a) current systems and (b) the managed migration process.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180753","180753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989498","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to identify vulnerable claimants on legacy benefits who require additional support for managed migration to universal credit.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180754","180754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989499","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to increase (a) universal and (b) other transitional support to help the transition to universal credit  under managed migration.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180755","180755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989500","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to reduce payment times for universal credit applicants.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180756","180756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989501","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that vulnerable claimants do not lose income when moving to universal credit through managed migration.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180757","180757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989502","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of automatically moving claimants that would otherwise undergo managed migration to universal credit from 2019.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180758","180758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989503","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to make it mandatory for (a) utility companies and (b) the private sector to contribute financially to flood protection when their infrastructure is at risk.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180729","180729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989504","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the 2018 NAO report on the financial sustainability of local authorities published by the NAO in March 2018, what plans he has to (a) promote a sustainable means of funding flood defences and (b) mitigate the risk that flooding presents to communities and the economy.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180730","180730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989505","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the new measure of poverty recommended by the Social Metrics Commission: a new measure of poverty, published in September 2018; and if she plans to adopt that new measure.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180731","180731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989506","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies on reducing the number of households living in poverty of the Social Metrics Commissions report, A new measure of poverty in the UK, published in September 2018.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180732","180732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989508","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from police forces on changes to police pension contributions.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180816","180816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989509","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to each police force of the revision of assumptions on public sector pension contributions.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180817","180817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989510","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether e-cigarettes which gain authorisation as licensed medicines from the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency will be taxed at the reduced rate of VAT when sold over the counter.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180700","180700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989511","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from police bodies on the potential effect of changes to employee pension contributions on police numbers.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180818","180818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989512","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the potential effect of changes to employee pension contributions on police numbers.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180819","180819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989513","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to introduce a national tariff for paediatric audiology services.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180843","180843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989514","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Rail Review announced on 11 October 2018 on the timing of the East Midlands franchise process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180710","180710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989515","2018-10-22","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 178377, what assessment she has made of the effect on the five integrated schools that were given approval to proceed to planning in March 2016 of the delay in announcing a second tranche of Fresh Start Agreement funding.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180847","180847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989516","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to Written Statement of 9 October 2018 on Building safety update, HCWS976, whether he plans to extend the ban on combustible materials to all hospitals irrespective of height.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180832","180832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989517","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to Written Statement of 9 October 2018 on Building safety update, HCWS976, whether he plans to extend the ban on combustible materials to all care homes irrespective of height.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180833","180833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989518","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 177254 on Medical equipment: waste disposal, how many of the 155 permitted healthcare waste sites in England are hospitals.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180685","180685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989519","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164527 on Buildings: insulation, how many hospitals above 18 metres have rainscreen cladding.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180834","180834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989520","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164527, how many non-high-rise hospitals that are below 18 metres have rainscreen cladding.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180835","180835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989521","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164527, how many high-rise care home buildings that are above 18 metres have rainscreen cladding.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180836","180836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989522","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164527, how many non-high-rise care home buildings that are below 18 metres have rainscreen cladding.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180837","180837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989523","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the criteria his Department used to determine the £9 billion Business Impact Target.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180701","180701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989524","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 175928 on Wind Power: Seas and Oceans, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of offshore wind’s classification as a Pot 2 technology as a result of the development of that sector since 2014.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180630","180630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989525","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department made of the use of drones by the Police and Fire Services of the effectiveness of those services in relation to (a) difficult to reach areas, (b) incidents involving a danger to life and limb and (c) public disorder events.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180702","180702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989526","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will review the Government's policy on hydraulic fracturing for shale gas; and if he will consider in that review the (a) extent of public opposition to that technique and (b) the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change's recent findings that significant decarbonisation must take place within 12 years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180631","180631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989527","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits for teenagers at school of staggering the start-time of the school day.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180703","180703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989528","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to make it a criminal offence to knowingly communicate with a person detained in the criminal justice system using an electronic communications system.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180704","180704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989529","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to lay legislative proposals before the House to change the tax credit sequencing rules applied to non-parental carers.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180796","180796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989530","2018-10-22","Department for International Development","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has allocated to programmes to eradicate the Guinea worm in (a) Ethiopia, (b) South Sudan, (c) Mali, (d) Chad and (e) other African countries.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180705","180705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989531","2018-10-22","Department for International Development","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made in collaboration with other countries on the eradication of the Guinea worm.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180706","180706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989532","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the level of risk of an Asian Hornet invasion in autumn 2018.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180707","180707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989533","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of historical tax credit overpayments to be referred from HMRC to her Department for recovery through universal credit payments.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180797","180797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989534","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which Department will be responsible for resolving disputes on the recovery of alleged tax credit overpayments by universal credit.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180798","180798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989535","2018-10-22","Department for International Trade","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2018 to Question 178257 on Trade Promotion, if he will publish the visits undertaken by each Trade Envoy in the last year.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180666","180666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989536","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the capacity of  (a) his Department and (b) agencies of his Department to replicate the functions of the European Chemicals Agency in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180708","180708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989537","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to increase driver awareness of the dangers of overtaking (a) cyclists and (b) other vulnerable road users without leaving sufficient space.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180667","180667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989538","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the inclusion in driver education on road safety of up-to-date visual tools and materials, including virtual reality films, to ensure that people are made aware of their driving from the perspective of other road users.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180668","180668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989539","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the merits of promoting virtual reality road safety awareness films as an educational tool for drivers.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180669","180669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989540","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of continued participation in the EU Registration, Evaluation, Authorisation and Restriction of Chemicals programme in (a) any withdrawal agreement with the EU and (b) the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180709","180709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989541","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations he has received from the National Police Air Service on force contributions to that Service.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180820","180820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989542","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 176641 on help to buy scheme: Oxfordshire, if he will (a) publish and (b) place in the Library the calculation relating to the average value of a property completion under that scheme in Oxfordshire.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180848","180848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989543","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether restrictions have been placed on the work of Saudi-based UK (a) military personnel and (b) private contractors to his Department, in relation to the (i) preparation, (ii) maintenance and (iii) operational use of air-delivered weapons used in the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180801","180801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989544","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what guidance the Government provides to (a) Saudi-based UK military personnel and (b) private contractors to the MoD under Saudi armed forces project on reporting suspicions of violations of international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180802","180802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989545","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government plans to support the construction of a frigate factory on the River Clyde.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180803","180803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989546","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the security of UK waters in the North Atlantic.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180804","180804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989547","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what preparations his Department has made for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180805","180805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989548","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to improve (a) housing and (b) lodgings for armed forces personnel.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180806","180806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989549","2018-10-22","Cabinet Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to improve the UK’s cyber security.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180807","180807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989550","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that clinical commissioning groups spend funds allocated for children and young people’s mental health services on those services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180711","180711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989551","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 2.16 of the National Audit Office report, Improving children and young people’s mental health services, published on 9 October 2018, what assessment he has made of the effect on his Department's ability to measure the expansion of NHS workforce against sustainability and transformation plans of Health Education England not expecting to have data on the number of NHS staff working in children and young people’s services until 2019.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180712","180712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989552","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 14 on page 9 of the National Audit Office report, Improving children and young people's mental health services, published on 9 October 2018, what steps he is taking to recruit additional NHS staff to work in those services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180713","180713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989553","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his spending priorities are for the modernising defence programme are.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180808","180808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989554","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on the (a) development and (b) implementation of the modernising defence programme.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180809","180809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989555","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will review his Department's policy on the right of armed forces personnel to join a (a) trades union and (b) political party.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180810","180810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989556","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of medical nutrition on the management of drug-resistant epilepsy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180714","180714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989557","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2018 to Question 172062 on Syria: chemical weapons, what the evidential basis is for his statement that the Director General of the Organisation for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons reported that they had been prevented from deploying to Douma by Russia and Syria.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180699","180699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989558","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 176140 on coal, what tonnage of house coal was the calculation based on that 3.3 kilotonnes of PM2.5 emissions were produced by burning house coal in the UK in 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180678","180678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989559","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings (a) he (b) his Ministers and (c) his officials have had with CPL Ltd over the last year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180679","180679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989560","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings (a) he, (b) Ministers in his department and (c) officials in his department, have had with the Competition and Markets Authority on CPL Ltd in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180680","180680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989561","2018-10-22","Department for International Development","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the amount of funding allocated to UK-based organisations spent on (a) overseas aid and (b) administrative costs within Wales in the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180844","180844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989562","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that adequate numbers of donors are available for patients requiring a stem cell transplant.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180770","180770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989563","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much statutory funding each Clinical Commissioning Group in England provided to hospices in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180771","180771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989564","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2018 to Question 171712, if he will publish his Department's plan for bringing HMP Berwyn up to full capacity.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180831","180831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989565","2018-10-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Gambling Commission undertook due diligence on Vasilijs Melniks before granting a licence to the Park Lane Casino in London.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180723","180723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989566","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals to the tribunals service in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England which related to (i) personal independence payments, (ii) employment and support allowance, (iii) income support, (iv) jobseeker's allowance and (v) tax credits, (vi) universal credit were successful in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180772","180772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989567","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the number of (a) prison officers and (b) qualified mental health practitioners employed at HMP Risley.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180643","180643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989568","2018-10-22","Department for International Development","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has allocated to provision of secure and properly screened toilets for Rohingya women refugees in Bangladesh in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180644","180644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989569","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that the new provider for University Academy Warrington has (a) expertise in and (b) a track record of raising the attainment of working class pupils; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180645","180645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989570","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what level of reserve funding police forces held at 31 March in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180737","180737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989571","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will take steps to ensure that GPs contact patients who are entitled to a free flu vaccination invite those patients to be vaccinated.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180646","180646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989572","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that people who are entitled to a free flu vaccination are aware that the vaccination can be obtained from pharmacies as well as from GP surgeries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180647","180647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989573","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect on the health and social care sectors in each nation of the UK of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180759","180759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989574","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers in each of the devolved administrations on his Department's assessment of the effect on the health and social care sector in each nation of the UK of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180760","180760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989575","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of people eligible for free flu vaccination have received that vaccine in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180648","180648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989576","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department consulted health and social care service providers on the effect on those sectors (a) throughout the UK and (b) in each of the four nations of the UK of leaving the EU.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180761","180761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989577","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that Kosovo receives universal recognition as a state ten years on from that country gaining independence.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180681","180681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989578","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether a land swap between Serbia and Kosovo will set a precedent for the territories in that region.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180682","180682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989579","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has consulted people who require health and social care services on the impact on those sectors (a) throughout the UK and (b) in each of the four nations of the UK of leaving the EU.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180762","180762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989580","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether a land swap between Serbia and Kosovo would have the effect of improve relations between those countries.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180683","180683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989581","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department consulted organisations working for and on behalf of individuals who require health and social care services on the effect on those sectors (a) throughout the UK and (b) in each of the four nations of the UK of leaving the EU.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180763","180763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989582","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department’s policy is on potential land swaps between Serbia and Kosovo; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180684","180684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989583","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will visit Hinckley to discuss the Hinckley and Bosworth Health and Wellbeing Partnership strategy of empowering people to manage their own physical and mental needs closer to home.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180640","180640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989584","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many nationals from other EU countries are employed in the NHS.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180764","180764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989585","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to replace the EU school fruit, vegetables and milk scheme; and for what reason such steps were not included in the Agriculture Bill.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180649","180649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989586","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on the online platforms that hate crime offences have been perpetrated on.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180738","180738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989587","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what change there has been in the number of nationals from other EU countries working in the NHS in the last two years.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180765","180765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989588","2018-10-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2018 to Question 178290 on Delegated Legislation, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the rate at which each Department is laying statutory instruments on EU exit domestic preparedness compared with the rate required to deliver a functioning statute book on the day that the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Mr Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180722","180722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989589","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking with Ministers in each of the devolved administrations to ensure the adequacy of supply of medicines throughout the UK after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180766","180766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989590","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has undertaken a risk assessment of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the population’s health and wellbeing in the event that there are shortages or disruptions to the supply of medicines after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180767","180767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989591","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of vacancies in the health and social care sectors across the UK; and how many such vacancies there are in each of the four nations.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180768","180768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989592","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of England's pig stock slaughtered annually do not pass vet inspections for release into the human food chain.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180663","180663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989593","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools each regional schools commissioner is responsible for.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180777","180777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989594","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of England's total cattle stock slaughtered annually do not pass vet inspections for release into the human food chain.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180664","180664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989595","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of people with Parkinson’s disease who have received enhanced levels of personal independence payments and the ongoing award in (a) Alyn and Deeside constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180654","180654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989596","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect on staffing levels at each tier of employment in her Department of the appointment of Interserve as the contractor for facilities management.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180799","180799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989597","2018-10-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many officials in his Department are working on health and social care policy.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180778","180778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989598","2018-10-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many officials in his Department are working on matters relating to employment rights.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180779","180779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989599","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost of maintenance requirements throughout the NHS estate for the next three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180780","180780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989600","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that the promises and pledges set out in the NHS Constitution on waiting times are met.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180781","180781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989601","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to develop new apps for the NHS; what budget has been made available for such development; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180782","180782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989602","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients left NHS referral to treatment waiting lists by reason of death in each of the last eight years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180783","180783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989603","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the quality of services delivered by Interserve since it was contracted to provide facilities management services to his Department.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180800","180800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989604","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the age profile was of midwives working in the NHS in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180784","180784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989605","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the age profile was of nurses working in the NHS in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180785","180785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989606","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to attend board meetings of the NHS Shared Business Service.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180786","180786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989607","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether it is his policy that clinical commissioning groups should fully implement the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines on in vitro fertilisation.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180787","180787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989608","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) staffing and (b) caseload levels have been in his Department's post-decision casework unit in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180674","180674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989609","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that transparency data on the NHS Property Services website is kept up to date.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180788","180788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989610","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his answer of 13 November 2017 to Question 111406 on Prescriptions: Fees and Charges, how many penalty charges have been issued in respect of wrongly claimed NHS prescriptions in each month since September 2017 for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180789","180789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989611","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) longest processing time was for documents to be issued following a decision by his Department's post-decision casework unit in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180675","180675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989612","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to resolve the NHS high-risk maintenance backlog.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180790","180790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989613","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to visit Neston train station.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180791","180791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989614","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total public spending per person in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) England has been in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180792","180792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989615","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people with mental health needs that will be unable to move to universal credit because they do not understand the communication about that transition in (a) the North East and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180727","180727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989616","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the publication of the findings of the pregnancy loss review.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180728","180728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989617","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage young people into farming.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180822","180822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989618","2018-10-22","Cabinet Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement of 9 October 2018, GOV.UK Verify programme, HCWS 978, whether it remains the Government's target to achieve 25 million Verify users by 2020.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180849","180849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989619","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health and Social Care of 21 June 2018, Official Report, column 232WH, on ME: Treatment and Research, what steps his Department has taken to collaborate with the Department for Work and Pensions on guidance for healthcare professionals for the assessment of people with ME.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180813","180813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989620","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will provide additional resources to the Tribunal Service in the North East of England to reduce waiting times for universal credit and personal independence payment tribunal hearings.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180696","180696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989621","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what evidence-based protocol on ME are healthcare professionals employed by his Department required to learn as part of their training.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180814","180814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989622","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has plans to improve the efficiency of the youth justice system; and what steps he is taking to reduce rates of youth re-offending.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180824","180824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989623","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of England's total sheep stock slaughtered annually do not pass vet inspections for release into the human food chain.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180665","180665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989624","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the efficiency of the processing of caseload at Camberwell Green Magistrates’ Court.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180825","180825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989625","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the oral contribution by the Prime Minister on 17 October 2018, if he will publish the procedure for a diabetic to obtain a Freestyle Libre Glucose Monitoring System through the NHS.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180697","180697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989626","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of IGCSE entries were taken in (a) state-funded schools (b) independent schools in 2018.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180739","180739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989627","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 177683 on Engineering and Physics: Vocational Guidance, for what reason his Department is not able on undertake a comparative assessment of an area of responsibility that is devolved in Wales and Scotland; and what steps the Government has taken to ensure that best practice is shared between the nations of the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180724","180724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989628","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether assessments made by his Department of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the health and social care sectors on (a) the UK and (b) each of the four nations of the UK have been shared with the relevant Ministers in those administrations.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180769","180769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989629","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for the roll-out of universal credit in Nottingham; which categories of claimants will be included in each phase of that roll-out; and what deadline is planned for the completion of that roll-out.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Mr Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180642","180642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989630","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2018 to Question 176531 on Carers: Unemployment, what (a) data and (b) methodology her Department uses to determine decisions on those interventions.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180842","180842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989631","2018-10-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taken to ensure the implementation of the commitment made in the Civil Society Strategy, published by his Department in August 2018, that being in receipt of taxpayers’ money should not inhibit charities from making their voices heard; and whether he has plans to end the use of anti-advocacy clauses.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180745","180745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989632","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost to HM Courts and Tribunal Service was to administer a First-Tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support Appeal) in relation to personal independence payments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180773","180773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989633","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the construction of High Speed Two on the (a) habitat and (b) population of barn owls.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180623","180623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989634","2018-10-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of anti-advocacy clauses in Government contracts on charities that have an income of less than £1 million pounds.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180746","180746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989635","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Stage 3 hearings resulted in the Judge awarding the defendants costs in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180686","180686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989636","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on the provision of the FluMist flu vaccine in schools; whether take-up of that vaccine by schools is voluntary; and what procedures his Department has put in place for parents who do not wish their children to be immunised with that vaccine.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180629","180629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989637","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his latest estimate is of (a) the overall cost and (b) cost of each element of HS2; and what the timetable is for the completion of phase 2.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180632","180632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989638","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to accept the recommendation of the Independent Monitoring Board report of 17 October 2018 on HMP Bedford to permit prisoners with a date for release to make an application for universal credit; and if he will discuss that recommendation with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180838","180838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989639","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the supply of epipens.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180734","180734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989640","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an estimate of the cost to (a) NHS trusts and (b) the public purse of transferring clinical waste management contracts from Healthcare Environment Services to Mitie at 15 NHS trusts.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180735","180735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989641","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to allocate funding to NHS trusts for the transfer of clinical waste management contracts from Healthcare Environment Services to Mitie, including any legal expenses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180736","180736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989642","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's target time is for processing applications for alternative payment arrangements under universal credit.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180774","180774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989643","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions he plans to make in the new asylum accommodation contracts to ensure that pregnant women and new mothers have access to adequate maternity care and advice.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180826","180826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989644","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October to Question 176311 on Offences Against Children: Sentencing, of the 3,234 people given custodial sentences in 2017 how many were (a) men and (b) women.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180742","180742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989645","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to page 4 of the 17 October 2018 Annual Report of the Independent Monitoring Board on HMP Bedford, if he will undertake a review of the role of local prisons.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180839","180839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989646","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to work with his counterparts from other countries to ensure that  global temperatures do not exceed 1.5 degrees C.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180662","180662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989647","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Minister for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation to the hon Member for Kettering of 11 October 2018 on Student Loan Book: Sale, Official Report, column 286, if he will (a) publish the range of estimates for the expected proceeds of the sale and (b) place in the Library a copy of the information shared with the hon. Member for Kettering.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180748","180748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989648","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the implications for the Government's policies of the Independent Monitoring Board's report of 17 October 2018 on HMP Bedford.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180840","180840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989649","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the mitigation measures agreed by HS2 Ltd to reduce the negative effect on biodiversity are (a) secured for the duration of the project and (b) monitored.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180775","180775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989650","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that High Speed Two does not cause the death of barn owls.","Biography information for Victoria Prentis","Victoria Prentis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180776","180776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989651","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 173935 on driving: licensing, what estimate he has made of the number of staff that will need to be recruited in order to meet increased demand for International Driving Permits in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180625","180625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989652","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 173935 on Driving: Licensing, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of International Driving Permits which will need to be issued in 2019-20, (b) individual cost of securing an International Driving Permit and (c) administrative cost of processing each application for an International Driving Permit in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180626","180626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989653","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Cabinet has held discussions on removing worker's rights that derive from EU law after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180641","180641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989654","2018-10-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect of exiting the EU without a deal on UK sellers of pre-owned software under the terms of the EU Directive on the Legal Protection of Computer Programs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180716","180716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989655","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the announcement, ESA Underpayments: Forecast Numbers Affected, Forecast Expenditure and Progress on Checking, published by her Department on 17 October 2018, what the reasons are for the delay in the estimated completion date of arrears payments to claimants of Employment and Support Allowance.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180651","180651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989656","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the factors that contributed to her Department's errors in calculating employment support allowance payments; and what procedures are being put into place to minimise the risk of further such errors.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180652","180652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989657","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of pensioners in receipt of free TV licences in each parliamentary constituency in Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180653","180653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989658","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the (a) amount of direct Government funding and (b) contribution from council tax through the police precept to each police force in England in each year from 2009 to 2016.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180740","180740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989659","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of whether the Government's plans for a skills-based immigration system after the UK leaves the EU will meet the skills requirements of the agri-food sector.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180695","180695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989660","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data Ofqual holds on IGCSE entries for (a) state-funded and (b) independent schools.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180741","180741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989661","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provisions will be in the new asylum accommodation contracts to ensure accommodation is safe for young children and infants before families are placed.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180827","180827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989662","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to ensure the continuation of the Single Electricity Market on the island of Ireland in the event that the UK leaves the EU Internal Energy Market.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180676","180676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989663","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the possibility of the UK remaining a member of the EU Internal Energy Market but not sharing a common rule-book with other members.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180677","180677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989664","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to discuss the human rights situation in Tibet with his Chinese counterpart as part of China's universal periodic review at the UN Human Rights Council on 6 November.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180821","180821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989665","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October to Question 176311, how many people were given prison sentences for child sexual abuse offences of (a) up to one year, (b) one to five years, (c) five to 10 years and (d) 10 years or more by plea in each year between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180743","180743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989666","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October to Question 176311, how many of the 3,234 people who were given prison sentences for child sexual abuse offences in 2017 had previously been convicted of other child sexual abuse offences.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180744","180744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989667","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department’s consultation on calorie labelling for food and drink served outside the home includes alcoholic drinks.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180670","180670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989668","2018-10-22","Wales Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, when the Government plans to publish its contingency plans for the transport network servicing trade and travel through Welsh ports to Ireland in the event that no deal is reached for the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180793","180793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989669","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of school teachers in England that are paid over £50,000 per annum.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180794","180794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989670","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of reported hate crime since January 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180795","180795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989671","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the import and export of urology devices to the UK of the UK not reaching a deal on the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180717","180717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989672","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that urology devices produced in the UK can continue to be sold in the EU without regulatory barriers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180718","180718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989673","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure the maintenance of frictionless trade in relation to medical devices after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180719","180719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989674","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that tariffs are not levied on the import of EU produced medical devices after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180720","180720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989675","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that there will be no disruption to the procurement of medical devices after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180721","180721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/989676","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the average amount of council tax is across the area of (a) the Shadow Dorset Unitary Authority and (b) the Christchurch, Poole and Bournemouth Shadow Authority for the purpose of his Department's approach to council tax harmonisation.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Sir Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180627","180627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/990282","2018-10-23","Home Office","2018-10-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the (a) effect on economic output of violence against women and girls and (b) total spending on public services to prevent and tackle that violence.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 181225","181225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/987831","2018-10-17","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of undertaking a review of the effectiveness of driving (a) offences and (b) penalties.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 179087","179087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988621","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the (a) duties and (b) responsibilities are for a Government Local Plan Inspector.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180140","180140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988622","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, under what circumstances a Government Local Plan Inspector is able to recommend the alteration of a Local Plan; and whether an inspector is able to recommend such an alteration when it will have an effect on the level of housing allocation in a locality.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180141","180141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988623","2018-10-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Objectively Assessed Need criteria includes population growth as a result of immigration.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180142","180142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988624","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what research funding the (a) UK Government and (b) EU have given (i) the University of Warwick and (ii) Coventry University in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180095","180095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988625","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the single use carrier bag charge; and whether he has plans to expand the scheme to other single use items.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180096","180096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988626","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of requests for exam re-marking for (a) GCSE, (b) BTEC, and (c) A-Level exams by students at (i) community and academy comprehensive schools, (ii) community and academy grammar schools, and (iii) private schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180097","180097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988627","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the adequacy of funding allocated to (a) Step Up to Social Work (b) other programmes that promote diversity in the social work profession; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180098","180098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988628","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce geographical variation in (a) funding and (b) performance between and within Cancer Alliances.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180311","180311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988629","2018-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is his policy to (a) reassess UK security (i) assistance to and (ii) co-operation with Governments that appoint individuals accused of involvement in torture to senior positions on security bodies and (b) withdraw that assistance when those allegations are deemed credible.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180063","180063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988630","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Department has made an assessment of adequacy of the injury and retirement data published by the Greyhound Board of Great Britain.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180246","180246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988631","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the number of instances where universal credit claimants have not received universal credit payments due to being paid every four weeks rather than per calendar month.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180312","180312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988632","2018-10-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of aesthetics of the built environment on people's quality of life.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180313","180313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988633","2018-10-18","Department for International Development","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of Israeli Government restrictions on the movement of goods into Gaza on UNWRA provided aid and humanitarian resources in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180314","180314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988634","2018-10-18","Department for International Development","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to educational support for Rohingya refugees in Myanmar and Bangladesh, in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180315","180315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988635","2018-10-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government's plans for the UK’s future trading relationship with the EU to provide the same level of access to the European Union as is currently provided to the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180316","180316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988636","2018-10-18","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if the Government will ensure the ongoing alignment of the six areas of cross-border cooperation set out in the Good Friday Agreement in the event that the backstop arrangement for the Northern Ireland border comes into force.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180317","180317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988638","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government plans for the European Convention on Human Rights to remain in force when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180064","180064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988639","2018-10-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to Eurostat, whether (a) the general public will lose access and (b) whether the UK Government will lose the ability to contribute when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180318","180318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988640","2018-10-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department (a) has taken and (b) plans to take to ensure that the Northern Ireland Boxing Association are included as a constituent part of GB Boxing; and what support the Government can provide for the Northern Ireland Boxing Association's application to join The International Boxing Association.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180211","180211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988641","2018-10-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to support boxers from Northern Ireland in representing boxing for (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180212","180212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988642","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has for the use of Article 6.4 of the Paris Climate Change Agreement in any alternative scheme to the EU Emissions Trading System after the UK leaves the EU to allow international greenhouse gas mitigation projects to count towards UK emission reduction targets.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180187","180187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988643","2018-10-18","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to replicate the provisions of Tier 2 visa requirements for EU students studying in the UK after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180251","180251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988644","2018-10-18","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing short-term visas for students from EU countries studying in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180252","180252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988645","2018-10-18","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect on the English language teaching industry in the UK of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180253","180253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988646","2018-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Government's press release of 14 October 2018 entitled Leading tech companies support code to strengthen security of internet-connected devices, what steps the Government plans to take against companies that do not abide by the voluntary code of practice.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180309","180309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988647","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will review the NICE appraisal methodology to take account of current challenges to combination treatments under the renegotiation of the pharmaceutical price regulation scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180156","180156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988648","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the proposed roll-out of universal credit in Liverpool Riverside constituency on the household finances of claimants of benefits in that constituency; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180103","180103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988649","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what power the Mayor of Greater Manchester has to franchise bus services; and whether the Government has provided additional funding to facilitate such franchising.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180276","180276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988650","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of bus journey usage in Greater Manchester in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180277","180277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988651","2018-10-18","Cabinet Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, to ask what steps his department has taken to ensure that central government Departments take account of social economic value under the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012 in public procurement.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180319","180319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988652","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether there is a timetable to return the former Collective Spirit Free School site to Oldham Council.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180278","180278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988653","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if the Government will provide additional funding to the Competition and Markets Authority.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180257","180257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988654","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the April 2018 Green Paper on Modernising Consumer Markets, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the mandatory participation in alternative dispute resolution being extended to cover non-regulated markets.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180258","180258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988655","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the UK Government will provide additional funding to National Trading Standards and Trading Standards Scotland.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180259","180259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988656","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the April 2018 Green Paper on Modernising  Consumer Markets, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to consumers who fail to cancel subscriptions following initial free trials; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180260","180260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988657","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of establishing an independent external organisation to review individual complaints about the (a) performance and (b) service provided by the Children and Family Court Advisory and Support Service.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180143","180143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988658","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 11 October 2018 on Immigration Health Surcharge, whether his Department has plans to publish the review of the evidence on the average cost to the NHS of treating surcharge payers.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180308","180308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988659","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish a list of the roles and responsibilities of (a) full-time and (b) part-time staff at the National County Lines Coordination Centre.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180086","180086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988660","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the recruitment and appointment process is for filling posts at the National County Lines Coordination Centre.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180087","180087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988661","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations he has received from (a) the National Crime Agency, (b) the Metropolitan Police, (c) the British Transport police, (d) any other arm of law enforcement, (e) local authorities and (f) charities and NGOs on reviewing the Modern Slavery Act 2015 and the way it is applied to county lines.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180088","180088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988662","2018-10-22","Department for International Development","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the amount of international aid funding allocated to properties at Khirbet al-Halawah that were demolished by Israeli forces; what (a) discussions she has had with her counterparts in the EU and (b) representations she has made to the Israeli Government on those demolitions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180249","180249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988663","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent meetings his Department has had with representatives of (a) Uber and (b) Airbnb on the county lines drug trade.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180089","180089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988664","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of potential changes to the level of high street retailing in the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180111","180111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988665","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications have been received from EU nationals for settled status; and how many of those applications (a) have been granted, (b) have been refused and (c) are awaiting a decision.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180101","180101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988666","2018-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the risk of flooding at properties neighbouring the Quaggy river  as a result of alterations to the flood defenses and construction of a school on the Bowring sports ground.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180085","180085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988667","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what timeframe has been set by his Department for the completion of security checks for immigration applications; and what steps his Department taken when that timeframe is not met.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180182","180182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988668","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2018 to Question 173578 on Local Government: Private Finance Initiative, how much funding his Department has allocated in the form of private finance initiative (a) grants and (b) credits to each local authority in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180183","180183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988669","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2018 to Question 176282 on Academies: Nottingham, for what reason (a) Park Vale Academy, (b) Bluecoat Academy (Aspley Lane), (c) Glenbrook Academy and (d) Springfield Academy were not included in the list provided in his Answer of 4 September 2018 to Question 167263 on Academies: Private Finance Initiative.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180184","180184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988670","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army Cadets there were in each year between 2007 and 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180112","180112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988671","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Sea Cadets there were in each year between 2007 and 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180113","180113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988672","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to Written Statement of 17 May 2018 on Energy Policy, HCWS690, what (a) methodology and (b) data were used by his Department for the statement that shale gas companies could make set payments to communities with shale developments for up to £10m.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180287","180287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988673","2018-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the adequacy of the recent treatment of road safety protesters by the Bangladeshi authorities in Dhaka.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180129","180129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988674","2018-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Bangladeshi Government on the recent treatment of road safety protesters in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180130","180130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988675","2018-10-18","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to engage with employers and community leaders in (a) Cornwall and (b) the South West on the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180247","180247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988676","2018-10-18","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the recommendations made by the Migration Advisory Committee in their recent report EEA migration in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180248","180248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988677","2018-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Bangladeshi Government on the restrictions to free speech enacted by that country's Digital Security Act and the effect of that Act on free and fair elections in that country.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180131","180131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988678","2018-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180065","180065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988679","2018-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure the safe release of the photographer Shahidul Alam from prison in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180132","180132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988680","2018-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180066","180066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988681","2018-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has plans to allocate additional funding for mobility payments to children under the age of three in 2019; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180219","180219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988682","2018-10-18","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180067","180067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988683","2018-10-18","Department for International Development","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between her Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of her Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180068","180068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988684","2018-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180069","180069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988685","2018-10-18","Department for International Trade","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180070","180070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988686","2018-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of electronic voting on voter fraud in the upcoming election in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180133","180133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988687","2018-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180071","180071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988688","2018-10-18","Cabinet Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180072","180072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988689","2018-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage (a) free and fair elections and (b) political activism in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180134","180134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988690","2018-10-18","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180073","180073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988691","2018-10-18","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180074","180074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988692","2018-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Bangladeshi counterpart on proposals to move Rohingya refugees to Bhasan Char island.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180135","180135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988693","2018-10-18","Scotland Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180075","180075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988694","2018-10-18","Wales Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180076","180076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988695","2018-10-18","Attorney General","2018-10-16","To ask the Attorney General, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180077","180077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988696","2018-10-18","Department for International Development","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding the Government has allocated to promote (a) freedom of expression, (b) rights to peaceful protest and (c) democratic engagement in Bangladesh in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180136","180136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988697","2018-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether gagging clauses have been used in contracts drawn up between his Department and any charities, voluntary sector organisations, social enterprises or companies with the intention of stopping any criticism of Ministers of his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180078","180078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988698","2018-10-18","Department for International Development","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the terms and conditions are for the provision of aid to Bangladesh to promote human rights and freedom of expression; and what steps the Government is taking to ensure compliance with those terms and conditions.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180137","180137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988699","2018-10-18","Department for International Development","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the value for money of the provision of development assistance to Bangladesh for freedom of expression and political engagement.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180138","180138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988700","2018-10-18","Department for International Development","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the progress of the strengthening political participation phase two aid project in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180139","180139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988701","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Minister for the Middle East of 4 July 2018, Official Report, column 333, on the demolition of Khan al-Ahmar, what progress he has made on the investigation.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180244","180244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988702","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to increase access to the natural gas network in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180144","180144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988703","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with representatives of European car manufacturing companies on their plans to retain manufacturing bases in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180145","180145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988704","2018-10-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he plans to respond to the letter of 12 April 2018 from British in Europe.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180175","180175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988705","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to encourage school leavers to start up their own business ventures.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180146","180146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988706","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many windfarms were built in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180147","180147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988707","2018-10-18","Department for International Trade","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on the UK trading on WTO terms after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180148","180148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988708","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many examining boards are using the (a) A* to E and (b) numeral grading system.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180149","180149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988709","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many fines were issued to parents for taking their children out of school during term time in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180150","180150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988710","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to increase funding for after school activities.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180151","180151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988711","2018-10-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2018 to Question 171404 on Research: EU Grants and Loans, whether it is Government policy to include association to the Ninth EU Framework programme in the framework for the future relationship with the European Union.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180176","180176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988712","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students resat their (a) maths and (b) English GCSEs in the academic year 2017-18.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180152","180152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988713","2018-10-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 27 September 2018 to Question 171405, in which negotiation rounds science and innovation has been discussed since March 2018; and in which forthcoming rounds science and innovation will be discussed.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180177","180177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988714","2018-10-18","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to increase personal income tax allowances for lower rate taxpayers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180153","180153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988715","2018-10-18","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of over-payments by HMRC to claimants in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180154","180154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988716","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding available to local authorities for specialist education services for deaf children.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180286","180286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988717","2018-10-18","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many parents in Northern Ireland applied for tax free childcare in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180155","180155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988718","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made a comparative assessment of the effect on the revenue that has accrued to the public purse of other EU countries of the introduction of a deferred payment of capital gains tax for trusts ceasing to be resident or non-resident individuals who trade through a national branch or agency.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180290","180290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988719","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what has been the annual cost to the public purse of section 187 of the Taxation of Chargeable Gains Act 1992 for each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180291","180291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988720","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the provision of specialised nursing care for people with secondary breast cancer in (a) East Sussex and (b) Brighton and Hove.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180266","180266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988721","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has accrued to the public purse each year as a result of the implementation of Chapter 8, Part 6A of the Taxation (International and Other Provisions) Act 2010.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180292","180292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988722","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made a comparative assessment of the effect on the revenue that has accrued to the public purse of other EU countries of the implementation of Council Directive (EU) 2017/1852 on tax dispute resolution mechanisms in the European Union.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180293","180293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988723","2018-10-22","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the Government plans to participate after the UK has left the EU in (a) EU Directive 2018/822 and (b) other agreements that facilitate the disclosure of information pertaining to cross-border tax arrangements.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180294","180294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988724","2018-10-18","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for indefinite leave to remain were made by Tier 1 migrants in the last 12 months; and how many of those applications were declined.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180306","180306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988725","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of people with multiple sclerosis in the Stroud constituency are no longer eligible for the higher rate of mobility support as a result of the transition from disability living allowance in each year since the introduction of personal independence payment.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180092","180092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988726","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","‘To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many subject access requests have been made to GP surgeries since the introduction of the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180307","180307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988727","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to introduce a paternity allowance for self-employed fathers.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180283","180283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988728","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of emergency admissions to NHS trusts in England from people over 65 years of age within 28 days of discharge in each financial year from 2013-14 to 2017-18.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180194","180194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988729","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will estimate the number of emergency admissions among people aged over 80 within 28 days of their discharge from hospital by NHS trust for each calendar year from 2013 to 2018.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180195","180195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988730","2018-10-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on how much and what proportion of the Revenue Account Budget (a) in total and (b) per smoker was allocated to stop smoking services and interventions by each local authority in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180196","180196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988731","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many sites providing NHS stop smoking services have (a) closed and (b) stopped providing such services by local authority in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180197","180197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988732","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the smoking quit rate was in (a) England, (b) each local authority, (c) each parliamentary constituency and (d) each clinical commissioning group area in England in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180198","180198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988733","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the smoking quit rate was for (a) BAME communities, (b) people living with mental health conditions and (c) people with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180199","180199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988734","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the smoking quit rate for people earning (a) £10,000 per annum or less, (b) £10,001 to £20,000 per annum, (c) £20,001 to £30,000 per annum, (d) £30,001 to £40,000 per annum and (e) £40,001 per annum and over in England in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180200","180200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988735","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the smoking prevalence for people earning (a) £10,000 per annum or less, (b) £10,001 to £20,000 per annum, c) £20,001 to £30,000 per annum, d) £30,001 to £40,000 per annum and e) £40,001 and over in England in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180201","180201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988736","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the smoking prevalence for (a) pregnant women, (b) people with mental health conditions, (c) people with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease and (d) BAME communities in (i) England and (ii) each local authority in England in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180202","180202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988737","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes in the level of funding for smoking cessation services on health inequalities.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180203","180203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988738","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Public Health England's document, Stop smoking options: guidance for conversations with patients, published on 20 August 2018, what evidence Public Health England assessed to inform its recommendation that E-cigarettes can help people quit smoking, with similar or better results than NRT.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180204","180204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988739","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation has made of the potential change in the number of cases of pneumococcal disease that will result from its advice to reduce a dose in the national infant pneumococcal programme from a 2+1 to a 1+1 schedule; and if he will publish the modelling used for that estimate.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180205","180205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988741","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation will publish the modelling and methodology used to support its view that there will be a small increase in cases of pneumococcal disease resulting from reducing a dose in the national infant pneumococcal programme; and how many additional cases of pneumococcal disease that committee considers acceptable.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180206","180206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988742","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of the Office for National Statistics' conclusions that there are 12,400 full-time direct jobs in nuclear energy reprocessing and generation in the UK.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180093","180093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988744","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether there are plans to review guidance on the licensing and availability of co-proxamol.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180284","180284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988745","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to encourage people to check their national insurance contribution records in advance of their retirement.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180122","180122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988747","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish the outcome of his Department's call for evidence on corporate liability for economic crime.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180123","180123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988748","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to faulty engines of the Ford Ecoboost, what steps the Office of Product Safety and Standards plans to take to support both the recall of that vehicle and consumers that have been affected.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180279","180279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988750","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which projects on business and human rights his Department has funded in each of the last five years; and what the total spend of each such project was in each of those years.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180124","180124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988752","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which projects on business and human rights his Department has funded in each of the last five years; and what the total spend of each such project was in each of those years.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180125","180125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988753","2018-10-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions there have been under the Sexual Offences Act 2003 in relation to arrangements where sex has been requested in return for accommodation in the City of Bristol.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180285","180285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988755","2018-10-18","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will ensure that the six areas of cross-border cooperation outlined in the Good Friday Agreement continue to be aligned in the event of a no-deal scenario.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180079","180079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988756","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the membership of the (a) Maritime 2050 panel and (b) Clean Maritime Council.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180163","180163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988758","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the (a) staffing and (b) funding levels required by the Maritime and Coastguard Agency to ensure compliance with International Maritime Organisation regulations for monitoring, verification and reporting of (i) sulphur dioxide, (ii) carbon dioxide and (iii) greenhouse gas emissions from (A) UK and (B) international registered merchant shipping in each year from 2018-19 to 2022-23.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180164","180164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988759","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the UK Government delegation to the 73rd meeting of the International Maritime Organisation’s Marine Environment Protection Committee in London 22-26 October 2018.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180165","180165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988761","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to review the operation of the three-year ratings training pilot introduced in the Tonnage Tax (Training Requirement) (Amendment) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180166","180166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988762","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many shipping companies have trained UK ratings as a result of the introduction of the pilot scheme in the Tonnage Tax (Training Requirement) (Amendment) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180167","180167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988764","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many UK ratings were trained by Tonnage Tax qualifying companies using the three-year pilot scheme introduced in the Tonnage Tax (Training Requirement) (Amendment) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180168","180168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988765","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to update the Maritime 2050 strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180169","180169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988767","2018-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of closing HMP Bedford and transferring prisoners to HMP Wellingborough when it is operational.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180281","180281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988768","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) positive and (b) negative Conclusive Grounds decisions were made to potential victims of human trafficking after referral to the National Referral Mechanism and the 45 day reflection period in each quarter of 2017.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180185","180185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988770","2018-10-18","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the average response time to dwelling fires by the Greater Manchester Fire and Rescue Service in each year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180117","180117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988771","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the NHS plans to take to tackle barriers to access to primary care for Gypsy, Roma and Traveller communities in the long term plan for the NHS.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180186","180186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988772","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the merits of the possible guiding principles set out in the final report of the 2018 Group of Governmental Experts on emerging technologies in the area of lethal autonomous weapons.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180126","180126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988774","2018-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the remit of the forthcoming Centre for Data Ethics and Innovation will include the role of artificial intelligence in autonomous weapons systems.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180127","180127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988775","2018-10-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on the potential risks associated with the creation of lethal autonomous weapons systems.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180128","180128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988776","2018-10-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department allocated from the early intervention grant to projects in Nottinghamshire in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180301","180301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988777","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve outcomes for children with special educational needs.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180302","180302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988778","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to support trials of new biometric technologies at UK airports.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180254","180254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988779","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect on reducing immigration queuing times at airports allowing passengers from five eyes partner countries to use ePassport gates would have.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180255","180255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988780","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will reverse the recent reduction in public health grants to local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180157","180157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988781","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will reverse the reductions made to local authority public health budgets since 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180158","180158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988782","2018-10-22","Northern Ireland Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many times the British Irish Council have met since January 2017.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180114","180114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988783","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the effect on rural households in Northern Ireland of recent trends in the level of gas prices.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180192","180192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988784","2018-10-18","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2018 to Question 177328 on Bank Services, what plans his Department has to reduce the number of unbanked people in the UK.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180090","180090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988785","2018-10-18","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance (a) his Department and (b) HMRC issue to small businesses to ensure the accurate completion of tax returns.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180193","180193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988786","2018-10-18","Treasury","2018-10-16","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent meetings (a) he, (b) other Ministers and (c) staff of his Department have had with the FinTech industry on reducing the number of unbanked people in the UK.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180091","180091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988787","2018-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that alternative payment arrangements are put in place as soon as possible to avoid rent arrears for tenants and a loss of income for landlords and agents.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180174","180174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988788","2018-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of banning (a) the keeping of primates as pets and (b) the sale of primates as pets.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180094","180094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988789","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the speech entitled Damian Hinds speech at Confederation of School Trusts conference, published by his Department on 11 October 2018, for what reasons parts of that speech have been redacted on the gov.uk website; and who took the decision to redact sections of that speech.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180288","180288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988790","2018-10-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many foreign nationals received training at the Royal Military Academy Sandhurst in each year between 2005 and 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180289","180289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988791","2018-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what strategy his Department has to tackle the use of synthetic cannabinoids in prisons.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180298","180298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988792","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Written Statement of 10 October 2018 on Government Asset Sale, HCWS979, what book value his Department has placed on the student loans to be sold in the second sale.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180208","180208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988793","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 December 2017 on Government Asset Sale, HCWS317, what estimate he has made of what the minimum price for the sale was that would have achieved value for money according to HM Treasury Green Book rules.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180209","180209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988794","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 December 2017 on Government Asset Sale, HCWS317, if he will publish the full value for money assessment undertaken in this asset sale; and what the the evidential basis was for his Department’s conclusion that the sale represented value for money according to HM Treasury Green Book rules.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180210","180210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988795","2018-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to protect and support prison staff from abuse.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180299","180299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988796","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date universal credit is planned to be fully rolled out and operational.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180213","180213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988797","2018-10-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the change has been to his Department's budget in real terms in each year since 2010; and what the projected real terms changes are for each year to 2022.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180218","180218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988798","2018-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to support prisoners who have mental health issues; and whether his Department has plans to expand the provision of such support.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180300","180300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988799","2018-10-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment assessment results have been overturned on appeal.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180214","180214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988800","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2018 to Question 170362 on Employment, whether he accepts all of the recommendations of the Carnegie Trust report referenced in that Answer; and what plans he has to implement the recommendations from the Carnegie Trust report.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180226","180226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988801","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2018 to Question 170362 on Employment, what discussions he has had with the Office for National Statistics on the collection of job quality data.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180227","180227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988802","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2018 to Question 170362 on Employment, what steps he has taken to develop a minimum job quality standard.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180228","180228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988803","2018-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2018 to Question 170362 on Employment, if he will establish an implementation group to support and advise on the delivery and development of the recommendations and proposals set out in the Carnegie Trust report referenced in his Answer.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180229","180229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988804","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers were employed in primary schools in each parliamentary constituency in Cheshire West and Chester in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180230","180230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988805","2018-10-18","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants were employed in primary schools in each parliamentary constituency in Cheshire West and Chester in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180231","180231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988806","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department has on the number of complaints that have been made on sales reps in maternity units in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180232","180232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988808","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will list all the services directly commissioned by NHS England.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180233","180233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988809","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which hospitals he has visited since taking his position.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180234","180234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988811","2018-10-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, through what mechanism his Department monitors how Local Enterprise Partnership's spend money from the public purse; and how his Department evaluates the results of that spending.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180235","180235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988812","2018-10-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what mechanisms are in place to prevent conflicts of interest among Local Enterprise Partnership board members.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180236","180236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988814","2018-10-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how the members of the Government's panel on the future of the high street were selected.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180237","180237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988815","2018-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many( a) successful and (b) unsuccessful employment tribunal claims for automatically unfair dismissal under sections 99-108 of the Employment Rights Act 1996 have been brought in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180238","180238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988817","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which stakeholders he met with during his visit to Leeds Bradford Airport on 2 August 2018.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180239","180239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988818","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the trends in the (a) quantity and (b) frequency of bus services in (a) Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency and (b) England since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180240","180240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988820","2018-10-18","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many supported bus services there have been in Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180241","180241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988821","2018-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the longest length of time was for a claimant of universal credit in Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency to receive an initial payment.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180242","180242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988823","2018-10-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect on the local environment of fracking.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180215","180215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988824","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of fixed-period exclusions in secondary schools in (a) the North East of England and (b) England.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180188","180188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988825","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) exclusions and (b) instances of off-rolling in school year (a) ten and (b) eleven there were in the North East of England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180189","180189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988826","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support pupils who have been excluded from secondary school to access (a) apprenticeships and (b) other forms of post-16 training.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180190","180190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988827","2018-10-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to support initiatives to bring an end to the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180216","180216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988828","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, a) what estimate he has made of the amount of unspent funds in employers’ accounts under the Apprenticeship Levy; for what reasons those funds remain unspent; and whether he has plans to extend the period of time within which levy-paying employers can use those funds.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180191","180191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988829","2018-10-22","Department for International Development","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has taken to support people in Yemen affected by the conflict in that country.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180217","180217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988830","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2018 to Question 176272 on Drugs: Imports, if he will place in the Library a copy of the non-disclosure agreements his Department has requested pharmaceutical companies to sign.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180178","180178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988831","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the evidential basis was for the request to pharmaceutical companies to increase stocks of medicines by six weeks in August 2018; and what recent estimate he has made of the length of time that there will be border disruption in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180179","180179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988832","2018-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2017 to Question 120296, what representations (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have received from (i) the Agricultural Biotechnology Council and (ii) manufacturers of genetically modified seed products on reducing the level of regulation of such products after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180159","180159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988833","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the number of pharmaceutical companies that have not agreed to stockpile medicines in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180180","180180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988834","2018-10-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2018 to Question 176274 on Drugs, when the Government plans to complete its consideration of the support that may be provided to suppliers in relation to the stockpiling of medicines; for what reasons that process was not completed before the Government advised suppliers to increase their stockpile of medicines; what assessment he has made of the effect on the supply of drugs of not providing that support; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180181","180181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988835","2018-10-22","Department for Education","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress he has made on appointing the Chair of the Independent Review into the Teaching Excellence Framework.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180102","180102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988836","2018-10-22","Department for Transport","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the change has been to his Department's budget in real terms in each year since 2010; and what the projected change will be in real terms in each year to 2022.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180207","180207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988837","2018-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the spread of myxomatosis on the brown hare population in the UK.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180274","180274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988839","2018-10-18","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to tackle hare coursing.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180275","180275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988840","2018-10-18","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many firefighter posts there were in the Greater Manchester Fire and Rescue Service in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15, (c) 2015-16, (d) 2016-17 and (e) 2017-18.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180118","180118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988842","2018-10-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that end of life patients are able to die at home.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180295","180295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988844","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the criteria used by (a) UK Visas and Immigration and (b) providers of asylum accommodation to assess the vulnerability of tenants.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180296","180296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988845","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the medical research sector will be able to recruit talented overseas professions through the immigration system that will be introduced after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180160","180160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/988847","2018-10-22","Home Office","2018-10-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what processes are in place to ensure that (a) service users and (b) advocates of service users are able to challenge refusals to relocate them to a different property under the new (i) Asylum Accommodation and Support and Advice and (ii) Issue Reporting and Eligibility Support contracts.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 180297","180297"
