"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431723","2015-11-26","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the sexual health component of the proposed public health funding formula does not use indicators relating to sexually transmitted infection rates.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17380","17380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431724","2015-11-26","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what weighting has been applied (a) to the sparsity indicator within the children's 0 to 5 services component relative to that for other components and (b) to address complex need within that component.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17381","17381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431725","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to prepare for the junior doctors' strikes due to commence on 1 December 2015; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect of such strikes on NHS services.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17291","17291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431726","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications his Department has received for the (a) Innovation Excellence and Strategic Development Fund and (b) Health and Social Care Volunteering Fund; and when he plans to announce the 2015-16 grant allocations from those funds.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17376","17376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431727","2015-11-26","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential proportion of local authorities which will experience (a) any reduction in their allocation and (b) a reduction of 20 per cent or more in their allocation as a result of the new proposed public health funding formula.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17382","17382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431728","2015-11-26","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the new proposed public health funding formula will be linked to an assessment of deprivation and greatest need in order to determine the allocation that different local authority areas receive; and what steps his Department is taking otherwise to ensure that areas of greatest need are not disproportionately affected by overall reductions in public health allocations.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17383","17383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431729","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with health bodies on ensuring timely treatment for people with alcohol-related illnesses.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17324","17324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431730","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what campaigns he plans to implement over the Christmas period in 2015 to draw public attention to the dangers of drinking and driving.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17325","17325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431731","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to prioritise (a) looked-after children and (b) other vulnerable groups within his Department's children and young people's mental health budget over the next five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17375","17375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431732","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children aged under 18 have visited A&E departments as a result of alcohol-related harm in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17319","17319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431733","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of children and adolescents admitted to hospital for alcohol-related illnesses and injuries.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17318","17318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431734","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will take steps at EU level to encourage better labelling of alcoholic drinks by providing (a) uniform information about strength and calorie content, (b) guidelines on safe drinking levels and (c) health warnings.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17320","17320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431735","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote alcohol treatment and counselling options that will help to prevent alcohol-related crime.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17321","17321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431736","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support children and families who are affected by alcohol abuse or harm.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17322","17322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431737","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to improve awareness of the health implications of drinking during pregnancy.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17323","17323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431738","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received about funding allocated by his Department to the organisation Action on Smoking and Health.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17348","17348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431739","2015-11-26","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he had with EMIS Health on data protection.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17384","17384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431740","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual budget of the tobacco policy team in his Department is; and what proportion of that budget was spent on external grants or contracts in the last year.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17349","17349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431741","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to encourage higher donor registration among (a) all people and (b) mixed ethnicity donors to the UK stem cell and bone marrow register.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17359","17359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431742","2015-11-26","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS England spent per head on mental health in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17404","17404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431743","2015-12-01","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason callers to the International Enquiry Service of UK Visas and Immigration are charged £1.37 per minute.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17393","17393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431744","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken and plans to take to ensure that out of city areas are adequately defended and protected from a repetition of the recent attacks in Paris.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17386","17386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431745","2015-12-01","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy for the free email service offered by the International Enquiry Service automatically to acknowledge safe receipt of messages sent to it by enquirers.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17394","17394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431746","2015-12-01","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what remedy exists for enquirers whose electronic communications with the International Enquiry Service are not answered.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17395","17395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431747","2015-12-01","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the webchat service offered by the International Enquiry Service has been unavailable when required by enquirers.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17396","17396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431748","2015-12-01","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy not to levy telephone charges for enquirers to the International Enquiry Service in addition to the standard rate until such time as the free alternative methods of contacting the organisation are working reliably.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17397","17397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431749","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of foreign nationals convicted of a crime in the UK were deported to their country of origin in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17388","17388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431750","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward proposals to introduce stricter UK border controls similar to those introduced by the French government following the recent Paris attacks.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17335","17335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431751","2015-11-26","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the efficiency of West Midlands Police.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17367","17367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431752","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were charged with drink-driving in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17327","17327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431753","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the proportion of crimes committed under the influence of alcohol in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17326","17326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431754","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with Brittany Ferries on the carriage of game birds on their ships.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17252","17252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431755","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to expand the role of the National Crime Agency in (a) West Africa and (b) the Sahel region.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17293","17293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431756","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many counter-terrorism personnel were employed in the West Midlands in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17296","17296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431757","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on the introduction of a 10 year firearms licence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17251","17251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431758","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on whether there are any police investigations into the involvement of the (a) UK intelligence and security agencies and (b) Government in the alleged rendition and torture of detainees.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17298","17298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431759","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2015 to Question 15363, what assessments she has made of the capacity of traffic police to enforce fixed-penalty notices for the traffic offences relating to use of mobile telephones.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17242","17242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431760","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the final file concerning the Metropolitan Police Service investigation known as Operation Lydd has been passed to the Crown Prosecution Service.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17299","17299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431761","2015-11-26","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what timetable she plans to set for ratification of the Istanbul Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women and Domestic Violence.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17189","17189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431762","2015-11-26","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 14607, what the evidential basis is for the assertion on page 8 of the consultation document, Tackling Exploitation in the Labour Market, published in October 2015, that there has been a shift from abuses of employment regulation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17158","17158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431763","2015-11-25","Department for International Development","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to ensure that the additional £40 million of aid her Department allocated in June 2015 to Yemen benefits its intended recipients.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17201","17201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431764","2015-11-26","Department for International Development","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her is taking to monitor the effectiveness of her Department's aid spending in Nepal.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17218","17218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431765","2015-11-25","Department for International Development","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department plans to ensure that data is collected on stateless children so that such children can be taken into account in measuring progress in achieving the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17195","17195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431766","2015-11-26","Department for International Development","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether conditions regarding respect for human rights are attached to aid funds provided to the government of Nepal.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17368","17368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431767","2015-11-25","Department for International Development","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the security situation in Yemen on the ability of non-governmental organisations to operate and deliver aid in that country.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17341","17341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431768","2015-11-25","Department for International Development","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment the Government has made of (a) the condition of the port infrastructure at Hodeida in Yemen and (b) Hodeida's ability to function as a port for the purpose of delivering and unloading international aid.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17342","17342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431769","2015-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many remote sites (a) are operational to enable witnesses to give evidence away from court, (b) were available for use by children under the age of 18 in 2014-15 and (c) were used by children under the age of 18 in that year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17345","17345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431770","2015-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure that fewer children who have been subject to abuse need to attend court to give evidence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17344","17344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431771","2015-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children under the age of (a) 13 and (b) 18 gave evidence from a (i) remote site and (ii) court building in 2014-15.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17346","17346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431772","2015-11-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is his policy to allow members of the public to make an application for a cremation in Welsh.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17308","17308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431773","2015-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made on the provision of remote sites from which children and young people can give evidence other than in a court building.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17248","17248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431774","2015-11-25","Department of Health","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of prisoners are identified as having an alcoholic disorder.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17328","17328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431775","2015-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sexual offences in which the offender was under the influence of alcohol were recorded in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17329","17329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431776","2015-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many case conferences have resulted in the reallocation of transgender prisoners to a prison which corresponds with the gender with which they self-identify in the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17377","17377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431777","2015-11-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to answer Question 13072, on Ministry of Justice: Departmental Responsibilities, tabled by the hon. Member for Hammersmith on 22 October 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17271","17271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431778","2015-11-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish information about the number of trans people in prison.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17215","17215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431779","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2015 to Question 15363, how many drivers incurred a fixed-penalty charge for using a mobile telephone at the wheel in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17243","17243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431780","2015-11-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many remote sites are operational to enable witnesses to give evidence away from court; in which areas such sites are located; how many such sites are available to children under the age of 18; and how many such sites have been used by children under the age of 18.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17247","17247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431781","2015-11-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Northern Ireland of 18 November 2015, Official Report, what steps her Department is taking to support military veterans who served in Northern Ireland in 1972.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17235","17235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431782","2015-11-25","Prime Minister","2015-11-23","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with the Chair of the Intelligence and Security Committee on the progress of its inquiry into the role of the Government and intelligence and security agencies in the alleged rendition and torture of detainees.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17297","17297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431783","2015-11-25","Prime Minister","2015-11-23","To ask the Prime Minister, (a) whether the RAF Voyager aircraft being refitted for ministerial travel has been leased to the Government, (b) what the capacity of that aircraft was before it was refitted and (c) what the cost of Prime Ministerial air travel has been since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17184","17184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431784","2015-11-25","Prime Minister","2015-11-23","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he had with his Indian counterpart during his recent visit on the death of Sikh people at the Golden Temple in Amritsar in June 1984.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17152","17152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431785","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will ring-fence revenue raised from the HGV Levy for investment in transport infrastructure.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17179","17179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431786","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will ring-fence funding for walking and cycling.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17207","17207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431787","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the traffic commissioners in enforcing bus service reliability and punctuality.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17180","17180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431788","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the trends in the number of bus reliability public inquiries held by the traffic commissioners since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17181","17181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431789","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress the traffic commissioners have made on reviewing and modernising the regulation of commercial vehicle drivers.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17182","17182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431790","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward proposals to amend the Civil Enforcement of Parking Contraventions (England) Representations and Appeals Regulations 2007 to enable the adjudicator to make an order awarding costs and expenses to appellants in successful parking appeals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17277","17277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431791","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what timetable he has set for the sale of the Vehicle and Operator Services Agency testing station in Ennerdale Road, Shrewsbury.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17378","17378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431792","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cars the DVLA clamped in each month of each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17350","17350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431793","2015-11-25","Department for Transport","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make contingency plans for delivery by bodies other than Network Rail of Control Period 5 projects that the Hendy Review determines to be undeliverable and which are necessary in order to realise the full benefit of the introduction of AT300 trains to the South West peninsula.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17347","17347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431794","2015-11-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with the National Offender Management Service on the implementation of guidelines on the care and management of transsexual prisoners.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17276","17276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431795","2015-11-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward proposals to amend the Gender Recognition Act 2004 to remove the requirement for a diagnosis of gender dysphoria as a pre-requisite for obtaining legal gender recognition.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17302","17302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431796","2015-11-26","Women and Equalities","2015-11-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she took steps to mark Transgender Awareness Week and Transgender Remembrance Day.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17303","17303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431797","2015-11-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward proposals to speed up the process for obtaining a Gender Recognition Certificate.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17220","17220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431798","2015-11-26","Women and Equalities","2015-11-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she plans to take to raise awareness of the prejudice against transgender people.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17221","17221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431799","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to ensure that there will be sufficient childcare places in place by April 2017 for pre-school aged children of parents who will be expected to seek work from that date under the provisions of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17265","17265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431800","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial and advisory assistance his Department offers to businesses to encourage them to employ, train and support people with physical and learning disabilities.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17267","17267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431801","2015-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure adequate expertise in local housing market conditions among staff administering universal credit in jobcentres.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17300","17300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431802","2015-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of (a) disabled people aged (i) under 25 and (ii) under 30 who participated in apprenticeships and (b) apprenticeships undertaken by disabled people in each of those age groups in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17196","17196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431803","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claiming which benefit have been referred to Help to Work since April 2014.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17198","17198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431804","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's policy is on the maximum travelling time for applicants to personal independence payment assessments; and what proportion of such assessments have complied with that maximum time in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17197","17197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431805","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of sanctions on employment outcomes for people with disabilities.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17192","17192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431806","2015-11-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will fund training costs of disabled apprentices aged 18 to 24 in accordance with the recommendations of Creating an inclusive apprenticeship offer, commissioned by the Apprenticeships Unit and published in January 2012.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17194","17194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431807","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions Ministers in his Department have had with representatives of mental health charities on the design of contracts for new welfare to work schemes.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17159","17159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431808","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what timetable his Department has set for drawing up contracts for new welfare to work schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17160","17160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431809","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many hours each week Jobcentre Plus work coaches are expected to spend with each participant in the Mandatory Intervention Regime under the Help to Work scheme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17161","17161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431810","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times participants in the Mandatory Intervention Regime under the Help to Work scheme are required to attend appointments at Jobcentre Plus each week.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17162","17162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431811","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether participants in Daily Work Search Review under the Help to Work scheme are set quotas for completing a minimum number of job applications.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17163","17163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431812","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what organisations are providers of Community Work Placements under the Help to Work scheme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17164","17164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431813","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of participants in (a) the Mandatory Intervention Regime, (b) Community Work Placements and (c) Daily Work Search Review under the Help to Work scheme have been sanctioned since April 2014.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17165","17165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431814","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) start fees, (b) short placement completion fees, (c) long placement completion fees and (d) job outcome fees have been paid to providers of Community Work Placements under the Help to Work scheme since April 2014.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17166","17166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431815","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to maintain a separate programme of employment support for people with disabilities after the end of the current contracts for the Work Programme and Work Choice.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17167","17167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431816","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans that referral to welfare to work schemes will be voluntary for people with disabilities after the end of the current contracts for the Work Programme and Work Choice.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17168","17168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431817","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of (a) referrals to the Work Programme since 2011 and (b) current participants in the Work Programme had no classifiable qualifications at the time of their referral.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17169","17169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431818","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people referred to the Work Programme since 2011 who had no classifiable qualifications at the time of their referral achieved a qualification before leaving that programme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17170","17170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431819","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people referred to Help to Work since April 2014 who have participated in (a) Community Work Placements and (b) Daily Work Search Review have subsequently been referred to the Mandatory Intervention Regime.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17171","17171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431820","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people referred to Help to Work since April 2014 have left the scheme after opening a claim for working tax credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17190","17190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431821","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people referred to Help to Work scheme since April 2014 have left the scheme after a job outcome fee was paid to the relevant provider.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17191","17191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431822","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people with alcohol-related problems who would be affected by the Government's proposals to withhold sickness benefits from people who refuse treatment.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17330","17330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431823","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people referred to the Work Programme since 2011 who had no classable qualifications at the time of their referral achieved a job outcome at any stage during their time on the Work Programme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17373","17373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431824","2015-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of the forms of his Department's website are available in Welsh.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17307","17307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431825","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on people who receive disability benefits being able to volunteer without it affecting their entitlement to those benefits.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17354","17354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431826","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department has set for referral to (a) Community Work Placements and (b) Daily Work Search Review once a claimant has joined the Help to Work scheme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17353","17353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431827","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to amend the three month rule for the habitual residence test to allow access to income based jobseeker's allowance for UK nationals returning to the UK after a period away who have retained financial commitments at home.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17352","17352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431828","2015-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of jobcentres have a private room in which Improving Access to Psychological Therapies services can take place.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17403","17403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431829","2015-11-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the ability of employees paid weekly to meet their living costs in the period between becoming unemployed and receiving their first payment of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17408","17408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431903","2015-11-26","Attorney General","2015-11-23","To ask the Attorney General, what recent steps the Crown Prosecution Service has taken to improve the conviction rate for rape and domestic violence.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902353","902353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432469","2015-11-26","Attorney General","2015-11-23","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with the Prime Minister on the information provided to Parliament on the legal basis for supporting coalition air strikes in Syria.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902357","902357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432470","2015-11-26","Attorney General","2015-11-23","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he has taken to promote pro bono work amongst members of the legal profession in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902355","902355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432471","2015-11-26","Women and Equalities","2015-11-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with her ministerial colleagues on the effect of the increase in the state pension age on women.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902395","902395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432472","2015-11-26","Women and Equalities","2015-11-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with her ministerial colleagues on the effect of the increase in the state pension age on women.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902391","902391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432473","2015-11-26","Women and Equalities","2015-11-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to raise girls' aspirations in schools.","Biography information for Amanda Solloway","Amanda Solloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902393","902393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432474","2015-11-26","Women and Equalities","2015-11-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to tackle race inequality.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902392","902392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432475","2015-11-26","Women and Equalities","2015-11-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of women taking up apprenticeships.","Biography information for Amanda Milling","Amanda Milling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902394","902394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/432476","2015-11-26","Women and Equalities","2015-11-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to reduce gender economic inequality.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902396","902396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431368","2015-11-24","Cabinet Office","2015-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 12011, when the consultation on making property ownership by foreign companies more transparent will begin.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17111","17111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431369","2015-11-24","Cabinet Office","2015-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the vulnerability of the UK's critical infrastructure from cyber attack; and what investment his Department is making to improve the security of the UK's critical infrastructure from such attacks.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17118","17118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431370","2015-11-24","Cabinet Office","2015-11-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how his Department is monitoring the implementation of the family test across Government.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17142","17142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431371","2015-11-24","HM Treasury","2015-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people making use of new pension freedoms have sought professional, regulated financial advice since April 2015.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17096","17096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431372","2015-11-24","HM Treasury","2015-11-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the local economy of the closure of the HM Revenue and Customs office in Shipley; and if he will place a copy of that assessment in the Library.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17099","17099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431373","2015-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department will meet the revised December 2015 target for upgrading air defence radars at RRH Benbecula and RRH Buchan to the TPS-77 radar standard.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17092","17092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431374","2015-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to communicate to local authorities and developers of onshore wind renewables projects the effect of the time taken to upgrade air defence radars at RRH Benbecula and RRH Buchan.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17093","17093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431375","2015-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the reasons are for the time taken to upgrade air defence radars at RRH Benbecula and RRH Buchan to the TPS-77 radar standard.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17094","17094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431376","2015-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what operational assessment has been undertaken of proposals to use the upgraded TPS-77 radar systems at RRH Benbecula and RRH Buchan as mitigation for planned wind turbine developments.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17105","17105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431377","2015-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the development of Watchkeeper.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17136","17136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431378","2015-11-24","Department for Education","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the planned move to a numeric GCSE grading system in England on the comparability and portability of GCSE results in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17143","17143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431379","2015-11-24","Department for Education","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has discussed the planned move to a numeric grading system for GCSEs in England with her Northern Ireland counterpart.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17144","17144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431380","2015-11-24","Department for Education","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department is undertaking of the effect on children's (a) attainment, (b) health and (c) attendance of the universal infant free school meals policy.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17131","17131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431381","2015-11-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the Northern Ireland Executive has the option to continue to issue its own Renewables Obligation Certificates.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17100","17100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431382","2015-11-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the average electricity bill was attributable to the levy imposed by the Levy Control Framework to meet the cost of feed-in tariffs in 2014-15.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17129","17129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431383","2015-11-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the Government's policy is on negotiating legally binding targets at the Paris World Climate Summit 2015.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17120","17120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431384","2015-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the disparity between Northern Ireland and the rest of the UK in the price farmers are able to achieve when selling livestock.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17113","17113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431385","2015-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Pet Animals Act 1951 to reflect the increasing number of animals sold over the internet.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17102","17102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431386","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the Government implements the UN Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17145","17145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431387","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information the Government holds on UK-linked companies committing human rights abuses abroad.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17140","17140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431388","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much the UK contributed to UN and African Union peacekeeping and stabilisation in low and middle income countries which (a) was not and (b) was classified as Official Development Assistance in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17128","17128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431389","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral reply by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Quality of 17 November 2015, Official Report, column 519, what specific support has been provided to Norfolk and Norwich University Hospitals Trust for winter 2015-16; what the financial value of that support is; and what the value is of the total of such support to all hospitals.","Biography information for Chloe Smith","Chloe Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17098","17098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431390","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department made of the effect of the Innovation Health and Wealth report, published in December 2011, on innovation in the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17109","17109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431391","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what effect the sunset review of NHS and his Department funded or sponsored innovation bodies, set out in the Innovation, Health and Wealth report, published in December 2011, had on the form, funding and effectiveness of such bodies.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17110","17110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431392","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) the Government's policy is and (b) guidance his Department has issued on the use of e-cigarettes as an alternative to smoking; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17114","17114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431393","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department is making preparations to plan for widespread resistance to known antibiotics.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17130","17130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431394","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent clinical assessments his Department has made of the potential medical benefits of cannabis.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17135","17135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431395","2015-11-25","Home Office","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people whose applications for asylum were rejected have been repatriated in 2015 to date.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17137","17137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431396","2015-11-24","Home Office","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government plans to take to (a) tackle sexual abuse and sexual crime involving 16 and 17 year olds and (b) better educate young people about sexual abuse.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17119","17119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431397","2015-11-24","Department for International Development","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what organisations her Department is working with to deliver humanitarian aid in Nepal.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17095","17095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431398","2015-11-24","Department for International Development","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aid her Department is providing to Indonesia to assist with tackling forest fires.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17121","17121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431399","2015-11-24","Department for International Development","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will prioritise funding to multilateral agencies that focus their aid programmes and investments in Least Developed Countries.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17122","17122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431400","2015-11-24","Department for International Development","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with Foreign Office Ministers on the implementation by UK Overseas Territories of public registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17123","17123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431401","2015-11-24","Department for International Development","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with HM Treasury Ministers on the implementation by UK Overseas Territories of public registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17124","17124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431402","2015-11-24","Department for International Development","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure its programme of work contributes to Goal 10 of the Sustainable Development Goals on reduced inequalities.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17125","17125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431403","2015-11-24","Department for International Development","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential benefits to developing countries of the implementation of public registers of beneficial ownership by UK Overseas Territories with financial centres.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17126","17126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431404","2015-11-24","Department for International Development","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department is contributing to the co-ordination of work across Government to support the achievement of the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17127","17127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431405","2015-11-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to page eight of the Stormont Agreement and Implementation Plan, published on 17 November 2015, what the further financial support of around £500 million from the Government will consist of and for what purposes it can be used.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17138","17138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431406","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what role he plans for Rail North in (a) assessing bids for the Northern and TransPennine Express rail franchises and (b) drafting the agreements for those franchises.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17097","17097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431407","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers he proposes that Rail North will exercise in respect of the Northern and TransPennine Express rail franchises by May 2016.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17103","17103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431408","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers he plans Rail North to assume in relation to rail franchises by 2020.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17104","17104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431409","2015-11-24","Women and Equalities","2015-11-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what research the Government Equalities Office has (a) commissioned and (b) assessed on the extent to which women are asked about their plans to have children during job interviews; and what steps the Government plans to take to reduce the incidence of that practice.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17107","17107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431410","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to review the rate at which small businesses can recover statutory maternity, paternity, adoption and shared parental leave pay.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17108","17108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431411","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution of the Government as an employer and commissioner to increasing rates of employment among disabled people.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17106","17106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431412","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2015 to Question 16265, what procedures jobcentre advisers follow when their clients request a referral to a foodbank for the fourth time in any given year.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17112","17112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431413","2015-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase the proportion of disabled people participating in apprenticeships.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17101","17101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431414","2015-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of the streams of data collected by his Department are (a) used by the Department, (b) read by how many people and (c) unused or unread.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17139","17139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431415","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what alternative options his Department offers to personal independence payment (PIP) applicants unable to travel to PIP assessment centres.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17141","17141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431416","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department offers to enable personal independence payment (PIP) applicants to attend PIP assessment centres.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17132","17132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431417","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many home visit assessments were offered to personal independence payment claimants in Scotland in the last 12 months; and whether his Department has declined to provide such assessments to any claimants who have requested such assessments.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17133","17133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431418","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of the costs of the contract for personal independence payment assessments is assigned to cover support and travel costs for claimants who need support to attend assessment centres.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17134","17134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431419","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that disabled people are supported to participate in apprenticeship schemes.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17115","17115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431420","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department plans to monitor the Government's progress on halving the disability employment gap; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17116","17116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/431421","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the economy of halving the disability employment gap; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17117","17117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429324","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of proposed closures to Open University regional centres on the numbers of (a) BAME and (b) disabled students in higher education.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16975","16975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429325","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment the Government has made of the benefit to businesses of a healthy workforce.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16968","16968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429326","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of additional regulation of the sale of fireworks.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16999","16999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429327","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15540, what assistance his Department gave to (a) Kent County Council, (b) other operational organisations and (c) businesses to cover costs and losses during the implementation of Operation Stack in 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16986","16986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429328","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what equality impact assessment the Government has undertaken on the implications of the planned abolition of maintenance grants.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17016","17016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429329","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed abolition of maintenance grants on the Government's target of doubling the proportion of people from disadvantaged backgrounds entering higher education between 2009 and 2020.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17017","17017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429330","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many small businesses have taken up the Apprenticeship Grant for Employers in each year that it has operated; and how many young apprentices have been taken on by businesses taking up that grant.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17018","17018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429331","2015-11-23","Women and Equalities","2015-11-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department is taking to eliminate the gender pay gap.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17030","17030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429332","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to help increase the number of women completing PhDs in STEM subjects.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17031","17031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429333","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on the RAB charge of the planned replacement of maintenance grants with means-tested loans.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17033","17033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429334","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the career progression of people aged 16 to 24 who have completed an apprenticeship since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17034","17034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429335","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit claimants have reported difficulties in renewing their claim online in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16963","16963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429336","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit claimants have received help with the digital skills required to renew their tax credit claim in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16964","16964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429337","2015-11-24","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of households with dependents under the age of 18 that will be affected by the draft Tax Credits (Income Thresholds and Determination of Rates) (Amendment) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17025","17025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429338","2015-11-24","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what account his Department took when preparing the Charter for Budget Responsibility, of the effect of (a) the Treaty on Stability, Coordination and Governance in the Economic and Monetary Union and (b) future EU treaty change in respect of that Treaty.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17027","17027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429339","2015-11-24","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the provisions of the Finance Act 2015 relating to penalties for late registration for the Alcohol Wholesaler Registration scheme will apply now implementation of that scheme has been delayed.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17003","17003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429340","2015-11-24","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information  has been provided to businesses to ensure that they are aware of their obligations under the Alcohol Wholesaler Registration scheme.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17004","17004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429341","2015-11-24","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many jobs will be created at each of the 13 new HM Revenue and Customs regional centres by 2021.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17008","17008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429342","2015-11-24","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many jobs will be lost at each of the 137 HM Revenue and Customs local offices to be closed by 2027.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17009","17009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429343","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the Exchequer is of the City Deals in each city region to date.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16995","16995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429344","2015-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when legislative provision will be made for the (a) establishment of the role of metro mayor for the West Midlands Combined Authority, (b) cancellation of the Police and Crime Commissioner election in the West Midlands and (c) establishment of the West Midlands Combined Authority.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17082","17082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429345","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what factors were considered by HM Revenue and Customs when making its decision to locate its regional hub in Leeds rather than Bradford.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17085","17085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429346","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what consultation HM Revenue and Customs conducted with its staff based in Yorkshire prior to its decision to locate its regional hub in Leeds.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17066","17066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429347","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative economic assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of HM Revenue and Customs locating its regional hub in (a) Leeds and (b) Bradford; and if he will place a copy of that assessment in the Library.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17067","17067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429348","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment he has made of the costs of HM Revenue and Customs locating its regional hub in (a) Leeds and (b) Bradford.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17068","17068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429349","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which potential sites HM Revenue and Customs identified in Leeds for its regional hub.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17069","17069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429350","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings HM Revenue and Customs held with (a) Leeds and (b) Bradford Council on deciding the location for its regional hub.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17070","17070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429351","2015-11-24","Cabinet Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people earn below the living wage.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17047","17047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429352","2015-11-24","Cabinet Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many young people in full-time employment earn below the living wage.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17048","17048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429353","2015-11-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) 16 to 24 year old and (b) 25 to 30 year old homeless people have been temporarily housed in bed and breakfast accommodation by their local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17049","17049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429354","2015-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what revenue contribution the Government has made to Sefton Council for the support of services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16944","16944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429355","2015-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will support the inclusion of a specific exemption for Holocaust research in the forthcoming European General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Lord Pickles","Sir Eric Pickles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16952","16952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429356","2015-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister of State for Defence Procurement of 23 June 2015, columns 861-62, for what reasons full and proper consultation with local fishing communities in advance of consultation on byelaw revision has not taken place; and if he will suspend the byelaw consultation relating to waters between the Scottish mainland and Raasay.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16970","16970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429357","2015-11-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the Voyager fleet has been fitted with the enhanced defensive aids suite; and what estimate he has made of the cost of fitting that suite to the remainder of that fleet.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17050","17050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429358","2015-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to provide better support for ex-servicemen and women and their families.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17083","17083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429359","2015-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues about providing more comprehensive support for ex-servicemen and women and their families.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17084","17084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429360","2015-11-24","Department for Education","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 14393, what proportion of the £4.2 billion funding to schools, local authorities, academy trusts and voluntary-aided partners has been allocated to Bracknell Forest Council.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17051","17051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429361","2015-11-23","Department for Education","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of how effectively pupil premium funding is used by schools to support disadvantaged highly-able pupils.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16988","16988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429362","2015-11-23","Department for Education","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will amend how the pupil premium is paid in order to reward schools that consistently improve results for all pupils while narrowing the attainment gap.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16989","16989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429363","2015-11-23","Department for Education","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that schools facilitate highly-able pupils from disadvantaged backgrounds accessing the best universities.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16987","16987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429364","2015-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, who she met during her visit to China in November 2015; and what was (a) discussed and (b) agreed at those meetings.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16985","16985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429365","2015-11-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's involvement was in the launch of E-Track on 18 November 2015 on the new European Commission programme on the Energy Transparency Centre of Knowledge (E-TRACK); and what the benefits are to the development of UK energy policy of E-TRACK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17053","17053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429366","2015-11-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the Government plans to create a new national scheme to improve home energy efficiency to replace the Green Deal scheme.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17055","17055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429367","2015-11-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress the Government has made on the UK commitment to ensure 20 per cent of its energy will come from renewables by 2020.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17056","17056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429368","2015-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the outcomes were of her visit to China in November 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16984","16984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429369","2015-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to raise the welfare standards of animals in battery cages.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17054","17054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429370","2015-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of permaculture techniques; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17035","17035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429371","2015-11-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to reduce instances of antibiotic resistance developing in farmed animals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17036","17036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429372","2015-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to meet the requirements of the Equine Identification Regulations in anticipation of requirements arising from EU regulation to monitor the importation and exportation of horses by 1 January 2016.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16945","16945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429373","2015-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that the tri-partite agreement between the UK, the Republic of Ireland and France on the importation and exportation of horses is achieving its aims; and if she will establish a comprehensive audit trail of movements to protect (a) consumers from exposure to illegal horse meat and (b) animals from cruelty.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16946","16946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429374","2015-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which government agency has overall responsibility for the control and monitoring of the movement of horses and their importation and exportation.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16947","16947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429375","2015-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received from rural community councils on their role in sustaining rural villages and communities.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16960","16960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429376","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to encourage the take-up of liquid petroleum gas conversions by taxis and vans.","Biography information for Rebecca Harris","Rebecca Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17080","17080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429377","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the establishment of a UN Commission of Inquiry into human rights violations against Rohingya people in Burma.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17077","17077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429378","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Chinese government on the reported disappearance of Gui Haiming and other employees of Sage Communications in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17090","17090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429380","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many full-time equivalent staff in his Department are engaged on work related to climate change in (a) posts around the world and (b) London.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16949","16949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429381","2015-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the government of Saudi Arabia on the reaffirmation in UN Security Council Resolution 2199 (2015) of 12 February 2015 of its Resolution 1373 (2001) on matters including the prevention and suppression of financing of terrorist acts.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17052","17052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429382","2015-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli government on the eviction of the Ghaith-Sub Laban family from their home in East Jerusalem.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16990","16990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429383","2015-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of continuing evictions of Palestinians from East Jerusalem on prospects for a two-state solution in that region.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16991","16991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429384","2015-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with the Moroccan ambassador to the UK Morocco's ban on the UN Secretary General's Personal Envoy to the Western Sahara visiting Western Sahara during his visit to that region to facilitate negotiations called for by the UN Security Council.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16971","16971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429385","2015-11-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Israeli government on the Children in Military Custody report, funded by his Department, which was published in June 2012.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17001","17001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429386","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the regulation of nurses and midwives remains appropriate for the health and social care environment as it evolves.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16966","16966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429387","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what timetable he proposes for legislative reform of the regulation of health care professionals.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16969","16969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429388","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to work with businesses to improve the health of the workforce.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16967","16967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429389","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2015 to Question 11834 to the hon. Member for Salford and Eccles, on what date he plans to announce the consultation on reform of the scheme for support for people affected by contaminated blood products.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16982","16982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429390","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a bill to reform the regulation  of healthcare professionals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16974","16974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429391","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the provision of services targeted at young people with dementia.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16992","16992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429392","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on the NHS of missed outpatient appointments due to (a) public transport and (b) other reasons.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16993","16993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429393","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has taken steps to recover costs to the NHS resulting from the actions of Hungarian journalist Ani Horvath as part of an investigation of fraud in the European Health Insurance Cards scheme.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17013","17013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429394","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for which drugs he is the marketing authorisation holder; and under what circumstances he became the marketing authorisation holder for each such drug.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17006","17006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429395","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Association of the British Pharmaceutical Industry on the Off-patent Drugs Bill.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17000","17000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429396","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of infection in NHS hospitals have been attributed to antibiotic resistant infections in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17037","17037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429397","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what financial support his Department has provided for research into antibiotic resistance in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17038","17038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429398","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NICE on conducting health technology appraisals for off-patent drugs that have been proven to be effective in new indications.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17007","17007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429399","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of NHS treatment measures to deal with antibiotic resistant infections; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17021","17021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429400","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has provided for clinical commissioning groups on the commissioning of off-patent drugs for use in new indications.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17022","17022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429401","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with clinical commissioning groups on commissioning of off-patent drugs for use in new indications.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17023","17023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429402","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many permanent gastroenterologist consultants were employed in the NHS in the last six years.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17024","17024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429403","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase the number of GPs; and what steps he is taking to ensure that employment terms and conditions for GPs encourage employment in areas with (a) an elderly demographic and (b) a high workload.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17026","17026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429404","2015-11-24","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when all NHS patients will be able to access their medical records online; and when the NHS will implement a secure unified email system.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16976","16976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429405","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures he plans to include in the forthcoming Order under section 60 of the Health Act 1999 to amend the legislation governing the Nursing and Midwifery Council.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16973","16973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429406","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to ensure that the access and waiting time standards for mental health set out in the NHS Five Year Forward plan are implemented in full.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16972","16972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429407","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effects on the cardiovascular health of local residents of continuous noise from aircraft taking off and landing.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17076","17076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429408","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the report, Disabled people's experiences of social care, published by the disability charity Scope in November 2015.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17059","17059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429409","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that disabled people receive the care they need to live independently.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17060","17060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429410","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure parity between the regulation of nurses and midwives and other regulated health professions.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17058","17058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429411","2015-11-23","Home Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the process will be for the cancellation of the Police and Crime Commissioner elections due to take place in May 2016 for areas now to form part of the West Midlands Combined Authority.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17081","17081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429412","2015-11-24","Home Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to amend the Act which results from the Investigative Powers Bill in the event of repeal of the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16948","16948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429413","2015-11-24","Home Office","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will issue a response to Early Day Motion (a) 162, Closures of abortion clinics and (b) 172, Buffer zones around abortion centres.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17014","17014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429414","2015-11-24","Department for International Development","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether (a) she or (b) another Minister from her Department plans to attend the Nutrition for Growth Summit schedules to take place during the Rio Summer Olympics.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17002","17002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429415","2015-11-23","Department for International Development","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what conditions are placed on her Department's funding for the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition; and whether such funding is (a) regularly reviewed and (b) preceded by local consultation in those countries that receive such funding.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17015","17015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429416","2015-11-23","Department for International Development","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to improve nutrition for women and children in lower middle income countries.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16943","16943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429417","2015-11-23","Department for International Development","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will introduce multi-year funding for child protection programmes in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16959","16959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429418","2015-11-23","Department for International Development","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of agroecology on food production in the developing world; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17073","17073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429419","2015-11-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total amount award by employment tribunals to claimants for (a) non-payment of wages and (b) non-compliance with minimum wage legislation was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17045","17045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429420","2015-11-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment tribunal claims for (a) non-payment of wages and (b) non-compliance with minimum wage legislation were made by women in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17046","17046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429421","2015-11-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many early conciliation cases processed by Acas in each quarter since October 2013 related to disputes regarding (a) non-payment of wages and (b) non-compliance with minimum wage legislation; and how many such cases (i) resulted in early conciliation and (ii) progressed to an employment tribunal.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17042","17042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429422","2015-11-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claims were taken to an employment tribunal for (a) non-payment of wages and (b) non-compliance with minimum wage legislation in each of the last five years; and how many such claims were upheld in each year.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17043","17043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429423","2015-11-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people who made an employment tribunal claim for (a) non-payment of wages and (b) non-compliance with minimum wage legislation in each quarter since October 2013 applied for (i) an issue fee remission and (ii) a hearing fee remission; and how many such applications were successful in each such quarter.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17044","17044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429424","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to support the conversion of cars to run on liquefied petroleum gas.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16965","16965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429425","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) salary and (b) contract length is of each member of the HS2 Independent Design Panel.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16961","16961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429426","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the requirements are for the funding and delivery of wifi on existing rail franchises.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16950","16950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429427","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what requirements for wifi delivery his Department plans to put in future rail franchises; and how his Department plans to assess the quality of wifi service provided pursuant to those franchises.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16951","16951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429428","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made on achieving the target of 55 per cent of primary school children walking to school by 2025.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16940","16940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429429","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will review the Public Service Vehicles Accessibility Regulations to make audio-visual announcement systems a requirement on all new buses.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16941","16941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429430","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many buses in England outside London are fitted with audio-visual announcement systems (AV); and what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of AV on bus patronage.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16942","16942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429431","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train services on the (a) Brighton and (b) East Grinstead line have been cancelled due to train reliability issues in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17039","17039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429432","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assurances he has received from Govia Thameslink Railway on the recruitment, training and in-service dates of train drivers.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17040","17040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429433","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains on the (a) Brighton and (b) East Grinstead line have been cancelled due to a lack of driver in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17041","17041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429434","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the reduction in car tax for people in receipt of personal independence payments is awarded from the date of application to DVLA rather than the date of award of such payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17062","17062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429435","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of road crossings in England are (a) puffin and (b) pedex crossings.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17019","17019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429436","2015-11-26","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the criteria are for authorising an average speed limit stretch of highway; what measures are in place to prevent an artificially low average speed limit being implemented; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17012","17012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429437","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the franchise agreements for Northern Rail and TransPennine Express will be published.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17020","17020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429438","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 14816, how much funding was allocated to local authorities for road resurfacing in 2014-15.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16997","16997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429439","2015-11-26","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to ensure that local highway agencies always give motorists sufficient and early notification of traffic delays, congestion and road accidents so that motorists approaching a black spot can use an alternative route; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17010","17010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429440","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many local authorities permit taxi drivers to charge for carriage of a wheelchair; and how many local authorities specify in their licensing rules that such charges may not be levied.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16996","16996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429441","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many open access contracts operate on the railway; and how many such contracts are currently under consideration.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17071","17071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429442","2015-11-26","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage local authorities to make greater use of flexible speed limits with electronic signs.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17011","17011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429443","2015-11-24","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of the estimate of surface access costs associated with an expansion of Heathrow Airport produced by (a) the Airports Commission and (b) the Mayor of London in his response to the Airports Commission consultation, published in February 2015.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17075","17075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429444","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2015 to Question 15352, on Cycling and Walking, which stakeholder groups his Department has engaged with since July 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17028","17028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429445","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to comments made by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Transport at a meeting about rail services between London and the Sussex coast on 27 May 2015, whether his Department's target of six months to stability for commuters between London and the Sussex coast has been met; whether rail services between Brighton and London are still flashing red at his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17074","17074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429446","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many sexual assaults on trains there have been in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17072","17072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429447","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which passenger rail contracts let by (a) his Department, (b) the Scottish Government, (c) the Welsh Government, (d) Transport for London and (e) Merseyrail are (i) franchises, (ii) concessions, (iii) management contracts and (iv) other types of passenger rail contract.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17091","17091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429448","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which current rail franchises include break clauses; and what is the purpose of each of those break clauses.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17079","17079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429449","2015-11-23","Women and Equalities","2015-11-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent assessment she has made on progress towards the target of 25 per cent female representation on FTSE 100 corporate boards by 2015.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17029","17029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429450","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 14680, on state retirement pensions, how many non-live cases there have been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17086","17086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429451","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 14680, on state retirement pensions, how many of those cases have been suspended in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17087","17087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429452","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on establishing pilot schemes to support carers to stay in work in North Tyneside, Northamptonshire, Cheshire West, Gateshead, Bury, North Somerset, South Gloucestershire, Staffordshire and Stoke and Sefton.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17088","17088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429453","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the age-standardised mortality rate of people declared fit for work by his Department since December 2011.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17089","17089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429454","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of tenants in the private rented sector were in receipt of housing benefit in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17032","17032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429455","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the habitual residence test on UK citizens returning to the UK from working overseas.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17078","17078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429456","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to improve employment support for people who are classed as economically inactive due to long term sickness or disability.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16994","16994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429457","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2015 to Question 15090, how much his Department spent on costs associated with the roll-out of universal credit between October 2014 and October 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16998","16998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429458","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department last audited the amount of unused space within each Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16981","16981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429459","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make transitional arrangements for women affected by changes to the state pension age introduced during the 2010 Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16983","16983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429460","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is his Department's policy that a jobseeker who is telephoned by a Jobcentre Plus adviser and does not answer the telephone on more than one occasion should be considered for a sanction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17005","17005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429461","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many voluntary redundancies there have been in his Department in 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17063","17063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429462","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of in-work recipients of housing benefits in the last five years.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17064","17064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429463","2015-11-24","HM Treasury","2015-11-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons expenditure on personal tax credits has increased since 2009.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17065","17065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429464","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of new claimants of employment and support allowances who will be placed in the work-related activity group from April 2017 to May 2020; and whether he has made an estimate of the number of those claimants who will be people with cancer.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17057","17057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429465","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disability discrimination tribunals have been brought against his Department as an employer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 17061","17061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429466","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how he plans to define (a) disability and (b) employment for the purposes of measuring the Government's progress towards halving the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16953","16953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429467","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to set targets for measuring progress towards the goal of halving the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16954","16954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429468","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to improve employment support for people with disabilities who are in receipt of the support component of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16955","16955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429469","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for housing benefit in the private rented sector in each of the last 10 years were made by people who were in work at the time they made their claim.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16956","16956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429470","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people currently in receipt of housing benefit in the private rented sector are also in receipt of (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) disability living allowance, (e) personal independence payment, (f) the state pension and (g) pension credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16957","16957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429471","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of households in receipt of universal credit who receive support for housing costs are also subject to all work-related requirements.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16958","16958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429472","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of jobseeker's allowance claimants have used Universal Jobmatch in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16977","16977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429473","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many working households in receipt of (a) working tax credit and (b) universal credit have marginal deduction rates of (i) less than 70, (ii) between 70 and 80, (iii) between 80 and 90 and (iv) more than 90 per cent on earned income above the level of the applicable disregard.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16962","16962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429474","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people making a new benefit claim in the last 12 months were offered training on IT literacy.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16978","16978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429475","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus offices have space in their building that is available for use by voluntary groups, social enterprises and mutuals to help equip claimants with the skills they need to use the internet.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16980","16980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429476","2015-11-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus offices host work clubs and service academies.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16979","16979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428969","2015-11-20","Attorney General","2015-11-18","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the CPS has recently taken to improve its support for (a) child witnesses and (b) people with learning disabilities who give evidence in criminal proceedings.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16813","16813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428970","2015-11-23","Attorney General","2015-11-18","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the use of hearsay evidence in court proceedings in reducing the number of unsuccessful cases due to victim or witness issues; and what estimate he has made of the number of cases where hearsay evidence has been used by prosecutors in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16836","16836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428971","2015-11-23","Attorney General","2015-11-18","To ask the Attorney General, how many cases of suspected non-compliance with minimum wage legislation were referred to the CPS in each of the last five years; and how many such referrals led to a prosecution in each of those years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16852","16852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428972","2015-11-20","Attorney General","2015-11-18","To ask the Attorney General, how many employers were (a) charged with and (b) convicted of a criminal offence by the Crown Prosecution Service for non-compliance with minimum wage legislation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16870","16870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428973","2015-11-20","Attorney General","2015-11-18","To ask the Attorney General, how many Crown Prosecution Service staff worked on (a) referrals for suspected non-compliance with minimum wage legislation and (b) prosecutions for non-compliance with minimum wage legislation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16871","16871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428974","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the higher education sector on extending the new postgraduate loans scheme to part-time taught masters students aged over 30.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16890","16890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428975","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of product safety guidance for manufacturers of children's fancy dress costumes; and what assessment he has made of the effect on safety of retailers classifying such costumes as toys rather than clothing.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16854","16854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428976","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many times the working groups on (a) public procurement, (b) international comparisons and (c) competitiveness and productivity have met since the Steel Summit on 16 October 2015; and what the actions and outcomes of each of those groups has been since their formation.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16849","16849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428977","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how he plans for part-time taught masters students who study at a minimum of 50 per cent intensity, but not by means of distance learning, to access the proposed new postgraduate loans scheme.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16891","16891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428978","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote the availability of loans to part-time students.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16892","16892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428979","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the higher education sector on extending the loan book to part-time students who wish to undertake a second degree.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16893","16893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428980","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which of the proposals in Higher education: teaching excellence, social mobility and student choice, published by his Department on 6 November 2015 are intended to enhance part-time higher education.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16894","16894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428981","2015-11-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15298, on Consumer Protection Measures in the Ticket Resale Market Review; who his Department contacted in Parliament; by what means they were contacted; and  what response his Department received from Parliament.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16885","16885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428982","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials in his Department are working on matters relating to High Speed 2; and what the grades of those officials are.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16905","16905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428983","2015-11-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will amend the criteria by which some students without permanent residence may be entitled to a student loan to reflect the judgement of the Supreme Court in the case of R v Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills (2015) UKSC 57.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16883","16883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428984","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement on (a) the UK economy as a whole, (b) each region and nation of the UK's economy, (c) each business sector in the UK economy, (d) large UK businesses and (e) UK SMEs.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16915","16915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428985","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 13.17 of HM Treasury's publication entitled, Fixing the Foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, Cm 9098, published in July 2015, what progress his Department has made on plans to introduce a degree apprenticeship in Leadership and Management to boost the capabilities of future business leaders.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16937","16937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428986","2015-11-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the privatisation of the Green Investment Bank will be by asset sale or as a going concern.","Biography information for Mr Nick Hurd","Mr Nick Hurd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16814","16814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428987","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer to Question 13261, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of conducting an area-based review of post-16 education and training institutions in (a) Tees Valley, (b) Birmingham and Solihull, (c) Greater Manchester, (d) Sheffield City Region, (e) Sussex Coast, (f) Solent and (g) West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16786","16786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428988","2015-11-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will assess the extent to which grants made by his Department to third parties are used for activities designed to influence his Department, other departments or Parliament.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16778","16778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428989","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the document Fixing the Foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, Cm 9098, what the evidential basis is for funding to UK Collaboration for Research in Infrastructure and Cities increasing productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16751","16751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428990","2015-11-23","Cabinet Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the rate is of (a) unemployment and (b) employment among people living in the UK who (i) were born in Lithuania and (ii) are Lithuanian nationals.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16773","16773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428991","2015-11-20","Cabinet Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK between the ages of 16 and 21 who earn less than £7.65 per hour.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16792","16792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428992","2015-11-23","Cabinet Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether reclassification by the Office of National Statistics of housing associations as public entities will entail their carrying the legislative obligations contained in the Freedom of Information Act 2000; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16827","16827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428993","2015-11-20","Cabinet Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK aged under 18 earning £3.87 per hour.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16804","16804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428994","2015-11-20","Cabinet Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK aged 21 and over earning £6.70 per hour.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16806","16806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428995","2015-11-20","Cabinet Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of apprentices in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK earning £3.30 per hour.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16803","16803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428996","2015-11-20","Cabinet Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK aged 18 to 20 earning £5.30 per hour.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16805","16805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428997","2015-11-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people resident in the UK of working age who were born in Lithuania are (a) in the G8 Claimant Count, (b) in receipt of employment and support allowance and other incapacity benefits and (c) lone parents in receipt of income support.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16848","16848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428998","2015-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of reductions in rents charged by housing associations on the number of new homes they propose to build.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16847","16847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/428999","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employees were identified as being paid less than the national minimum wage following HM Revenue and Customs enforcement activity in each of the last five years; and how many of those employees were compensated in full.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16850","16850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429000","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers were identified as being paid less than the national minimum wage in each of the last five years; how many and what proportion of such employers were issued with a formal notice of underpayment; how many and what proportion of those employers issued with such a formal notice (a) paid arrears in full on receipt of that notice and (b) were pursued by HM Revenue and Customs in the civil courts.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16851","16851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429001","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding has been provided to HM Revenue and Customs to enforce compliance with minimum wage legislation in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16853","16853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429002","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 15239, how much of the £3.6 billion of tax credits overpayments his Department has recovered in 2015 to date.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16924","16924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429003","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what training is provided to HM Revenue and Customs staff to prepare them for handling applications for allowable expenses for ministers of religion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16899","16899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429004","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that section 75 of the Northern Ireland Act 1998 is taken into account in decisions about the future of HM Revenue and Customs offices in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16896","16896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429005","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the European Commission on the abolition of Value Added Tax on sanitary products.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16882","16882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429006","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many projects, of what value, have received investment through the Pensions Infrastructure Platform in (a) 2015 and (b) since the platform's launch.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16934","16934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429007","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by HM Revenue and Customs to enforce compliance with minimum wage legislation in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16938","16938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429008","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress the Government has made on its proposed plans to introduce a degree apprenticeship in Leadership and Management as announced in Fixing the Foundations: Creating a more Prosperous Nation, Cm 9098, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16910","16910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429009","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid to employees in arrears as a result of enforcement of minimum wage legislation by HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16920","16920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429010","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid to HM Revenue and Customs in fines for non-compliance with minimum wage legislation in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16921","16921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429011","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs jobs in (a) Bradford and (b) West Yorkshire will be lost as a result of the proposed restructuring plan.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16841","16841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429012","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the £2,000 employment allowance is not allotted to NHS dentists employed as independent contractors.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16797","16797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429013","2015-11-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made by the Emerging Industry Action Group.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16862","16862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429014","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the extent to which grants made by his Department to third parties are used for activities designed to influence his Department, other departments or Parliament.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16777","16777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429015","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect on the UK economy of the 0.3 per cent reduction in eurozone economic growth in quarter 3 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16746","16746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429016","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ringfence spending on the Homelessness Prevention Grant until 2020 in the Spending Review.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16785","16785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429017","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will hypothecate revenue generated from Vehicle Excise Duty to local roads maintenance from 2017.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16766","16766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429018","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of the air quality benefits of using liquefied petroleum gas in transport to inform its taxation policies.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16767","16767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429019","2015-11-23","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the document Fixing the Foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation Cm 9098, what the evidential basis is for proposed reforms to tax credits increasing productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16750","16750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429020","2015-11-20","Department for Education","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent progress has been made on the application by Romford Football Club to build a stadium on Westlands playing field; and when she expects a decision on that application will be reached.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16758","16758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429021","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what date the £75 million Mayoral Investment Fund pledged as part of the Liverpool City Region Deal was paid to Liverpool City Council.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16793","16793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429022","2015-11-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the activities of organisations and bodies fully funded by local authorities are subject to the conditions of the Code of Recommended Practice on Local Authority Publicity.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16795","16795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429023","2015-11-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of his proposed changes to business rates on (a) Merseyside and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16907","16907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429024","2015-11-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which areas of Wales (a) have access to 4G and (b) are planned to receive access to 4G by 2016-17; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16872","16872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429025","2015-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his Department's budget is for the 2021 UK City of Culture competition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16856","16856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429026","2015-11-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with his international counterparts on tackling doping in sport.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16824","16824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429027","2015-11-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with Ofcom on introducing requirements on communications providers to improve access to relay video services since Ofcom's review of relay services on 2011-12.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16828","16828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429028","2015-12-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the number of businesses in Newton Abbot constituency which have download speeds of 10Mb/s.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16788","16788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429029","2015-12-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the number of businesses in Newton Abbot constituency which have superfast broadband of 24Mb/s.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16789","16789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429030","2015-11-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of the Broadband Connection Voucher Scheme on businesses planning to make an application ahead of the original closure date of March 2016; what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on securing the funding required to re-open and extend that scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16799","16799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429031","2015-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total expenditure was on the Single Source Regulation Office in each quarter since its formation.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16858","16858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429032","2015-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2015 to Question 428, what progress has been made in ensuring funding from the Armed Forces Covenant (Libor) Fund is distributed across the UK; and which organisations in each region of the UK have benefited from that fund to date.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16834","16834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429033","2015-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role he expects the Single Source Regulation Office to have in the procurement of the Successor class submarine.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16859","16859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429034","2015-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the triple lock on pensions does not apply to disability war pensions.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16781","16781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429035","2015-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the triple lock on pensions does not extend to disability war pensions.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16889","16889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429036","2015-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the proposed byelaw changes for the waters between the Scottish mainland and the Island of Raasay.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16884","16884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429037","2015-11-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made with the implementation of the recommendations made in Lord Ashcroft's Veterans' Transition Review, published in February 2014.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16906","16906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429038","2015-11-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department conducted an economic impact assessment of the proposed byelaw changes for the waters between the mainland of Scotland and the Island of Raasay.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16917","16917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429039","2015-11-23","Department for Education","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage the teaching of emergency first aid skills in schools.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16898","16898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429040","2015-11-20","Department for Education","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress is being made on the implementation of 30 hours of free childcare for working parents.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16877","16877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429041","2015-11-20","Department for Education","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many heads of academies are paid more than the Prime Minister.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16815","16815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429042","2015-11-20","HM Treasury","2015-11-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost is to the Exchequer of the City Deals in each city region to date.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16816","16816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429043","2015-11-20","Department for Education","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many employees of academies, in which roles, are paid more than the Prime Minister.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16817","16817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429044","2015-11-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what date in January 2016 is set for her Department to announce its decision on feed-in tariffs following its review.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16756","16756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429045","2015-11-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to encourage energy providers to join the Warm Home Discount Scheme.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16818","16818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429046","2015-11-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress her Department has made towards its renewable energy target for 2020; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16833","16833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429047","2015-11-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will re-introduce feed-in tariff preaccreditation for community renewable energy schemes.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16794","16794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429048","2015-11-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress her Department has made on plans to improve energy efficiency across schools through introducing solar hubs.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16932","16932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429049","2015-11-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many officials in her Department are working on matters related to High Speed 2; and what the grades of those officials are.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16904","16904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429050","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to bring forward proposals to ban the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16919","16919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429051","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will assess the extent to which grants made by her Department to third parties are used for activities designed to influence her Department, other departments or Parliament.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16780","16780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429052","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs in Wales have been placed on the register of exempt dogs under section 4A and section 4B procedures under the Dangerous Dogs (Amendment) Act 1997 in each year since 1997; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16791","16791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429053","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the level of stocks of sea bass since the implementation of restrictions on landing that fish by (a) commercial and (b) recreational fishermen in 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16783","16783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429054","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken to ensure that organic food producers are subsidised under the Common Agricultural Policy.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16784","16784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429055","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of whether ending her Department's funding for the National Wildlife Crime Unit would affect the UK's Commitment to Action on the illegal wildlife trade.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16776","16776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429056","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how her Department plans to ensure it works in partnership with businesses involved with wildlife issues to enhance public and private sector involvement in combating wildlife crime after March 2016.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16775","16775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429057","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support the establishment of an independent, international and impartial body to investigate violations of international humanitarian and human rights law in Yemen.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16757","16757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429058","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on supporting a new UN Security Council Resolution in the event that Resolution 2216 remains an obstacle to a negotiated peace in Yemen.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16744","16744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429059","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage Saudi Arabia and other parties to the conflict in Yemen to refrain from using explosive weapons with wide-range effects in populated areas in order to avoid high levels of civilian casualties.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16745","16745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429060","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the report by Waging Peace on the use of rape as a weapon of war in the conflict in the Darfur region of Sudan.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16765","16765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429061","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on establishing marine protection zones in British Overseas Territories; and whether each such zone will require the consent of that Territory's national assembly prior to its creation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16747","16747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429062","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to improve diplomatic and economic ties with the new government in Burma.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16748","16748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429063","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the likelihood of success of the planned peace talks between the Yemeni government and Houthis in that country; and what steps the Government is taking to support agreement on an immediate ceasefire at those talks.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16749","16749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429064","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has received representations from any representatives of the Israeli government to stop funding specified Israeli human rights NGOs.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16798","16798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429065","2015-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) military and (b) financial support his Department has provided to the Kurdish region in northern Iraq and Syria in the last year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16857","16857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429066","2015-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts from Arab League states on the threat posed by ISIS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16935","16935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429067","2015-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his (a) Iranian and (b) Russian counterparts to discuss the threat posed by ISIS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16933","16933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429068","2015-11-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take other than airstrikes to respond to the threat posed by ISIS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16823","16823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429069","2015-11-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Indian Prime Minister on Kashmir during his recent visit to the UK.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16855","16855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429070","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the incidence of depression among new mothers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16825","16825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429071","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with NICE and the Roche group of companies steps to reduce the cost of breast cancer drugs.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16826","16826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429072","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that adequate funding is provided to North Tees and Hartlepool NHS Foundation Trust to maintain a full range of services during the winter period.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16809","16809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429073","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the fit and proper test for individuals running care homes for the elderly; and what plans he has to make changes to that test.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16810","16810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429074","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the implementation of the recommendations made in the Innovation, Health and Wealth report, published by his Department in December 2011.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16811","16811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429075","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to (a) reduce waiting times for children to receive an assessment for a mental health condition and (b) address the disparity between those waiting times across different NHS mental health trusts.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16909","16909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429076","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the reliability of diagnostic tests for pernicious anaemia.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16903","16903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429077","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the benefits of allowing easier access to vitamin B12.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16902","16902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429078","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the appropriate frequency with which people with pernicious anaemia should receive vitamin B12 replacement injections; what the guidelines are for GPs on granting requests by individual patients for injections to be administered more frequently than prescribed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16897","16897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429079","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to change attitudes to personal health issues among men.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16895","16895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429080","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will respond to the Cabinet Office funded report relating to early deaths among people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16927","16927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429081","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that CCGs do not reduce expenditure on mental health budgets to cover deficits in the acute hospital sector.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16928","16928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429082","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to address the higher incidence of mental illness among young LGBT people.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16931","16931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429083","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the incidence of his Department giving grants to organisations which subsequently use the money to try to influence (a) his and (b) other Government departments.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16835","16835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429084","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012 on recoverable costs in medical negligence cases.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16807","16807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429085","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on ensuring that mental health is removed as an obstacle to entering the workplace.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16843","16843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429086","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on support for people with mental health conditions who claim jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16842","16842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429087","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the extent to which grants made by his Department to third parties are used for activities designed to influence his Department, other departments or Parliament.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16779","16779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429088","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors trained in the UK emigrated in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2013 and (d) 2014; and what assessment he has made of the effect such emigration has had on the provision of emergency medicine.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16771","16771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429089","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of doctors working in hospitals are from non-UK countries.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16772","16772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429090","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the recommendations in the report by ukactive entitled Blueprint for an Active Britain, published in November 2015.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16768","16768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429091","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to reduce loneliness and isolation for elderly people through increased contact during transitional care.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16752","16752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429092","2015-12-01","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will change the criteria for primary and acute care provision better benefit rural communities.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16754","16754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429093","2015-12-01","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will change the criteria for multi-specialty community providers better to benefit rural areas.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16755","16755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429094","2015-11-23","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the effect of increased cyber-security funding on the numbers of (a) frontline police and (b) police community support officers.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16769","16769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429095","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will hold discussions with the National Association of Retired Police Officers on steps to support national security.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16761","16761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429096","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to include all Partnership for Action against Wildlife Crime wildlife crime priorities within the Counting Rules Code 96.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16762","16762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429097","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how her Department plans to ensure that police forces and partner agencies are supported to undertake wildlife criminal investigations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16763","16763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429098","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how her Department plans to ensure it identifies organised crime groups involved in wildlife crime through the information sharing process after March 2016.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16764","16764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429099","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) child and (b) adult EU nationals were (i) identified as potential victims of trafficking and (ii) returned to their country of origin in each of the last 5 years; and how many of those returned to their country of origin were so identified as potential victims of trafficking.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16759","16759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429100","2015-11-23","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to address stress-related sickness absence in the police force.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16930","16930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429101","2015-11-23","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on accepting asylum claims from (a) Syrian refugees who have reached the UK travelling through other EU member states without claiming asylum in one of those states and (b) such refugees who reside with family members who have a right to reside in the UK.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16916","16916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429102","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish the report on overseas domestic worker visas carried out by James Ewins.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16918","16918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429103","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to lay before Parliament her report on the steps she will take in relation to the powers conferred by section 48 of the Modern Slavery Act on independent child trafficking advocates.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16880","16880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429104","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the operation of the National Crime Agency in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16887","16887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429105","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the extent to which Northern Ireland's land border with another EU member state creates a challenge in protecting Northern Ireland from terrorist threats.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16888","16888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429106","2015-11-23","Attorney General","2015-11-18","To ask the Attorney General, whether he plans to change the arrangements or level of funding for specialist rape and sexual offence prosecutors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16908","16908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429107","2015-11-23","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2015 to Question 12956, how many of the suspicious activity reports received under the provisions of the Terrorism Act 2000 have been investigated; and how many prosecutions have resulted from those investigations.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16923","16923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429108","2015-11-23","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the cost of reimbursing communication service providers under the provisions of the draft Investigatory Powers Bill in the first 10 years in which an Act arising from that draft bill is in force.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16912","16912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429109","2015-11-23","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2015 to Question 15325, how any of those asylum claims resulted in a positive asylum decision.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16913","16913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429110","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who initially claimed asylum as unaccompanied children have applied to extend or vary their leave in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16864","16864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429111","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many young people aged between 18 and 25 who applied for asylum as unaccompanied children were served with removal directions in each year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16863","16863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429112","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children who have had their claims certified have been removed from the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16869","16869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429113","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of detainees held in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre  are receiving medication for mental health problems; and what proportion of those detainees have had their dosage increased since being held in detention.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16875","16875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429114","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women held in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre have refused to eat for one or more consecutive days in 2015.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16876","16876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429115","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children have had their claims certified in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16865","16865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429116","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many young people over 18 who applied for asylum as unaccompanied children in each year since 2010 have been (a) removed from the UK and (b) left voluntarily.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16866","16866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429117","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people aged between 18 and 25 who claimed asylum as unaccompanied children and had their claims certified have been removed from the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16867","16867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429118","2015-11-20","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many young people over 18 who claimed asylum as unaccompanied children and had their claims certified have appealed out of country in each of the last five years; and how many such appeals were successful.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16868","16868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429119","2015-11-23","Department for International Development","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the effect of the recruitment of doctors to the NHS from developing countries on the health services in those countries.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16770","16770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429120","2015-11-20","Department for International Development","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support is being provided to refugees currently on the island of Lesbos.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16796","16796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429121","2015-11-20","Department for International Development","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to attach conditions to aid to Pakistan relating to the prevention of persecution of and discrimination against Christians.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16819","16819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429122","2015-11-20","Department for International Development","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of her Department's budget is spent on supporting water, sanitation and hygiene services; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16873","16873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429123","2015-11-20","Department for International Development","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the relationship between clean water and sanitation in schools and girls' school attendance in developing countries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16874","16874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429124","2015-11-20","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number of people in prison (a) as a result of and (b) with a gambling addiction.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16878","16878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429125","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people in Wales have been prosecuted under sections (a) 1(3), (b) 3(1) and (c) 3(3) of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 in each year since 1991; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16879","16879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429126","2015-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are serving sentences beyond the limit of the tariff for the crimes for which they were sentenced.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16922","16922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429127","2015-11-23","Department of Health","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health in-patient units and beds there have been in English prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16929","16929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429128","2015-11-23","Home Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) independent domestic violence advisers and (b) independent sexual violence advisers operating in the criminal justice system in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16840","16840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429129","2015-11-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16838","16838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429130","2015-11-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people in Wales have been subject to proceedings in a magistrates' court for offences under the Dogs Act 1871 in each year since 1997; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16790","16790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429131","2015-11-23","Leader of the House","2015-11-18","To ask the Leader of the House, what steps his Office has taken to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16839","16839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429132","2015-11-23","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department has taken to embed the family test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16837","16837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429133","2015-11-20","Prime Minister","2015-11-18","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he had with representatives of the Russian government at the recent G20 meeting on Syria.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16812","16812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429134","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to embed the Family Test into its policy making.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16802","16802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429135","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Chancellor of the Exchequer's Financial Statement of 8 July 2015, Official Report, column 327, when the consultation on extending the deadline for new cars and motorbikes to have their first MOT test from three to four years will begin; who will be invited to respond to that consultation; and when that consultation will end.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16881","16881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429136","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer to Question 15214, what assessment his Department has made of reference in the Quality Contract Scheme Board's report to bus operators being compensated by the Government for future losses that might be incurred as a result of franchising.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16886","16886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429137","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Transport for London on the ability of its ticket machines to accept banknotes issued by Scottish banks.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16911","16911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429138","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of night flights to and from Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16936","16936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429139","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many miles of local authority road are in a poor structural condition in (a) England outside London and (b) London.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16782","16782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429140","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the concentration of flight paths over residential areas near Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16861","16861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429141","2015-11-20","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to lay the Office for Road and Rail's first Highways England Monitor before the House when it is complete.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16808","16808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429142","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of aircraft on nitrous dioxide levels in Greater London.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16860","16860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429143","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people work on High Speed 2 in (a) his Department and (b) HS2 Ltd; and what the (i) grade, (ii) salary and (iii) location is of each such person.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16830","16830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429144","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which companies have expressed an interest in bidding for the seven engineering contracts announced by the Chancellor of the Exchequer on his recent visit to China.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16831","16831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429145","2015-11-23","Department for Transport","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which legal advisers and barristers have been used by (a) HS2 Ltd and (b) his Department on matters relating to High Speed 2 since the start of the project; and how much each such adviser or barrister (i) has been paid and (ii) is owed.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16832","16832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/429146","2015-11-23","Wales Office","2015-11-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising (i) in 2014-15 prices and (ii) as a proportion of his Department's expenditure in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 16787","16787"
