"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890491","2018-04-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS trusts and healthcare organisations there are in (a) East Sussex, (b) West Sussex and (c) Sussex; and what the respective tasks are of those trusts and organisations.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137383","137383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890492","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to review the number of Tier 2 visas issued; and what representations she has received on increasing the number of Tier 2 visas issued.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137384","137384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890493","2018-04-27","Prime Minister","2018-04-24","To ask the Prime Minister, what are her objectives are for her two years as the Commonwealth Chair-in-Office.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137385","137385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890494","2018-04-27","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps have been taken as part of the £100 million programme for low-cost move on accommodation to enable people leaving hostels and refuges to make a sustainable recovery from a homelessness crisis into independent living; and how much of that money has been spent to date.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137467","137467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890495","2018-04-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133971, for what reasons that answer does not contain information on the difference between the installation cost figures used in the 2016 cost-benefit analysis update and energy suppliers’ current data on installation costs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137413","137413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890496","2018-04-26","Department for International Development","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many full-time equivalent officials in her Department work on the promotion of freedom of religion and belief.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137527","137527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890497","2018-04-26","Department for International Development","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in which countries full-time or full-time equivalent DFID officials are employed to work on freedom of religion or belief.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137528","137528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890498","2018-04-27","Department for Transport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government undertook its sampling to establish which roads would be included in the Major Road Network.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137516","137516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890499","2018-04-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has plans to limit the fees charged by online fundraising platforms on Gift Aided money; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137638","137638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890500","2018-04-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the transparency of the fees charged by online fundraising platforms on Gift Aided money, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137639","137639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890501","2018-04-27","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the press release entitled Life sentences for killer drivers, published by his Department on 15 October 2017, what progress he has made on  (a) implementing an increase to the maximum penalty for the offences of causing death by (i) dangerous driving and (ii) careless driving whilst under the influence of drink or drugs to life imprisonment and (b) creating a new offence of causing serious injury by careless driving.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137592","137592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890502","2018-04-26","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice of 24 April 2018, Official Report, column 717, on Victims Law when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals for a Victim's Law.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137525","137525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890503","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish a strategy document on steps to improve the responsiveness of NHS England to complaints; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137481","137481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890504","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Windrush helpline is staffed by people who are directly employed by her Department.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137392","137392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890505","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Minister in her Department is responsible for the Windrush helpline and taskforce.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137393","137393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890506","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he made the decision that Ministers will not meet military charities which are not members of Confederation of Service Charities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Sir Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137506","137506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890507","2018-04-27","Department for Transport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the second remedial plan for the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern franchise will be published before the new timetable is introduced in May 2018.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137644","137644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890508","2018-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many disqualification orders have been issued in England and Wales under s34 of the Animal Welfare Act 2006 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137655","137655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890509","2018-05-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many disqualification orders issued under section 34 of the Animal Welfare Act 2006 have been breached in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137656","137656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890510","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the second remedial plan for the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern franchise, whether he has made an assessment of the potential benefits to (a) the company and (b) passengers of any new default levels .","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137645","137645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890511","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to provide the Migration Advisory Committee with the (a) number of Tier 2 (General) Certificate of Sponsorship applications since November 2017 and (b) (i) number of and (ii) information on subsequent refusals of those applications due to the cap being reached in each month since November 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137657","137657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890512","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Departments have been provided with (a) the number and (b) details of Tier 2 (General) Certificate of Sponsorship refusals as a result of the annual cap being reached since November 2017 to inform those Departments' policy work.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137658","137658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890513","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which critical national infrastructure sites the Ministry of Defence Police provides civil policing and armed security for.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137500","137500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890514","2018-04-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the amount spent by his Department on promoting regional tourism in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137473","137473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890515","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent meetings he has had with social media companies to discuss the (a) prevalence, (b) removal and (c) prevention of hate speech and other extreme content on social media platforms.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137474","137474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890516","2018-04-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much central government funding was provided to the Information Commissioners Office in each of the last three years; what what central government funding is planned to be provided to that Office in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137475","137475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890517","2018-04-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's policy on onshore wind on domestic energy prices.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137476","137476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890518","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure disabled people in receipt of employment and support allowance do not face repeated work capability assessments when they move to a Universal Credit full-service area.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137589","137589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890519","2018-04-27","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March to Question 132182 on Housing: Finance, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the bidding process for local authorities councils to be allocate housing-related funding.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137637","137637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890520","2018-04-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to classify small businesses as preferential creditors in cases of (a) insolvency and (b) bankruptcy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137408","137408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890521","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to reduce the number of attacks on shop workers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137409","137409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890522","2018-04-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations has he made to the Government of Kosovo on the rendition of six Turkish citizens from that country to Turkey; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137428","137428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890523","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has plans to (a) participate and (b) organise events for Respect for Shopworkers' Week.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137410","137410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890524","2018-04-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the criteria are for accessing his Department’s Nationwide Gigabit Broadband Voucher Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137411","137411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890525","2018-04-27","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate he has made of the amount of court time which has been saved by allowing people accused of shoplifting to the cost of £200 to plead guilty by post; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137412","137412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890526","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the proposals of Trans Pennine rail submitted to him on the provision of train services on Boxing Day 2018.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137429","137429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890527","2018-04-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received from the hospice movement on the effect of the proposed pay increases for NHS staff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137509","137509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890528","2018-04-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans for voluntary hospices to be able to access the additional government funding being set aside to fund the proposed NHS pay increases.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137510","137510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890529","2018-04-27","Department for Education","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of eligible (a) three and (b) four year olds have received an eligibility code for 30 hours of free childcare for the summer 2018 term.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137632","137632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890530","2018-04-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March to Question 133805, on Dental Health: Children, how many and what proportion of local authorities have (a) toothbrushing programmes and (b) community fluoride varnish schemes; and if he will list the local authorities which have such programmes.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137414","137414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890531","2018-04-27","Department for International Development","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to support the United Nations Relief and Works Agency in maintaining its operation after the recent reduction in funding provided by the US.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137402","137402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890532","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals there were against personal independence payments determinations in (a) Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) Bradford district in 2017; and how many of those appeals were upheld.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137430","137430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890533","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much each national park authority spent on programmes to improve public transport access to national parks in 2017-18.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137431","137431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890534","2018-04-26","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 52 of the Joint report from the negotiators of the European Union and the United Kingdom Government on progress during phase 1 of negotiations under Article 50 TEU on the United Kingdom's orderly withdrawal from the European Union, whether the commitment made in that paragraph includes all EU rights normally associated with residents in a Member State; and if he will list those rights.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137432","137432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890535","2018-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what dates officials of his Department visited Gaza to inspect (a) hospitals and (b) other other medical facilities.since 30 March 2018.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137403","137403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890536","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fatalities resulting from fire there were in Yorkshire and the Humber in each year since 2010.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137433","137433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890537","2018-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations has he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the use of live fire against Palestinian demonstrators since 30 March 2018.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137404","137404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890538","2018-04-27","Department for Education","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of eligible two year old children receive 15 hours of free early years education each week.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137633","137633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890539","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the terms of reference of the feasibility study into the restoration of the Skipton to Colne railway link.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137434","137434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890540","2018-04-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to representatives of the Egyptian government on the granting of permits to residents in Gaza who need medical treatment that can only be provided outside of Gaza.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137405","137405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890541","2018-04-26","Department for International Development","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what amount of funding the UK provided to the United Nations Relief and Works Agency in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137406","137406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890542","2018-04-27","Treasury","2018-04-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 135820, on Children: Day Care, how much was spent each month on (a) call centre support and (b) IT support for (i) tax-free childcare and (ii) 30 hours of free childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137634","137634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890543","2018-04-27","Treasury","2018-04-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse has been of administering childcare vouchers in each of the last 36 months.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137635","137635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890544","2018-04-26","Department for International Development","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government supports the right of Syrian refugees voluntarily to return to Syria.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137407","137407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890545","2018-04-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2018 to Question 133974, on Access to Work Programme, when her Department plans to publish its update to the Equality Analysis.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137415","137415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890546","2018-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page 9 of the Submarine Delivery Agency Corporate Plan 2018-2019, whether three Government non-executive directors and three independent non-executive directors have been appointed to the Submarine Delivery Agency Board.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137501","137501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890547","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the eligibility of international Kabaddi players for Tier 5 visas.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137652","137652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890548","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will meet with representatives of the England Kabaddi Federation to discuss the eligibility of international competitors for the Tier 5 visa.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137653","137653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890549","2018-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Submarine Delivery Agency Framework Document, published by his Department on 23 April 2018, what the timetable is for the Submarine Delivery Agency to have its own Employee Relations Framework.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137502","137502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890550","2018-04-27","Department for Education","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the average weekly cost of childcare  in Warrington for a child (a) under two and (b) two to four years of age.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137455","137455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890551","2018-04-27","Department for Education","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he plans to take to improve the performance of secondary schools against Gatsby benchmark number 7.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137461","137461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890552","2018-04-27","Department for Education","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many employers have been asked to answer the employer skills survey in 2018.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137462","137462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890553","2018-04-27","Department for Education","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions has he had with (a) employers and (b) further education colleges on the effect of health and safety requirements on the use of work experience and work placements.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137463","137463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890554","2018-04-27","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting time was for patients in A&E in the North East of England in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137541","137541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890555","2018-04-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to close the pay gap between people (a) with and (b) without disabilities.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137542","137542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890556","2018-04-27","Treasury","2018-04-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 14 December 2017 to Question 118571, on Overseas Trade: China, whether the Government has made an alternative estimate to that provided by OLAF for alleged duty loss.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137598","137598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890557","2018-04-27","Cabinet Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who do not have photo identification in the local authority areas which are piloting photo ID to vote in the elections on 3 May 2018.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137599","137599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890558","2018-04-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what restrictions apply to the sale of shares in any wholly owned company limited by shares which have been set up by a NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137601","137601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890559","2018-04-27","Department for Education","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 April 2018 to Question 136788, on Students: Loans, how many of the 793 Nursing, Midwifery and Allied Health Professions students were overpaid by over £1000.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137464","137464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890560","2018-04-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans her Department has to publish the list of subcontractors for the Work and Health Programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137386","137386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890561","2018-04-27","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans he has for his Department to allocate resources from the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137387","137387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890562","2018-04-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria her Department plans to use to determine which jobseekers should be referred to the Work and Health Programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137388","137388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890563","2018-04-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what performance targets she has set for the Work and Health Programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137389","137389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890564","2018-04-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he last met with representatives of the Swansea Tidal Lagoon project.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137492","137492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890565","2018-04-27","Treasury","2018-04-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of taxpayers who are paying an effective marginal rate of tax on income in excess of (a) 40, (b) 50, (c) 60 and (d) 70 per cent once account has been taken of tax arrangements relating to pension contributions in the most recent tax year for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137456","137456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890566","2018-04-27","Department for International Development","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2018 to Question 128376, on Developing Countries: Coal Fired Power Stations, what support her Department provides to developing countries fully deploying abated coal-fired power projects.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137457","137457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890567","2018-04-27","Department for International Development","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February to Question 128376, on Developing Countries: Coal Fired Power Stations,what steps her Department is taking to encourage multilateral organisations to provide financing for projects fully deploying abated coal-fired power; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137458","137458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890568","2018-04-27","Treasury","2018-04-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's consultation on the tax treatment of heated tobacco products, published on 20 March 2017, whether he is taking steps to introduce a new category for heat-no-burn tobacco products; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137459","137459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890569","2018-04-27","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what impact assessment Department has conducted on the estimated cost to (a) Government Departments, (b) companies, (c) charities, (d) political parties and (e) voluntary organisations of the introduction of the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137427","137427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890570","2018-04-27","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) armament and (b) sensors are planned to be included in the Royal Fleet Auxiliary Fleet support ships which are currently being tendered; what combat systems will be used to control those armament and sensors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137603","137603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890571","2018-04-27","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland has had with the Leader of the House on bringing a motion before the House to reduce the representative money paid to Sinn Fein; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137493","137493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890572","2018-04-27","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what meetings she has held with the leaders of each of the political parties in the Northern Ireland Assembly since the collapse of the talks in mid February 2018; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137494","137494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890573","2018-04-27","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will clarify her plans on the use of her statutory power to call Northern Ireland Assembly Elections; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137495","137495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890574","2018-04-27","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to initiate talks between the main political parties in Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137496","137496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890575","2018-04-26","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much time he spent (a) in Northern Ireland and (b) visiting the border area on 23 April 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137497","137497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890576","2018-04-26","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she has taken to support the Northern Ireland Policing Board since the collapse of the Northern Ireland Assembly; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137498","137498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890577","2018-04-27","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what reasons she did not exercise her power to cut the salaries of members of the Northern Ireland Assembly; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137499","137499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/891260","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on support for community transport services.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905043","905043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/891261","2018-04-30","Department for Transport","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on Government support for local authorities to maintain local roads.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905039","905039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/891301","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support his Department provides to local authority schemes to reduce levels of violent crime.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 905029","905029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/885293","2018-04-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were registered blind in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136158","136158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889262","2018-04-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","What progress his Department has made on taking legal action against people who set up illegal encampments on its land.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 904880","904880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889870","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the 2017 changes to apprenticeship funding on the (a) number of employees and (b) level of funding of further education colleges with a role as partner providers for apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136922","136922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889871","2018-04-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the powers available to the Information Commissioner’s Office to enforce their guidelines on online child safety.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136923","136923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889872","2018-04-26","Women and Equalities","2018-04-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when the Government plans to publish its response to the recommendations made by the Equality and Human Rights Commission in its report entitled Turning the Tables: Ending Sexual Harassment at Work, published in March 2018.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136924","136924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889873","2018-04-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to ensure that (a) information society services and (b) social media platforms cannot be used by (i) third parties and (ii) foreign states to influence UK (A) elections and (B) democratic processes.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136925","136925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889874","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether British military officers played a role in Qatar's training of armed opposition groups in the western mountains of Libya during the war in 2011.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136926","136926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889875","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the Rail Ombudsman to commence operations.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136927","136927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889876","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to her Answer of 22 March 2018 to Question 133837, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of tendering a contract with a taxi company to enable vulnerable claimants to travel to assessments without having to pay travel costs upfront.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136928","136928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889877","2018-04-26","Treasury","2018-04-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money has been raised from the Apprenticeship Levy by HMRC since its introduction in April 2017.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136929","136929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889878","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much and what proportion of the sums raised for the apprenticeship levy were spent on apprenticeships in 2017-18.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136930","136930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889879","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the value for money of the Government's new nuclear power programme compared with other alternatives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136931","136931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889880","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in seeking views from local authorities on the forthcoming Reducing Interparental Conflict programme and the range of interventions to be made available through it, whether local authorities were made aware that reducing couple conflict, rather than improving parenting, would be the primary goal of that programme.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136932","136932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889881","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether leaders from the Western Balkans countries who have denied that the Srebrenica massacre was an act of genocide will be attending the Western Balkans summit in the UK in July.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136933","136933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889882","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the most recent average point score per entry was for students of A-levels and equivalent qualifications in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England who were (i) eligible and (ii) not eligible for free school meals aged 15.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136934","136934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889883","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report of 16 April in the Farmers' Guardian on  why 25 per cent of British farms could go bankrupt after Brexit, what steps his Department is taking to ensure such farms remain viable.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136935","136935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889884","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the efficiency of the use of audio recording equipment during fitness for work assessments.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136936","136936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889885","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what measures he is taking to increase the number of passenger rail journeys in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136937","136937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889886","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what change there was in the level of UK emissions in March 2018 compared with March in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136938","136938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889887","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he retains the legal power to revise the terms and conditions of student loans, including those sold to the Student Loans Company; and whether his Department has any plans to standardise those terms and conditions irrespective of the higher education start date of those loans.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136939","136939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889888","2018-04-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to update the timeshare regulations to address issues around trying to relinquish timeshares.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136940","136940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889889","2018-04-26","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2018-04-23","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the status is of the Electoral Commission investigation into the activities of Momentum during the 2017 General Election campaign.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136941","136941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889890","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when people in receipt of Support for Mortgage Interest will receive an acknowledgment from her Department confirming receipt of their loan application.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136942","136942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889891","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in her Department are available to visit Support for Mortgage Interest claimants with additional needs who require face-to-face support in understanding and completing the loan application process.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136943","136943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889892","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her departmental telephone helpline for Support for Mortgage Interest claimants has been fully functional in the last month.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136944","136944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889893","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much she has reallocated from her Department's budget for (a) low-level crime and (b) intelligence to the budget for enforced removals in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136945","136945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889894","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to increase the hourly rate to nursery providers under the 30-hours free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136946","136946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889895","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has plans for all the money provided to local authorities under the 30-hours free childcare scheme to be passed on to childcare providers.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136947","136947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889896","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 April 2018 to Question 134875, on Armed Forces, how the National Security Capabilities Review has been able to assess the size of the armed forces as sufficient to deliver Joint Force 2025 in the absence of a prescribed minimum number of personnel to deliver Joint Force 2025.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136948","136948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889897","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 April 2018 to Question 134875, on Armed Forces, whether he has made an estimate of the minimum size of the armed forces required for them to fulfill all their UK and overseas commitments.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136949","136949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889898","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to improve the gender balance in the take-up of STEM apprenticeships.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136950","136950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889899","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 March 2018 to Question 133895, when his Department plans to respond to the Cycle Safety Review, published on 9 March 2018.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136951","136951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889900","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government’s equality impact assessment for universal credit identified any potential negative impacts on women.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136952","136952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889901","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she (a) has had or (b) plans to have with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on automatic split payments for women receiving universal credit.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136953","136953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889902","2018-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of effect of Personal Learning Plans in ensuring the delivery of hate crime education in prisons.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136954","136954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889903","2018-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department holds on prisoners' Personal Learning Plans; and what such data his Department plans to hold in future.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136955","136955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889904","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Commander UK Amphibious Forces Headquarters is to be folded into a revamped Maritime Battle Staff  this year.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136956","136956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889905","2018-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training is provided to prisoners on the use of social media; and under what programmes such training operates.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136957","136957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889906","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support human rights groups working on business and human rights.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136958","136958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889907","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations he made to his counterpart in the Thai Government on the imposition of a 10 million Baht fine on Andy Hall for damages to Natural Fruit Co Ltd. following his civil defamation conviction.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136959","136959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889908","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of changes to amphibious capabilities if Commander UK Amphibious Forces is merged into the Maritime Battle Staff.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136960","136960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889909","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to counter open-source tracking of RAF aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136961","136961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889910","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to trial dismounted position and navigation sensors for the armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136962","136962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889911","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to expand its portfolio of air-to-ground missile; and which current projects are considering this capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136963","136963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889912","2018-04-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which local authorities have not had a corporate peer challenge from the Local Government Association since 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136964","136964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889913","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to integrate the Mk41 Vertical Launch System into Type 31 frigates as part of that programme's requirements.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136965","136965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889914","2018-04-26","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many (a) staff and (b) consultants in his Department are paid more than the Prime Minister pro-rata.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136966","136966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889915","2018-04-26","Department for International Trade","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many (a) staff and (b) consultants in his Department are paid more than the Prime Minister pro-rata.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136967","136967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889916","2018-04-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) staff and (b) consultants in his Department are paid more than the Prime Minister pro-rata.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136968","136968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889917","2018-04-26","Scotland Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, for what reasons his Department's responses to Freedom of Information requests have not been published on the publications section of his Departments web pages since 21 August 2014;  and where those responses are now published.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136969","136969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889918","2018-04-25","Cabinet Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on whether non-UK EU citizens who are serving as councillors will be able to continue to serve as councillors (a) during any transitional phase and (b) after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136970","136970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889919","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on negotiations for a new pharmacy contract; and what the timetable is for the interim arrangements published in the Drug Tariff to remain in place.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136971","136971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889920","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that stocks of medicines that are in short supply are distributed equitably and proportionately amongst community pharmacies.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136972","136972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889921","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what services and Government funding are available for women (a) in need of support throughout a crisis pregnancy and (b) after experiencing an abortion.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136973","136973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889922","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to offer an advanced service for community pharmacies to provide weight management to tackle obesity.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136974","136974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889923","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) competitiveness and (b) effectiveness of the wholesale pharmaceutical market to provide an affordable supply of medicines for patients.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136975","136975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889924","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will set a date for commencement of those provisions of the Deregulation Act 2015 which relate to public rights of way.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136976","136976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889925","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to respond to the letter of 21 February 2018 from the hon. Member for Bishop Auckland on the time taken to process the Basic Payment Scheme application of a constituent.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136977","136977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889926","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the accessibility of her Department's Claimant Service and Experience Survey for claimants with hearing loss.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136978","136978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889927","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133468, if he will place a copy of the most recent report of the Army’s internal audit of welfare and care issues at AFC Harrogate in the Library.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136979","136979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889928","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people of the Windrush generation have been denied out-of-work social security support in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136980","136980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889929","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people of the Windrush generation have been denied disability social security support in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136981","136981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889930","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people of the Windrush generation have been denied state pension support in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136982","136982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889931","2018-04-25","Church Commissioners","2018-04-23","To ask the Honourable Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, could she update the House on the view of the Church of England’s Education Office following the publication of the Government’s response to the Out-of-school education consultation.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136983","136983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889932","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to ban or limit the use of non-biodegradable plastic in the packaging of bread and other bakery products; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136984","136984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889933","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 28 March 2018 that his Department will have access to £600 million for the Dreadnought program this coming financial year, how these additional funds will be spent; and for what reasons access to additional funds was required.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136985","136985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889934","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the contingency fund for the Dreadnought programme that has been used to supplement that programme’s costs to date.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136986","136986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889935","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the case of R (QSA and others) v Secretary of State for the Home Department and Secretary of State for Justice [2018] EWHC 407 (Admin), if she will assess the equity of the criminal record disclosure regime to ensure that it balances the public interest with the rights of an individual applicant for employment.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136987","136987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889936","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of how much money from the Dreadnought programme’s contingency fund will be spent by that programme’s completion.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136988","136988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889937","2018-04-26","Department for International Development","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what proportion of her Department's aid budget has been allocated to Commonwealth countries in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136989","136989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889938","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, following the case of R (QSA and others) v Secretary of State for the Home Department and Secretary of State for Justice [2018] EWHC 407 (Admin), if she will ensure that the criminal record disclosure regime enables the filtering of multiple minor offences.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136990","136990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889939","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral evidence given by Ms Cat Little to the Public Accounts Committee on 14 March 2018, HC 880, whether his Department expects the projected costs of the Dreadnought programme to increase.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136991","136991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889940","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral evidence given by Ms Cat Little to the Public Accounts Committee on 14 March 2018, HC 880, how much money does his Department plan to bring forward to fund the Dreadnought programme.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136992","136992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889941","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Q97 of the oral evidence given by Stephen Lovegrove to the Public Accounts Committee on 14 March 2018, HC 880, what assessment his Department has made of the likelihood of the projected costs of funding the UK’s warhead programme, the Trident II missile programme and the common missile compartment programme increasing.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136993","136993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889942","2018-04-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of receipts from Right to Buy sales received by each local authority were retained for providing replacement social housing in each year since 2012-2013.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136994","136994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889943","2018-04-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timescale is for all the people who survived the Grenfell Tower fire to have moved into permanent new housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136995","136995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889944","2018-04-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timescale is for all high-rise residential accommodation with dangerous aluminium composite material cladding to have had it removed and replaced.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136996","136996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889945","2018-04-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will expand the clearing house scheme of housing for people with a history of rough sleeping.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136997","136997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889946","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that as many as possible (a) new and (b) existing homes reach energy performance certificate band C by 2035.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136998","136998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889947","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the long-term trajectory for energy performance standards across the private rented sector.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136999","136999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889948","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of energy performance standards in the social housing sector.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137000","137000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889949","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of levels of energy efficiency in (a) new and (b) existing commercial buildings.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137001","137001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889950","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to issue a call for evidence on the adequacy of trigger points for Energy Performance Certificates.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137002","137002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889951","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of including energy efficiency in the lending decisions of mortgage companies.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137003","137003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889952","2018-04-26","Department for International Trade","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, on what dates he or officials from his Department met with representatives of the Legatum Institute; which representatives of the Department and the Institute attended each meeting; and what was the content and purpose of each meeting.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137004","137004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889953","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of increasing the use of hydrogen for domestic heating on the level of household emissions.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137005","137005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889954","2018-04-25","Cabinet Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the annual infant mortality rates in England were by household income quintile for each of the past 10 years for which information is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137006","137006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889955","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an estimate of the cost to the public purse of ensuring that all homes are rated at least energy performance certificate band C by 2035; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137007","137007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889956","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average waiting times were for GP appointments in the 10 (a) most deprived and (b) least deprived areas of England in each of the past 10 years for which information is available,.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137008","137008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889957","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the long-term potential for hydrogen to lower the emissions required for the heating of residential properties.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137009","137009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889958","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the average number of GPs per income quintile of the population in England in each of the most recent 10 years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137010","137010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889959","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of DIY dentistry among low-income households.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137011","137011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889960","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to recruit a clinical nurse specialist to support adults in the neuromuscular service at Salford Royal NHS Trust.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137012","137012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889961","2018-04-26","Treasury","2018-04-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received relief from the hydrocarbon oils duty on climate change levy supply of taxable commodities not for burning or consuming in the UK in the most recent financial year for which data is available.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137013","137013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889962","2018-04-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the live music industry in (a) London and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137014","137014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889963","2018-04-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to support women’s football in (a) Lewisham, Deptford constituency, (b) London and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137015","137015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889964","2018-04-25","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Football Association on women’s football.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137016","137016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889965","2018-04-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason Homes England has not produced quarterly updates on the (a) Affordable Homes Programme 2015 to 2018 and (b) Shared Ownership and Affordable Homes Programme 2016 to 2021 in each of the last two years, and if he will take steps to ensure that the information is published.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137017","137017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889966","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of girls who play football in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137018","137018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889967","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to attend the UN General Assembly conference on nuclear disarmament from 14 to 16 May.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137019","137019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889968","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 April 2018 to Question 135350, if she will estimate the number of people in receipt of the upper rate of employment support allowance who have died of motor neurone disease since October 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137020","137020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889969","2018-04-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the Shared Housing and Affordable Homes Programme 2016-21 prospectus will be updated to reflect additional funding committed since January 2017.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137021","137021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889970","2018-04-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the starter homes land fund that has been spent to date.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137022","137022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889971","2018-04-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the total spending on grant funding for affordable homes by the (a) Homes and Communities Agency and (b) Greater London Authority was in each financial year from 2009-10 to 2017-18.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137023","137023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889972","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships are available in (a) Lewisham, Deptford constituency, (b) Lewisham borough and (c) London.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137024","137024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889973","2018-04-26","Cabinet Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what dates the quarterly supplier reviews for Serco were collected; and when the next quarterly supplier review for that company is due.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137025","137025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889974","2018-04-26","Cabinet Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what dates the quarterly supplier reviews for Capita were collected; and when the next quarterly supplier review for that company is due.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137026","137026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889975","2018-04-25","Cabinet Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information the Government uses from the quarterly returns of strategic suppliers; and for what purpose the Government uses that information.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137027","137027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889976","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many notifications her Department's secure portal has received of bank current accounts which match immigration checks; how many of those notifications resulted in enforcement action by her Department; how many of those notifications included information about regular payments to the account; and what were the nationalities of the account holders.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137028","137028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889977","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of people from (a) Lewisham, Deptford constituency and (b) Lewisham borough who graduated from university in the 2016-17 academic year.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137029","137029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889978","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the average weekly cost of a childcare place in (a) Lewisham, Deptford constituency, (b) Lewisham borough and (c) London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137030","137030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889979","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment the Government made prior to the introduction of the hostile environment immigration policy of its potential effect on the (a) entitlement to social security support and (b) general wellbeing of Commonwealth migrants who have been long-term residents of the UK.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137031","137031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889980","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions her Department has had with the Home Office on the effect of the hostile environment immigration policy on the entitlement of Commonwealth migrants who have been long-term residents of the UK to social security support.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137032","137032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889981","2018-04-26","Cabinet Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to Capita's refinancing deal announced on 23 April 2018, whether that company has been designated a high risk supplier; and whether an improvement plan has been agreed with that company.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137033","137033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889982","2018-04-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Departments holds on the average cost of a home purchased by first-time buyers in (a) Lewisham, Deptford constituency, (b) Lewisham borough and (c) London in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137034","137034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889983","2018-04-25","Treasury","2018-04-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's policy is on a cap on banker's bonuses after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137035","137035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889984","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government has provided to interested parties in respect of establishing a second commercial air link to the Falkland Islands.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137036","137036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889985","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visitor visas have been (a) applied for and (b) granted for each non-EU country in (i) 2017 and (ii) 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137037","137037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889986","2018-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many meetings have taken place between private water companies and (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department in the last six months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137038","137038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889987","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many meetings have taken place between private water companies and (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department in the last six months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137039","137039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889988","2018-04-26","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the timetable is for the Derry City Deal to be signed.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137040","137040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889989","2018-04-26","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will make an assessment of the (a) economic and (b) fiscal effect of the Government's proposals for a Derry city deal.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137041","137041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889990","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much compensation has been received by victims of trafficking identified by the Gangmasters' Licensing Authority in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137042","137042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889991","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2018 to Question 135421, how many potential victims of trafficking were identified from 1 October 2015 to 30 June 2017 during the period over which Operation Magnify was conducted.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137043","137043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889992","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2018 to Question 135421 on Construction: Undocumented Workers, how many of the 85 potential victims of trafficking identified during Operation Magnify were arrested prior to being identified in that way; and for which offences those arrests took place.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137044","137044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889993","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2018 to Question 135421, how many arrests of potential perpetrators of trafficking and modern slavery were made in relation to cases of trafficking identified during Operation Magnify; and what the outcome of those arrests has been.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137045","137045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889994","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which agency is leading Operation Aidant; and between which agencies have partnership agreements been established.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137046","137046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889995","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many potential victims of trafficking have been (a) identified and (b) referred to the National Referral Mechanism under Operation Aidant.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137047","137047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889996","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many arrests for illegal working have been made during Operation Aidant.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137048","137048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889997","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 135084, how many fines for the employment of illegal workers have been levied since the commencement of the scheme in 2008.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137049","137049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889998","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an recent assessment of the link between adverse childhood experiences and (a) risky health behaviours, (b) chronic health conditions and (c) premature death.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137050","137050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/889999","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in how many IVF cycles where 20 or more eggs were collected fresh embryo transfers were carried out in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015, (d) 2016 and (e) 2017.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137051","137051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890000","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in how many IVF cycles where 15 or more eggs were collected were fresh embryo transfers were carried out in (a) 2013, (b) 2014, (c) 2015, (d) 2016 and (e) 2017.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137052","137052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890001","2018-04-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for commencing and concluding the planned three-yearly review of the implementation of shared parental leave.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137053","137053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890002","2018-04-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make representations to the freeholders of Heysmoor Heights, Liverpool on the funding the fire safety measures required after the Grenfell Tower tragedy as a result of the decision by the owners of Cityscape to fund their fire safety measures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137054","137054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890003","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent progress has been made on identifying a new contractor to complete the building of the new Royal Liverpool University Hospital after the collapse of Carillion; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137055","137055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890004","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to make an assessment of the adequacy of support provided to registered disabled students (a) at and (b) about to enter further or higher education.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137056","137056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890005","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many registered disabled students in (a) further and (b) higher education have received support from his Department in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137057","137057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890006","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what mental health support is available for teachers in (a) the North East and (b) England.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137058","137058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890007","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps Network Rail is taking to improve power supply on the East Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137059","137059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890008","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of upgrading the power supply on the East Coast Main Line to ensure that the network is ready for the full roll-out of Class 800 and Class 801 trains.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137060","137060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890009","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the net change has been in the number of (a) primary school teachers and (b) secondary school teachers in the North East in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137061","137061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890010","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department and Network Rail are taking to make the East Coast Main Line a digital railway.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137062","137062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890011","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 135177, how many of the applicants for the position of Chair of the Social Mobility Commission were (a) women and (b) BAME.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137063","137063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890012","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps Network Rail are taking to reduce journey times on the East Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137064","137064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890013","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy in the number of neuromuscular NHS consultants available to meet the treatment needs of patients with neuromuscular conditions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137065","137065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890014","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the net change has been in the number of police officers in (a) the North East and (b) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137066","137066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890015","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS operations were cancelled in (a) the North East and (b) England in each of the last three months.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137067","137067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890016","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) discussions and (b) correspondence his Department has had with Greater Anglia in relation to its commitment to provide four 90-minute services per day between Norwich and London during calendar year 2018.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137068","137068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890017","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of allowing women to take misoprostol at home; and whether abortion clinics provide facilities to allow women to remain at the clinic until the process has finished.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137069","137069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890018","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many indulgence passages have been granted by the RAF to (a) service personnel by branch of the armed forces and (b) civilians in each of the last five years; and to which overseas locations those passages were granted.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137070","137070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890019","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 131978, how can residents who live near an incinerator find out the amount of (a) PM2.5, (b) PM1 and (c)  PM0.1 particulate matter emitted by the incinerator.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137071","137071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890020","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 131978, why incinerators are exempt from monitoring and reporting on emissions of PM 2.5 and of PM10, when other industries are required separately to monitor and report the incidence of such particles.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137072","137072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890021","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the 11 intelligence analyst pinch-points are which are referred to in paragraph 2.5 on page 19 of the National Audit Office's report, Ensuring sufficient skilled military personnel, published on 18 April 2018.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137073","137073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890022","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Nigeria on the return of abductees from (a) Chibok and (b) other parts of that country.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137074","137074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890023","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help tackle modern slavery in Libya.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137075","137075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890024","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Design Acceptance Certificate for the European Pressurised Reactor expires in December 2022.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137076","137076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890025","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Design Acceptance Certificate for the European Pressurised Reactor is renewable; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137077","137077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890026","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether EDF has informed him that it plans to seek a renewal of the Design Acceptance Certificate (DAC) for the European Pressurised Reactor when the current DAC expires; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137078","137078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890027","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Design Acceptance Certificate for the European Pressurised Reactor (EPR) could be used for a re-designed EPR; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137079","137079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890028","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 2.5 on page 19 of the National Audit Office's report, Ensuring sufficient skilled military personnel, published on 18 April 2018, what assessment his Department has made on the effect of the shortfall of intelligence analysts on its operations and its ability to deliver agreed defence tasks.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137080","137080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890029","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135379 on Incinerators, what equipment is used by operators of waste incinerators (a) monitor and (b) report on emissions of (i) PM10 and (ii) PM2.5.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137081","137081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890030","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Ministerial approval was sought by UK Border Force prior to re-advertising roles in the Northern Ireland office without the requirement to hold a British passport.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137082","137082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890031","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is the policy of the UK Border Force no longer to require its employees across the UK to be British citizens.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137083","137083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890032","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the provision of careers information, advice and guidance in schools accommodates the needs of young people with special educational needs and disabilities.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137084","137084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890033","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the careers strategy, what plans his Department has to extend the provision of qualified careers guidance counsellors.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137085","137085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890034","2018-04-26","Cabinet Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the process is for deciding which public sector jobs are reserved and require British citizenship.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137086","137086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890035","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) US administration, (b) Japanese Government and (c) South Korean Government on the planned talks between the US and North Korea.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137087","137087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890036","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the criteria are for the Government deciding to review the sanctions which the UK imposes on North Korea.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137088","137088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890037","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135379 on 19th April 2018, what the reason is for the question on Form PI-1 - Pollution Inventory Reporting which requires operators of many industrial processes to report separately on emissions of PM10 and PM2.5 when there is no commercially available equipment for the continuous monitoring of PM10 and PM2.5.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137089","137089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890038","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135158, if he will classify paramedic science as an exception course to allow those who study it as a second degree to obtain a student loan.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137090","137090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890039","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Thai counterpart on the recent ruling that UK human rights activist, Andy Hall, must pay 10 million Baht in damages to the Natural Fruit Co Ltd. as a result of his conviction for civil defamation conviction; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137091","137091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890040","2018-04-25","Department for International Trade","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what safeguards are in place to ensure that UK companies investing in the Thai poultry farm industry comply with (a) business and (b) human rights obligations.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137092","137092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890041","2018-04-26","Attorney General","2018-04-23","To ask the Attorney General, when he plans to answer Question 132843.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137093","137093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890042","2018-04-30","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether regular safeguarding inspections of sub-contractors are carried out by the Salvation Army in its capacity as  the Government’s modern slavery victim care contract manager.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137094","137094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890043","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his oral contribution of 23 April 2018, whether he will plans to realigning the definition of lethal autonomous weapons within the eight month period recommended by the House of Lords Report on Artificial Intelligence, published on 16 April 2018.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137095","137095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890044","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what action she is taking to ensure adequate access to housing for the Windrush generation.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137096","137096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890045","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the report of the Women and Equalities Select Committee, Building for Equality: Disability and the Built Environment, published on 25 April 2017. what plans his Department has update Local Government Note 1/11 published in October 2011 to take into account the recommendations on shared space schemes.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137097","137097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890046","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any Government-owned companies are responsible for train maintenance on the West Coast mainline.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137098","137098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890047","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the incidence of chlamydial abortion in sheep.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137099","137099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890049","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to amend the driving test to take into account shared space schemes.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137100","137100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890050","2018-04-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135870, on Theatre: Closures, whether his Department has taken any steps to ascertain the viability of regional theatre.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137101","137101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890051","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to introduce a means-test for the £200 self-contribution under the disabled students' allowance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137102","137102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890052","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons why Form PI-1 - Pollution Inventory Reporting sets the reporting threshold for PM2.5 at 1000kg per annum and the reporting threshold for PM10 at 1000 kg per annum when the reporting threshold for total particulate matter is 10,000 kg per annum.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137103","137103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890053","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of conferring qualified teacher status on people who have completed the (a) the early years professional status and (b) early years teacher status, and if he will make a statement on his Department's early years workforce strategy.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137104","137104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890054","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what processes her Department uses to notify people of their state pension entitlement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137105","137105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890055","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have not received notification of state pension entitlement within two months of retirement  in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137106","137106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890056","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department provides compensation to people who do not receiver notification of state pension entitlement within two months of their retirement date.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137107","137107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890057","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will make it his policy to review the early years national funding formula to enable childcare settings to pay graduate-level wages to at least one member of staff.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137108","137108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890059","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking ensure the adequacy of guidance issued to childcare providers on the support his Department offers on graduate qualifications.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137109","137109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890060","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to improve the transparency of the (a) content of the modules within the early years initial teacher training course and (b) routes from that course to qualifications that can follow.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137110","137110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890061","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to his answer of 20 April 2018 to Question 135442 on Air Pollution, what steps he has taken to ensure that (a) the public and (b) people living in close proximity to waste incinerator sites have adequate information on the dispersal of  emissions of (i) PM 0.1, (ii) PM 1, (iii) PM 2.5 and (iv) PM10 from waste incinerator sites.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137111","137111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890062","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will disaggregate the data for primary initial teacher training and those for the early years initial teacher training programme in any future relevant publications on gov.uk.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137112","137112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890063","2018-04-25","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to publish its report on Pakistan covering immigration and political and human rights.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137113","137113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890064","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of introducing mandatory early years training for reception teachers.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137114","137114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890065","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the transfer of (a) urban and industrial by-products and (b) hazardous waste from Israel to the West Bank.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137115","137115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890066","2018-04-26","Department for International Development","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Idlib, Syria; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137116","137116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890067","2018-04-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to promote the Rent to Buy scheme as a route into home ownership; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137117","137117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890068","2018-04-26","Department for International Development","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April to Question 134885, on Israel: Palestinians, which local civil society organisations her officials consulted.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137118","137118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890069","2018-04-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to increase access to sports and fitness facilities for people on low incomes.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137119","137119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890070","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on outcomes for vulnerable children of the variation in the level of access to children's services throughout England.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137120","137120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890071","2018-04-25","Attorney General","2018-04-23","To ask the Attorney General, how many police officers have been charged by the CPS and then acquitted after a trial in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137121","137121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890072","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 23 April 2018 to Question 136501, how the Government plans for the UK to participate in the European Medicines Agency during the transition period after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137122","137122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890073","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glenrothes of 12 March 2018 on applications for personal independence payments from people affected by mental illness.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137123","137123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890074","2018-04-30","Department for International Development","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State, Department for International Development of 18 April 2018, Official Report, column 307 on Modern Slavery, what the functions of the business hub will be; where the hub will be located; and what the hub's governance structure will be.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137124","137124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890075","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to promote careers in the NHS.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137125","137125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890076","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to extend the 28-week cap on Statutory Sick Pay.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137126","137126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890077","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department plans to alter the criteria for industrial injuries disablement benefit so that more workers left with long-term injuries at work are able to receive payments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137127","137127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890078","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with the Home Department on the effect of (a) the status of immigration bail under Schedule 10 to the Immigration Act 2016, and (b) associated bail conditions prohibiting studying on the ability of asylum seekers to (i) take part in educational activities and (ii) sit examinations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137128","137128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890079","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support visits by urban schools to the countryside.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137129","137129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890080","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Red Ensign Group conference 2018 is planned to take place; whether officials of his Department plan to attend that conference; and what the cost to the Maritime and Coastguard Agency is of (a) supporting and (b) attending that conference.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137130","137130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890081","2018-04-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the recommendations made by Marcus Keppel-Palmer in his Report, Stand up for seating: Why all-seated football stadia should be reconsidered.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137131","137131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890082","2018-04-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he has made an assessment of the risk to safety of football supporters standing during football matches.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137132","137132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890083","2018-04-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on the capacity at football stadia of the introduction of safe standing areas.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137133","137133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890084","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health  and Social Care, how many Health Service Investigation Branch investigations into late-term stillbirths were (a) undertaken and (b) completed in 2017.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137134","137134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890085","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on what date the Health Service Investigation Branch took responsibility for investigating avoidable baby deaths; and what estimate he has made of the annual caseload in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137135","137135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890086","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether parents will be involved in Health Service Investigation Branch investigations of avoidable baby deaths; and whether evidence collected during such investigations will be shared with parents.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137136","137136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890087","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the number of NHS professionals working in (a) endoscopy and (b) on screening for bowel cancer for men and women between the age of 50 and 74.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137137","137137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890088","2018-04-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria he plans to use to decide whether to support lifting the suspension of Russian credentials at the council of Europe.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137138","137138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890089","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have had a reduction in the amount of their benefit entitlement as a result of the transfer from disability living allowance to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137139","137139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890090","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money has been accrued to the public purse from applications for citizenship from the Windrush generation.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137140","137140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890091","2018-04-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that claimants of benefits remain eligible for the Motability scheme as a result of the change from disability living allowance to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137141","137141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890092","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to ensure the effectiveness of capacity assessments for people with learning disabilities who wish to look after a child.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137142","137142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890093","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the criteria are for capacity tests used to assess a person's suitability to look after a child; and what guidance his Department has issued on the use of those criteria.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137143","137143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890094","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many meetings he has had with representatives of local authorities since 1 January 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137144","137144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890095","2018-04-26","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in the Borough of Halton were prosecuted for illicit drugs offences in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137145","137145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890096","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department plans to take to reduce delays at the Dartford Crossing.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137146","137146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890097","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Government of Eritrea on respect for (a) freedom of religion and (b) human rights.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137147","137147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890098","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment has he made of effect on recruitment to the Royal Navy of the opening of the United Kingdom Naval Support Facility in Mina Salman, Bahrain.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137148","137148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890099","2018-04-25","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has held discussions with other Ministers on the process by which EU regulations and directives will enter into force during the implementation period after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137149","137149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890100","2018-04-25","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the implementation of European Court of Justice judgments during the implementation period after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137150","137150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890101","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many A&E units closed in each constituency in each year between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137151","137151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890102","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospitals closed in each constituency in each year between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137152","137152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890103","2018-04-26","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 904216, in which constituencies the 110 libraries were that closed between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137153","137153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890104","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money the Child Maintenance Service has collected from paying parents in collection fees in (a) the UK and (b) in Scotland in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137154","137154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890105","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of apprenticeship starts have been taken by (a) a person of BAME background and (b) women in each sector subject area in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137155","137155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890106","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the additional cost to students in loan fees following the increase in March of the retail prices index.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137156","137156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890107","2018-04-26","Department for Education","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the oral contribution of the Chancellor of the Exchequer of 17 April 2018, Official Report, column 176, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the future of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137157","137157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890108","2018-04-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many complaints about the Green Deal have been raised with him under the Green Deal Framework (Disclosure Acknowledgement Redress etc) Regulations 2012; and how many of his decisions resulted in (a) a reduction (b) a cancellation  (c) no sanction and (d) no cancellation in respect of a green deal loan.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137158","137158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890109","2018-04-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of green deal complaints are appealed to the Secretary of State under the Green Deal Framework (Disclosure Acknowledgement Redress etc) Regulations 2012.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137159","137159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890110","2018-04-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what is the average waiting time was for a decision on a green deal complaint raised with the Secretary of State under the Green Deal Framewor (Disclosure Acknowledgement Redress etc) Regulations 2012.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137160","137160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890111","2018-04-26","Cabinet Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has designated G4S as a high risk strategic supplier.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137161","137161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890112","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money the Child Maintenance Service collected from receiving parents in collection fees in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137162","137162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890113","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount in collection fees taken by the Child Maintenance Service from paying parents has been in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137163","137163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890114","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount in collection fees taken by the Child Maintenance Service from receiving parents has been in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137164","137164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890115","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-resident parents are in maintenance arrears through the Child Maintenance Service; and what amount of money is outstanding in such arrears in Scotland.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137165","137165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890116","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-resident parents are in maintenance arrears through the Child Maintenance Service; and what amount of money is outstanding in such arrears in Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath constituency.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137166","137166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890117","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential long-term trauma and detrimental effects on mental health caused to people affected by the Windrush scandal; and what steps the Government is taking to provide counselling, talking therapies and ongoing support to all those affected and their families.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137167","137167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890118","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to maintain competition in clinical trials after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137168","137168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890119","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to ensure continued access to the EU clinical trials portal and database after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137169","137169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890120","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to support the maintenance of links between regulators, research ethics committees, researchers and the pharmaceutical industry in the UK and the European Medicines Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137170","137170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890121","2018-04-26","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will negotiate a deal with the EU to allow mutual recognition agreements on the manufacture and distribution of investigational medicinal products and pharmacovigilance services after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137171","137171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890122","2018-04-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many violence-at-work incidents have been reported at Govan job centre; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137172","137172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890123","2018-04-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to eliminate violence-at-work incidents in (a) Govan jobcentre and (b) her Department's offices across the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137173","137173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890124","2018-04-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the most recent risk assessment was conducted at Govan jobcentre on violence at work; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137174","137174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890125","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) full-time equivalent staff and (b) people were employed in the Passport Office in (i) May and (ii) November of (A) 2013, (B) 2014, (C) 2015, (D) 2016 and (E) 2017.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137175","137175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890126","2018-04-27","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the projected full-time equivalent staff numbers are for the Passport Office in both peak periods and low season in (a) 2018, (b) 2019 and (c) 2020; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137176","137176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890127","2018-04-26","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Solicitors Regulation Authority on the conduct of Blackstones and BW Legal in their work on behalf of private parking companies.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137177","137177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890128","2018-04-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing enhanced consular services in Hargeisa, Somaliland.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137178","137178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890129","2018-04-26","Department for International Development","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid her Department provided aid to Somaliland which was delivered by multilateral agencies in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137179","137179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890130","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to support commuters on the Great Western line who will be affected by planned closures and alterations to services in summer 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137180","137180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890131","2018-04-26","Home Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many inquiries about issues relating to the immigration status of members of the Windrush generation have been received by her Department (a) on the Windrush helpline and (b) from people in Wales in 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137181","137181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890132","2018-04-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to issue new guidance to planning authorities on the proportion of affordable homes in any new development on which they can insist; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137182","137182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890133","2018-04-26","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the UK has to increase military assistance to Jordan for (a) training and (b) equipment.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137183","137183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890134","2018-04-26","Department for Transport","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what methodology will be used to decide which road schemes to fund this summer; and whether his Department is considering funding a north-west relief road in Shrewsbury.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137184","137184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890135","2018-04-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with European countries on preventing the construction of the Nord Stream 2 pipeline.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137185","137185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890136","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his Polish counterpart on increasing the number of UK troops on rotational deployment to the Suwalki gap.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137186","137186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890137","2018-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what military assistance in the form of (a) funding and (b) training his Department provided to Jordan in (i) 2005, (ii) 2015 and (iii) 2017.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137187","137187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/890138","2018-04-25","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the UK will retain the exclusive use of the six-nautical-miles and 12-nautical-miles fishing zones during the proposed 21-month implementation period before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 137188","137188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/886260","2018-04-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussion he has had with his counterparts in other EU member states on cyber security risks relating to 5G mobile networks.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136455","136455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887864","2018-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to allow people to submit evidence by e-mail to the Money Claims Online website.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136859","136859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887865","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to support SMEs to tender for contracts issued as a result of the National Shipbuilding Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136860","136860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887866","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to (a) support and (b) grow the UK defence radar industry.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136861","136861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887867","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to upgrade the Sampson radars on the Type 45 destroyers to provide those destroyers with ballistic missile detection and tracking capability.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136862","136862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887868","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the existing Type 102 radar held in storage by BAE Systems is not currently deployed.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136863","136863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887869","2018-04-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to improve the availability of support that is offered for the friends and families of suicide victims.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136864","136864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887870","2018-04-24","Department for International Development","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Bangladeshi Government on the protection of Rohingya refugees in Bangladesh from the effects of the monsoon season; and (a) with whom she had and (b) what the outcome was of those discussions.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136865","136865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887871","2018-04-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to provide support to owners of new-build leasehold homes who are charged fees other than ground rent by the freeholder.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136866","136866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887872","2018-04-24","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will hold discussions with the Secretary of State for Justice on introducing tighter measures for companies that employ drivers so that such companies are automatically informed when an employee is convicted of a motoring offence and subsequently loses their professional driving licence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Mr Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136867","136867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887873","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135939, how much funding his Department provided to former Wakefield City Academy Trust schools and their new trusts by 1 April 2018.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136868","136868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887874","2018-04-25","Department for Education","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2018 to Question 135939 on Wakefield City Academies Trust (WCAT), if he will list the (a) nine WCAT schools for which new trusts have been identified but which have not yet transferred to them and (b) one WCAT school for which no new trust has been identified.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136869","136869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887875","2018-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2018 to Question 135699, how much additional funding his Department has allocated to the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory for running costs of the Chemical Weapons Defence Centre during the current spending period.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136870","136870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887876","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of staff morale in the Health and Safety Executive.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136871","136871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887877","2018-04-25","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of staff morale in the Advisory, Conciliation and Arbitration Service.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136872","136872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887878","2018-04-24","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that taxis and private hire vehicles are accessible to people with disabilities.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136873","136873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887879","2018-04-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the statutory definition is of a disability access vehicle; and whether that definition is different to a wheelchair accessible vehicle.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136874","136874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887880","2018-04-24","Department for Education","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to consult small and medium-sized businesses on the future of (a) technical and (b) vocational education.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136875","136875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887881","2018-04-24","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve bus services in (a) the East Midlands and (b) Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136876","136876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887882","2018-04-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a decision on the base-porting arrangements of the new Type 26 frigates will be announced in the report of the defence modernisation programme.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136877","136877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887883","2018-04-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the new guidance on viability with fixed returns for developers and landowners does not lead to a reduction in the number of affordable homes being built due to the construction of only that proportion of such homes which ensures they meet fixed profit levels.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136878","136878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887884","2018-04-26","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of additional affordable homes that will be built over the next 10 years as a result of the new viability system in the updated National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136879","136879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887885","2018-04-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will put in place provisions to ensure that when a developer uses a viability assessment to argue down the affordable housing element of a housing scheme on the grounds that the scheme would not meet its fixed profit level but the scheme subsequently makes a larger profit than predicted the developer will make a contribution towards affordable housing in the community.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136880","136880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887886","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time is for a hearing by the Upper Tribunal of an appeal by her Department against a decision by the First-tier Tribunal to allow an award of personal independence payment.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136881","136881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887887","2018-04-24","Wales Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the renaming of the Second Severn Crossing.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136882","136882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887888","2018-04-24","Wales Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will publish the representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the renaming of the Second Severn Crossing.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136883","136883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887889","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial safeguards his Department have put in place to protect vulnerable claimants in the event that their claim is delayed as a result appeals by her Department on the First-tier decision to award personal Independence payments.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136884","136884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887890","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to publish a digital railway (a) strategy and (b) delivery plan.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136885","136885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887891","2018-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria her Department uses for appealing decisions by the first-tier tribunal  to award personal independence payments.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136886","136886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887892","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what  the timetable is for the electrification of the Bolton to Preston line; and what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Network Rail deliver the project.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136887","136887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887893","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has plans to amend the (a) Northern, (b) Transpennine Express and (c) East Midlands Trains franchise as a result of the delay to the introduction of the May 2018 timetable.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136888","136888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887894","2018-04-24","Wales Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with officials at Clarence House on the petition against the renaming of the Second Severn Crossing.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136889","136889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887895","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the capacity of Network Rail to (a) plan for and (b) deliver the December 2018 timetable.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136890","136890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887896","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people with dementia are currently detained under the Mental Health Act 1983.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136891","136891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887897","2018-04-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what financial support the Government has provided for research into the use, composting and tertiary recycling of polylactic acid as fresh feedstock for the manufacture of plastic bottles in the last financial year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136892","136892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887898","2018-04-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with industry representatives on setting a date by which polyethylene terephthalate in plastic bottles will have been phased out and replaced by polylactic acid.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136893","136893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887899","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of incidences of swine fever in Europe; what recent assessment he has made of the level of risk of swine fever outbreaks in the UK; what contingency plans his Department has put in place in the event of an outbreak of swine fever in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136894","136894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887900","2018-04-24","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to update the Highway Code.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136895","136895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887901","2018-04-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate his Department has made of the cost of the trim and compensation system for the Dreadnought programme; and whether that estimate is an increase on previously made estimates.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136896","136896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887902","2018-04-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, from which budgets the cost of the Dreadnought programme’s trim and compensation system will be funded.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136897","136897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887903","2018-04-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his (a) Israeli and (b) Palestinian counterparts on the Middle East peace process.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136898","136898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887904","2018-04-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of Exhibit 606 as listed in Part 2 of the Service Inquiry report into the accident involving Tornado GR4 ZD743 and Tornado GR4 ZD812 over the Moray Firth on 3 July 2012.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136899","136899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887905","2018-04-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he intends to meet with representatives of the Caribbean to discuss concerns on the immigration status of people of Caribbean birth who have been living and working in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136900","136900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887906","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an estimate of the number of citizens of Caribbean birth currently living in the UK who in each year since 2010 (a) have been told they do not have the right to remain in the UK, (b) are awaiting deportation and (c) have been deported.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136901","136901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887907","2018-04-24","Department for International Development","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much money has been spent to support countries in the Caribbean in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136902","136902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887908","2018-04-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what records his Department made of emission changes in UK energy generation in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136903","136903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887910","2018-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what date he plans to introduce a UK-wide ban on ivory sales.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136904","136904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887911","2018-04-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to measure the carbon dioxide emissions of biomass energy generation plants.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136905","136905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887912","2018-04-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on the (a) employment and (b) involvement in any Ministry of Defence contracts of (i) spouses of Members of Parliament, (b) spouses of Ministers and (c) the spouse of the Prime Minister.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136906","136906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887913","2018-04-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to make an announcement on the reduced stake for fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136907","136907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887914","2018-04-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reason it has taken more than three months to assess the evidence on reducing the stakes on fixed odds betting terminals (FOBTs) following the closure of the consultation on gaming machines and social responsibility measures; and what steps have been taken to ensure that people who experience harm due to the high stakes on FOBTs in the interim are supported.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136908","136908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887915","2018-04-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have held meetings with representatives of bookmakers since the end of the consultation on proposals for changes to gaming machines and social responsibility measures.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136909","136909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887916","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the publication of the consultation on the regulation of medical associate professionals.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136910","136910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887917","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to ensure police forces have identified a single point of contact on modern slavery and exploitation at the (a) strategic command and (b) tactical investigative level.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136911","136911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887918","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that single points of contact for victims of modern slavery and exploitation (a) share best practice (b) convene quarterly regional meetings and (c) convene six-monthly national meetings.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136912","136912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887919","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to increase the capacity of the Modern Slavery Threat Group to produce intelligence-based assessments of the (a) national, (b) regional, and (c) cross-border threat from modern slavery.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136913","136913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887920","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to recommendation 4 of the Modern Slavery Act Review, what steps her Department have taken to introduce training for front-line (a) police officers and (b) criminal justice staff to (i) raise awareness of and (b) support victims of modern slavery.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136914","136914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887921","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to recommendation 5 of the Modern Slavery Act Review, what support has her Department provided to the Modern Slavery Threat Group to establish an online resource centre for (a) single points of contact and (b) approved account holders working for other organisations.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136915","136915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887922","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to recommendation 6 of the Modern Slavery Act Review, what support has her Department provided to the Modern Slavery Threat Group to (a) improve data collection by disseminating guidance on which cases should be recorded as exploitative or trafficking offences, and (b) enforce the use of nationally consistent processes to (i) collect and (ii) assess data and intelligence from partner organisations.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136916","136916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887923","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to recommendation 7 of the Modern Slavery Act Review, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that all complainants in (a) trafficking and (b) exploitation cases provide statements to police officers who are trained to deal with vulnerable witnesses.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136917","136917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887924","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to recommendation 8 of the Modern Slavery Act Review, what steps her Department has taken to adopt the two-stage Achieving Best Evidence interview process.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136918","136918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887925","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will meet representatives of Govia Thameslink Railway to discuss Great Northern Line rail services at Oakleigh Park.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136919","136919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887926","2018-04-25","Department for Transport","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Govia Thameslink Railway on the implementation of their proposed RailPlan20/20 timetable.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136920","136920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887927","2018-04-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care what information his Department holds on levels of (a) breast cancer, (b) bowel cancer, (c) cervical cancer, (d) diabetic eye, (e) abdominal aortic aneurysm and (f) fetal anomaly screening in each year since those NHS screening programmes were introduced.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136921","136921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887052","2018-04-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using faith-based leaders as facilitators to promote peace and reconciliation amongst the ethnic and religious communities in Syria and Iraq.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136620","136620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887053","2018-04-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential savings to be accrued to the public purse of the return of unused medicines to the NHS.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136621","136621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887054","2018-04-23","Department for International Development","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking help ensure the safety of schools in northern Nigeria from attack from Boko Haram.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136622","136622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887055","2018-04-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to promote environmental sustainability in businesses.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136623","136623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887056","2018-04-24","Department for Education","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to make Universities UK subject to Freedom of Information requests.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136624","136624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887057","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether Coagadex is available on the NHS for patients with the hereditary factor X deficiency bleeding disorder; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136625","136625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887058","2018-04-24","Department for Transport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities in increasing the number cycle paths on public roads.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136626","136626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887059","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to make an assessment of the potential merits of amending the law on the use of medicinal cannabis to expand its availability for people with (a) chronic pain and b) long-term degenerative conditions for whom other treatments haven't worked.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136627","136627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887060","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has the power and competence to issue a temporary licence for the treatment of Alfie Dingley which his parents have requested.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136628","136628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887061","2018-04-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133771, if his Department will take steps to notify Parliament when lethal force is used by British armed forces outside of an area of armed conflicts to which the UK is party.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136629","136629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887062","2018-04-24","Treasury","2018-04-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the security of HMRC’s practice of returning important personal documents including (a) passports and (b) birth certificates by standard post.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136630","136630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887063","2018-04-24","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February to Question 125468, how many gas SMETS2 meters have been installed, and how many of those meters have been connected to the DCC.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136631","136631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887064","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training is provided to teachers on (a) psychological and (b) trauma issues raised by young people with challenging behaviour.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136632","136632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887065","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to include practical life lessons into the PSHE curriculum.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136633","136633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887066","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of educating young people from Black and Minority Ethnic groups about their ethic cultural heritage.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136634","136634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887067","2018-04-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total value is of services delivered to his Department through contracts with Strategic Communications Laboratories since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136635","136635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887068","2018-04-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the total value is of services delivered to his Department through contracts with Strategic Communications Laboratories since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136636","136636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887069","2018-04-24","Department for International Trade","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to ensure that UK trade with developing countries will promote women’s rights after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136637","136637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887070","2018-04-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of access to arbitration for victims of press abuse and intrusion.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136638","136638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887071","2018-04-24","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take to ensure that children and their parents can receive legal redress where they have been victims of a large-scale data breach.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136639","136639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887072","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Government programmes that assist low-income families who are supporting children with autism.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136640","136640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887073","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to respond to the Green Paper on Transforming children and young people’s mental health provision.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136641","136641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887074","2018-04-23","Department for International Development","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to support programmes on (a) sexual and reproductive health and (b) assistance for survivors of gender based violence for Rohingya women and girls.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136642","136642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887075","2018-04-23","Department for International Development","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to programmes in Cox's Bazar to prepare that place for the forthcoming monsoon season.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136643","136643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887076","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking as a result of the statement by Andrew Haines, the Chief Executive of the Civil Aviation Authority, that the UK should remain in the European Aviation Safety Authority as full members.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136644","136644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887077","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of having an independent air safety regime on the ability (a) to land UK-certified aircraft in EU states and (b) of EU certified aircraft being able to land in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136645","136645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887078","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the UK not being a member of the European Aviation Safety Authority on the ability of UK flights to operate in EU airspace between the UK and Gibraltar.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136646","136646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887079","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what impact the UK being outside of the European Aviation Safety Authority would have on the ability of UK flights to operate in EU airspace flying in between the UK and the UK military bases on Cyprus.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136647","136647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887080","2018-04-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the options for procuring glucose monitoring devices for people with diabetes in order to ensure that those devices are procured effectively.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136648","136648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887081","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on the economy of the UK not participating in the EU digital single market.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136649","136649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887082","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect on the economy of the UK leaving the EU without replacing EU research funding.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136650","136650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887083","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, the proportion of Horizon 2020 (a) projects originating in the UK and (b) funding that the UK received in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136651","136651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887084","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what contingency plans have been made to replace EU research funding in the event that the UK is unable to conclude a withdrawal agreement with the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136652","136652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887085","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much EU research funding the UK received in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136653","136653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887086","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 134929 on Local Government Finance, whether the Government has provided any funding to date to (a) local authorities, (b) combined authorities and (c) elected mayors.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136856","136856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887087","2018-04-24","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many security staff were employed in each year since 2010, and if he will make a statement .","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136654","136654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887088","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to monitor the compliance of organisations and companies with their duty to provide accessible toilets under Document M of the 2010 Buildings Regulations 2010; and if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of those provisions in respect of that duty.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136655","136655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887089","2018-04-24","Department for Education","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information the Government holds on the number of young people not in education, employment or training in Newcastle.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136656","136656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887090","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of international comparators of rates of robbery since 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136857","136857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887091","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people susceptible to drug (a) use, (b) selling and (c) running as a result of (i) homelessness, (ii) exclusion from school and (iii) living in care.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136858","136858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887092","2018-04-23","Wales Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what regulations he (a) has introduced as a result of EU legislation since 23 June 2016 and (b) plans to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2018 and (ii) 2019; and what estimate he has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136657","136657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887093","2018-04-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with local authorities on funding for local government after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136658","136658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887094","2018-04-24","Department for Education","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussion he has had with representatives of the  British Assistive Technology Association on the £200 self-contribution required from disabled students who are in receipt of Disability Support Allowance funded equipment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136659","136659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887095","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on the registration of EU nationals for indefinite leave after the UK leaves the EU, and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136660","136660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887096","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with the National Fire Chiefs Council on reducing fires in the home with an electrical source of ignition.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136661","136661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887097","2018-04-23","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial strategy on reducing the number of electrical fires in the home caused by faulty white goods.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136662","136662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887098","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the Government's policy is on the introduction of legally-binding International Labour Organization Convention on ending violence and harassment in the world of work.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136663","136663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887099","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if the Government supports the explicit inclusion of (a) domestic workers and (b) unpaid care workers in the proposed International Labour Organization Convention on ending violence and harassment in the world of work.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136664","136664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887100","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to support the inclusion of the UN Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights in the proposed International Labour Organization Convention on ending violence and harassment in the world of work to ensure that companies adhere to the standards throughout their supply chains.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136665","136665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887101","2018-04-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has to ensure that (a) the UN Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights are included in the proposed ILO Convention on ending violence and harassment in work and (b) companies adhere to those standards throughout their supply chains.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136666","136666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887102","2018-04-24","Department for International Development","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will introduce the use of the Dun and Bradsheet human trafficking risk index when allocating funding.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136667","136667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887103","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date the proposal to destroy the Windrush landing cards was first presented to a Minister in her Department.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136668","136668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887104","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date a Minister in her Department approved the destruction of the Windrush landing cards.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136669","136669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887105","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date the Windrush landing cards were destroyed.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136670","136670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887106","2018-04-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many mobile phone masts there are in Ochil and South Perthshire constituency.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136671","136671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887107","2018-04-23","Treasury","2018-04-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to improve disabled access to public buildings through the tax system.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136672","136672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887108","2018-04-23","Treasury","2018-04-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to support charities undertaking building works through the tax system.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136673","136673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887109","2018-04-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she make it her policy to provide further (a) guidance and (b) financial support for WASPI women until they reach the state pension age.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136674","136674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887110","2018-04-24","Department for Transport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department has provided for transport projects in Coventry since 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136675","136675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887111","2018-04-24","Department for Education","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary school teachers have been recruited in each year since 2010, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136676","136676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887112","2018-04-24","Department for Education","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the number of people enrolling in secondary education teacher training.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136677","136677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887113","2018-04-24","Home Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children living in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry spent time in a police station as a place of safety as a result of a mental health condition in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136678","136678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887114","2018-04-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question 134985, on Armed Forces: Children, what the timetable is for the review into whether there is a requirement to extend the Educational Support Fund to be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136679","136679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887115","2018-04-24","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the answer of 27 February 2018 to question 128776, on Armed Forces: Officers, what the timetable is for the information requested to be provided.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136680","136680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887116","2018-04-23","Department for Education","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of parents not eligible to receive 30 hours free childcare because their income is from a University or other stipend.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136681","136681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887117","2018-04-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2018 to Question 134276, on Prison Service: Dismissal, how many of those 419 cases of dismissal resulted in referrals to the police; what those referrals were for; and what the outcomes of those referrals were.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136682","136682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887118","2018-04-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2018 to Question 134276, on Prison Service: Dismissal, what the grounds for dismissal were of each of the 133 staff dismissed for the reason labelled Other.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136683","136683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887119","2018-04-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions has he had with his counterpart in Pakistan on the effect of blasphemy laws on minority communities in Pakistan.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136684","136684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887120","2018-04-24","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of ring-fencing part of the rebate paid by the pharmaceutical industry in the next iteration of the Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme for the purposes of investing in NHS data infrastructure.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136685","136685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887121","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to protect the public purse from (a) risks and (b) liabilities during the construction of new nuclear power stations.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136686","136686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887122","2018-04-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Indian Government in respect of recent protests in India in support of religious freedoms.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136687","136687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887123","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will undertake to run a full public consultation prior to the use of any (a) loan guarantees from Government and (b) direct public funds to support the new nuclear programme.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136688","136688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887124","2018-04-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Brunei government on (a) freedom of religion and (b) respect for fundamental freedoms.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136689","136689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887125","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department is considering any funding options to support the new nuclear power station at Wylfa Newydd, Wales, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136690","136690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887126","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Japan on the project finances for the proposed new nuclear power station at Wylfa Newydd in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136691","136691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887127","2018-04-23","Department for Transport","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in EU member states on ensuring reciprocity of air traffic management systems after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136692","136692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/887128","2018-04-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what evidence his Department holds on the reliability of the performance of the advanced boiling water reactors being considered for the proposed new nuclear power station at Wylfa Newydd in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 136693","136693"
