"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514357","2016-04-25","Cabinet Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which directorates of the National Security Secretariat have experienced greater than average turnover in staff since May 2010.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34843","34843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514358","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total receipt from government asset sales was in 2015-16.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34917","34917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514359","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the value for money of the UK's financial contribution to the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34880","34880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514360","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials work in his Department's Referendum Unit; and what the estimated cost is of the Unit.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34958","34958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514361","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many national insurance numbers were issued to nationals from other EEA member states in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34959","34959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514362","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many national insurance numbers were issued to nationals from other EEA member states which have been active in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34960","34960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514363","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many new national insurance numbers were issued automatically to persons (a) turning 16 in each year since 2000 and (b) who have had to apply by virtue of not being automatically issued with a national insurance number in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34961","34961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514364","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost of establishing a system to calculate the indexation of child benefit payments in accordance with the proposal to amend EU Regulation (EC) No 883/2004 on the coordination of social security systems.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34965","34965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514365","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of child benefits exported by nationals of other EEA member states living in the UK; and what that cost would be were the proposed indexation from the amendment of Regulation (EC) No 883/2004 on the coordination of social security systems to be already implemented.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34966","34966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514366","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of non-UK EEA nationals who will be in receipt of child benefit payments in each of the next five years where the dependent is living outside the UK.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34962","34962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514367","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of cases of child benefit being exported outside the UK from 1 January 2020 when it is proposed that the UK will be permitted to index link that benefit payment to the member state where the dependent child resides.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34963","34963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514368","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to index link child benefit payments made in relation to children living outside the UK; and what his estimate is of the savings to the public purse from this index-linking.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34964","34964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514369","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made a financial assessment of the changes to the UK's fiscal position which will result from the renegotiation of the UK's terms of EU membership.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34968","34968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514370","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects to begin negotiations on the post-2020 EU Multi Annual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34969","34969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514371","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the annual amount that the UK will (a) pay into the EU, (b) receive in return through EU schemes and (c) receive in return through the UK rebate in each year between 2020 and 2030.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34970","34970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514372","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 22 October 2012, Official Report, column 619W, on child benefit: EU nationals, if he will provide the number of non-UK EEA nationals who have dependents eligible to receive child benefit where the dependent is (a) in the UK and (b) outside the UK by country in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and what his estimate is of the value to the public purse of the child benefit paid.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34967","34967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514373","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs plans to withdraw the valuation check services for the validation of valuation estimates of works of art and antiques as part of the withdrawal of the valuation check service for employee share ownership schemes.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34758","34758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514374","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings or consultations his Department had with companies and industry groups offering and promoting employee share ownership schemes before announcing the withdrawal of HM Revenue and Customs' valuation check service in February 2016.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34759","34759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514375","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will commission independent research on the potential effect on employee share ownership scheme take-up of planned withdrawal of the HM Revenue and Customs' valuation check service on 31 March 2016.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34760","34760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514376","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce further Pensioner Bonds with a higher interest rate than is available commercially.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34765","34765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514377","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the Government's review of English regional airports potentially affected by the devolution of Air Passenger Duty to be completed.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34766","34766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514378","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK public finances of fluctuations in the Pound Sterling-Euro exchange rate causing a decrease in funding received by the UK from EU funding schemes; and what contingencies he has arranged for such circumstances.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34861","34861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514379","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from (a) the EU Commission, (b) the EU Parliament and (c) other EU member states on (i) the future of the UK rebate and (ii) proposing the reduction of the UK rebate.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34859","34859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514380","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK public finances of fluctuations in the Pound Sterling-Euro exchange rate causing an increase in the amount of the UK's contribution to the EU budget; and what contingencies he has arranged for such circumstances.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34860","34860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514381","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 34 of his Department's paper, Budget 2016: Policy Costings, published in March 2016, what the source is of the £425 million  increase in revenue estimated for 2019-20 from abolishing the Carbon Reduction Commitment and offsetting increase to the Climate Change Levy.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34800","34800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514382","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 36 of his Department's paper, Budget 2016: Policy Costings, published in March 2016, what the source is of the £5 million increase in revenues from updating technologies with access to enhanced capital allowance for 2017-18 to 2020-21.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34799","34799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514383","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a list of all HM Revenue and Customs offices which are scheduled to close.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34775","34775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514384","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.95 of the Budget 2016, whether his Department plans to maintain the same level of funding for sports activities, breakfast clubs in schools and extending the school day in circumstances where receipts from the Soft Drinks Industry Levy decline as the tax base for that levy reduces.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34776","34776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514385","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.97 of the Budget 2016, what progress his Department is making on proposals for using the UK Guarantees Scheme for infrastructure in the circumstances referred to.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34777","34777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514386","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that changes to Stamp Duty Land Tax do not contravene EU legislation on discrimination in respect of trading activities.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34788","34788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514387","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many owners of listed properties used for residential purposes sought approval for alterations to those properties in (a) 2012, (b) 2013, (c) 2014 and (d) 2015.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34791","34791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514388","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to Article 18 of EU Directive 41/2003, what steps he has taken to ensure that the assets of Local Government Pension Scheme funds are invested in the best interests of the scheme members.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34785","34785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514389","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to Article 18 of EU Directive 41/2003, what steps he has taken to ensure that separation of the pension institution from the administration authorities has been achieved in Local Government Pension Schemes.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34786","34786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514390","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how he has assessed that EU Directive 41/2003 has been properly implemented in respect of the Local Government Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34787","34787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514391","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to ensure the adequacy of provision of affordable homes to rent to help house London's homeless population.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34796","34796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514392","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many parish councils were created in the last Parliament.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34840","34840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514393","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of local authorities expected to have a shortfall in adult social care funding after implementation of the two per cent social care precept.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34812","34812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514394","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what research his Department has commissioned on the effect of immigration on the demand for (a) housing and (b) for social housing.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37973","37973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514395","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount of additional housing needed to provide (a) private sector and (b) social sector accommodation for immigrants from (i) EU and (ii) non-EU countries.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37974","37974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514396","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the additional housing needed to provide (a) private and (b) social sector accommodation for immigrants from (i) EU and (ii) non-EU countries in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34975","34975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514397","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding the UK is due to receive in each year to 2030 of Regional Development Funds and Structural Funds under future EU Multi Annual Financial Frameworks.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37971","37971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514398","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of Regional Development Funds and Structural Funds that the UK is due to receive in each year to 2020 under the current EU Multi Annual Financial Framework.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 37972","37972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514399","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in local government spending on future votes turnout for elections in respect of staff capacity (a) for registration and (b) at polling stations; and what assessment he has made of the effect of such changes on (i) the provision of vote registration campaign materials and (ii) the number of people likely to vote by post.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34947","34947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514400","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidelines he has issued to local authorities to require them to record the proportion of their procurement spent on small and medium-sized businesses.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34925","34925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514401","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have submitted efficiency plans as part of the multi-year settlement offer.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34918","34918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514402","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what measures his Department has in place for helping to ensure that areas without parish or town councils are (a) serving demand for allotments and (b) ensuring adequate protection for currently designated allotment land.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34898","34898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514403","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of protection within the National Planning Policy Framework for ancient woodland.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34899","34899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514404","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to review the operation of the National Planning Policy Framework before the end of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34913","34913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514405","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of local government procurements that have been spent on small and medium-sized businesses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34922","34922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514406","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount of local government procurement that has been spent on small and medium-sized businesses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34923","34923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514407","2016-04-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the implementation of the Government's Digital Inclusion Strategy, published in April 2014.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34914","34914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514408","2016-04-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding his Department has allocated to (a) the digital inclusion strategy and (b) other digital inclusion measures in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34915","34915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514409","2016-04-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will place in the Library copies of all correspondence between Ministers in his Department and newspaper editors, executives and proprietors about press regulation policy and Leveson Part 2 since May 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34850","34850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514410","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of (a) the Cyber Streetwise campaign and (b) her Department's policies on reducing the level of cyber crime.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34921","34921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514411","2016-04-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to make announcements on progress on his plans for the next BBC Charter.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34762","34762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514412","2016-04-25","Cabinet Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the estimated cost is of introducing a National Defence medal; and what plans his Department has to reconsider the award of a National Defence medal.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34745","34745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514413","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made since the publication of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015 on the Trident renewal programme in November 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34747","34747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514414","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 April 2016 to Question 33374, what the conviction rate was for each offence in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34802","34802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514415","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) serving military personnel and (b) civilian staff were seconded to (i) the Joint Intelligence Organisation's Assessments Staff and (ii) the National Security Secretariat within the Cabinet Office during 2015.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34932","34932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514416","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of ex-service people with post-traumatic stress disorder in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34927","34927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514417","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the processes and policies in place proactively to identify symptoms of post-traumatic stress disorder in service-people returning from war zones.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34928","34928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514418","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military and (b) civilian UK personnel are currently deployed in Tunisia; and in what capacity such personnel are deployed.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34930","34930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514419","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the planned duration is of the current deployment of UK military personnel to Tunisia.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34931","34931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514420","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many enlisted soldiers gained A-levels while serving in the armed forces in each of the last five years; and in which subjects those A-levels were obtained.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34912","34912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514421","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33689, how many teachers of GCSE (a) English and (b) mathematics were employed by the armed forces in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34910","34910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514422","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children attending a breakfast club in primary schools in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) Bradford in the last 12 months for which records are available.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34881","34881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514423","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of children attending a breakfast club in secondary schools in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) Bradford in last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34889","34889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514424","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to make autism awareness a compulsory part of initial teacher training.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34892","34892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514425","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how she plans for the £10 million increase in funding to expand breakfast clubs in schools announced in paragraph 1.95 of Budget 2016 to be distributed; and how her Department plans to monitor the spending of that funding.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34905","34905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514426","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 April 2016 to Question 32295, what progress has been made on undertaking a psychological assessment for every child who enters the UK care system.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34919","34919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514427","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of additional breakfast club places which will be created by the £10 million increase in funding announced in paragraph 1.95 of Budget 2016 in (a) England, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) Bradford.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34906","34906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514428","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the annual salary was for directors at the New Schools Network in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34884","34884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514429","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether directors at the New Schools Network are required to declare any interests in relation to their position at that charity.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34885","34885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514430","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department has allocated to the New Schools Network in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34887","34887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514431","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many unsuccessful free school applications have been facilitated by the New Schools Network in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34888","34888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514432","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many complaints her Department has received on the activities of the New Schools Network in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34877","34877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514433","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many successful free school applications have been assisted by the New Schools Network in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34876","34876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514434","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research her Department has (a) undertaken and (b) commissioned on the effect of immigration on the demand for school places; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34955","34955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514435","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from (a) local authorities and (b) other bodies on the pressures on school places due to immigration from (i) EU and (ii) non-EU countries.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34954","34954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514436","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of creating a new (a) school place and (b) classroom in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34949","34949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514437","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on taking account of the effect on the demand for school places caused by immigration (a) in general and (b) from nationals from other EEA countries.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34950","34950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514438","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 April 2016 to Question 32295, what proportion of children in care had Strength and Difficulties Questionnaire scores which required further assessment be given to those children in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34956","34956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514439","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to increase the number of school places in Crawley.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34742","34742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514440","2016-04-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that smart meters are installed in areas with poor mobile signal.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34737","34737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514441","2016-04-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects the Government's review of the case for the Swansea Bay tidal lagoon to be completed.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34767","34767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514442","2016-04-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of households which receive the Warm Home Discount are in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34808","34808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514443","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who are eligible to receive the winter fuel payment and have voluntarily chosen not to receive it in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34894","34894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514444","2016-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much CAP funding the UK is due to receive under the current EU multi-annual financial framework in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34816","34816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514445","2016-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of how much CAP funding the UK is due to receive under future EU multi-annual financial frameworks in each year to 2030.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34817","34817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514446","2016-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much CFP funding the UK is due to receive under the current EU multi-annual financial framework in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34818","34818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514447","2016-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of how much CFP funding the UK is due to receive in each year to 2030 under future EU multi-annual financial frameworks.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34819","34819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514448","2016-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research her Department is (a) carrying out and (b) encouraging into extending the use of materials that biodegrade more quickly.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34801","34801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514449","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2016 to Question 29629, if the Government will make it its policy to introduce targeted sanctions against individual members of the Maldivian government if the recommendations of the Commonwealth Action Group are not implemented in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34773","34773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514450","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Indian government on recent protests and clashes in the Handwara and Kupwara districts in Kashmir.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34774","34774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514451","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli authorities on the planned demolition of the Palestinian settlements of Susiya and Umm al-Hiran.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34746","34746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514452","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his international counterparts on reports that a UN-funded Palestinian non-governmental orgaisation, Rural Women's Development Society, organised an event commemorating a Palestinian terrorist who killed three Israeli civilians.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34797","34797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514453","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his international counterparts on reports of a UN-funded Palestinian non-governmental organisation, Union of Agriculture Work Committee, organised a tree planting ceremony honouring 209 martyrs of the popular uprising.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34798","34798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514454","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to raise the projected demolition of the villages of Susiya and Um Al Hiran with the government of Israel.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34839","34839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514455","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US and Japanese counterparts about nuclear tests by North Korea.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34822","34822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514456","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received any reports of (a) violence against opposition officials, candidates and activists and (b) intimidation of journalists during the Parliamentary elections taking place in Serbia.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34852","34852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514457","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in countries on the UN Security Council on referring crimes by Daesh to the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34853","34853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514458","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the state of UK relations with Iran.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34895","34895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514459","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the fairness of conduct of elections in Serbia.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34854","34854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514460","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Gambia on the arrest, alleged torture and deaths of Ousainou Darboe and other members of the Gambian Opposition United Democratic Party; and what steps he is taking to ensure that the government of Gambia release those other members of that party who are detained as soon as possible.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34856","34856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514461","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to request that the UN Security Council refer crimes by Daesh to the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34855","34855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514462","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office of 20 April 2016, Official Report, column 995, whether Daesh has committed crimes that should be referred to the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34875","34875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514463","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to Ministers: quarterly return October to December 2015, published on 24 March 2016, whom he met during the visit to Saudi Arabia that began on 27 October 2015; and what the agenda was at those meetings.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34844","34844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514464","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to Ministers: quarterly return October to December 2015, published on 24 March 2016, whom he met during the visit to Kuwait that began on 26 November 2015; and what the agenda was at those meetings.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34845","34845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514465","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on the introduction of citizenship-for-investment schemes by EU member states; and what assessment she has made of the need for increased transparency of such schemes.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34847","34847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514466","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on the introduction of citizenship-for-investment schemes by EU member states.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34848","34848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514467","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Hungarian government about the sale of Hungarian residency bonds through off-shore companies.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34846","34846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514468","2016-04-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will raise with the Moroccan ambassador to the UK the death of Brahim Saika in Gulemin police station on 15 April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34948","34948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514469","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on the proportion of women with fibroadenoma who went onto develop breast cancer in 2015.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34937","34937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514470","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 31 March 2016 to Question 31789, how many people were (a) newly diagnosed and (b) already diagnosed as suffering from inflammatory bowel disease in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34936","34936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514471","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of prescription charges on people with multiple sclerosis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34866","34866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514472","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department collects on the health outcomes of autistic people who do not have a learning disability or mental health condition.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34864","34864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514473","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many junior doctors work in the NHS.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34865","34865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514474","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of women who had fibroadenomas surgically removed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34886","34886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514475","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on the number of women in England who were diagnosed with fibroadenomas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34882","34882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514476","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice NHS England provides for women who have developed fibroadenomas.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34883","34883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514477","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which clinical commissioning groups in England fund (a) no, (b) one, (c) two, (d) three and (e) more than three cycles of IVF treatment.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34891","34891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514478","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the cost of IVF treatment to the NHS in England.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34890","34890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514479","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of junior doctors who work at weekends; and if his Department will provide data on the number of (a) weekends and (b) part weekends worked in each month by junior doctors.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34902","34902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514480","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the new junior doctors' contract on elective weekend care.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34903","34903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514481","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people with autism who are in receipt of a personal health budget.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34901","34901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514482","2016-04-25","Cabinet Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of people who died of Sudden Adult Death Syndrome in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34924","34924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514483","2016-04-25","Cabinet Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people died of sudden cardiac death in the UK by (a) age and (b) region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34908","34908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514484","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the time taken for patients outside London to receive stroke rehabilitation treatment.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34814","34814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514485","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the vacancy rate is for spinal surgery specialists in England.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34815","34815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514486","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 34106, occupational health, if he will make it his policy to collect the information referred to.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34836","34836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514487","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on connections between hayfever, sleeping and allergy tablets and memory, cognitive and concentration difficulties.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34823","34823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514488","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on the use of nirolumab and ipilimumab to treat skin cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34824","34824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514489","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department has received from NHS employers on the number of junior doctors who have worked weekends in the last six months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34825","34825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514490","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure paramedics receive appropriate psychological support after witnessing traumatic events.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34833","34833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514491","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to collect data from private sector providers of NHS mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34834","34834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514492","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what specialist training in mental health commissioning is provided to clinical commissioning group mental health commissioners.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34835","34835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514493","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, under which statute he has the power to impose contracts on junior doctors.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34838","34838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514494","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of nurses that will need to be recruited from abroad to maintain levels of health care provision during the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34813","34813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514495","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the costs of Care Quality Commission primary care inspections were to GP practices in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34781","34781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514496","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors have applied for a Certificate of Good Standing in the last six months.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34794","34794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514497","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department measures and demonstrates parity of esteem between mental and physical health in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34778","34778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514498","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the Sustainability and Transformation Fund is applied to NHS Mental Health Trusts.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34779","34779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514499","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of primary care inspections by the Care Quality Commission on improving clinical outcomes for patients.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34780","34780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514500","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that all blood cancer patients have access to a clinical nurse specialist or equivalent point of contact as part of their care.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34820","34820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514501","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the post-treatment recovery package is adapted to meet the specific needs of blood cancer patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34821","34821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514502","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's advertisement on the Hays Recruitment Agency website for a temporary Senior Deputy Head of Media Planning and Strategy on a daily rate of pay, whether the post holder will be paid through (a) the Department's payroll, (b) that agency or (c) a limited company.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34810","34810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514503","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on the diagnosis and early treatment of primary hyperparathyroidism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34805","34805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514504","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals he has visited on Saturdays and Sundays since his appointment; and on what dates such visits were made.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34743","34743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514505","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support carers assisting people with mental health conditions.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34749","34749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514506","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned on the causes and consequences of neural tube defect-affected pregnancies.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34772","34772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514507","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total number of visit visa applications was from Sri Lanka in 2015; and how many such applications were refused.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34736","34736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514508","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to improve support resources available to students who have been victims of sexual assault.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34756","34756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514509","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to raise awareness of the seriousness of stalking (a) through social media and (b) otherwise.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34757","34757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514510","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role her Department had in the selection of appointed local authority heads of social services departments from 1985 to 2015.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34804","34804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514511","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department routinely collects on the nationality, gender and pass rate of applicants for the Life in the UK and Knowledge of Language test; and if she will make it her Department's policy to publish data providing a breakdown of such data by nationality, gender and pass rate.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34782","34782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514512","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the prevalence of mental health issues among firefighters; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34792","34792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514513","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20367 and of 18 January 2016 to Question 22101, what the spend for the Cyber Streetwise campaign was on (a) media spend and production, (b) PR, partnership and social, (c) research and (d) website in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34842","34842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514514","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20367, how the figure of approximately two million adults who have adopted safer online behaviours that will better protect them was reached; and how such behaviours were measured.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34841","34841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514515","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that police officers receive appropriate psychological support after witnessing traumatic events.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34837","34837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514516","2016-04-25","Department for International Development","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of UK development assistance on the availability of clean water in the last 10 years in (a) sub-Saharan African countries and (b) other countries.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34764","34764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514517","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any further courts and tribunal offices are planned for closure in addition to those announced in the Government's response to the consultation on the court and tribunal estate, published in February 2016.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34809","34809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514518","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions a judicial officer has not imposed a victims surcharge or any other fine following a request to do so in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34942","34942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514519","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions his Department has had with officials from the (a) Canadian government and (b) EU on the implications to the UK judicial system of the ratification of the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34929","34929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514520","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost of moving Bedford County Court from Shire Hall, St Paul's Square, Bedford, to the Employment Tribunal building in Howard Street, Bedford.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34926","34926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514521","2016-04-27","Leader of the House","2016-04-20","To ask the Leader of the House, pursuant to his Answer of 3 March 2016, Official Report, column 1102, when he expects the review of English votes for English laws procedures to take place.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34857","34857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514522","2016-04-25","Northern Ireland Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans she has to consult more widely on potential reduction of the regional Electoral Office presence and local services throughout Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34763","34763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514523","2016-04-25","Prime Minister","2016-04-20","To ask the Prime Minister, for what reasons an agreement was not reached with other EU heads of government and state to prevent EU migrants from claiming tax credits and child benefit in the first four years that they are resident in the UK.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34868","34868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514524","2016-04-25","Prime Minister","2016-04-20","To ask the Prime Minister, what contingency plans he is preparing for the European Parliament's possible rejection of (a) part or (b) all of the renegotiated terms of membership which he agreed in February 2016.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34870","34870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514525","2016-04-25","Prime Minister","2016-04-20","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the renegotiated terms of the UK's membership of the EU permit the (a) European Commission, (b) European Court of Justice, (c) European Parliament and (d) European Council to prevent the UK from applying the emergency brake mechanism.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34869","34869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514526","2016-04-25","Prime Minister","2016-04-20","To ask the Prime Minister, when he plans to respond to the hon. Member for Ashfield's correspondence of 8 March 2016 on voter registration.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34920","34920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514527","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has plans to include duties on wheelchair accessibility from the platform to the train in the next franchise for the West Coast Mainline at (a) Lancaster and (b) Wigan North Western.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34904","34904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514528","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with rail franchises in the North of England on improving the service to Sunderland rail station.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34938","34938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514529","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment his Department has made of the affordability of motor vehicle insurance in the UK.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34946","34946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514530","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which Departments provide how much funding to the Centre for Connected and Autonomous Vehicles.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34862","34862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514531","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 32463, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on his announcement of 23 April 2015 of a special scheme to help small businesses in Runcorn and Widnes using the new Mersey Gateway Bridge and the existing Silver Jubilee Bridge from 2017.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34811","34811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514532","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent changes there have been to Vehicle Certification Agency emissions testing; and what recent discussions he has had with Volkswagen on  progress on fixing all defeat devices.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34806","34806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514533","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for testing of emissions data by the Vehicle Certification Agency of Mitsubishi Motors having falsified fuel economy data; what information his Department holds on the number of vehicles affected by their falsification in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34807","34807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514534","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the projected cost savings are from the closure of the Marine Offices in (a) Brixham, (b) Leith and (c) Newlyn; and what the value is of (i) land and (ii) buildings on each site.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34784","34784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514535","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the potential costs to the UK freight sector of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34789","34789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514536","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost to UK ports of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34790","34790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514537","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the projected cost savings are from the proposed closure of the Marine Offices in (a) Beverley, (b) Orpington and (c) Harwich in 2018; and what the value is of (i) land and (ii) buildings on each site.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34783","34783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514538","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department is making available to the South Gloucestershire Unitary Authority for completion of new road projects.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34793","34793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514539","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers Rail North has in relation to the Northern and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34771","34771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514540","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what legislation or regulations the establishment and functions of the Rail North and the Rail North Board are based.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34753","34753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514541","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when it is planned that Rail North will take on full responsibility for the Northern and TPE franchises.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34754","34754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514542","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on whether there is a correlation between staffing levels on trains and stations and the number of reported sexual offences on trains and in stations.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34755","34755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514543","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made representations to Sanef Tolling about the length of time taken between a penalty notice being issued under the Dart Charge scheme  and the date of the offence.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34750","34750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514544","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average time was between a penalty notice being issued under the Dart Charge scheme and the date of the offence in each month since the start of that scheme.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34751","34751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514545","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who the members are of (a) Rail North and (b) the Rail North Board; and how those members are appointed.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34744","34744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514546","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on preparation for the expected start of construction works to the A417 Missing Link in Gloucestershire in 2020.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34748","34748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514547","2016-04-25","Wales Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, when he plans to publish the draft Wales Bill.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34768","34768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514548","2016-04-25","Wales Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the devolution of Air Passenger Duty to Wales.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34769","34769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514549","2016-04-25","Wales Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on the Government's review of the case for a Swansea Bay tidal lagoon.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34770","34770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514550","2016-04-25","Wales Office","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Welsh Government about the possibility of Wales hosting the 2026 Commonwealth Games.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34863","34863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514551","2016-04-25","Women and Equalities","2016-04-20","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, which women's organisations the Minister for Women has met since May 2015.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34907","34907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514552","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 April 2016 to Question 32294, what account is taken of a person's earlier claim for work capability assessment if the person submits a new claim for employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34909","34909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514553","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 34050, how much funding his Department has allocated to the work programme and work choice in the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34911","34911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514554","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of the new national living wage on carers who will lose their eligibility for the carer's allowance for working 16 hours per week.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34896","34896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514555","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of the new national living wage on (a) carers and (b) the eligibility of carers who work 16 hours per week for carer's allowance.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34897","34897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514556","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people in Carmarthenshire had their disability benefits stopped as the result of an assessment in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34878","34878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514557","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Carmarthenshire are in receipt of disability benefits.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34879","34879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514558","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time is for the Independent Case Examiner to review accepted cases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34867","34867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514559","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much in (a) in-work and (b) out-of-work benefits has been paid from the public purse in respect of persons who are nationals of other EEA member states.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34951","34951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514560","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many nationals from other EEA member states in receipt of benefits have not contributed through employment for those benefits.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34952","34952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514561","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides to health care professionals on applying the power in regulation 35 of the Employment Allowance Regulations 2008 to award employment and support allowance to claimants in the support group in exceptional circumstances.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34944","34944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514562","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has undertaken any research on circumstances in which he would seek to apply the emergency break on benefit under the UK's reform of its EU membership.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34953","34953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514563","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 8 March 2016 to Questions 30341 and 30342 and with reference to the Answers of 5 December 2013 to Question 179450 and 21 January 2014 to Question 182897, when his Department (a) decided to stop collecting the required information and (b) began to collect information in such a way that it can only be provided at disproportionate cost.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34945","34945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514564","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have been awarded employment and support allowance (ESA) under regulation (a) 29 and (b) 35 of the Employment and Support Allowance Regulations 2008; and how many such claimants were originally in the ESA support group.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34943","34943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514565","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 April 2016 to Question 32377, what proportion of local authorities will receive the Targeted Affordability Funding referred to; and whether Birmingham City Council qualifies as an area for such funding.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34939","34939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514566","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for core regulatory activities within the Health and Safety Executive in the next three years.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34795","34795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514567","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing the eligibility threshold for carer's allowance to enable carers working 16 hours per week on the new National Living Wage to keep their entitlement to that allowance.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34752","34752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514568","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will adopt recommendations 58 to 63 of the All Party Parliamentary Inquiry Report, Feeding Britain.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34739","34739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515583","2016-04-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to support prisoners with mental health problems.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904680","904680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515584","2016-04-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review access to compensation for victims of familial sexual abuse before 1979.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904678","904678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515585","2016-04-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the Government's policy is on the UK remaining a party to the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904683","904683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513931","2016-04-25","Attorney General","2016-04-19","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of cases in each year since 2010 is delayed as a result of CPS files not being handed over to the defence in time before the start of proceedings.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34591","34591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513932","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) prosecuted for, (b) convicted of, (c) cautioned for and (d) given a non-custodial sentence for rape in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34640","34640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513933","2016-04-25","Attorney General","2016-04-19","To ask the Attorney General, how many fraud prosecutions were carried out in each CPS business area in England and Wales in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34646","34646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513934","2016-04-21","Attorney General","2016-04-19","To ask the Attorney General, what his policy is on expanding the Unduly Lenient Scheme; and if he will consult on any such changes before their introduction.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34708","34708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513935","2016-04-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people have taken shared parental leave to date; how many people have made a claim for shared parental pay since April 2015; and what proportion of such claimants were fathers and partners.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34711","34711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513936","2016-04-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he last reviewed his Department's industrial strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34730","34730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513937","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department has spent on its industrial strategy in each year in which that strategy has been in force.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34731","34731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513938","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for how long the proposed apprenticeship levy vouchers will be valid.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34732","34732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513939","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether employers who pay the proposed apprenticeship levy and provide training will be able to use levy vouchers in their own organisations.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34733","34733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513940","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made in discussions with the devolved administrations on the drawing-down of funds on apprenticeships when the apprenticeship levy is introduced in April 2017.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34723","34723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513941","2016-04-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33918, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of policy staff travelling from his Department's office at 1 Victoria Street, London to his Department's Sheffield Office at St Paul's Place.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34702","34702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513942","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the reasons are for the reduction in the proportion of his Department's budget spent with small and medium-sized enterprises between 2013 and 2015.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34681","34681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513943","2016-04-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the annual cost is of policy staff from his Department's office at St Paul's Place, Sheffield travelling to London.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34669","34669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513944","2016-04-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what criteria his Department uses to judge the quality of apprenticeships.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34675","34675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513945","2016-04-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 11 April 2016 to Question 32406, if he will make it his policy that the Advisory, Conciliation and Arbitration Service collect the number of national minimum wage inquiries relating to the domiciliary care and residential care sectors.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34603","34603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513946","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on reaching its target of £1 trillion a year in exports by 2020.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34614","34614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513947","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who will act on behalf of the Pubs Code Adjudicator in situations where one of the parties to that adjudication objects to the Adjudicator's involvement.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34615","34615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513948","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the role of the Enterprise Directorate of his Department was in the (a) appointment of the Pubs Code Adjudicator and (b) development of the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34553","34553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513949","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support his Department plans to provide to the Pubs Code Adjudicator; and which directorate of his Department will oversee that support.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34554","34554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513950","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which directorate of his Department oversaw the appointment of the Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34555","34555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513951","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which directorate of his Department oversaw the development of the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34556","34556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513952","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what value of contracts has been awarded through the Small Business Research Initiative in each year for which records are available.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34697","34697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513953","2016-04-21","Cabinet Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials in his Department are working on research relating to the EU Referendum; and what estimate he has made of the total (a) number of man-hours and (b) cost of that work up to 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34621","34621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513954","2016-04-21","Cabinet Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what representations his Department has received on the potential effect on universities and university research of the proposed ban on public funds being used to lobby Government.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34672","34672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513955","2016-04-21","Cabinet Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions his Department has had with universities on the potential effect on university research of the proposed ban on public funds being used to lobby Government.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34673","34673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513956","2016-04-21","Cabinet Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to exempt universities and university research from the proposed ban on non-government organisations using funds from Government to lobby Government.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34674","34674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513957","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the businesses and sectors which have failed to sign up to the Alcohol Wholesaler Registration Scheme; what steps his Department is taking to ensure that such businesses sign up to that scheme; and what steps his Department is taking to exclude from the market those businesses suspected to be trading fraudulently and which did not register by the 31 March 2016 deadline.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34684","34684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513958","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many wholesalers have been found as a result of their failure to sign up to the Alcohol Wholesaler Registration Scheme to have been trading in alcohol fraudulently since the introduction of that scheme","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34685","34685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513959","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses had signed up for the Alcohol Wholesaler Registration Scheme by the 31 March 2016 application deadline; whether the number of businesses was in line with the 20,000 businesses that HM Revenue and Customs estimated could be required to register; and what steps are being taken to tackle any shortfall in numbers.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34721","34721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513960","2016-04-25","HM Treasury","2016-04-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses had signed up for the Alcohol Wholesaler Registration Scheme by the 31 March 2016 application deadline.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34722","34722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513961","2016-04-21","HM Treasury","2016-04-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who the tax assurance commissioner is in HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34626","34626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513962","2016-04-21","HM Treasury","2016-04-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times he has attended public meetings of the Treasury Committee since his appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34567","34567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513963","2016-04-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what modelling his Department has carried out on the potential effect of a bilateral trade deal between the UK and India (a) in general and (b) on UK economic growth.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34700","34700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513964","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure local authorities can adequately fund learning disability services.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34518","34518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513965","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to (a) end the indefinite detention of asylum-seekers in the UK and (b) introduce a limit on such detention in line with other European countries.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34524","34524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513966","2016-04-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the quality of local assurance frameworks prepared by local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34525","34525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513967","2016-04-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many times he has attended public meetings of the Communities and Local Government Committee since his appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34560","34560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513968","2016-04-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department provided in start-up costs for the Greater Manchester City Region Mayor.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34627","34627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513969","2016-04-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the National Audit Office report of March 2016 on Local Enterprise Partnerships, HC887.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34599","34599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513970","2016-04-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent representations she has received on the potential link between cavity wall insulation and dampness in houses.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34594","34594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513971","2016-04-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether a devolution deal with Cheshire and Warrington is dependent on the introduction of an elected mayor.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34725","34725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513972","2016-04-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure changes to supported housing will not adversely affect vulnerable people.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34707","34707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513973","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what criteria will be used to decide which 70 regions will be reached by the cultural citizens programme; and by what criteria the success of that programme will be judged.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34575","34575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513974","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with Ofcom on diversity in the broadcasting sector; what further steps he expects Ofcom to take to secure improvements in diversity in that sector; and whether he plans to encourage Ofcom to make use of its powers under Section 27 of the Communications Act 2003 and other relevant legislation.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34581","34581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513975","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who applied for UK citizenship in the year ending June 2015 (a) applied for exemption from the language requirements and (b) were granted such an exemption.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34572","34572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513976","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provision is made for people with learning disabilities and mental health problems in the system for testing applicants for UK citizenship.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34573","34573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513977","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the European Capitals of Culture process of the UK voting to leave the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34605","34605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513978","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many organisations have failed to register as data controllers with the Information Commissioner's Office under the terms of the Data Protection Act 1998 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34619","34619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513979","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the total operating budget for the BBC in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34631","34631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513980","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of full-time equivalent officials in his Department working on the BBC Charter Renewal consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34632","34632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513981","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations (a) his Department and (b) the Information Commissioner's Office have received on the failure of organisations to register as data controllers with the Information Commissioner's Office under the terms of the Data Protection Act 1998; and what steps (i) his Department and (ii) the Information Commissioner's Office have taken to ensure that organisations (A) are compliant with such terms of the Data Protection Act 1998 and (B) pay their notification fees.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34620","34620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513982","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the introduction of the next BBC Royal Charter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34630","34630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513984","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department plans to promote clearer pathways into the arts and cultural sectors to develop a more diverse leadership and workforce in those sectors.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34569","34569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513985","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department plans to hold events for cities intending to apply to be the 2023 European City  of Culture.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34570","34570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513986","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 8 of the Culture White Paper, published in March 2016, when his Department will require funded bodies in the arts and culture sectors to publish their strategies for increasing diversity.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34571","34571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513987","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 4 March 2015 to Question 225425, what progress has been made on the assessment of the feasibility of the creation of a Sikh regiment.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34580","34580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513988","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) status and (b) purpose is of the Defence Diversity and Inclusion Programme established in September 2013.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34579","34579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513989","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Russian language (a) speakers, (b) interpreters and (c) translators are employed in the intelligence department of his Department; and what steps he is taking to increase the number of such experts in that Department.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34523","34523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513990","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times he has attended public meetings of the Defence Committee since his appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34568","34568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513991","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on running costs for RAF (a) Menwith Hill, (b) Lakenheath and (c) Croughton in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34618","34618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513992","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what data his Department collects on allegations made against service personnel accused of committing (a) sexual assault and (b) rape.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34639","34639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513993","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the intake of BAME servicemen and women was as a proportion of total intake for each year from 2006 to the latest available figures.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34582","34582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513994","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of servicemen and women recruited from black, Asian and minority ethnic backgrounds.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34578","34578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513995","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for how many properties vacated by a service family leaving service family accommodation at march out Carillion Amey has accepted a cleaning fee in the last three years; how much was charged for each clean; which contractor performed the deep clean and how the standard for that clean was assessed.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34611","34611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513996","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many challenges to the new Service Family Accommodation gradings have resulted in  a change of banding since 1 February 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34612","34612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513997","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many challenges to the new Service Family Accommodation gradings have been received by the Cost Assurance and Analysis Service since 1 February 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34613","34613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513998","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK armed forces personnel are embedded in foreign armed forces; and with which forces such personnel are embedded.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34713","34713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513999","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has made to the government of Saudi Arabia on the designation of the Yemeni cities Sa'da and Marran as military targets by the Saudi Arabian-led coalition on 8 May 2015.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34726","34726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514000","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure that UK defence capability can effectively respond to a threat from Russia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34703","34703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514001","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what priority issues were discussed and conclusions reached at the UK-US bilateral annual stocktake of the UK-US Mutual Defence Agreement on atomic energy matters in April 2016; who attended that stocktake from which organisations; and what the cost was of that stocktake.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34677","34677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514002","2016-04-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what joint exercises his Department has held with participants from the US National Nuclear Security Administration on rapid response to emergency nuclear incidents, including those potentially involving terrorists, in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34679","34679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514003","2016-04-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what guidance his Department issues to Commanding Officers dealing with allegations of sexual assault, voyeurism and sexual activity in a public lavatory as set out in Schedule 2 of the Armed Forces Act 2006.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34687","34687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514004","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how deprivation factors are taken into account in school funding formulae.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34666","34666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514005","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether local authorities will retain rights of overage, clawback or pre-emption or any other interest in land transferred to her as a result of the Government's recent academisation proposals.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34663","34663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514006","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether a standard precedent lease will be issued to all schools planned to be converted to an academy under her Department's recent proposals; what the proposed standard length is of such leases; whether a market rent will be charged; whether the tenant will be responsible for (a) internal and (b) structural maintenance; whether formal consent will be required from her Department before any underlettings or assignments; and whether the local authority will be (i) noted on the lease and (ii) holding an interest right on the property.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34662","34662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514007","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children attending primary school were born outside the UK.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34719","34719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514008","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which of her Department's directors has responsibility for implementation of its commitments under the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34727","34727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514009","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether a property management company will be created for land held as a result of the proposals to transfer land owned by local authorities to the Secretary of State as part of the policy of converting all schools to academies.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34606","34606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514010","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of legal costs (a) to her Department and (b) to the academies and local authorities affected arising following the transfer of all local authority school land to the Secretary of State under the plans to convert all schools to academies; and what estimate she has made of such costs of the granting of leases to each academy under those plans.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34607","34607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514011","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with teachers on her proposal that all schools be required to convert to academies.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34616","34616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514012","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services on the health, wellbeing and performance of young people in schools and colleges.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34608","34608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514013","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has provided to schools on their compliance with the milk requirements of her Department's school food standards.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34609","34609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514014","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent representations her Department has received from primary schools on the requirement to make milk available during the school day.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34595","34595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514015","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start centres were in operation on 1 March 2016.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34596","34596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514016","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on the provision of universal infant free school meals.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34597","34597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514017","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of her Department's school food standards on milk consumption in primary schools.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34598","34598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514018","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her letter of 9 October 2015, when she will provide a substantive answer to the hon. Member for Birmingham, Hodge Hill on concerns raised in that letter on behalf of Mr M. Ikhlaq.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34589","34589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514019","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans for local authorities to continue to receive basic need allocations of capital for new school places under her proposals for all schools to become academies.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34590","34590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514020","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which (a) primary and (b) secondary school in each English education authority has the (i) lowest and (ii) highest proportion of children on free school meals.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34543","34543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514021","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on development of an early years workforce strategy.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34532","34532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514022","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of a majority leave vote in the EU referendum on teacher recruitment and retention.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34728","34728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514023","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of a majority leave vote in the EU referendum on the teaching and learning of modern foreign languages.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34729","34729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514024","2016-04-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many times she has attended public meetings of the Energy and Climate Change Committee since her appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34562","34562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514025","2016-04-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that people in receipt of Government administered free cavity wall insulation schemes do not suffer damp in their houses after insulation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34593","34593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514026","2016-04-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she has signed the Investor Agreement with EDF to proceed with Hinkley Point C as set out in the departmental minute of 21 October 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34709","34709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514027","2016-04-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the number of households which will refuse a smart meter.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34655","34655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514028","2016-04-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects to sign the Investor Agreement for Hinkley Point C power station; and what conditions will have to be fulfilled by EDF before that signing.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34625","34625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514029","2016-04-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what research her Department has commissioned on the particular challenges of implementing cyber security to cover small modular reactors (SMRs); and whether the recently announced competition for research on SMRs includes research on cyber security.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34678","34678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514030","2016-04-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage schools to procure their food from local producers and suppliers.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34676","34676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514031","2016-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of banning micro beads.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34735","34735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514032","2016-04-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made in implementing the British Food Plan across all Government departments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34649","34649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514033","2016-04-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many times she has attended public meetings of the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Committee since her appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34561","34561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514034","2016-04-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many applications for emergency authorisation for the use of neonicotinoids have been received since February 2016; and how many such applications have been granted.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34699","34699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514035","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times he has attended public meetings of the Foreign Affairs Committee since his appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34557","34557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514036","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable and process is, including parliamentary scrutiny, for ratification by the UK of the EU-Israel Civil Aviation Agreement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34540","34540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514037","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Russian language (a) speakers, (b) interpreters and (c) translators are employed by his Department; and what steps he is taking to increase the number of such experts working in his Department.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34522","34522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514038","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to counter Russian disinformation against western countries and NATO.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34521","34521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514039","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on tensions in Nagorno-Karabakh.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34533","34533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514040","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of the Russian Federation on tensions in Nagorno-Karabakh.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34534","34534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514041","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) the Russian business community and (b) other Russian citizens living in the UK on Russian attitudes towards the West.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34520","34520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514042","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress his Department has made on steps to ease the blockade of Gaza, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office on 25 February 2015, Official Report, columns 155-8WH.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34617","34617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514043","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials in his Department work in the referendum unit.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34712","34712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514044","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31117, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the findings from the 2014 paper by Kavanagh and others, Introduction and sustained high coverage of the HPV bivalent vaccine leads to a reduction in prevalence of HPV 16/18 and closely related HPV types; and whether such findings have been taken into account when assessing the differential impact of the bivalent and quadrivalent HPV vaccines on genital wart incidence.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34693","34693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514045","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31117, whether the time period referred to when providing details of the not anticipated reduction in genital warts associated with the bivalent vaccine takes into account the impact of the introduction of the quadrivalent vaccine in 2012.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34694","34694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514046","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase capacity in UK medical schools to enable an increase in the number of UK-trained doctors entering the NHS.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34705","34705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514047","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to (a) ensure families of the poorest care home residents are supported by their local authority and (b) to penalise local authorities that are non-compliant with the requirements of the Care Act 2014.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34706","34706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514048","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish an annual report on the UK Five Year Antimicrobial Resistance Strategy in 2016; and when he expects the next five year report on that strategy to be published.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34664","34664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514049","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the annual costs incurred in clinical negligence legislation due to the failure of the NHS Litigation Authority to (a) properly investigate claims early in the process and (b) offer a realistic settlement at the earliest possible time; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34682","34682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514050","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides to GPs to assist with the cost of insuring work undertaken outside of normal working hours.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34665","34665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514051","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of job offers on the terms and conditions of the new junior doctor contract have been (a) accepted and (b) rejected to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34686","34686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514052","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors have been recruited into City Hospitals Sunderland NHS Foundation Trust in the last five years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34716","34716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514053","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many autistic people in England have died by suicide in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34634","34634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514054","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce premature death among people (a) with autism and a learning disability and (b) with autism and no learning disability.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34636","34636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514055","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups collect (a) prevalence and (b) standardised mortality data on autistic people as part of their joint strategic needs assessments.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34635","34635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514056","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure suicide prevention services are autism-appropriate.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34648","34648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514057","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what length of time Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Trust had to wait for Disclosure and Debarring Service checks for (a) doctors and (b) nurses offered posts for accident and emergency in each month in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34610","34610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514058","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average level of funding for GPs in (a) Southampton City Clinical Commissioning Group, (b) comparator clinical commissioning groups and (c) England was in each of the last 3 years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34583","34583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514059","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons an annual report on the UK Five Year Antimicrobial Resistance Strategy was not published in 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34577","34577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514060","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to measure and improve the rate of premature mortality of people with autism who have no co-occurring learning disability.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34536","34536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514061","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the scope is of the current consultation on the Government National Carers Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34537","34537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514062","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to introduce a GP registry for autism to allow the collection of population-level data.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34519","34519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514063","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions Ministers of his Department have had with counterparts in non-EU states on policies and steps to reduce the number of neural tube defect-affected pregnancies.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34551","34551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514064","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by what date he expects that the population of England will be covered by the National Congenital Anomaly and Rare Disease Registration Service.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34552","34552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514065","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative information his Department holds on the rate of pregnancies affected by neural tube defects in the UK and in other EU member states.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34545","34545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514066","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals he has visited in an official capacity in 2016 to date; and what the date of each such visit was.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34546","34546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514067","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England on commissioning of integrated paediatric continence services.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34547","34547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514068","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will expand the scope of the Learning Disability Mortality Review to include people with autism and a learning disability.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34538","34538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514069","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve provision of IVF as a result of the meeting held by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State with Monitor and NHS England on 14 December 2015.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34539","34539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514070","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to merge clinical commissioning groups during the course of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34588","34588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514071","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the provision of urgent care centres on levels of attendance at A&E departments.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34584","34584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514072","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people undertake quality assurance in the NHS outside of clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34585","34585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514073","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent by the NHS on asthma drugs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34586","34586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514074","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent from the public purse on the maintenance of NHS buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34587","34587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514075","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31117, whether there has been any lasting duration of the HPV reduction that Public Health England have associated with the bivalent vaccine.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34695","34695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514076","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31117, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the 2016 paper by Mesher and others, Reductions in HPV 16/18 in a population with high coverage of bivalent HPV vaccination in England: an ongoing cross-sectional study; and whether such findings have been taken into account when assessing the differential impact of the bivalent and quadrivalent HPV vaccines on genital wart incidence.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34696","34696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514077","2016-04-25","Department of Health","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33901, if he will make it his policy to collect such information in future.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34698","34698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514078","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 18 April 2016, HCWS679, on immigration detention, who will be eligible under these proposals to authorise the detention of a pregnant woman for the first 72 hours.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34701","34701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514079","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 18 April 2016, on immigration detention, HCWS679, how many pregnant women (a) are detained and (b) have been detained for immigration purposes at the border in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34690","34690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514080","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times she has attended public meetings of the Home Affairs Committee since her appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34559","34559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514081","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on whether gross or net figures for rental income should be used in the calculation for the income threshold under spousal visa rules.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34550","34550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514082","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to allocate additional resources to police forces to combat the risks posed by drones to aircraft.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34549","34549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514083","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many interventions by the Forced Marriages Unit led to criminal prosecutions of people perpetrating forced marriages.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34529","34529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514084","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of victims rescued by the Forced Marriages Unit in each year since 2005 have been under 18 years old.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34530","34530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514085","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people (a) are protected and (b) have previously been protected but no longer are by a Forced Marriage Protection Order.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34531","34531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514086","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provision is made for people on the high end of the autistic spectrum with speech and language difficulties; or who are non-verbal, in the system for application for UK citizenship; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34574","34574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514087","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what grounds her Department grants exemptions from (a) the life in the UK written test and (b) the language requirements of an application for UK citizenship; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34576","34576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514088","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who applied for UK citizenship applied for an exemption from the written life in the UK test between June 2014 and June 2016; and how many such applications were refused.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34602","34602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514089","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to deploy British police officers to popular holiday resorts abroad as a result of the outcome of the pilot scheme in summer 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34633","34633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514090","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current average waiting time is for the completion of pre-employment checks by the Disclosure and Barring Service; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34656","34656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514091","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the time taken for the completion of pre-employment checks by the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34657","34657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514092","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking with the Metropolitan Police Service to reduce the time taken to complete pre-employment checks by the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34658","34658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514093","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which guidance her Department provides to local authorities on the retention of case files for victims of serious child abuse in local authority-provided care.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34667","34667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514094","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current average waiting time is for the completion of pre-employment checks by the Disclosure and Barring Service involving (a) Cleveland Police and (b) the Metropolitan Police Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34659","34659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514095","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 18 April 2016, on immigration detention, HCWS679, how many pregnant women (a) are detained and (b) have been detained for immigration purposes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34691","34691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514096","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 18 April 2016, on immigration detention, HCWS679, whether there will be independent oversight of decisions to detain pregnant women.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34689","34689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514097","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 18 April 2016, on immigration detention, HCWS679, in what ways the policy to end the routine detention of pregnant women differs from the current policy that pregnant women should be detained only in exceptional circumstances.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34718","34718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514098","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 18 April 2016, on immigration detention, HCWS679, whether notice will be given to pregnant women who will be detained.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34688","34688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514099","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 April 2016 to Question 33257, what the Government's policy is on (a) granting residency to and (b) possible prosecution of people who arrive in the UK as either refugees or asylum seekers who are married to a child under 16 when such marriages were undertaken legally outside the UK and were not performed under duress.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34734","34734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514100","2016-04-21","Department for International Development","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will take steps to ensure that protection and empowerment of girls is given equal priority to that of women at the World Humanitarian Summit in May 2016.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34528","34528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514101","2016-04-21","Department for International Development","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will take steps to ensure that the global risk platform to be debated at the World Humanitarian Summit in May 2016 meets the needs of people affected by natural and social disasters.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34526","34526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514102","2016-04-21","Department for International Development","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will take steps to address the issue of funding for child protection interventions in humanitarian contexts at the World Humanitarian Summit in May 2016.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34527","34527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514103","2016-04-21","Department for International Development","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations the Government has made to the Israeli government on the confiscation near Qalqillhya on 7 May 2015 of 3,000 metres of water pipes funded by her Department as part of a project with the UN Food and Agriculture Organisation and the Palestinian Ministry of Ariculture.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34541","34541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514104","2016-04-21","Department for International Development","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many times she has attended public meetings of the International Development Committee since her appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34565","34565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514105","2016-04-25","Home Office","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2016 to Question 29547, what assessment she has made of the efficacy of steps taken to reach vulnerable Yazidis now located in Turkish camps to enable them to be resettled in the UK under the Syrian Vulnerable Person Resettlement Programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34724","34724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514106","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) access to justice and (b) early settlement of claims of changes made in the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34720","34720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514107","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33485, in what capacity those polygraph examinations have been conducted; and for what reasons polygraph examinations have been so used to examine sex offender behaviour.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34692","34692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514108","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, against the Boards of which community rehabilitation companies he has exercised his powers of written consent since 1 February 2015; and against what proposals such powers have been used.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34660","34660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514109","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, against which community rehabilitation companies the Authority Step-in action provided for by section 27 of the Community Rehabilitation Companies (CRC) Amended and Restated Services Agreement has been used since 1 February 2015; and in response to which issues such an action has been taken.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34661","34661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514110","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employees there were in each Community Rehabilitation Company on (a) 31 January and (b) 31 December 2015.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34629","34629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514111","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many community rehabilitation cases have been (a) breached, (b) recalled and (c) terminated for good progress since June 2014.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34628","34628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514112","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which community rehabilitation companies have been the subject of an authority audit by his Department since February 2015; and if he will publish such reports.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34623","34623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514113","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether community rehabilitation companies (CRCs) have current information sharing agreements in place with their local police forces; and which CRCs do not have such an agreement in place.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34624","34624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514114","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the outcome was of the National Offender Management Service Authority Audit of South Yorkshire Community Rehabilitation Company in September 2015 on that company's risk management.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34622","34622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514115","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of domestic homicides that are linked to people who have been convicted of (a) breaching restraining orders, (b) breaching non-molestation orders and (c) stalking offences in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34650","34650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514116","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people convicted of stalking offences have received therapeutic custodial sentences or hospitalisation orders in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34651","34651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514117","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has undertaken or commissioned research into the relationship between people who are convicted of multiple breaches of restraining orders and commission of stalking offences.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34652","34652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514118","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of psychological assessment and rehabilitation of people convicted of stalking offences under Sections 2A and 4A.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34653","34653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514119","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have received the maximum custodial sentences for stalking offences under (a) Section 2A and (b) Section 4A of the Protection from Harassment Act 1997 in each year since those sections were brought into force.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34654","34654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514120","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Prevention of Future Death Notices were issued to each NHS ambulance trust in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34647","34647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514121","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of instances in which enforcement agent fees paid by a defendant were transferred directly by HM Courts and Tribunal Services to enforcement agents in each of the last five years; and what estimate he has made of the amounts transferred in that period.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34637","34637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514122","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent officials of his Department work facilitating co-operation with enforcement agents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34638","34638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514123","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of court fines referred to enforcement agents in the last year and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34643","34643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514124","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Prevention of Future Death Notices issued by coroners in England and Wales related to failures of NHS ambulance services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34644","34644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514125","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the total number of court fines issued in each of the last five years; and what estimate he has made of the value of such fines.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34641","34641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514126","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Prevention of Future Death Notices were issued by coroners in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34645","34645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514127","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the total payment made to enforcement agents for the collection of outstanding court fines in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34642","34642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514128","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of proposals to deny parole or release to people incarcerated for charges of murder for as long as they refuse to disclose the whereabouts of their victim's remains.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34592","34592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514129","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times he has attended public meetings of the Justice Committee since his appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34564","34564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514130","2016-04-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the Government has spent during Public Law Project v The Lord Chancellor [2015] EWCA Civ 1193, 25 November 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34548","34548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514131","2016-04-25","Leader of the House","2016-04-19","To ask the Leader of the House, what progress has been made on plans for the complete renovation of the Palace of Westminster; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34544","34544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514132","2016-04-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33237, what assessment his Department has made of the potential health risks of the use of lasers by driverless vehicles.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34542","34542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514133","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times he has attended public meetings of the Transport Committee since his appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34563","34563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514134","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on whether drivers who are waiting for medical tests to confirm whether they are safe to drive should retain their licence in the meantime.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34604","34604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514135","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) male and (b) female employees (i) his Department, (ii) Network Rail, (iii) Highways England, (iv) HS2 Ltd, (v) the Office of Rail and Road, (vi) the DVLA, (vii) the Drive Vehicle Standards Agency and (viii) the VCA has.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34683","34683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514136","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress has been made on the Thameslink programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34670","34670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514137","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much will be spent on rail infrastructure between 2015 and 2020; and how much was so spent between (a) 2010 and 2015 and (b) 2005 and 2010.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34671","34671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514138","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to spread best practice from the Cycle City Ambition scheme to those cities and towns not part of that scheme.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34668","34668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514139","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister of State of 10 March 2016, Official Report, column 419, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of implementing temporary measures to ensure public safety when drones are used while his Department considers the best action to take.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34680","34680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514140","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33638, whether his Department has recently requested any advice from the European Commission on the compliance with state aid rules of awarding Public Service Obligation subsidies that specify airports both origin and destination.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34715","34715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514141","2016-04-25","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 April 2016 to Question 33988, whether Stagecoach or Virgin has proposed a reduction in the premium profile of the current InterCity East Coast franchise during the discussions referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34714","34714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514142","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress is being made to increase the number of train stations with step-free access.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34710","34710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514143","2016-04-21","Women and Equalities","2016-04-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many times she has attended public meetings of the Women and Equalities Committee since her appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34558","34558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514144","2016-04-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times he has attended public meetings of the Work and Pensions Committee since his appointment.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34566","34566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514145","2016-04-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on a person providing child maintenance having their payments regarded for the purpose of an income assessment for means-tested benefit.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34535","34535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514146","2016-04-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps he has taken to support women who have been affected by state pension inequalities.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34717","34717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514147","2016-04-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people in Hampshire had their disability benefits stopped following an assessment in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34600","34600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/514148","2016-04-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Hampshire receive disability benefits.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34601","34601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515101","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department plans to take to improve the performance of schools in parts of the country where there has been persistent underperformance.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904629","904629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515102","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to meet demand for school places in Somerton and Frome constituency.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904637","904637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515103","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to require all primary and secondary schools to become academies.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904638","904638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515104","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to assist teachers in managing their workload.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904635","904635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515105","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what future plans she has for the role of parents in the running of their children's school.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904641","904641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515106","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve the quality of data it holds on the mental health of looked-after children.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904640","904640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515107","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans the Government has to support the most vulnerable children and families.","Biography information for James Morris","James Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904630","904630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515108","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department is making on ensuring that funding is distributed fairly across schools.","Biography information for Victoria Atkins","Victoria Atkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904639","904639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515109","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to require all primary and secondary schools to become academies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904636","904636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/515110","2016-04-25","Department for Education","2016-04-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures her Department has implemented to support children who are permanently excluded from school.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904634","904634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513498","2016-04-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) full-time equivalent civil servants work in his Department and (b) civil servants work full-time on the Northern Powerhouse agenda.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34358","34358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513499","2016-04-21","HM Treasury","2016-04-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many schemes have benefited from the Business Premises Renovation Allowance in each of the last five years; and what the average value of such benefit was.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34300","34300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513500","2016-04-20","HM Treasury","2016-04-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment (a) his Department and (b) the Financial Conduct Authority has made of the effect that the GC16/2  proposal, published in February 2016, to require lenders to issue default notices before collecting from guarantors would have on (i) the number of borrower defaults subsequently reported to the Credit Reference Agencies, (ii) borrowers' credit scores and (iii) levels of financial exclusion.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34271","34271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513501","2016-04-20","HM Treasury","2016-04-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's consultation on enforcing guarantor loans, GC16/2, published in February 2016, whether his Department has received representations from the (a) Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) and (b) any other organisation on the consistency of the FCA's proposed interpretation of the word enforce in section 87(1)(e) of the Consumer Credit Act.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34272","34272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513502","2016-04-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to apply the agent of change principle to pubs which play live music.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34280","34280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513503","2016-04-20","Department for Transport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support his Department is offering to local authorities to promote the provision of electric car charging points.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34281","34281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513504","2016-04-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the Government plans to publish the White Paper on the BBC Charter.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34265","34265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513505","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on the future of Channel 4.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34320","34320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513506","2016-04-20","Department for Education","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in Shropshire have been converted into academies.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34254","34254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513507","2016-04-20","Department for Education","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve the quality of data that it holds about the mental health of looked-after children.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34274","34274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513508","2016-04-20","Department for Education","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people her Department employs as statisticians.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34275","34275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513509","2016-04-20","Department for Education","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in her Department hold qualifications at A-level or above in statistics.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34276","34276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513510","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations her Department has received on the financial management of (a) Beacon Multi-Academy Trust and (b) schools under the management of that trust.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34297","34297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513511","2016-04-21","Department for Education","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations her Department has received on the (a) expansion of existing schools or (b) creation of new schools from (i) Beal High School and (ii) the Beacon Multi-Academy Trust.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34298","34298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513512","2016-04-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, why it is the Government's policy to grant subsidies for biomass and not for coal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34262","34262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513513","2016-04-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department holds data on the amount of carbon dioxide emitted per one tonne of (a) biomass and (b) coal when burned; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34263","34263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513514","2016-04-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department holds up-to-date estimates of the level of coal reserves in (a) England, (b) Scotland and (c) Wales; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34264","34264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513515","2016-05-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which campaign groups attended the initial meeting of key stakeholders at the litter strategy advisory group.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34307","34307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513516","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in The Gambia following recent disturbances including in the state of Coma.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34301","34301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513517","2016-04-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) investigate whether JC Bamford Excavators has supplied equipment which has been used in construction of illegal settlements and destruction of Palestinian homes and (b) make an assessment of whether that company has contravened the UN Guiding Principles on Business and Human Rights.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34294","34294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513518","2016-04-20","Department of Health","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the cost of medical indemnity insurance premiums on the number of female GPs returning to work after maternity leave.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34259","34259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513519","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to maximise the take-up of Healthy Start vouchers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34321","34321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513520","2016-05-03","Department of Health","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance has been issued to local authorities and other Government departments on engagement with the (a) British Soft Drinks Association, (b) Food and Drinks Federation, (c) Wines and Spirits Association and (d) Tobacco Manufacturers Association.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34308","34308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513521","2016-04-21","Department of Health","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the (a) Wales Office and (b) Welsh Government on ensuring that Welsh victims of contaminated blood are not left worse off than counterparts in other parts of the UK in any compensation arrangements.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34303","34303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513522","2016-04-20","Department of Health","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many days patients in (a) England, (b) Morecambe Bay and (c) Blackpool spent in hospital waiting for equipment or support aids to be made available to them to allow their discharge in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34277","34277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513523","2016-04-20","Home Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unwilling parties to a forced marriage have twice been prevented from such a marriage by the Forced Marriage Unit since it was set up.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34278","34278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513524","2016-04-20","Home Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Forced Marriage Unit takes to monitor the safety of UK residents rescued from forced marriages abroad who return to the UK.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34279","34279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513525","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many financial remedies were incurred as a result of breaches of the contract between the UK Border Agency and G4S Care and Justice Services in the North East Yorkshire and Humberside region for the provision of accommodation, transport and related services for persons claiming asylum or granted refugee status; and what the total cost of such remedies was.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34299","34299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513526","2016-04-20","Home Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many further submissions lodged under rule 353 of the immigration rules were made from (a) London, (b) the Midlands, (c) Northern Ireland, (d) the North-East and North West of England, (e) Yorkshire and the Humber, (f) Scotland and (g) Wales in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2014-15 and (iii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34327","34327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513527","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the taxpayer was of policing the Conservative Party event at the Crowne Plaza Hotel near Chipping Norton on 14 April 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34295","34295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513528","2016-04-20","Home Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many grants of leave to remain on protection or non-protection grounds stemmed from applications made from people based in (a) London, (b) the Midlands, (c) Northern Ireland, (d) the North East and North West of England, (e) Yorkshire and the Humber, (f) Scotland and (g) Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34326","34326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513529","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been convicted of selling a knife to someone under age since the introduction of the Violent Crime Reduction Act 2006.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34293","34293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513530","2016-04-21","Home Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding has been allocated to youth-focused projects in South Wales Police area as part of the PREVENT programme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34302","34302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513531","2016-04-20","Home Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of the level of transparency and scrutiny used by fire and rescue authorities during their recruitment processes.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34261","34261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513532","2016-04-20","Department for International Development","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress has been made in implementing the commitments set out in the EU/Bangladesh Sustainability Compact.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34266","34266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513533","2016-04-20","Department for International Development","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether it is Government policy to link an extension of the Generalised System of Trade Preferences for Bangladesh to further improvements in that country's garment sector on factory safety and labour rights.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34267","34267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513534","2016-04-20","Department for International Development","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will support a change to legislation to require UK registered companies to publish a full list of their suppliers internationally, to enhance transparency and accountability and to ensure adherence to international labour standards in company supply chains.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34268","34268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513535","2016-04-20","Department for International Development","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made representations to the government of Bangladesh on trade union recognition and adherence to ILO core labour standards in that country's export processing zones.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34269","34269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513536","2016-04-21","Department for International Development","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the total value of (a) general budget support and (b) sectoral budget support provided by her Department was in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34304","34304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513537","2016-04-20","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners from HMP New Hall attended accident and emergency departments as a consequence of the use of psychoactive substances in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34273","34273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513538","2016-04-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is on making doping in sport a criminal offence.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34291","34291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513539","2016-04-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of a custodial sentence given to someone convicted of animal cruelty was in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34292","34292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513540","2016-04-20","Northern Ireland Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the potential devolution of powers relating to electoral matters in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34282","34282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513541","2016-04-20","Northern Ireland Office","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment her Department has made of potential arrangements for the introduction of online electoral registration in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34283","34283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513542","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the total cost of legal fees for the High Speed 2 project since its inception; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34286","34286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513543","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what forecast his Department has made of the total cost of legal fees for the High Speed 3 project over the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34287","34287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513544","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the amount set aside for compensation payments to residents along the route of the High Speed 2 line for each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34288","34288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513545","2016-04-21","Department for Transport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to protect aircraft operating out of UK airports from the safety risks posed by drones.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34296","34296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513546","2016-04-20","Department for Transport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to update its 2013 aviation demand forecasts before publishing an updated version of the 2013 Aviation Policy Framework.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34270","34270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513547","2016-04-20","Department for Transport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government has taken to increase the safety of cycling.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34258","34258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513548","2016-04-20","Department for Transport","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria local authorities will be measured against when applications for funding from the Pothole Action Fund are considered.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34260","34260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513549","2016-04-20","HM Treasury","2016-04-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's latest estimate is of the number of parents with children who will be claiming tax credits in April 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34255","34255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513550","2016-04-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's latest estimate is of the number of parents with children who will be claiming employment and support allowance in April 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34256","34256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513551","2016-04-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's latest estimate is of the number of parents with children who will be claiming housing benefit in April 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34257","34257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513552","2016-04-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's latest estimate is of the number of parents with children who will be claiming income support in April 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34289","34289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513553","2016-04-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's latest estimate is of the number of parents with children who will be claiming universal credit in April 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34290","34290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513554","2016-04-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department is using to determine whether Dupuytren's Contracture should be included on the list of prescribed diseases covered by Industrial Injuries Disablement Benefit.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34284","34284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/513555","2016-04-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-04-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average time has been taken for the Governemnt to determine whether an illness or disease should be included on the list of prescribed diseases covered by Industrial Injuries Disablement Benefit following a recommendation by the Industrial Injuries Advisory Council.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 34285","34285"
