"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78344","2014-07-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of post boxes that have been decommissioned since the privatisation of Royal Mail.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206301","206301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78345","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many firms have been allocated funds which have subsequently been withdrawn with the removal of match funding under the Passport to Export scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206272","206272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78346","2014-07-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the procedures for consultation before the decommissioning of post boxes by Royal Mail.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206302","206302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78347","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of properties in each London borough sold in each year since 2010 were sold to foreign buyers.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206265","206265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78348","2014-07-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make representations to Royal Mail on the need to conduct local consultation prior to the decommissioning of post boxes.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206303","206303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78349","2014-07-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will place in the Library all data he holds on the effect of the decommissioning of post boxes on (a) elderly and (b) disabled people.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206304","206304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78350","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many firms are participating in the Passport to Export scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206275","206275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78351","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many firms (a) applied and (b) were approved to take part in the Passport to Export scheme in each month of its operation.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206276","206276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78352","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of apprentices are working less than 16 hours per week as part of their apprenticeship.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206277","206277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78353","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of apprentices are not currently receiving (a) on the job and (b) off the job training as part of their apprenticeship.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206278","206278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78354","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of apprentices are not (a) contractually entitled to be paid and (b) receiving the apprentice national minimum wage.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206281","206281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78355","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to (a) start and (b) publish the apprenticeship pay survey.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206282","206282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78356","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on privatising part or all of the Student Loan book before May 2015.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206295","206295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78357","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of direct delivery competition on Royal Mail and the sustainability of the universal service obligation.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206359","206359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78358","2014-07-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 9 April 2014, Official Report, column 292W, on Royal Mail, by what date he expects to make a decision on whether a discretionary payment will be made; and whether he expects this decision to be made after the report of Lord Myners on the privatisation of Royal Mail has been submitted.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206362","206362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78359","2014-07-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) meetings and (b) discussions on the privatisation of Royal Mail took place between (i) Ministers, (ii) officials, (iii) the Financial Adviser to HM Government, (iv) the banking syndicate working on the privatisation and (v) priority investors (A) ahead of and (B) since the privatisation of Royal Mail.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206368","206368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78360","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of suppliers to his Department have been paid within the time specified on their invoice in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206340","206340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78361","2014-07-21","Cabinet Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 291W, on Government Digital Service, whether all Government Digital Service staff are members of the Civil Service ICT professional group.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206242","206242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78362","2014-07-21","Cabinet Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 291W, on Government Digital Service, how many (a) male and (b) female (i) permanent and (ii) contract staff of the Government Digital Service were in each grade in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206243","206243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78363","2014-07-21","Cabinet Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason no Minister in his Department was able to represent his Department in the debate on the political independence of charities scheduled to take place in Westminster Hall on 15 July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206244","206244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78364","2014-07-21","Cabinet Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206142","206142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78365","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206155","206155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78366","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of tax revenue foregone as a result of people who are UK resident, but not domiciled for tax purposes, not paying tax on non-UK source income.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206109","206109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78367","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when HM Revenue and Customs will next audit the compliance and performance of Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited in respect of all the STEPS Contractor's obligations under the agreement, including those applicable to the implementation of any change and all personnel and management policies and practices and quality management under 17.1 (d) of the private finance initiative contract between HM Revenue and Customs and Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206250","206250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78368","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many call attempts were made to HM Revenue and Customs contact centres on each working day between 16 June and 4 July 2014; how many such calls were answered; and how many answered calls led to a request for a needs enhanced support face-to-face meeting.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206218","206218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78369","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of whether there have been any benefits to the internal work of HM Revenue and Customs of the release of data about VAT registration to private credit ratings agencies.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206160","206160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78370","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse was of external consultants employed by his Department in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206287","206287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78371","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Preston constituency were self-employed and in receipt of working tax credit in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206321","206321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78372","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with regard to the Mapeley-Salisbury STEPS contract for cleaning services in Northern Ireland, how much HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) has paid towards the Mapeley-Salisbury STEPS contract for cleaning services in Northern Ireland; what arrangements HMRC and Mapeley have in place to monitor the STEPS contract with staff representatives; for what reasons former civil servants employed by ISS on the Mapeley STEPS contract have not received a pay award in 2013 in line with the terms of the contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206334","206334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78373","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were employed by HM Revenue and Customs in the Large Business Service (LBS) in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15 to date; and how many companies the LBS worked with in each of those years.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206356","206356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78374","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many unresolved tax enquiries there were in the Large Business Service (LBS) in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15 to date; and how many unresolved tax enquiries in the LBS are (i) one year old and (ii) more than three years old.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206355","206355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78375","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which local authorities in England publish on their websites (a) the names and addresses of individuals and businesses convicted under the Food Hygiene (England) Regulations 2006, (b) details of the offences for which those individuals and businesses were convicted and (c) the penalty levied by the courts in each such case.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206316","206316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78376","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 3 December 2013, Official Report, column 630W, on EU grants and loans, how much and what proportion of 2007 to 2013 European Regional Development Fund monies allocated to the UK with match-funding in place have been (a) contractually committed and (b) drawn down in (i) each English region and (ii) in total to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206317","206317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78377","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many council homes were built in each London Borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206262","206262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78378","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average sector rent was in each London Borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206263","206263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78379","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of new homes needed annually to meet London's housing needs into 2020.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206259","206259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78380","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of new affordable homes in each London Borough were rented at below (a) 70 per cent, (b) 60 per cent and (c) 50 per cent of market rent in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206260","206260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78381","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many affordable homes were built in each London Borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206261","206261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78382","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many properties in each London borough were classified as empty in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206264","206264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78383","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of funds allocated in each region under the European Regional Development Fund have been returned as a result of slippage and underperformance in each region; and on what dates each such withdrawal took place.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206266","206266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78384","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which bids in each region have been (a) accepted and (b) rejected under the European Regional Development Fund since May 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206274","206274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78385","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes in each London Borough failed to meet the decent homes standard in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206256","206256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78386","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many children were recorded as living in overcrowded housing in each London Borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206257","206257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78387","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people were recorded as living in overcrowded housing in each London Borough in each of the year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206258","206258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78388","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential liability to Government should the take-up rate in the proposed 2015 firefighters' pension scheme be lower than anticipated.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206187","206187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78389","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206143","206143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78390","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many broadcasters in (a) Wales and (b) the UK have been closed as a result of their inability or refusal to pay the Authority for Television On Demand's regulatory fees.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206114","206114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78391","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many households in Northern Ireland held a black and white television licence in January (a) 2009 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206164","206164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78392","2014-07-22","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2014, Official Report, column 63W, on teachers: offences against children, how many teachers have lost their job as a result of having a sexual or other relationship with a student under the age of 16 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206247","206247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78393","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage community organisations to take up EU funding offered by the Europe for Citizens Programme and similar schemes in order to commemorate the centenary of World War I through exchanges and visits.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206181","206181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78394","2014-07-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he last met BLTV Ltd to discuss its progress on delivering the local television franchise for the Birmingham area.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206245","206245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78395","2014-07-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how long a local television franchise is valid for; and whether BLTV will launch in Birmingham within the period of its existing franchise.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206246","206246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78396","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his policy to consult local residents on decisions on the construction of mobile telephone masts under the mobile infrastructure project where plans for construction have been through pre-planning and published.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206306","206306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78397","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which tourist and cultural attractions (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department (i) have visited and (ii) plan to visit in (A) Preston constituency, (B) Lancashire, (C) North West England and (D) London in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206325","206325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78398","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will discuss with the BBC Trust measures to increase coverage of life, history and culture in Lancashire across the BBC national television and radio network.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206327","206327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78399","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how often Lancashire has specifically been featured in his Department's overseas promotion of tourism in the UK in the last four years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206326","206326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78400","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department will announce a decision on the future of the Apache helicopter upgrade.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206336","206336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78401","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the Government has to preserve HMS Illustrious when she is withdrawn from service in December 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206370","206370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78402","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if the Government will investigate the tourism potential of preserving HMS Illustrious.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206371","206371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78403","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what weighting his Department will give to (a) UK content, (b) UK employment and (c) a wider strategy of support for the UK helicopter production industry in taking a decision on the future of the Apache helicopter upgrade.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206337","206337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78404","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings (a) Ministers and (b) senior officials in his Department have held with representatives of Lockheed Martin in each year since 2010; and what was discussed at each such meeting.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206335","206335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78405","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what hospitality the Chief of Defence Materiel has received from Lockheed Martin in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206330","206330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78406","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings have been held between the Chief of Defence Materiel and representatives from Lockheed Martin in each year since 2010; and what was discussed at each.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206331","206331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78407","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what events were hosted by Lockheed Martin which (a) Ministers in and (b) senior officials of his Department attended in an official capacity in each year since 2010; and what was discussed at each.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206332","206332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78408","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the new contract to extend the life of the Sentinel aircraft until 2018 will be signed.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206329","206329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78409","2014-07-21","Cabinet Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to make an announcement on recommendations relating to the award of the National Defence Medal.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206314","206314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78410","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on where naval vessels should be constructed after 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206162","206162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78411","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to promote recruitment to the army cadets in Northern Ireland in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206163","206163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78412","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions since 2010 product recall notices have been issued for equipment being used by the armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206183","206183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78413","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost was of each successfully trained recruit of (a) Phase 1 and 2 training at ITC Catterick, (b) Phase 1 training at ATC Pirbright, (c) Phase 1 training at ATR Bassingbourn and (d) Phase 1 training at AFC Harrogate including trainee salaries and associated costs in the most recent years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206117","206117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78414","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost of running Phase 1 training at AFC Harrogate including trainee salaries and associated costs was in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206118","206118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78415","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total cost of running the Combat Infantryman's Course (Phase 1 and 2 training) at ITC Catterick including trainee salaries and associated costs was in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206119","206119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78416","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206144","206144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78417","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) attendance by RAF Northolt personnel and (b) related marketing materials at the European Business Aviation Convention and Exhibition on 20 to 22 May 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206197","206197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78418","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what grounds he has concluded that the use of RAF Northolt for commercial flights does not constitute state aid; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206188","206188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78419","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average duration is of all completed traineeships to date.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206126","206126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78420","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many traineeships completed to date have lasted six weeks or less.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206127","206127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78421","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what target she has set for the number of 16 to 17 year olds to (a) enrol on the Youth Contract programme, (b) be re-engaged into a positive outcome following the Youth Contract programme and (c) be retained in that positive outcome for five out of six months over the course of the Youth Contract programme.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206128","206128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78422","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the annual cost to her Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206145","206145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78423","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2014, Official Report, column 636W, on free schools, what assessment she has made of the feasibility of changes to the way personal information is recorded in free school applications to reduce the cost of redaction of that information; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206239","206239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78424","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been paid to each provider of the Youth Contract for 16 to 17 year olds since September 2012.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206180","206180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78425","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will place in the Library a copy of the service level agreement between the Haberdashers' Aske's Federation Trust and the schools in which it operates.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206166","206166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78426","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools have been approved by her Department which do not have identified sites; and in which local authority area each such school wishes to operate.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206167","206167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78427","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2014, Official Report, column 75W, on academies: land, what (a) amount of public investment and degree of enhancement, (b) amount of private investment and degree of enhancement, (c) length of time the land has been in public use and (d) value of land at the date of determination would trigger a determination in order to protect the public investment in land where it ceases to be used by an academy.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206202","206202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78428","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of the core target group of 16 to 19 year olds have (a) applied for and (b) been accepted onto a traineeship to date.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206213","206213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78429","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 16 to 19 year olds who have not achieved English and mathematics to level two are not continuing to study these subjects.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206214","206214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78430","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 16 to 19 year olds are not undertaking a study programme.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206215","206215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78431","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academy brokers there are; and how much her Department has spent on academy brokers in the last financial year.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206216","206216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78432","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on legal costs on appealing decision notices served by the Information Commissioner since 2010.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206217","206217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78433","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions her Department has had with (a) the Haberdashers' Aske's Federation Trust and (b) that Trust's auditors on possible fraud within the Trust.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206165","206165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78434","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what checks the Education Funding Agency makes on the quality of auditors and others taking professional fees for services provided to academies.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206234","206234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78435","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the responsibilities will be of the Minister of State in her Department, the hon. Member for Bognor Regis and Littlehampton.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206249","206249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78436","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Ofsted inspections were carried out in the local education authority of Birmingham in (a) primary, (b) secondary, (c) straight-through, (d) nursery and (e) other schools in the academic years (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206315","206315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78437","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance (a) her Department and (b) Ofsted provides to Ofsted inspectors about the monitoring of school engagement with Prevent.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206357","206357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78438","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if she will take steps to increase maintenance loans for university accommodation in respect of (a) students in places with expensive accommodation costs and (b) other students.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206377","206377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78439","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the turnover of head teachers has been in state-funded schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206384","206384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78440","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on the basis of what research findings the Government developed its proposals to decrease the role of coursework in GCSE and A-level curriculums.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206380","206380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78441","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of applications her Department has received for free schools in districts experiencing a high or severe need for extra primary school places in the present academic year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206385","206385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78442","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government's proposed reforms to A-levels will entail that students will have to decide which subjects they wish to continue to A-levels at the beginning of Year 12 rather than later in that year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206378","206378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78443","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government's proposed reforms to A-levels, if she will bring forward safeguards to prevent students making uninformed decisions about their subject choices and being limited as to the degree they can apply for at university as a result of having to make subject decisions at the beginning of Year 12.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206379","206379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78444","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish a list of all free schools that are planned to open in September 2014 that still have places available before they reach their planned admission number; and how many places at each such school are currently available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206386","206386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78445","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which free school projects pre-approved to open in September 2014 have since been (a) cancelled or withdrawn and (b) delayed; and what the pre-opening expenditure was for each such project.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206387","206387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78446","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the size is of the (a) external and (b) internal play area on the (i) temporary and (ii) permanent site of each free school that is (A) open and (B) planning to open in September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206388","206388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78447","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the total staff cost has been of (a) the Office of Unconventional Oil and Gas, (b) the Office of Carbon Capture and Storage, (c) his Department's human resources services, (d) the EMR delivery unit and (e) his Department's press office in each year since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206298","206298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78448","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the amount of gas transferred from (a) Scotland to England and (b) England to Scotland through onshore interconnectors in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206341","206341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78449","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what dates the no-fly zones around nuclear facilities have been violated since May 2010; and what steps his Department has taken to ensure such violations do not occur in future.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206186","206186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78450","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206146","206146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78451","2014-07-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations he has received from Ofgem and other regulatory bodies on the decision to consult on a large-scale solar PV Renewables Obligation closure grace period deadline of 13 May 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206116","206116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78452","2014-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will estimate the annual cost to her Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206147","206147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78453","2014-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the restricted grant-in-aid to Royal Gardens Botanical, Kew has been in each financial year since 2007.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206134","206134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78454","2014-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on the investigation into criminal prosecutions as a result of the adulteration of beef products with horsemeat; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206280","206280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78455","2014-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many meetings (a) Chris Elliot and (b) members of his team have had with representatives from the meat importation sector during the investigation into criminality in the food chain.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206279","206279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78456","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken in response to the discovery of horsemeat in other foods in 2013 to improve co-operation between Government departments on public health issues.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206397","206397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78457","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps in co-operation with major retailers to prevent unhealthy food being marketed more favourably than healthier foods.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206401","206401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78458","2014-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to restrict the use of antibiotics on farms to the treatment of sick animals.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206200","206200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78459","2014-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the CITES Management Authority has declared that the Cayman Turtle Farm is a humane facility.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206288","206288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78460","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to de-escalate the situation in Gaza.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206289","206289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78461","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent talks Ministers in his Department have had with (a) Israeli and (b) Palestinian leaders on the current situation in Gaza.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206290","206290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78462","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that West Nile virus is not introduced from the United States to Ascension Island.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206361","206361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78463","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Ugandan government and (b) his EU counterparts on the Anti-Homosexuality Act in Uganda; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on Uganda of the sanctions against that country announced by the US administration on 19 June 2014 in response to the Anti-Homosexuality Act.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206360","206360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78464","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to help the 223 girls kidnapped in North East Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206372","206372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78465","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the timetable is for the Montserrat Conservation and Environmental Management Bill.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206343","206343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78466","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how the 1 million pledged by the UK to the UN's Safe Schools Initiative is being used to ensure that children are being protected.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206373","206373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78467","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on the delivery of the package of assistance pledged by the Prime Minister to the Nigerian government following the recent kidnapping of schoolgirls in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206374","206374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78468","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) Palestinians and (b) Palestinian children who have been killed as a result of Israeli military action in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206375","206375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78469","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) Israelis and (b) Israeli children who have been killed as a result of Israeli military action in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206376","206376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78470","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to prevent the use and development of nuclear weapons by North Korea; and what assessment he has made of the recent missile tests in the Gongwan Province.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206223","206223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78471","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the average salary gap is between women and men in his Department.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206220","206220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78472","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent changes in Japan's constitution and its defence doctrine.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206184","206184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78473","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the implementation of each of the recommendations in the report, Children in Military Custody, published in June 2012.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206208","206208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78474","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with the government of Burma reported threats that ethnic Rohingya identifying themselves as such in the census could face arrest.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206292","206292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78475","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the statement of 10 July 2014 by the Secretary General of the UN on the escalating tensions between Israel and Palestine.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206284","206284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78476","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2014, Official Report, column 643W, on Diego Garcia, if he will immediately publish the contents of all the records referred to in the Answer.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206294","206294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78477","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether Israeli military action during Operation Protective Edge has complied with its international legal obligations.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206229","206229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78478","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will investigate whether any UK manufactured weapons or components have been used by Israeli military forces during Operation Protective Edge.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206225","206225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78479","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the degree to which the Cayman Turtle Farm is a humane captive breeding facility.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206226","206226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78480","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many emergency travel documents were issued in (a) June 2013 and (b) June 2014.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206105","206105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78481","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Sri Lankan counterpart (a) on that country's duties to uphold human rights and (b) in response to recent attacks on Muslims in that country.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206124","206124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78482","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which senior medical and administrative staff responsible for the operation of the Gamma Knife Centre at St Bartholomew's Hospital Trust are employees of (a) the Trust and (b) the Hospital Corporation of America.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206125","206125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78483","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206148","206148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78484","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to engage with the public about (a) care.data and (b) ways of opting-out of care.data before data is collected.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206189","206189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78485","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what payments have been received by the NHS in return for the advertising of Optical Express services on the NHS Choices website.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206198","206198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78486","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 313W, on ovarian cancer and 24 June 2014, Official Report, columns 156-7W, on ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome, if his Department will collect data on the number of women admitted to hospital with ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome (OHSS); if he will take steps to ensure systematic reporting of OHSS from egg sharing and egg donation; if he will make it his policy that ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome be notifiable; and if he will take steps to ensure that women are accurately informed of the risk of hospitalisation from OHSS when considering egg donation or egg sharing procedures.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206103","206103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78487","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contractual arrangement is in place between the Hospital Corporation of America (HCA) and St Bartholomew's Hospital Trust regarding (a) ownership of the Gamma Knife and (b) leases that HCA may have in relation to the property.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206111","206111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78488","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much St Bartholomew's Hospital Trust invested in the establishment of its Gamma Knife Centre in 2009; what the source of such funding was; and how much of that investment has since been recouped.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206112","206112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78489","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the revenue division is between the Hospital Corporation of America and St Bartholomew's Hospital Trust London for fees charged to NHS England for treating NHS patients on the Gamma Knife housed in St Bartholomew's Hospital.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206113","206113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78490","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Lancashire residents were admitted to a mental health unit that was not their nearest facility in urgent or emergency situations because of a lack of beds since April 2012; how many such patients lived in West Lancashire constituency; and how much has been spent on private sector provision for such patients.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206122","206122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78491","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many beds in each UK spinal cord injury centre are ring fenced for the exclusive treatment of spinal cord injured readmissions or outpatients.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206237","206237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78492","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training on the potential risks of opioid substitution treatment medications is provided to pharmacists, social workers and health visitors.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206228","206228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78493","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many beds in each UK spinal cord injury centre have been ring fenced for the treatment of spinal cord injured readmissions or outpatients in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206236","206236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78494","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate the alleged misallocation of the specialist spinal injury beds at Stoke Mandeville Hospital and the use by non-spinal cord injury patients.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206238","206238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78495","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason the NHS logo appears on the Optical Express website; what the relationship between Optical Express and the NHS is; whether NHS funding (a) is and (b) has been provided to Optical Express in order to carry out procedures on NHS patients; and how many NHS patients were referred to Optical Express by the NHS in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206230","206230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78496","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to co-ordinate with the devolved administrations to plan for the effects of an ageing population.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206395","206395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78497","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to put in place a media campaign to educate the public about alternatives to antibiotics.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206396","206396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78498","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Care Quality Commission look at (a) current and (b) historic patient files and consent forms.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206241","206241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78499","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the advertising of Optical Express under the services section of the NHS choices website, for what reason his Department concluded that Optical Express does not fall under the excluded advertising categories set out in the NHS Choices terms and conditions for offering cosmetic surgery and procedures including Botox and sunbeds; and what assessment he has made of whether advertising Optical Express services is an appropriate use of NHS funding used to maintain the website.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206231","206231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78500","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the recommendations in the report Medications in Drug Treatment: Tackling the Risks to Children published on 29 April 2014 by Adfam.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206273","206273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78501","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of supporting people with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206285","206285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78502","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average age at which children are diagnosed with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206286","206286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78503","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 310W, on diabetes, what information his Department collects centrally about diabetics.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206283","206283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78504","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to support the establishment of charities that support people with learning disabilities working in communities throughout the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206400","206400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78505","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to improve the transparency and accountability of the NHS complaints process; and if he will take steps to prevent vexatious complaints being made.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206398","206398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78506","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to improve the support available to young carers; and what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on improving such support.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206399","206399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78507","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what audit has taken place in each of the last five financial years of the extent to which the uses to which the UK contribution to the World Health Organisation budget has been put have met Government objectives; and what those objectives were.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206206","206206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78508","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the World Health Organisation budget was contributed by the Government in the most recent year for which figures are available; and what the sterling value of that contribution was.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206203","206203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78509","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what formula determines the proportion of the World Health Organisation annual budget that should be contributed by each member state government; and when that formula was last updated.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206204","206204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78510","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the UK contribution to the World Health Organisation budget is counted towards the Government's target of contributing 0.7 per cent of gross national product to international development.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206205","206205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78511","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and which private sector companies awarded NHS contracts have subcontracted work from NHS hospitals and surgeries to prisons in England; and which prisons are involved in such contracts.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206161","206161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78512","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have suffered complications following knee and hip operations related to osteoarthritis in the last five years.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206190","206190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78513","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of doctors against whom allegations of abuse made by patients have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206350","206350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78514","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of (a) eating disorder beds and (b) eating disorder services have been delivered by the private sector in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206351","206351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78515","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department allocated to National Breastfeeding Week in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206352","206352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78516","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has an infant feeding coordinator.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206353","206353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78517","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his assessment is of the trial publication online of the Red Book for expectant mothers.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206354","206354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78518","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings Ministers in his Department have had with representatives of (a) the tobacco industry and (b) tobacco control charities to discuss proposals for legislation on plain packaging of cigarettes in the last 12 months.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206333","206333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78519","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the amount to be paid in additional payments to staff at HM Passport Office who commited to work a set number of overtime hours between 5 July and 31 August 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206344","206344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78520","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals Great Britain 2013, what procedures are included in the direct diagnosis category.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206313","206313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78521","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals Great Britain 2013, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the changes in the number of procedures in the fundamental biological research category.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206311","206311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78522","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals Great Britain 2013, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the large number of procedures in the direct diagnosis category.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206312","206312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78523","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from local authorities within Compass asylum contract areas on the (a) suitability of accommodation for asylum seekers provided by Compass, (b) overcrowding in that accommodation, (c) the need for local authorities to be notified when asylum seekers became resident there and (d) additional services required from local authorities when large numbers of asylum seekers move to an area.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206305","206305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78524","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many discretionary referrals have been made from the National Crime Agency Child Exploitation and Online Protection unit to the Disclosure and Barring Service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206296","206296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78525","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission an independent evaluation of the use of GPS tracking by police services in England and Wales.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206139","206139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78526","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department gives to research councils for the purpose of conducting non-animal tests or research.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206207","206207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78527","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department gives to research councils to fund tests or research involving animals.","Biography information for Martin Horwood","Martin Horwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206210","206210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78528","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the people identified to date by the National Crime Agency investigation into online child abuse had previously worked in regulated activity.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206233","206233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78529","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the longest period between inspection visits made to any UK establishment licensed under the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 (as amended 2012) currently is for establishments deemed by the Animals in Science Regulation Unit to be of (a) high, (b) medium and (c) low risk.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206182","206182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78530","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was of external consultants employed by her Department in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206232","206232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78531","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what reports she has received on the time taken for the Metropolitan Police to act in the case of a foreign national conducting a seminar which is alleged to have encouraged assistance with suicide in London, June 2013; and what steps she is taking to ensure that the case is now properly investigated.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206115","206115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78532","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to routinely refuse visas to foreign nationals who enter the UK with the aim of encouraging or assisting suicide.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206107","206107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78533","2014-07-22","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who the target demographic is for the modern slavery helpline run in conjunction with the NSPCC; and what services and support will be offered through this helpline.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206159","206159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78534","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made in securing the return of Agung Mantra to the UK.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206129","206129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78535","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will estimate the annual cost to her Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206149","206149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78536","2014-07-22","Home Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funds have been made available to the NSPCC for the establishment and running costs of the modern slavery helpline.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206158","206158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78537","2014-07-21","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the names are of the candidates who have been short-listed for consideration for the position of Clerk of the House and Chief Executive; and what the country of residence of each such candidate is.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206209","206209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78538","2014-07-21","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, who decided on which days to migrate the IT accounts of hon. Members and hon. Members' staff to Office 365.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206392","206392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78539","2014-07-21","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, column 176-7W, on computer software, what further feedback the Commission has received from (a) hon. Members, (b) hon. Members' staff and (c) other users on migration to Office 365 since that Answer was given.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206393","206393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78540","2014-07-21","House of Commons Commission","2014-07-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, columns 176-7W, on computer software, what estimate the Commission has made of the (a) average and (b) aggregate amount of time spent by (i) hon. Members, (ii) Members' staff and (iii) others in migrating to Office 365.","Biography information for Thomas Docherty","Thomas Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206394","206394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78541","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many times her Department has referred cases of suspected bribery, fraud or money laundering concerning UK aid money to (a) the Serious Fraud Office and (b) the Crown Prosecution Service since 2009-10.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206338","206338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78542","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will place in the Library any correspondence her Department has received from the Serious Fraud Office on what steps it is taking to investigate reports referred to it by her Department that UK aid may have been channelled via CDC Group and Energy Capital Partners into companies linked to James Ibori; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206339","206339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78543","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department allocates to Palestine; and if she will commission a review of how effective that funding is in serving her Department's objectives in Palestine.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206381","206381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78544","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to aid Palestinian citizens who have been injured, orphaned, made homeless and lost their livelihoods as a result of Israel's recent air strikes; and whether she plans to keep the level of such funding under review in the light of future developments in that conflict.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206382","206382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78545","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that UK assistance to the Democratic Republic of Congo is not misused or misappropriated.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206221","206221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78546","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that particular attention to the most marginalised and people in vulnerable situations is specifically referenced in the language of the targets and goals in the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206178","206178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78547","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will support proposals to amend the goal on education to provide free, equitable and inclusive quality education and life-long learning opportunities for all in the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206179","206179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78548","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many programmes based in Papua New Guinea have been considered for funding since April 2004; and how many have received funding.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206185","206185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78549","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the UK is taking to ensure that all Palestinian civilians made homeless during Operation Protective Edge will have their homes rebuilt as swiftly as possible.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206227","206227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78550","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received of an increase in death rates in camps for the Rohingya following the expulsion of MSF and other agencies from Rakhine State, Burma.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206293","206293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78551","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when the Government plans to announce the UK's contribution to the Green Climate Fund; and whether that contribution will be, proportionately, in accord with the funding being sought by the Fund for its initial resource mobilisation.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206291","206291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78552","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will estimate the annual cost to her Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206150","206150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78553","2014-07-21","Department for International Development","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will ensure that the UK's financial contribution to the Green Climate Fund is announced at the Climate Summit in September 2014.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206110","206110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78554","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206151","206151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78555","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the capabilities are of the multi-purpose ankle tag; and what forms of surveillance and supervision it makes possible.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206133","206133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78556","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons the hardware and software providers in the new contract for electronic monitoring of offenders have been separated.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206135","206135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78557","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what reasons were given to him by Buddi for its withdrawal from the new electronic contract in March 2014.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206136","206136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78558","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on fitting tags and trackers at court or prison.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206137","206137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78559","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent each month on court buildings that were closed in the period up to their disposal since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206199","206199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78560","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 326W, on young offenders, on what date each adult male establishment was first designated both as a prison and a young offender institution; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206251","206251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78561","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the likely effect on prison numbers of Clause 25 of the Criminal Justice and Courts Bill.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206211","206211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78562","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the monthly cost is of each court building which has been closed but not disposed of since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206212","206212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78563","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on devolving responsibility for tagging contracts to police and crime commissioners.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206138","206138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78564","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many businesses have been convicted under the Food Hygiene (England) Regulations 2006 in each magistrates' court in Lancashire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206328","206328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78565","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on providing non-stipendiary magistrates with electronic copies of Sentencing Guidelines and updates thereof free of charge; and what plans his Department has to provide non-stipendiary magistrates with electronic copies of Sentencing Guidelines and updates thereof free of charge.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206323","206323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78566","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many whole time equivalent staff were employed at each magistrates' and Crown court in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206324","206324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78567","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been made redundant by Her Majesty's Courts and Tribunals Service (HMCTS) in each year since the foundation of HMCTS; and what the cost of redundancies at HMCTS was in each of those years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206322","206322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78568","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) first-tier and (b) upper-tier tax tribunal judges there were in 2013-14; for how many days (i) first-tier and (ii) upper-tier tax tribunal panel members sat in that year; how many (A) first-tier and (B) upper-tier tax tribunal expert panel members there were in that year; and how much was paid to tax tribunal panel members in that year.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206358","206358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78569","2014-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 326W, on young offenders, how many young offenders were held in each establishment on the latest day for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206297","206297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78570","2014-07-21","Leader of the House","2014-07-16","To ask the Leader of the House, how many days were allocated to business not introduced by a Government Minister in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206176","206176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78571","2014-07-21","Leader of the House","2014-07-16","To ask the Leader of the House, how many amendments to Government bills were not debated in the House due to a lack of time in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206177","206177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78572","2014-07-21","Leader of the House","2014-07-16","To ask the Leader of the House, with reference to the commitment in the Coalition Agreement, when he plans to introduce a Parliamentary Business of the House Committee.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206173","206173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78573","2014-07-21","Leader of the House","2014-07-16","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will bring forward proposals to provide that the Leader of the House should be elected by the whole House, not appointed by the Prime Minister.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206174","206174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78574","2014-07-21","Leader of the House","2014-07-16","To ask the Leader of the House, how many programme motions were proposed in each year since the introduction of such motions; and how many such motions were agreed to.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206175","206175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78575","2014-07-21","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps she is taking to publish the names of the 228 on-the-runs with comfort letters after the publication of the Hallett Report; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206248","206248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78576","2014-07-21","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will estimate the annual cost to her Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206152","206152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78577","2014-07-21","Scotland Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206153","206153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78578","2014-07-22","Scotland Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what work the Office of the Advocate-General for Scotland has commissioned by external consultants in relation to work on the Scotland Analysis programme; which consultants were used; and how much such consultancy has cost.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206366","206366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78579","2014-07-22","Scotland Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many officials of the Office of the Advocate-General for Scotland have been allocated to work on the Scotland Analysis programme; and if he will estimate the cost to the public purse of that work.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206364","206364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78580","2014-07-22","Scotland Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what meetings (a) he and (b) officials of the Office of the Advocate-General for Scotland have had with the right hon. Member for Edinburgh South West as part of the Scotland Analysis programme; and what was discussed at each such meeting.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206365","206365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78581","2014-07-22","Scotland Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what (a) external organisations and (b) officials in the Office of the Advocate-General for Scotland he has engaged with as part of the Scotland Analysis programme; and what was discussed at each such consultation.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206363","206363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78582","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206154","206154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78583","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train operating companies (TOCs) missed their annual punctuality targets in each year of Control Period 4, 2009-14; and whether the Office of Rail Regulation has the power to impose fines on TOCs for missing punctuality targets for timetabled train services.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206191","206191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78584","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to replace the Class 170 units transferred to Chiltern Railways from the Transpennine Manchester to Cleethorpes service.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206219","206219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78585","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the punctuality of South West Trains' passenger rail services in each month since that company formally entered into a deep alliance with Network Rail in April 2012.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206196","206196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78586","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what South West Trains' punctuality score was in each month since 1 January 2009; and how that score compared with the (a) national average and (b) punctuality target in each such month.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206195","206195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78587","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which occasions train operating companies have been fined by (a) his Department and (b) the Office of Rail Regulation for (i) missing punctuality targets or (ii) late running passenger services; and what the amount of the fine was in each such case.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206192","206192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78588","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the existing franchise agreements between his Department and train operating companies contain punctuality targets for timetabled passenger services; what each such target is; and what the penalties are for missing such targets.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206193","206193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78589","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria are used to establish whether delays of over five minutes to a scheduled commuter train service in (a) London and (b) the South East are caused by (i) Network Rail, (ii) the train operating company or (iii) other factors; and what changes have been made to those critera since January 2008 .","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206194","206194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78590","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what modifications Rail North made to the proposals recently put to his Department for the Transpennine and Northern Rail franchises.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206391","206391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78591","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, to whom and by what mechanism is Rail North accountable.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206389","206389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78592","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which councillors represented on Rail North agreed to the consultation paper issued by his Department on the Transpennine and Northern Rail franchises; and what council each such councillor represented.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206390","206390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78593","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the punctuality of South West Trains passenger rail services in each month since South West Trains formally entered into a deep alliance with Network Rail in April 2012.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206319","206319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78594","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were injured in road traffic accidents where the driver's visual acuity was found to be below the legal acceptable level in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206318","206318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78595","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the journey time from Cleethorpes to Manchester Airport on the service proposed in his Department's consultation document on the Transpennine franchise published in June 2014.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206307","206307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78596","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of drivers whose visual acuity was poor who were involved in road traffic accidents in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206308","206308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78597","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost is of road traffic accidents in the UK where poor visual acuity was a contributory factor in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206309","206309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78598","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road traffic accidents there were per 100,000 of the population in (a) the UK, (b) London and (c) Barnet in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206320","206320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78599","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the punctuality score of South West Trains was in each month between 1 January 2009 and 2014 to date; and what the (a) national average and (b) national punctuality target was in each such month.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206349","206349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78600","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria are used to establish whether delays over five minutes to a scheduled commuter train service in (a) London and (b) the South East were caused by (i) Network Rail, (ii) the train operating company or (iii) other factors; and what changes have been made to those criteria since January 2008.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206348","206348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78601","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which occasions train operating companies have been fined by (a) his Department and (b) the Office of Rail Regulation for (i) missing punctuality targets or (ii) late running passenger services; and what the amount of the fine was in each such case.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206346","206346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78602","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the existing franchise agreements between his Department and train operating companies contain punctuality targets for timetabled passenger services; what the target is in each case; and what the penalties are for missing such a target.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206347","206347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78603","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train operating companies (TOCs) missed their annual punctuality targets in each year of Control Period 4, 2009-14; and whether the Office of Rail Regulation can impose fines on TOCs for missing punctuality targets for timetabled train services.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206345","206345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78604","2014-07-21","Department for Transport","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the potential financial savings that would be incurred in his consultation document on TransPennine and Northern Rail franchises were implemented without change.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206383","206383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78605","2014-07-21","Wales Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206156","206156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78606","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the annual cost to his Department of (a) stationery and (b) postage incurred when sending a ministerial reply to hon. Members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206157","206157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78607","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the time taken to (a) process claims for personal independence payments and (b) receive a work capability assessment appointment.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206132","206132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78608","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average time is taken to process an application for funeral expenses from the Social Fund from the time an application is submitted to a decision being taken.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206104","206104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78609","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many current applications for funeral expenses from the Social Fund have been outstanding for longer than (a) 16 days, (b) 18 days and (c) 21 days.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206106","206106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78610","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the main reasons for the time taken to process personal independence payment claims.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206123","206123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78611","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in West Lancashire constituency have waited more than nine months to receive a work capability assessment interview in the last three years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206120","206120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78612","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department made of the staffing levels required to efficiently process the transfer of employment and support allowance claimants to the personal independence payments claims.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206121","206121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78613","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on legal fees in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206240","206240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78614","2014-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of households in Banff and Buchan constituency whose incomes from benefit payments have reduced by (a) 10 per cent, (b) between 20 and 49 per cent and (c) 50 per cent or more since May 2010.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206253","206253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78615","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total expenditure on housing benefit in London was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206255","206255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78616","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much in housing benefit has been paid to private sector landlords in London in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206254","206254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78617","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people for whom Youth Contract wage incentives have been paid since April 2012 have been (a) male, (b) female, (c) disabled and (d) Black and minority ethnic.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206170","206170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78618","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus workclub schemes are in operation; and how many such clubs were established in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206171","206171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78619","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the reasons for trends in long-term unemployment among people over 50.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206172","206172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78620","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2014, Official Report, column 110W, on personal independence payment, if he will estimate the number of people who do not currently claim disability living allowance who go into debt while their claims for personal independence payment are pending.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206201","206201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78621","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Youth Contract wage incentive payments made since April 2012 have related to work activity of (a) over 30 hours' duration and (b) between 16 to 29 hours' duration per week.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206168","206168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78622","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseekers were supported through the Flexible Support Fund in 2013; and what proportion of such were (a) men, (b) under 25 years old and (c) over 50 years old.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206169","206169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78623","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many officials are currently working on the universal credit programme.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206235","206235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78624","2014-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of households in Perth and North Perthshire constituency whose incomes from benefit payments have reduced by (a) 10 per cent, (b) between 20 and 49 per cent and (c) 50 per cent or more since May 2010.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206252","206252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78625","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, column 278W, on personal independence payments, what his Department's definition is of a mature system; and how he proposes that the maturity of the system will be measured.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206342","206342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78626","2014-07-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the impact assessment of the single-tier pension published in October 2013, if he will make an estimate of how many people reaching state pension age after implementation of the single-tier pension in (a) the UK and (b) Scotland would have been eligible for savings credit in (i) 2020 and (ii) 2030 had savings credit not been abolished.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206369","206369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78627","2014-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on how many claims for benefits made by telephone by people in Preston constituency in 2014 to date were interrupted by the claimant running out of credit.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206310","206310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/79201","2014-07-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the situation in Israel and Palestine.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905000","905000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77828","2014-07-17","Attorney General","2014-07-15","To ask the Attorney General, how many applications for a preliminary hearing for a Deferred Prosecution Agreement (a) the Director of Public Prosecutions and (b) the Serious Fraud Office have made since 24 February 2014.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205838","205838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77829","2014-07-17","Attorney General","2014-07-15","To ask the Attorney General, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by the Law Officers' Departments since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205965","205965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77830","2014-07-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Solicitors Regulation Authority is continuing to endorse the Law Society practice note on Sharia succession rules; and whether such an endorsement is compatible with the SRA's obligations under the Equality Act 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205890","205890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77831","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many bids to the Export Refinancing Facility have been (a) received and (b) approved since its launch; and how many firms have received funds under the scheme to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206027","206027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77832","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his letter of 2 May 2014 which was placed in the Library, on what date agreement was reached with each of the pilot fishing investors in Royal Mail on share allocations.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206021","206021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77833","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff (a) in his Department and (b) its executive agencies are currently working wholly or in part on the issue of Sunday trading.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206023","206023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77834","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many firms have received assistance under the Direct Lending Scheme to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206025","206025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77835","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department  holds on the current ownership of shares in Royal Mail.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206024","206024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77836","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assurances were sought from priority investors ahead of the privatisation of Royal Mail on long-term holding of shares by (a) Ministers in his Department (b) Officials in his Department (c) the Financial Adviser to the Government and (d) the banking syndicate working on the privatisation.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206026","206026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77837","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the financial advantages enjoyed by larger companies in preventing their marketing and promotional emails from being blocked by servers.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205876","205876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77838","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he received from representatives of secondary ticketing websites on the guidance to or implementation of the Consumer Contracts (Information, Cancellation and Additional Charges) Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205818","205818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77839","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by his Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205964","205964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77840","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assistance the UK has given to the developments of the SESAME (Synchrotron-light for Experimental Science and Applications in the Middle East) project; and what collaborative scientific research projects the UK supports between Israel, Iran and the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205936","205936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77841","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the net benefit to the UK export sector as a result of the recent Farnborough Airshow.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206009","206009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77842","2014-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for remissions relating to fees for employment tribunal proceedings have been (a) made and (b) awarded in each month since July 2013; and what has been the (i) average cost of assessing each claim and (ii) total aggregate cost to the public purse of making such assessments.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206019","206019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77843","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what agreement was sought from priority investors on the long-term holding of shares in Royal Mail.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206020","206020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77844","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he, Ministers or officials in his Department have had with secondary ticketing websites about guidance to or implementation of the Consumer Contracts (Information, Cancellation and Additional Charges) Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205806","205806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77845","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from secondary ticketing websites about amendments tabled to the Consumer Rights Bill.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205807","205807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77846","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he, Minister and officials in his Department have had with Ministers or officials in the (a) Department of Culture, Media and Sport and (b) Home Office about the resale of tickets and the Consumer Rights Bill.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205808","205808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77847","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consideration he has given to lowering the tuition fee cap for students studying STEM subjects.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205814","205814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77848","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the European Commission about inclusion of the glass manufacturing industry in Annex II to the Certain State aid measures in the context of the greenhouse gas emission allowance trading scheme post-2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205708","205708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77849","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with the European Commission about the compensation scheme for the carbon price floor and inclusion of the glass manufacturing industry in Annex II to the Certain State aid measures in the context of the greenhouse gas emission allowance trading scheme post-2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205711","205711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77850","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on the competitiveness of the British glass, manufacturing, ceramics and mineral products industries of not being eligible for the compensation scheme for the carbon price floor; and whether he has discussed this issue with the European Commission.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205714","205714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77851","2014-07-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what services Healthcare UK offers to organisations based in the devolved regions.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205756","205756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77852","2014-07-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-15","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when (a) due diligence will be completed and (b) funds will be drawn down by winning bidders under the Local Growth Fund.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206011","206011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77853","2014-07-17","Cabinet Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by his Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205966","205966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77854","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by his Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205980","205980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77855","2014-07-22","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what average length of time was taken to provide individual taxpayers with refunds of overpaid tax in (a) the most recent year for which figures are available and (b) the preceding four years.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205873","205873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77856","2014-07-22","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many taxpayers qualified for a refund on their 2013-14 tax payments; how many of them received the refund; and what the average value is of these refunds.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205874","205874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77857","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will lower tax duty on cigarettes.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205907","205907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77858","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he  has made of the direct financial benefit of the abolition of air passenger duty bands C and D to airports in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205812","205812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77859","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs has spent on Tackling Tobacco Smuggling strategy in each year since 2010-11; how many of his Department's staff worked on implementing that strategy in each such year; and how many such staff were engaged in (a) detection, (b) intelligence-gathering and analysis, (c) investigations and (d) the provision of legal advice.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206017","206017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77860","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the success of steps taken to encourage and facilitate first time buyers and young people to get onto the property ladder.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205895","205895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77861","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 438W, on tax evasion, what recent progress has been made by HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) in initiating proceedings against all current HMRC fugitives; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206010","206010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77862","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost in salaries was for those officials in his Department employed in tackling tobacco smuggling (a) in total, (b) in detection, (c) in investigations and (d) on intelligence matters in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206015","206015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77863","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what expenditure HM Revenue and Customs has incurred in operating x-ray scanners to tackle tobacco smuggling in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206016","206016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77864","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce the bureaucracy required to apply for a new mortgage.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205997","205997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77865","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when HM Revenue and Customs last audited the (a) compliance and (b) performance of Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited in respect of the Five Year Plan under 17.1 (a) of the Private Finance Initiative contract between HM Revenue and Customs and Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205998","205998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77866","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many adults claim child tax credit for children not residing in the UK; and for how many children such UK child benefit is claimed.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205924","205924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77867","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when HM Revenue and Customs will next audit the (a) compliance and (b) performance of Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited in respect of the Five Year Plan under 17.1 (a) of the private finance initiative contract between HM Revenue and Customs and Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205999","205999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77868","2014-07-17","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what extra revenue HM Revenue and Customs has received since entry into force of the UK-Swiss Confederation Taxation Co-operation Agreement; and what discussions the Government is having with other jurisdictions on similar agreements on tax avoidance.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205846","205846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77869","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the HM Revenue and Customs leases for Abbey House and Parkside Court in Telford are up for renewal; whether Matheson House in Telford is part of the HM Revenue and Customs estate; and, if so, when its lease is due for renewal.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205796","205796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77870","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many HM Revenue and Customs staff in each (a) grade and (b) pay band were loaned to the UK Border Agency on 10 July 2014 to cover staffing shortfalls.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205797","205797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77871","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many external contractors and consultants were employed in each business area in HM Revenue and Customs at the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205798","205798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77872","2014-07-21","HM Treasury","2014-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total cost was of employing external contractors and consultants on HM Revenue and Customs-related work in 2013-14.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205799","205799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77873","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions have taken place on the future of sites in Telford as part of the Building for the Future programme.","Biography information for David Wright","David Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205800","205800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77874","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish his Department's review of the New Homes Bonus.","Biography information for Mr Nick Raynsford","Mr Nick Raynsford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206022","206022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77875","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons the actuarial reduction for a firefighter who retires earlier than normal pension age under the proposed new pension scheme for firefighters is calculated from the state pension age and not the scheme's normal pension age.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205715","205715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77876","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether a formal valuation of the existing firefighters' pensions schemes has been carried out since the Government Actuary's Department published its formal valuation in 2009.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205716","205716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77877","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the terms are of the firefighter pensions offer agreed by the Northern Ireland Executive.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205751","205751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77878","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to standardise the social housing bandings, determining needs priority, between local authorities to ensure that eviction and forced homelessness is given priority in the bandings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205762","205762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77879","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the suitability for other negotiations of the accrual rate for pension entitlement used within the offer agreed by the Northern Ireland Executive in negotiations on firefighter pensions.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205752","205752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77880","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) social housing and (b) emergency housing facilities were available to Bournemouth Borough Council in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205763","205763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77881","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has tasked the National Board with setting guidelines on making decisions on ill-health retirement for firefighters.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205753","205753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77882","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department paid to (a) G4S, (b) Serco, (c) Sodexo, (d) GEOAmey, (e) Capita, (f) Atos, (g) Mitie, (h) Working Links, (i) A4E, (j) MTC Amey, (k) GEO Group and (l) Carillion in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205850","205850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77883","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the annual administrative costs of the firefighters pension scheme 1992 and the new firefighters pension scheme 2006.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205754","205754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77884","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homeless shelters there were in (a) Dorset, (b) Bournemouth and (c) Bournemouth East constituency in each of the last 10 years; and how many such shelters were (a) operated by the local authority and (b) independently operated.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205764","205764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77885","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the expenditure of Bournemouth Borough Council has been on assisting (a) homeless people and (b) people at risk of being homeless in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205765","205765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77886","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government Actuary's Department has considered what accrual rate for the proposed 2015 firefighters' pension scheme would allow retirement at 55 without an actuarial reduction.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205755","205755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77887","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people have applied to Bournemouth Borough Council for local authority services on grounds of being (a) homeless and (b) at risk of being homeless in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205766","205766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77888","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the administration costs of the proposed 2015 firefighters' pension scheme.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205713","205713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77889","2014-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average debt level per capita is of local authorities in (a) England and (b) the North West; and what the level of debt per capita is in Warrington Borough Council.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205952","205952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77890","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Northern Ireland Executive's offer to firefighters on pensions is cost neutral.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205937","205937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77891","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish his Department's response to the Review of Property Conditions in the Private Rented Sector and a summary of the views submitted in response to that consultation.","Biography information for Mr Nick Raynsford","Mr Nick Raynsford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205934","205934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77892","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what research he has undertaken into the effects of the changes introduced in 2010 to Part F of the Building Regulations.","Biography information for Mr Nick Raynsford","Mr Nick Raynsford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205935","205935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77893","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions the Future High Streets Forum has met this year; and who has attended each such meeting.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206018","206018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77894","2014-07-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by his Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205967","205967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77895","2014-07-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department paid to (a) G4S, (b) Serco, (c) Sodexo, (d) GEOAmey, (e) Capita, (f) Atos, (g) Mitie, (h) Working Links, (i) A4E, (j) MTC Amey, (k) GEO Group and (l) Carillion in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205851","205851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77896","2014-07-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by his Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205968","205968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77897","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) masts are operational and (b) premises receive a mobile signal as a result of the Mobile Infrastructure Project.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205802","205802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77898","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many masts will be erected in Cambridgeshire as part of the Mobile Infrastructure Project.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205803","205803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77899","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of how many premises in Cambridgeshire will benefit from the Mobile Infrastructure Project.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205804","205804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77900","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many masts are operational in Cambridgeshire as a result of the Mobile Infrastructure Project.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205805","205805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77901","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has had discussions with Pan European Game Information on its pricing structure and effect on the UK video games industry.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205813","205813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77902","2014-07-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with the major auction houses on the sale of stolen antiquities from conflict areas and the links between the proceeds of such sales and the funding of terrorism.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205722","205722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77903","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, When he expects the mobile infrastructure project to be completed.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205801","205801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77904","2014-07-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make representations to telecoms companies on ceasing the practice of charging for paper bills for customers who do not have internet  access.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205827","205827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77905","2014-07-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the legacy of the 2012 Olympic Games for participation in clay pigeon shooting in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205768","205768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77906","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the cost of restructuring the shipbuilding agreement with BAE Systems.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206043","206043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77907","2014-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department will spend on the D-5 missile life extension programme in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206044","206044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77908","2014-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average time taken was by each arm of the Armed Forces to make serving personnel available to the civilian police in connection with criminal investigations in the most recent period for which figures are available; and how many approaches the civilian police have made to the Armed Forces for access to serving personnel in relation to indictable offences.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205983","205983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77909","2014-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his objectives are in negotiations with the Kenyan government on a memorandum of understanding for continued use of the Nanyuki training facility.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205893","205893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77910","2014-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the net benefit to UK defence exports as a result of the recent Farnborough Airshow.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206008","206008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77911","2014-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by his Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205969","205969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77912","2014-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department paid to (a) G4S, (b) Serco, (c) Sodexo, (d) GEOAmey, (e) Capita, (f) Atos, (g) Mitie, (h) Working Links, (i) A4E, (j) MTC Amey, (k) GEO Group and (l) Carillion in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205852","205852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77913","2014-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he intends to lay before the House a Statutory Instrument to reflect the establishment of the Veterans Advisory and Pensions Committees; and if he will make  statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205921","205921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77914","2014-07-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that service personnel are effectively reintegrated into society following active service duty.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205910","205910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77915","2014-07-17","Cabinet Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much the Deputy Prime Minister's Office paid to (a) G4S, (b) Serco, (c) Sodexo, (d) GEOAmey, (e) Capita, (f) Atos, (g) Mitie, (h) Working Links, (i) A4E, (j) MTC Amey, (k) GEO Group and (l) Carillion in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205853","205853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77916","2014-07-21","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-15","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the criteria were for the choice of representation on the Northern Futures Board announced on 4 July 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205795","205795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77917","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her targets are for improvement at the University Academy, Liverpool; and in what timescale she will require such improvements to be made.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205793","205793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77918","2014-07-17","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that schools promote British values.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205909","205909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77919","2014-07-17","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether IGCSE qualifications will be included in 14 to 16 school performance tables after 2016.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205843","205843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77920","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many studio colleges have fulfilled the terms of their funding agreements for student recruitment targets.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205789","205789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77921","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many studio colleges that have fallen behind or failed to meet their student recruitment numbers have been given an extension of time to make further progress to achieve the numbers of students set out in their funding agreements; and what the average additional time given to those colleges to recruit enough students to fulfil funding agreement criteria was.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205787","205787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77922","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many studio colleges have fallen behind or failed to meet the levels of student recruitment required for them to meet the terms of their funding agreements.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205788","205788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77923","2014-07-21","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is in the remit of Ofsted to investigate pupils' safety from asbestos in school buildings when it inspects schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205782","205782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77924","2014-07-17","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department paid to (a) G4S, (b) Serco, (c) Sodexo, (d) GEOAmey, (e) Capita, (f) Atos, (g) Mitie, (h) Working Links, (i) A4E, (j) MTC Amey, (k) GEO Group and (l) Carillion in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13 and (iv) 2013-14.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205854","205854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77925","2014-07-17","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to promote alternatives to university to young people.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205881","205881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77926","2014-07-17","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has issued to ensure staff at free schools receive appropriate levels of background check.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205878","205878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77927","2014-07-17","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that parents of disruptive children are made fully aware of their child's bad behaviour.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205879","205879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77928","2014-07-17","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that schools teach pupils the importance of participating within the democratic process.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205920","205920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77929","2014-07-17","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential value of the Careers Lab programme and the recommendations of its recent report Inspiring the Next Generation to her Department's skills policy.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205923","205923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77930","2014-07-17","Department for Education","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding Crawley constituency will receive through the pupil premium in the financial year 2014-15.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205712","205712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77931","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the additional solar PV expected to be deployed to 2020-21 as a result of the measures proposed in the latest feed-in tariff consultation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205721","205721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77932","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reason a Renewable Obligation Certificate banding review for cuts to the large-scale PV Renewable Obligation band in 2015 and 2016 was ruled out as an option in the recent Renewables Obligation consultation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205719","205719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77933","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to deliver the Government's aim of 20 GWp of solar PV by 2020.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205720","205720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77934","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the total amount of gas consumed in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206004","206004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77935","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of total gas storage capacity in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland; and how much such capacity is (i) short range storage and (ii) long range storage.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206007","206007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77936","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what dates he has met representatives from (a) Cuadrilla, (b) Dart Energy, (c) iGas, (d) Europa Oil and Gas, (e) Greenpeace, (f) Friends of the Earth and (g) the Royal Society for the Protection of Birds in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206006","206006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77937","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 304W, on the green deal scheme, what estimate his Department has made of the average cost of energy efficiency improvements for households that have received money back under the green deal home improvements fund.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206000","206000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77938","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the quantity of gas imported to the UK through the (a) Bacton-Zeebrugge pipeline and (b) the St Fergus-Frigg/Heimdal pipeline in each month since June 2010.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206005","206005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77939","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) safety and (b) security events were reported to him by the Office for Nuclear Regulation in each 12 month period since May 2010; and what action was taken to correct the problems highlighted in each such case.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205875","205875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77940","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of whether support levels for accredited solar PV plants will be maintained for the 20 year duration specified in the Renewables Obligation order; and what the Government's policy is on (a) Renewables Obligation scheme and (b) solar PV.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205820","205820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77941","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by his Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205970","205970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77942","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 304W, on the Green Deal Scheme, whether the 450 million of financial support for domestic installation of energy efficiency measures announced in the Autumn Statement in December 2013 is in addition to (a) the 125 million allocated to the Green Deal Cashback Scheme announced in January 2013 and (b) the 200 million allocated to the Green Deal Programme in November 2011.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205957","205957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77943","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 304W, on the Green Deal Scheme, if he will make it his policy that no household receives more in money back under the Green Deal Home Improvements Fund than the cost of the installation of the energy efficiency measures.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205958","205958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77944","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2014, Official Report, column 536W, on the Green Deal Scheme, how much of the 200 million announced in November 2011 has (a) been spent, (b) been allocated for expenditure and (c) not yet been allocated for expenditure.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205959","205959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77945","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 305W, on housing energy, what programmes, projects and policies were funded under the financial support allocated to the Green Deal Programme in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2013-14.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205960","205960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77946","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 305W, on housing: energy, how much of the financial support allocated to the Green Deal Programme in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2013-14 was spent in each year.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205961","205961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77947","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 304W, on the Green Deal Scheme, how many households have received money from the Green Deal Home Improvements Fund to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205962","205962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77948","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2014, Official Report, column 304W, on the Green Deal Scheme, what the average amount paid has been to households under the Green Deal Home Improvements Fund to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205963","205963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77949","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what conversations he has held with (a) energy companies, (b) cavity wall insulation companies and (c) local authorities on the effect of the Government's changes to the Energy Company Obligation on the UK's ability to meet its carbon-saving obligations.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205790","205790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77950","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the total amount of Levy Control Framework budget spent on the Renewables Obligation in 2013-14; and what his forecast is for Renewables Obligation spend in 2014-15.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205847","205847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77951","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of National Audit Office analysis indicating that 29 million will be available for Contracts for Difference contracts in 2015-16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205848","205848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77952","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the annual saving to the Levy Control Framework budget from closure of the Renewables Obligation to large-scale solar from April 2015; what that saving is as a proportion of that budget in (a) 2016, (b) 2017, (c) 2018, (d) 2019 and (e) 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205849","205849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77953","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department has made compensation payments to householders whose homes have suffered damage from work under the Affordable Warmth Obligation.","Biography information for Mr John Denham","Mr John Denham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205828","205828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77954","2014-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will hold discussions with cavity wall insulation companies on potential job losses arising from changes in the Energy Company Obligation.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205792","205792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77955","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to simplify existing environmental, marine and agricultural regulations.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205985","205985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77956","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her most recent estimate is of the UK population of each species of bumble bee; and what steps she is taking to increase the numbers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205771","205771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77957","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by her Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205971","205971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77958","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effects of the CAP reforms on farmers.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205877","205877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77959","2014-07-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the UK's performance towards the targets in the Kyoto protocol on emission reduction targets between 2008 and 2012.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205988","205988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77960","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the success of steps taken to meet the 2013 and 2020 EU Landfill Directive.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205986","205986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77961","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to restore upland peat sites.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205987","205987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77962","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department's study to determine whether cage-based breeding can meet the needs of game birds, reference AW1303 has made; what the cost of that study was; and for what reason the findings of that study have not been published.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206013","206013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77963","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's position is in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on future-proofing UK and EU standards of consumer and worker protection, animal welfare and environmental sustainability following the conclusion of those negotiations.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205724","205724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77964","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's position is in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on any weakening of farm animal welfare provisions in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205733","205733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77965","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's position is in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on labelling of products containing GM in the UK food chain; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205728","205728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77966","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's position is in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on food procurement rules and the ability of the Government to stipulate conditions on procurement which recognise local and regional food and the economic and other benefits of sourcing local and regional food for public procurement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205729","205729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77967","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of whether measures to achieve regulatory convergence under the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership may lead to a lower standard of food production in the UK in respect of (a) food safety, (b) food labelling and transparency, (c) animal welfare, (d) worker protections and (e) consumer protections; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205730","205730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77968","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's position is in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on poultry treated with hyper-chlorinated water entering the UK food chain; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205731","205731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77969","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's position is in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on meat treated with antibiotics as growth promoters entering the UK food chain; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205732","205732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77970","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's position is in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on meat and dairy products derived from cloned animals in the UK food-chain; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205726","205726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77971","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's position is in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on pork and other meats treated with lactic acid and other organic washes entering the UK food-chain; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205725","205725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77972","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the (a) British Association for Shooting and Conservation and (b) Countryside Alliance on Larsen traps for the control of corvids.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205767","205767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77973","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken to implement the commitments contained in the white paper, The Natural Choice: securing the value of nature published in 2011.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206012","206012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77974","2014-07-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's position is in the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations on meat containing ractopamine entering the UK food-chain; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205727","205727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77975","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made about human rights and the humanitarian situation in Kashmir in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205717","205717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77976","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support religious tolerance of Christians in India.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205995","205995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77977","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the opening of the airport on St Helena does not lead to the development of child sex tourism in that territory.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205829","205829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77978","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department has received about allegations of child abuse and police corruption on St Helena since May 2010; when that information was received; and what steps his Department took in response to that information.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205830","205830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77979","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information the Governor of St Helena has received about allegations of child abuse and police corruption in that territory since May 2010; when that information was received; and what steps the Governor took in response to that information.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205831","205831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77980","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the sale on stolen antiquities to fund violent conflict and terrorism in Iraq.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205749","205749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77981","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in other NATO member states on the Middle East.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205996","205996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77982","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on steps to tackle Islamic extremism in Europe.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205913","205913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77983","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political stability of Egypt.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205914","205914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77984","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage freedom of religion in Burma and other South-East Asian countries.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205891","205891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77985","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what level of assistance his Department has provided to rebels in Syria; what form such support has taken; and what steps  he is taking to prevent its misuse.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205892","205892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77986","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he  is taking to protect biodiversity on the Pitcairn Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205917","205917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77987","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that Crimea is still internationally recognised as part of the Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205915","205915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77988","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the importance of the sustainability of the British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205916","205916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77989","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he had with his Libyan counterparts about violence in Tripoli.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205816","205816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77990","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, What recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205919","205919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77991","2014-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Tripoli.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205817","205817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77992","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to tackle offences of child abuse on St Helena.","Biography information for John Hemming","John Hemming","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205832","205832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77993","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by his Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205972","205972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77994","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce tension in the on-going conflict between Israel and Palestine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205911","205911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77995","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what consular assistance is available to British nationals travelling to and around North Korea.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205908","205908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77996","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the theft of antiquities by ISIS and their sale in the international arts market.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205842","205842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77997","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Chinese counterpart on the health and whereabouts of human rights' lawyer Mr Gao Zhisheng following his further detention by Chinese authorities.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205837","205837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77998","2014-07-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the newly elected President of the Syrian National Council.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205844","205844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/77999","2014-07-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with Sotheby's Auction House on the sale of conflict antiquities in the UK domestic marketplace.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205839","205839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78000","2014-07-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will bring forward legislation to outlaw the sale of stolen conflict antiquities in the UK.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205840","205840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78001","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the right hon. Member for Chelmsford can expect a response from the Chief Executive of NHS England to his letter of 30 May 2014 on his constituent Mr John McPhee.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205784","205784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78002","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost per night is of a bed in (a) an intensive therapy unit or high dependency unit, (b) a district general hospital, (c) a spinal cord injury centre and (d) a spinal cord injury centre for a ventilated spinal cord injured patient.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205785","205785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78003","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage parents to prevent the consumption of alcohol by children; and what steps are being taken by schools to assist this prevention work.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205770","205770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78004","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with medical authorities on the use of botox as a painkiller; and whether it is used as such in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205769","205769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78005","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request NHS England to authorise the use of Gamma Knife for NHS patients at University College Hospital London.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206028","206028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78006","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data his Department gathers on the number of patients with diabetes who are admitted to hospital each month as a result of a hypoglycaemic episode; and what estimate has been made of the overall cost of hypoglycaemia to the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205903","205903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78007","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the value is of duplicate supplier payments identified by his Department since 2010; and what proportion of such payments have since been recovered in each of the last two financial years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205973","205973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78008","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to report to hon Members on the steps he is taking to ensure the continued quality and availability of assistive technology.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205835","205835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78009","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reason none of the 42 million his Department has made available for increasing the use of radiotherapy is to be spent on treating cancer patients with Stereotactic Ablative Radiotherapy this year.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205834","205834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78010","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what role NHS England plays in the development of advice given by the Prescribed Specialised Services Advisory Group to Ministers on which specialised services should be included in regulations setting out those services which NHS England must commission.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206003","206003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78011","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the new Single Operating Model for investigating mental health homicides for the NHS in England will become operational.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205925","205925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78012","2014-07-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will extend victims' rights to victims of mentally disordered offenders to be more comparable with those rights afforded to victims in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205927","205927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78013","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many individual funding requests per indication were received by NHS England for radiotherapy treatment in the last financial year; and how many requests, per indication, were refused by NHS England.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205953","205953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78014","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the NHS budget allocated to (a) diabetes, (b) cancer, (c) dementia and (d) cardiovascular disease.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205929","205929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78015","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will issue new guidance to NHS Trusts on the timely provision of information to victims' families following a mental health homicide.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205926","205926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78016","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons NHS England is instructing hospitals with patients presenting as clinically urgent to treat such patients with innovative radiotherapy at the hospital's financial risk while it decides whether to fund the patient; and how hospitals which have followed that instruction receive reimbursement for that expenditure if NHS England subsequently refuses to fund the treatment.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205954","205954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78017","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, to what extent NHS England is obliged to follow guidance issued by Monitor.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205780","205780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78018","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects to make a decision on the North Tees and Hartlepool NHS Foundation Trust's submission on a new hospital at Wynyard.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205723","205723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78019","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress NHS England has made on development of the (a) mission and vision and (b) service-level planning elements of its five year strategy for specialised services; when publication of that strategy is expected; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205758","205758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78020","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England plans to publish its five year strategy for specialised services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205759","205759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78021","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how NHS England evaluates service specific A3 change proposals for its five-year strategy development for specialised services; when authors of those proposals will learn the outcomes of their proposals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205760","205760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78022","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department and (b) NHS England plan to take to reduce premature mortality from respiratory disease.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205718","205718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78023","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many repeat abortions were performed on women aged (a) 25 to 30, (b) 30 to 35, (c) 35 to 40, (d) 40 to 45 and (e) 45 years and over by gestation in weeks; and how many abortions those women had previously undergone.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205990","205990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78024","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on (a) the current waiting time following referral for a first appointment at Charing Cross Gender Identity Clinic (GIC), (b) how many people are currently receiving treatment at that clinic and how long the average wait is between appointments; what assessment his Department has made of how many patients Charing Cross GIC can treat in a year according to best practice guidelines and within existing resources; what discussions he has had with the Chief Executive of NHS England on the steps necessary to increase provision of services for trans people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206001","206001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78025","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's publication, Abortion Statistics, England and Wales: 2013, published in June 2014, which method of stopping the fetal heart besides feticide is referred to in paragraph 2.25.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205991","205991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78026","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women who underwent an abortion in 2013 had previously had an ectopic pregnancy.","Biography information for Mr Joe Benton","Mr Joe Benton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205992","205992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78027","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether patients and their families are entitled to receive copies of consent forms they have signed.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205948","205948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78028","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the British Medical Association and cancer groups on studies of the potential effects of aspirin on cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205824","205824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78029","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that the operation to remove fibroids by MR Guided Focused Ultrasound Surgery (MRgFUS) be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205823","205823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78030","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to facilitate the establishment of a gender identity clinic in Brighton and Hove; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 206002","206002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78031","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women in each age group had hysterectomies  in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205822","205822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78032","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how NHS England's specialised commissioning taskforce intends to incorporate work submitted by (a) clinical reference groups and (b) other stakeholders in response to its requests for A3 change proposals to inform the development of its five year strategy for specialised services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205757","205757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78033","2014-07-21","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that internal defibrillators be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205821","205821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78034","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with Transport for London the installation of hand sanitisers on London Underground trains and platforms.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205750","205750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78035","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how long the North Tees and Hartlepool NHS Foundation Trust's submission on a new hospital at Wynyard has been considered by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205709","205709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78036","2014-07-17","Department of Health","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are for the time taken to make a decision on the North Tees and Hartlepool NHS Foundation Trust's submission on a new hospital at Wynyard.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205710","205710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78037","2014-07-17","Home Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take additional steps to tackle human trafficking within the UK's borders.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205994","205994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78038","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the NSPCC about its current and future plans to train staff to run her planned modern slavery helpline; what that training will include; what the estimated cost is of such training; and which body will provide the training.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205949","205949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78039","2014-07-21","Home Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to whom the NSPCC will refer cases of people (a) from EU countries and (b) who are not EU nationals, who call her planned modern slavery helpline and are identified as victims of modern slavery.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205950","205950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78040","2014-07-17","Home Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many regulated procedures conducted in Wales under the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 involved (a) mice, (b) rats, (c) guinea pigs, (d) hamsters, (e) rabbits, (f) horses and other equids, (g) sheep, (h) pigs, (i) birds, (j) amphibians, (k) reptiles, (l) fish, (m) cats, (n) dogs, (o) New World primates and (p) Old World primates in 2013; and how many such procedures involved (i) genetically modified animals and (ii) animals with harmful genetic defects.","Biography information for Jonathan Evans","Jonathan Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205735","205735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78041","2014-07-17","Home Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places in Wales were designated as a (a) supplying establishment, (b) breeding establishment and (c) scientific procedure establishment under the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 at the end of 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Evans","Jonathan Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205742","205742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/78042","2014-07-17","Home Office","2014-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many animals were used in regulated procedures under the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986 in Wales in 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Evans","Jonathan Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 205743","205743"
