"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750257","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when  he expects HM Prison Berwyn to be operating at full capacity.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3936","3936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750258","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many restricted patients' discharge procedures were awaiting approval by his Department in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4032","4032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750259","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that Category C male prisoners from North Wales are considered for transfer to HM Prison Berwyn.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3937","3937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750260","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce sentencing guidelines for offences under the Housing Acts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3794","3794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750261","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) psychiatrists and (b) psychologists are employed in prison and young offender institutions.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3845","3845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750262","2017-07-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to ensure consistency in sentencing criminal landlords for housing-related offences.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3793","3793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750263","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of how many staff are employed in a 1,300-capacity category C prison (a) directly and (b) in the supply chain.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3730","3730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750264","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, where the funding will come from for the building of the proposed prison at Hindley.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3731","3731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750265","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have been transferred between prisons who have (a) completed and (b) incomplete OASys in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3711","3711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750266","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will launch a review into the process of, and arrangement for, sentence planning to ensure that prisoners transferring from other prisons arrive with a complete and up to date OASys.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3712","3712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750267","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have been employed in Offender Management Units in each prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3713","3713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750268","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on Offender Management Unit staff in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3714","3714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750269","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was of contracts tendered out for prison maintenance by (a) prison and (b) private sector service provider in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3715","3715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750270","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will launch a review into the contractual agreements of private sector service providers for maintenance work in prisons.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3716","3716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750271","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners (a) requested and (b) were granted access to laptop computer facilities in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3717","3717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750272","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons have dedicated equalities departments.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3718","3718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750273","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) capacity and (b) attendance was of the prisons education, learning and skills departments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3719","3719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750274","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidelines his Department has produced for prisons on Access to Justice on (a) how and when computers can be accessed by prisoners and (b) for how long and what actions and tasks can be undertaken.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3720","3720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750275","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convicted sex offenders have (a) started and (b) completed the Sex Offender Treatment Programme; and of those offenders how many are (i) in prison, (ii) released and (iii) in a bail hostel.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3721","3721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750276","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of sex offences in category (a) adult: violent/serious rape, sexual assault, (b) adult other: possession and distribution of banned material, (c) child contact: any sexual offence involving direct sexual contact with a victim who is under 16 years old (or under 18 years old in cases of incest, prostitution and abuse of a position of trust), (d) child other: abuse of a position of trust (not involving direct sexual contact) with a victim who is under 16 years old following grooming and other child non-contact offences, (e) child image: creation, possession and distribution of indecent images of a victim under 18 years old, (f) breach of conviction/release conditions related to a sexual offence, (g) prostitution/soliciting involving a victim who is over 18 years old and related offences such as running or promoting a brother, (h) non-sexual violent: violent non-sexual offences, (i) non-sexual non-violent have (i) undertaken the Sex Offender Treatment Programme and (ii) gone on to re-offend in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3722","3722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750277","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to create a new scheme to rehabilitate offenders since the halt of the Sex Offender Treatment Programme.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3723","3723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750278","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the review into the Sex Offender Treatment Programme was commissioned; and which Minister commissioned that review.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3724","3724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750279","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons undertook at least one segregation monitoring and review meeting in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3725","3725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750280","2017-07-12","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons operate a personal officer programme.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3726","3726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750281","2017-07-12","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if he will make it his policy to introduce legislation requiring the Electoral Commission to publish details of all reportable donations and loans received by political parties in Northern Ireland since January 2014.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3732","3732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750282","2017-07-12","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the contribution from the Minister for the Cabinet Office on 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what work is being done to progress work to distinguish Gypsies and Travellers using 2011 census classifications in his Department.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3874","3874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750283","2017-07-13","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether he plans to review the proxy vote process in Northern Ireland to reduce the risk of misuse.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3898","3898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750284","2017-07-12","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the oral Answer of 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what steps his Department has taken to use 2011 census classifications, including on Gypsies and Travellers, to audit racial disparities in public service outcomes.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4060","4060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750285","2017-07-12","Prime Minister","2017-07-10","To ask the Prime Minister, what the cost of hospitality provided to Paul Dacre was at 10 Downing Street on 24 October 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3872","3872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750286","2017-07-12","Prime Minister","2017-07-10","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2017 to Question 1816, how many meetings of (a) her and (b) her predecessor's political cabinet Ruth Davidson MSP was invited to and attended.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3925","3925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750287","2017-07-12","Prime Minister","2017-07-10","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2017 to Question 1788, how many meetings of (a) her and (b) her predecessor's political cabinet Andrew Davies AM was invited to and attended.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3926","3926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750288","2017-07-12","Scotland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 1974, if he will publish the artwork and text of each of the adverts used by his Department during March 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3980","3980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750289","2017-07-12","Scotland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 1974, what social media platforms were included in his Department's social media spend during March 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3979","3979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750290","2017-07-12","Scotland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 1974, what demographics were targeted by his Department's social media spend during March 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3978","3978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750291","2017-07-12","Scotland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the contribution from the Minister for the Cabinet Office on 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what work is being done to progress work to distinguish Gypsies and Travellers using 2011 census classifications in his Department.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3875","3875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750292","2017-07-12","Scotland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the oral Answer of 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what steps his Department has taken to use 2011 census classifications, including on Gypsies and Travellers, to audit racial disparities in public service outcomes.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4061","4061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750293","2017-07-12","Scotland Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 1974, what geographical areas were targeted by his Department's social media spend during March 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3977","3977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750294","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4024","4024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750295","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3994","3994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750296","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4009","4009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750297","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers (a) his Department and (b) local authorities have to charge operators for its installation of mobile traffic lights.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4078","4078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750298","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral Answer of 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what steps his Department has taken to use 2011 census classifications, including on Gypsies and Travellers, to audit racial disparities in public service outcomes.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4062","4062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750299","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will regulate the use of mobile traffic lights to ensure sufficient warning is given to road users.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4077","4077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750300","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what compensation arrangements are in place to support passengers affected by the recent closures at Paddington station.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4076","4076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750301","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to assess the resilience of Great Western Railway as a result of the recent closures of Paddington station.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4075","4075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750302","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many motor vehicles in each vehicle excise duty class are registered to Scottish addresses by registration (a) before and (b) after 1 April 2017.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4083","4083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750303","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the contribution from the Minister for the Cabinet Office on 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what work is being done to progress work to distinguish Gypsies and Travellers using 2011 census classifications in his Department.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3876","3876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750304","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government plans to publish its response to the consultation on the proposed changes to the Renewable Transport Fuel Obligation Order.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3892","3892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750305","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Network Rail on the Edinburgh to Glasgow Improvement Programme works.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4050","4050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750306","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions (a) he and (b) officials of his Department have had with (i) the Chancellor of  the Exchequer and (ii) officials of HM Treasury on rail fares policy since 13 June 2017.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4040","4040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750307","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with Nexus on that company's proposals for new rolling stock for the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3916","3916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750308","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Network Rail on noise and vibration pollution caused by certain types of freight wagons in use on the rail network; and whether any changes to regulations (a) have been or (b) are under consideration to reduce noise and vibration pollution.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3753","3753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750309","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the effectiveness of Network Rail's re-planning of Control Period 5.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3812","3812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750310","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that road accident and casualty statistics are published on time; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3841","3841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750311","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Government's policy is on reducing deaths and injuries to road users; and if he will adopt casualty reduction targets.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3843","3843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750312","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has conducted a cost-benefit analysis on proposals to build a community cycle path along the B4044 from Eynsham to Botley.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3790","3790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750313","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has conducted a cost-benefit analysis on proposals to build a cycle route from Oxford to Didcot.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3791","3791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750314","2017-07-12","Wales Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the contribution from the Minister for the Cabinet Office on 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what work is being done to progress work to distinguish Gypsies and Travellers using 2011 census classifications in his Department.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3877","3877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750315","2017-07-12","Wales Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the oral Answer of 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what steps his Department has taken to use 2011 census classifications, including on Gypsies and Travellers, to audit racial disparities in public service outcomes.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4063","4063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750316","2017-07-12","Women and Equalities","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the oral Answer of 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what steps her Department has taken to use 2011 census classifications, including on Gypsies and Travellers, to audit racial disparities in public service outcomes.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4058","4058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750317","2017-07-12","Women and Equalities","2017-07-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the contribution from the Minister for the Cabinet Office on 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what work is being done to progress work to distinguish Gypsies and Travellers using 2011 census classifications in her Department.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3879","3879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750318","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the contribution from the Minister for the Cabinet Office on 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what work is being done to progress work to distinguish Gypsies and Travellers using 2011 census classifications in his Department.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3878","3878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750319","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the average length of telephone calls it receives from universal credit claimants in areas where the universal credit full digital service is being rolled out.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3864","3864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750320","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what proportion of disability benefit claims his Department asks a claimant's doctor for medical evidence directly rather than seeking that evidence through the claimant.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3887","3887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750321","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on which date (a) he or (b) a Minister of his Department last visited Torrington Avenue Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3861","3861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750322","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on which date (a) he or (b) a Minister of his Department last visited Cofa Court Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3860","3860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750323","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of the time of directors of the Benefits and Pensions Digital Technology Services Limited (BPDTS) is spent as (a) employees of his Department and (b) employees of BPDTS; who in his Department awards work to BPDTS; whether there is any financial benefit to those directors from work awarded by his Department to that company; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3829","3829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750324","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the proposed closure of a number of jobcentres in the North West on travelling time and distance for claimants.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4046","4046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750325","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of his Department's processing and contact centre in Bootle Linacre on the response times for caseload in the local area.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4049","4049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750326","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of constituents in the Vale of Clwyd constituency have had their original personal independence payments overturned as a result of (a) mandatory reconsideration or (b) an appeal hearing in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3981","3981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750327","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether people with mental or physical health problems living in supported housing will be exempt from the local housing allowance rate cap for housing benefit.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3888","3888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750328","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the optimum number of universal credit claimants for the caseload of a work coach in a (a) live service and (b) full digital service area.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4030","4030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750329","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the roll-out of the universal credit full digital service to date.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4029","4029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750330","2017-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 1 March 2016 to Question 27621, what guidance his Department provides to its staff on proactively making callers who want to discuss universal credit aware that staff can call them back free of charge.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4028","4028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750331","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of (a) the cost-effectiveness and (b) resource efficiency of employment and support allowance claimants who have been found fit to work claiming jobseeker's allowance while waiting for the result of a mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3774","3774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750332","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to (a) ensure that the outcome of assessments conducted by his Department on people seeking to claim employment and support allowance are correct and (b) reduce the number of decisions based on such assessments which are overturned on appeal.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3772","3772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750333","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many 0345 telephone numbers his Department operates.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3846","3846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750334","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) longest and (b) mean waiting times to his Department's (i) universal credit helpline and (ii) 0345 phone lines.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3847","3847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750335","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is the Government's policy that support for mortgage interest will become an interest-bearing loan secured against the mortgaged property from April 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3727","3727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750336","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the Government's policy from April 2018 will be on support for mortgage interest.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3742","3742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750337","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the Government's policy is on families with more than two children claiming universal credit and child tax credit.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3743","3743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750338","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on new claims for employer support childcare vouchers from April 2018.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3744","3744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750339","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the new single financial guidance body will host a pensions dashboard.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4095","4095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750340","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time was for calls to (a) the universal credit helpline and (b) his Department's 0345 phone lines in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4085","4085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750341","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to claimants of an average length call to his Department's 0345 numbers.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4086","4086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750342","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral Answer of 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what steps his Department has taken to use 2011 census classifications, including on Gypsies and Travellers, to audit racial disparities in public service outcomes.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4064","4064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750343","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of constituents in Vale of Clwyd constituency in receipt of disability living allowance have subsequently been assessed as ineligible for personal independence payments in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4074","4074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750344","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are in receipt of universal credit in Southampton.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4110","4110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750345","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support is given to claimants of universal credit during the assessment process.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4112","4112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750346","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what repayment support is given to claimants who take out a hardship payment.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4113","4113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750347","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what review of the universal credit policy has been undertaken since its implementation; and what assessment that review made of the effectiveness of that policy at reducing the number of workless households.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4111","4111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750348","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what income support is given to benefit claimants who transition from one benefit to another to prevent long periods of no income.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4115","4115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750349","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants in Southampton have taken out a hardship payment.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4114","4114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750350","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4011","4011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750351","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the proposed programme of Jobcentre Plus closures on the rollout of the full digital service of universal credit.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3962","3962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750352","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the (a) number of telephone calls it receives from universal credit claimants and (b) level of assistance with telephone enquiries needed by claimants in (i) areas where the universal credit full digital service is being rolled out and (ii) other areas.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3960","3960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750353","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of women in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK who will be affected by changes to the state pension age for women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3918","3918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750354","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how claims for universal credit by people who are not able to use IT are made and managed in full digital service areas.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3961","3961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750355","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of children were living in poverty in Vale of Clwyd constituency in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3941","3941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750356","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4026","4026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750357","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average number of bids received for each contract put out to tender by his Department was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3996","3996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750358","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what claimant support is offered to individuals with low levels of literacy, numeracy or computer skills.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4116","4116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750359","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 27 June 2017, Official Report, column 441, what organisations on the EU Exit Business Advisory Group represent the chemicals industry.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3968","3968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750360","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many contracts put out to tender by (a) his Department and (b) former constituent Departments have been (i) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3953","3953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750361","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of public procurement contracts (a) his Department and (b) former constituent Departments awarded through framework agreements in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3951","3951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750362","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the amount of student (a) fees not paid and (b) loans not repaid by foreign students from (a) EU and (b) non-EU countries was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3746","3746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750363","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has received any representations on the Post Office's planned operation of Transcash in 2017-18.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3839","3839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750364","2017-07-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received from the Centre of Alternative Technology on the contents of his proposed Clean Growth Plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3814","3814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750365","2017-07-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the Clean Growth Plan.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3815","3815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750366","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that administration fees charged by car insurance companies for changes to policies are proportionate to the cost of the policy change.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3934","3934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750367","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many bids on average were received for each contract put out to tender by his Department and its previous constituent Departments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3930","3930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750368","2017-07-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the adequacy of the length of maternity and paternity leave of parents who have multiple births.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3880","3880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750369","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what digital format (a) has previously been used and (b) is currently in use to store data on the Sellafield nuclear waste plant; and what estimate he has made of the length of time each of those formats will last.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3865","3865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750370","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the level of carbon emissions from his Department's estate since his Department's establishment.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3863","3863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750371","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much (a) his Department and (b) each of his Department's (i) non-departmental public bodies and (ii) executive agencies spent on external consultants and advisers since his Department was established.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3853","3853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750372","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many receptions he has hosted for representatives of print and broadcast media since the establishment of his Department; how much each such reception cost; and how many people attended each such reception.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3854","3854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750373","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many expert groups his Department has set up since its establishment; and what the areas of their expertise are.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3855","3855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750374","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the cost of sickness pay to staff in his Department has been since it was established.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3856","3856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750375","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will list his Department's premises in the UK with more than 10 members of staff by nation and region.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3850","3850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750376","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many bids were on average received for each contract put out to tender by his Department since it was established.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3929","3929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750377","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much was disbursed on advertising by (a) his Department and (b) each of its (i) non-departmental public bodies and (ii) executive agencies since his Department was established.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3840","3840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750378","2017-07-13","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the benefits of and opportunities for trade and investment are shared across the regions and nations of the UK.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3778","3778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750379","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the total value of exports of goods and services was to (a) countries comprising the EU single market and (b) the rest of the world in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3747","3747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750380","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered since his Department's creation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3952","3952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750381","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of public procurement contracts his Department awarded through framework agreements since his Department's creation.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3950","3950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750382","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many trade delegates he has led since taking up his position; and to which countries he has led those delegates.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4096","4096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750383","2017-07-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2017 to Question 2279, on immigration: EU nationals, what the Government's policy is on the status of partners of EU citizens from non-EU countries residing in the UK on a visa sponsored by an EU citizen with permanent residency as set out in the Immigration Rules.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3957","3957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750384","2017-07-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many contracts put out to tender by his Department have been (a) cancelled and (b) re-tendered in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3956","3956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750385","2017-07-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2017 to Question 239, on what dates he plans to release the list of sectors his Department has been examining.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3781","3781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750386","2017-07-13","Home Office","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 6 of her Department's policy paper, Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, whether applicants for settled status will be required to pass the citizenship test.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3782","3782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750387","2017-07-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to his Department's policy paper, Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, what his policy is on the legal status of UK nationals residing in other EU member states in the context of the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3786","3786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750388","2017-07-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 6 of his Department's policy paper, Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, whether the rights accrued by those who obtain settled status in the UK will be for life.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3787","3787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750389","2017-07-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of procurement contracts were awarded through framework agreements by his Department since it was established.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3927","3927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750390","2017-07-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many bids were on average received for each contract put out to tender by his Department since it was established.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3928","3928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750391","2017-07-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether it is the Government's policy to remain part of the European Observatory on the supply of medical radioisotopes.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 4043","4043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750392","2017-07-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2017 to Question 2279, on immigration: EU nationals, whether the process will differ for people (a) with permanent residence applying for a grant of settled status and (b) submitting new applications to reside in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3958","3958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750393","2017-07-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the English language would cease to be an official language of the EU after the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3894","3894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/750901","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made towards an outcome for the Southeastern franchise.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900465","900465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/751586","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the costs and benefits of rail franchising.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900473","900473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/751587","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress he has made on the electrification of the Great Western main line.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900470","900470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/751588","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of emissions from road transport.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900469","900469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/751589","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department is taking steps to increase the national speed limit on motorways.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900474","900474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/751590","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to make a decision on the new fleet for the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900467","900467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/751591","2017-07-13","Department for Transport","2017-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to make a decision on the Crossrail 2 business case; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900472","900472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749613","2017-07-11","Cabinet Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the (a) amount and (b) proportion of public procurement placed with small and medium-sized businesses in (i) Oxford city, (ii) Oxford West and Abingdon constituency and (iii) Oxfordshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3673","3673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749614","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been saved in 2017 prices as a result of the imposition of the public sector pay cap.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3645","3645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749615","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much he plans to spend on social security in each of the next five financial years as a percentage of gross domestic product.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3655","3655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749616","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many contracts have been awarded by or on behalf of his Department to (a) Brewin Dolphin PLC, (b) Tullett Prebon PLC, (c) PARC, (d) Oxera, (e) Goodacre UK, (f) RELX, (g) Royal Dutch Shell, (h) KPMG, (i) Lloyds, (j) Bishop Fleming Accountants, (k) Ernst & Young, (l) Clerical Medical, (m) Heathrow Airport, (n) Deloitte, (o) PwC, (p) Grant Thornton and (q) Slaughter & May since July 2015; and what the value was of each of those contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3606","3606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749617","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many contracts have been awarded by or on behalf of his Department to (a) Brewin Dolphin PLC, (b) Tullett Prebon PLC, (c) PARC, (d) Oxera, (e) Goodacre UK, (f) RELX, (g) Royal Dutch Shell, (h) KPMG, (i) Lloyds, (j) Bishop Fleming Accountants, (k) Ernst & Young, (l) Clerical Medical, (m) Heathrow Airport, (n) Deloitte, (o) PwC, (p) Grant Thornton and (q) Slaughter & May between July 2010 and July 2015; and what the value was of each of those contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3607","3607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749618","2017-07-11","HM Treasury","2017-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last discussed with members of the US Cabinet trade in steel between the US and the UK.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3621","3621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749619","2017-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for the introduction of legislative proposals on banning pension cold-calling and blocking suspicious pension pot transfers.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3624","3624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749620","2017-07-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of borough-wide licensing schemes in raising standards and improving safety in the private rented sector.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3654","3654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749621","2017-07-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce regulations on the level of maintenance fees borne by leaseholders.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3660","3660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749622","2017-07-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2017 to Question 371, whether there is a requirement to remove polystyrene ceiling tiles from older buildings.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3678","3678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749623","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many council homes have been sold in (a) Ashford constituency and (b) Nottingham in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3706","3706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749624","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will set out the criteria against which applications for additional funding from local authorities for work to address fire safety in tower blocks will be assessed.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3700","3700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749625","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons he appointed a recovery taskforce for the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea Council and not Commissioners; and how the powers, responsibilities and accountability of that taskforce differ from those of Commissioners.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3702","3702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749626","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will set out the powers, scope, responsibilities and accountability of the recovery taskforce appointed to run the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3701","3701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749627","2017-07-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what incentives are available to local authorities to build council housing on (a) brownfield and (b) greenfield sites.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3707","3707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749628","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings (a) she and (b) Ministers of her Department have had with representatives of S4C since 1 January 2017.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3697","3697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749629","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 1 March 2017 to Question 65037, which items from the Government Art Collection have been displayed at public museums or galleries in the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3698","3698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749630","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with representatives of the performing arts industry on diversity in casting voice-only performances.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3699","3699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749631","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to introduce fines for social media companies which fail to remove extremist content from their platforms.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3681","3681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749632","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with social media companies to ensure that they comply with their terms of service on removing offensive content including hate speech from their platforms.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3685","3685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749634","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with social media companies on the adoption of a consistent approach to reporting and removing hate speech across all platforms.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3682","3682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749635","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will postpone any decision on the proposed takeover of Sky by 21st Century Fox until after the publication of any report on the second stage of the Leveson Inquiry.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3669","3669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749636","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with social media companies on educating their employees on (a) antisemitic, (b) Islamophobic and (c) racist images or discourse on their platforms.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3683","3683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749637","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with social media companies to agree a single working definition of hate crime between all platforms.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3684","3684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749638","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Wales on whether devolution of broadcasting should be included in the remit of the S4C review.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3620","3620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749639","2017-07-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the timetable is for the consultation on amending the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulation 2003 to introduce director liability for breaches of that regulation.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3632","3632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749640","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will include the devolution of broadcasting in the remit of the S4C review.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3619","3619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749641","2017-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the implications for the public purse of Annington's 2021 review of rents on the properties sold to it by his Department in 1996; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3649","3649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749642","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to maintain the UK's involvement in the Erasmus scheme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3679","3679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749643","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in each local authority and constituency are registered in independent alternative provision for excluded young people; how many of those children are (a) enrolled or (b) being directed offsite for their education there for more than one day a week in each year since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3659","3659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749644","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 10 October 2016 to Question 46648, from the hon. Member for Ashfield, on schools: nurses, if she will provide the same data for the Hull local authority for each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3656","3656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749645","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 29 March 2017 to Question 68665, from the hon. Member for York Central, on schools: City of York, if she will provide the same data for the Hull local authority for each year since 2005.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3657","3657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749646","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children, by age, are home-schooled in each (a) local authority and (b) parliamentary constituency in each year since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3650","3650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749647","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which schools in England have closed their sixth form since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3640","3640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749648","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which academies have closed in England since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3641","3641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749649","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which sixth form colleges have closed in England since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3642","3642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749650","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 20 April 2017 to Question 70790 on arts: teachers, if she will publish the same data on the total number of (a) primary and (b) secondary school teachers for each school subject in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3690","3690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749651","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 27 March 2017 to Question 68496, on class sizes: York, if she will publish the same data for Hull in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3691","3691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749652","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on 16 to 19-year-old education in each financial year since 2014-15.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3688","3688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749653","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department allocated to 16 to 19-year-old education in each financial year since 2014-15.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3689","3689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749654","2017-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish the Government's draft Air Quality Plan before the summer recess.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3665","3665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749655","2017-07-11","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will set target dates for phasing out (a) petrol and (b) diesel vehicles.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3680","3680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749656","2017-07-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will set a target date for the UK to become carbon neutral.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3676","3676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749657","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what advice the Government provides to British companies which supply or are considering to supply the Burmese military or are considering entering into joint ventures or other business arrangements with military-owned or military-linked companies from that country.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3630","3630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749658","2017-07-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his Argentinian counterpart; and what was discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3626","3626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749659","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on the safety and freedom of speech of political dissidents.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3666","3666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749660","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with his EU counterparts on the human rights situation in Turkey.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3668","3668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749661","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with Turkish Government officials on human rights in that country.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3667","3667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749662","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health visitors have been employed in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3703","3703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749663","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to provide alternative sources of advice to support new parents in areas where there is a shortage of health visitors.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3704","3704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749664","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which specialist areas of medicine are experiencing shortages of (a) consultants and (b) registrars; and how many vacancies there are in those disciplines.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3705","3705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749665","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will subsidise GP's indemnity costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3623","3623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749666","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of establishing the NHS Property Board.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3633","3633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749667","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Cabinet committees and sub-committees relating to the UK leaving the EU he is a member of.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3610","3610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749668","2017-07-12","Department of Health","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost of treating tooth decay in the NHS has been in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3611","3611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749669","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are employed at the National Cyber Security Centre; and what estimate he has made of changes to that number in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3636","3636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749670","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what process her Department plans to use to identify all existing lawful EU residents and their families eligible for the period of blanket residence permission, outlined in paragraph 24 of her Department's policy paper, Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017; and what the procedure will be for applications for such permission.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3708","3708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749671","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of her Department's capacity to implement the policy proposals outlined in her Department's policy paper  Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3710","3710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749672","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether  she plans to update her Department's guidance on removals and revocations of European Economic Area nationals as outlined in her Department's policy paper Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3709","3709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749673","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister of State, Home Office of 29 June 2017, HL 783, column 551, whether local authorities with capacity to care for a greater number of unaccompanied children than that set out under the provisions of section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016 and the Written Ministerial Statement made on 26 April 2017, HCWS 619, will be able to apply to do so.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3686","3686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749674","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints were made about the loss of passport application packs or documents contained within those packs by Sopra Steria in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3664","3664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749675","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans are in place for the National Cyber Security Centre to assist companies in fighting against organised cyber-crime and preventing cyber-attacks.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3643","3643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749676","2017-07-12","Cabinet Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans are in place for the National Cyber Security Centre to assist schools in fighting against organised cyber-crime and preventing cyber-attacks.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3644","3644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749677","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total amount remaining in the Special Grant available to police forces is for 2017-18.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3658","3658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749678","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of responses to domestic violence incidents which took place 24 hours after the incident was reported by each police force.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3653","3653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749679","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether employees of the National Cyber Security Centre are included in the one per cent public sector pay cap.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3638","3638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749680","2017-07-12","Home Office","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of people classified as low risk on the Sex Offenders Register are recorded in the Disclosure and Barring Service's automatic barring list (a) with and (b) without representations.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3639","3639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749681","2017-07-11","House of Commons Commission","2017-07-07","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what recent discussions the Commission has had with trustees of the Parliamentary Contributory Pension Fund on that fund's investments in carbon-intensive industries and fossil fuels; and whether those discussions included consideration of divestment of such investments.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3671","3671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749682","2017-07-12","Department for International Development","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding was provided to support the peace process in Burma in 2016-17; and which organisations were recipients of that funding.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3631","3631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749683","2017-07-12","Department for International Development","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to address the shortfall in funding for internally displaced people in Shan State and Kachin State in Burma.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3629","3629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749684","2017-07-11","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in UK prisons were convicted of terrorism-related offences; and how many of those prisoners are scheduled for release in the next (a) six months, (b) year, (c) three years and (d) five years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3663","3663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749685","2017-07-11","Prime Minister","2017-07-07","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions she has had with her Russian counterpart on the treatment of political prisoners in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3622","3622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749686","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3627","3627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749687","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much central Government investment has been provided to (a) Coventry and (b) the West Midlands to upgrade the cycling network in those areas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3628","3628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749688","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department has made available for cycling in (a) Sunderland and (b) the North East since 2010.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3634","3634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749689","2017-07-11","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to issue the statutory regulations and guidance to the Bus Services Act 2017.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3651","3651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749690","2017-07-11","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all public-facing transport staff receive disability awareness training.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3652","3652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749691","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his oral contribution of 4 July 2017, Official Report, column 1137, which routes currently operated under the East Midlands franchise are anticipated to benefit from a significantly shorter journey time as a result of the new Thameslink timetable; and what those changes in journey times will be.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3696","3696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749692","2017-07-11","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list the 20 Highways England controlled A-roads which experience the largest increase in traffic during the summer.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3672","3672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749693","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the level of public funding for cycling per head of population in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3687","3687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749694","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page five of High Speed Two Limited's Initial Framework Agreement with the TUC, published on 8 April 2016, if he will list the dates on which the joint committee has met.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3694","3694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749695","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 13 April 2016 to Question 33920, on National Air Traffic Services: Government shareholding, if it remains his policy to sell the Government's shareholding in the National Air Traffic Service.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3695","3695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749696","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 1538, on railways: fares, what plans he has to increase the cost of regulated rail fares by RPI plus zero per cent in 2018.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3692","3692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749697","2017-07-12","Department for Transport","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with representatives of the airline industry and other key stakeholders on the resumption of direct flights to Sharm El-Sheikh; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3693","3693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749698","2017-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of women born in the 1950s who are subject to changes in the state pension age in (a) Oxford West and Abingdon constituency and (b) Oxfordshire.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3670","3670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749699","2017-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time is by region to complete mandatory reconsiderations of employment and support allowance claims.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3675","3675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749700","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the findings of the Trussell Trust report on financial and food insecurity, published in June 2017, on the number of people with health conditions who use food banks.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3661","3661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749701","2017-07-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the findings of the Trussell Trust report on financial and food insecurity, published in June 2017, on the number of employment and support allowance claimants using food banks in the UK.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3662","3662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749702","2017-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent in 2016-17 on processing jobseeker's allowance claims that were subsequently withdrawn following mandatory reconsideration of an employment and support allowance claim.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3677","3677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749703","2017-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to tackle pension scams; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3625","3625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749704","2017-07-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the implications for the motor manufacturing industry of the UK leaving the EU with no deal.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3616","3616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749705","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the implications are for his Department's policies of data published by the Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders on 20 June 2017 on investment in the automotive sector during the first half of 2017.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3608","3608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749706","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what response the Government plans to make to the request by the Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders of 20 June 2017 for an interim agreement for the UK to remain in the customs union as long as necessary to agree a comprehensive trade deal with the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3609","3609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749707","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to support the British automotive industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3635","3635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749708","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the value of the contracts awarded by his Department to McKinsey & Co in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3637","3637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749709","2017-07-11","Department for International Trade","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he last discussed with members of the US Cabinet trade in agricultural goods between the US and the UK.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3646","3646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749710","2017-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is his policy to ban the importation of American beef containing artificial growth hormones after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3647","3647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749711","2017-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he last discussed with his European counterparts imports of American beef containing artificial growth hormones.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3648","3648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749712","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with each of the devolved administrations on the functions of a new Board of Trade.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3612","3612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749713","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations on a new Board of Trade he plans for each nation and region of the UK.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3613","3613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749714","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to consult the devolved administrations on trade deals for (a) fishing, (b) agriculture and (c) transport.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3614","3614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749715","2017-07-12","Department for International Trade","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in Welsh Government on the representation of Wales on the Board of Trade.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3615","3615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749716","2017-07-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the length of discussions on the EU trade deal.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3617","3617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749717","2017-07-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, for what reasons the Government chose its planned cut-off date for EU citizens to retain UK citizenship after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3618","3618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749718","2017-07-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with (a) Oxford University and (b) Oxford Brookes University on the residence status of staff and students from other EU countries at those universities when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3674","3674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749283","2017-07-11","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2017 to Question 861, on regulation, if he will set out the 850 savings referred to by (a) region and (b) sector of those businesses.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3354","3354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749284","2017-07-10","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff have left or agreed settlements to leave his Department under (a) voluntary exit, (b) voluntary redundancy and (c) compulsory redundancy since 1 November 2016; and how much compensation was paid in those cases.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3359","3359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749285","2017-07-10","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his oral contribution of 5 July 2017, Official Report, column 1151, how many of the 2394 alleged cases of electoral fraud since 2010 led to a (a) police investigation, (b) charge, (c) court case and (d)  conviction.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3390","3390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749286","2017-07-10","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3401","3401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749287","2017-07-10","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost to the public purse was for special advisers, including the cost of redundancies, across all Government departments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3464","3464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749288","2017-07-11","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will assess the effect on public procurement of the UK leaving the EU without having agreed a trade deal with the EU.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3495","3495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749289","2017-07-10","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Government will appoint a Minister with sole responsibility for cyber security.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3526","3526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749290","2017-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Government Departments are disability confident.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3588","3588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749291","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will make representations at the United Nations on international cyber attacks by advancing a policy of sanctioning any state actors found to be involved in those attacks.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3528","3528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749292","2017-07-11","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of staff across central government departments have their pay capped at one per cent; and what proportion of such staff that figure represents.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3590","3590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749293","2017-07-11","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times certificates of past performance have been requested by in-scope organisations as set out in the Public Procurement Note published on 25 March 2015; and what proportion of all contracts above the value of 20 million have included a Certificate of Past Performance.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3603","3603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749294","2017-07-11","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the number of single parents who have been affected by the public sector one per cent pay cap.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3594","3594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749295","2017-07-11","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of inflation on public sector workers who have had their pay capped.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3593","3593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749296","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cases have been brought for non-compliance with the national minimum wage in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available in (a) Ellesmere Port and Neston, (b) the North West, (c) England and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3508","3508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749297","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3413","3413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749298","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the rise in the Consumer Price Index on consumer spending habits in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3468","3468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749299","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps are being taken to improve transparency of loans made to Governments outside the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3421","3421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749300","2017-07-11","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many secondments there have been from (a) the Office of Tax Simplification to placements outside of Government and (b) from outside Government to the Office of Tax Simplification since July 2012.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3399","3399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749301","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the US Commerce Secretary; and what was discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3384","3384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749302","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last met the US Treasury Secretary; and what was discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3385","3385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749303","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he will make an assessment of the effect on the insurance sector of the UK leaving the EU without having agreed a trade deal with the EU.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3386","3386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749304","2017-07-11","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether, over the course of Control Period 5, the cost of delivery for UK railways is projected to exceed the original funding assumptions for enhancements.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3310","3310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749305","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to prevent the closure of the last remaining local bank in communities where there is a high population.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3391","3391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749306","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to increase housebuilding.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3393","3393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749307","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many staff have left or agreed settlements to leave his Department under (a) voluntary exit, (b) voluntary redundancy and (c) compulsory redundancy since 1 November 2016; and how much compensation was paid in those cases.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3360","3360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749308","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the availability of domestic violence refuges for women across local authorities.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3426","3426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749309","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of local government on the 100 per cent business rates retention policy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3427","3427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749310","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what reports his Department has received of incidents of cladding coming away from external walls on high-risk buildings.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3422","3422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749311","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the safe installation of cladding or external wall insulation on high-rise buildings.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3423","3423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749312","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations his Department has had from (a) local authorities, (b) local councillors and (c) others on the 100 per cent business rates retention policy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3428","3428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749313","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to bring forward amendments to improve safety standards in planning regulations.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3425","3425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749314","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3402","3402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749315","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions Ministers of his Department have had with representatives from police forces on the effect of business rate changes on local police stations.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3469","3469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749316","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will commission an expert panel to review the leasehold sector.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3470","3470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749317","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions Ministers of his Department have had with their counterparts in the Home Office on the effect of business rate changes on local police stations.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3471","3471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749318","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether  he plans to reform the leasehold sector.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3476","3476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749319","2017-07-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to conduct combustibility tests on exterior cladding other than aluminium composite material cladding.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3489","3489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749320","2017-07-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many members of staff from each contributing Department will form part of the team supporting the public inquiry into the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3490","3490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749321","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many privately-owned residential blocks in (a) the Manchester City Council area, (b) Greater Manchester and (c) the UK have submitted samples of cladding for safety-testing since the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3472","3472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749322","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to restrict housing developers from being able to recommend solicitors to prospective buyers.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3509","3509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749323","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he will bring forward consultation on leasehold reform.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3510","3510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749324","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of regional variations in business rate income across local authorities; and what assessment his Department has made of the effect of those variations on the provision of local public services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3522","3522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749325","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to tackle regional variations in adult social care funding.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3523","3523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749326","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to publish an impact assessment setting out the effect of regional variations in adult social care funding on service provision.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3524","3524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749327","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on unmet social care needs in England.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3525","3525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749328","2017-07-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that leasehold management companies meet their contractual obligations to tenants.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3529","3529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749329","2017-07-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 612, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of fire safety inspections in residential buildings where property ownership is divided among a large number of private sector landlords and owner-occupiers.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3598","3598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749330","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the implications of S4C's report entitled S4C: Pushing the Boundaries, published on 7 April 2017, for the Independent Review of S4C.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3601","3601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749331","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether she will make a decision on referring the 21st Century Fox bid for Sky to the Competition and Markets Authority before the summer recess; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3592","3592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749332","2017-07-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to tackle doping in (a) elite and (b) amateur UK sport.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3459","3459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749333","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the representation of BME people in (a) the Royal Collection and (b) the national collection of art; and what proportion of those portrayed in the visual arts in each of those collections are BME.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3589","3589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749334","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she plans to take to invite trades union representatives to her Department on the Independent Review of S4C.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3488","3488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749335","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the safety of children who play interactional games online with strangers.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3493","3493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749336","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department takes to prevent parents and guardians buying video games for children which are not certified as appropriate for a child's age.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3494","3494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749337","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with Teledwyr Annibynol Cymru on the Independent Review of S4C.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3485","3485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749338","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions her Department has had with the Welsh Government's Culture, Welsh Language and Communications Committee on the Independent Review of S4C.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3486","3486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749339","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish correspondence between her Department and the Wales Office on the Independent Review of S4C.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3487","3487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749340","2017-07-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much her Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3403","3403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749341","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of downloading of additional content of videogames that will potentially change the age classification of the game.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3440","3440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749342","2017-07-10","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to tackle the use of performance-enhancing drugs in (a) elite and (b) amateur UK sport.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3424","3424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749343","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the child protection implications of the Snap Map service available to users of Snapchat; and if she will take steps to ensure that children and vulnerable people who use that service have their location data protected from unofficial third parties.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3356","3356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749344","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make representations to Snap Inc. about the data protection and privacy implications of the Snap Map feature available to users of the Snapchat service.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3357","3357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749345","2017-07-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the potential merits of introducing tax incentives to compensate the tourism industry for any increase in the cost of employing EU citizens after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3398","3398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749346","2017-07-11","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the effect on defence procurement of the UK leaving the EU without having a trade deal with the EU.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3309","3309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749347","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff have left or agreed settlements to leave his Department under (a) voluntary exit, (b) voluntary redundancy and (c) compulsory redundancy since 1 November 2016; and how much compensation was paid in those cases.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3361","3361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749348","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the size of the British Army; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3380","3380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749349","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3404","3404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749350","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel from his Department supported the (a) civilian and (b) military components of Operation Temperer following the activation of that operation on 23 May 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3537","3537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749351","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what financial resources the Government committed to support the (a) civilian and (b) military components of Operation Temperer following the activation of that operation on 23 May 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3538","3538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749352","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many aircraft in the RAF Chinook helicopter fleet are (a) operational and (b) in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3539","3539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749353","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has paid in compensation to complainants affected by low-flying aircraft in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3581","3581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749354","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what command acquisition and support plans for equipment and support requirements are in place between (a) Navy Command, (b) Army Command, (c) Air Command, (d) Joint Forces Commands and Defence Equipment and Support.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3540","3540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749355","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel from his Department who support the (a) civilian and (b) military components of Operation Temperer had leave cancelled during the period of the operation's activation from 23 May 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3582","3582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749356","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many successful prosecutions there have been for unauthorised entries to military bases in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3573","3573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749357","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many unauthorised entries to MOD firing ranges have been recorded in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3574","3574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749358","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many unauthorised entries to military bases have been recorded in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3575","3575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749359","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many successful prosecutions of foreign nationals there have been made for unauthorised entries under the provisions of the Serious Organised Crime and Police Act 2005 to (a) AWE Aldermaston, (b) AWE Burghfield, (c) HMNB Devonport, (d) HMNB Clyde, (e) RNAD Coulport, (f) Northwood Headquarters, (g) RAF Fylingdales, (h) RAF Menwith Hill, (i) RAF Croughton, (j) RAF Lakenheath, (k) RAF Feltwell, (l) RAF Mildenhall, (m) RAF Brize Norton, (n) SMC Marchwood, (o) RAF Fairford and (p) RAF Welford in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3571","3571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749360","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects his Department to complete the order for all 50 AH-64E Apache attack helicopters.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3570","3570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749361","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many unauthorised entries under the provisions of the Serious Organised Crime and Police Act 2005 have been recorded at (a) AWE Aldermaston, (b) AWE Burghfield, (c) HMNB Devonport, (d) HMNB Clyde, (e) RNAD Coulport, (f) Northwood Headquartes, (g) RAF Fylingdales, (h) RAF Menwith Hill, (i) RAF Croughton, (j) RAF Lakenheath, (k) RAF Feltwell, (l) RAF Mildenhall, (m) RAF Brize Norton, (n) SMC Marchwood, (o) RAF Fairford and (p) RAF Weldon in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3572","3572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749362","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on how many schools teach anti-racism education; and what assessment her Department has made of the quality of that education.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3605","3605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749363","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to raise awareness of Inflammatory bowel disease and its effect on students' attainment.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3577","3577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749364","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what systems are in place for schools reporting hate incidents occurring in the classroom.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3599","3599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749365","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2017 to Question 1477, on schools finance, whether she plans to publish that response before the Autumn Budget Statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3442","3442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749366","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3405","3405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749367","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) families and (b) children who will benefit from the new 30 hours free childcare for three and four-year-olds when it becomes available in September 2017; and what estimate she has made of how many of those children will be (i) increasing their use of formal childcare and (ii) starting to use formal childcare.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3429","3429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749368","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many additional childcare places have been created in each quarter since May 2015 to support the roll-out of the 30-hour childcare offer.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3430","3430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749369","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) parents and (b) childcare providers have signed up to the Childcare Choices website in each month since it has been in operation.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3431","3431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749370","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many providers who have signed up to the Childcare Choices website to deliver 30 hours free childcare are (a) PVI providers, (b) maintained nursery schools or nursery classes and (c) childminders.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3432","3432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749371","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of families estimated to be eligible for 30 hours free childcare have signed up for that care via the Childcare Choices website; and what proportion of those families have gone on to register with a childcare provider.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3433","3433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749372","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure all maintained schools receive adequate funding for catering for children with special needs.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3389","3389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749373","2017-07-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the findings of the 2016 Apprenticeship Pay Survey.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3394","3394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749374","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to include creative, artistic and technical subjects in the English Baccalaureate.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3358","3358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749375","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on changing the schools admissions code to give summer-born and premature children the right to start reception at compulsory school age.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3392","3392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749376","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the implications for her Department's policies are of the findings from the Institute for Fiscal Studies of 4 July 2017 on the comparative effect of the removal of the maintenance grant on levels of debt from students from poorer and richer families.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3397","3397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749377","2017-07-11","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on future use by her Department of funds allocated for apprenticeships before the introduction of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3395","3395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749378","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to introduce legislative proposals on grammar schools.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3327","3327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749379","2017-07-12","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect on the educational outcomes of children of an entrance exam to some state schools at the age of 10 or 11.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3328","3328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749380","2017-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that current food standards are maintained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3329","3329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749381","2017-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assistance he is receiving from the Chancellor of the Exchequer to ensure that his Department is fully funded to undertake its review of EU legislation on food and agriculture.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3332","3332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749382","2017-07-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3406","3406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749383","2017-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of staff of his Department and each of his Department's agencies are covered by the remit of a pay review body.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3604","3604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749384","2017-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of staff within each sponsored non-departmental public body of his Department fall within the remit of a pay review body.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3602","3602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749385","2017-07-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of staff of his Department are covered by the remit of a pay review body.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3600","3600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749386","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3408","3408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749387","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the levels of media freedom and plurality in Turkey.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3474","3474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749388","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has plans to make representations to his counterpart in Turkey on the arrest of Idil Eser, director of Amnesty International, Turkey.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3477","3477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749389","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received from the European Space Agency on the suspension of Voyager flights to and from Ascension Island and the re-routing of the South Atlantic airbridge.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3478","3478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749390","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2017 to Question 2035, what recent representations he has made to his US counterpart on bringing forward the refurbishment of Wideawake airfield on Ascension Island.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3484","3484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749391","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has spoken to his US counterpart on the recent missile test in North Korea.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3445","3445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749392","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his North Korean counterpart.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3447","3447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749393","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions (a) he and (b) the UK ambassador to the People's Republic of China have had with their Chinese counterparts on the status of the Sino-British Joint Declaration.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3455","3455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749394","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has spoken to Carrie Lam, the Chief Executive of Hong Kong, since 1 July 2017.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3450","3450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749395","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 4 April 2017 to Question 69434, what response he has received from the Government of Saudi Arabia to his enquiry about the attack by a helicopter on a boat carrying Somali civilians off the coast of Yemen on 16 March 2017; whether he has yet been able to establish whether the helicopter that fired on that boat was made in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3308","3308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749396","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assurances he has given to his counterparts in the Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies that the Government will replace funding provided by the EU when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3301","3301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749397","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which of the UK's Overseas Territories have a fully-functional register of beneficial ownership; and which of those territories does not have such a fully-functional register.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3350","3350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749398","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last discussed alleged human rights abuses in Iran with his Iranian counterpart.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3396","3396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749399","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 July 2017 to Question 2349, whether he or the Minister for Asia plan to seek a meeting with Lord Patten of Barnes to discuss (a) human rights and the state of democracy in Hong Kong and (b) the Joint British-Sino Declaration.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3347","3347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749400","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on recent statements made by the People's Republic of China that the Sino-British Joint Declaration no longer has any significance and is not binding on the People's Republic of China.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3348","3348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749401","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff have left or agreed settlements to leave his Department under (a) voluntary exit, (b) voluntary redundancy and (c) compulsory redundancy since 1 November 2016; and how much compensation was paid in those cases.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3363","3363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749402","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in Bosnia-Herzegovina.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3583","3583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749403","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many inflammatory bowel disease specialist nurses have been employed by the NHS in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3569","3569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749404","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on eliminating out-of-area placements for mental health patients.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3544","3544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749405","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the proportion of children under the age of two who have visited an NHS dentist in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3545","3545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749406","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment he has made of the number of BAME organ donors and longer transplant waiting times for patients from those backgrounds.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3546","3546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749407","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to ensure safe staffing levels are maintained in the NHS.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3547","3547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749408","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff have left or agreed settlements to leave his Department under (a) voluntary exit, (b) voluntary redundancy and (c) compulsory redundancy since 1 November 2016; and how much compensation was paid in those cases.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3364","3364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749409","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the budget of the East of England Ambulance Service has been increased to account for the additional workload of the Essex Success Regime hospital reconfiguration proposals.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3355","3355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749410","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the provision of specialised nursing care for people with secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3383","3383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749411","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to review the medical exemption criteria for prescription charges.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3382","3382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749412","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions and meetings the management of West Hertfordshire NHS Hospitals Trust has had with (a) Crown Estates and (b) Hertfordshire County Council on available green field sites for a new acute hospital for West Hertfordshire.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3434","3434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749413","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress is being made on the investigation into maternity services at the Countess of Chester hospital.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3375","3375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749414","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are the for the time taken to publish Health Education England's mental health workforce strategy; and if he will set a date for its publication.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3441","3441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749415","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Cancer Transformation Funding that was made available to Cancer Alliances following an announcement by NHS England in December 2016 in supporting the roll-out of the Recovery Package, stratified pathways and early diagnosis measures across England.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3315","3315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749416","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the proposals made in each Sustainability and Transformation Plan regarding end of life care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3317","3317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749417","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress is being made on implementing Recommendation 65 of the Cancer Strategy for England; and whether every person with cancer will have access to the elements of the Recovery Package by 2020.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3312","3312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749418","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of whether people from lower socio-economic groups are less likely to receive the end of life care which they choose.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3318","3318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749419","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department and NHS England will publish a progress report on each recommendation made in the Cancer Strategy for England.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3313","3313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749420","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people had access to advance care planning in advance of their death in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3319","3319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749421","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to publish a carers strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3320","3320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749422","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when Cancer Transformation Funding will be available to support the Recovery Package and stratified pathways in England.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3314","3314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749423","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were detained under section (a) 135 and (b) 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3341","3341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749424","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health nurses are in post in (a) Liverpool, (b) England and (c) each region of England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3343","3343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749425","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the recommendations in the Government Response to the Review of Choice in End of Life Care will be implemented by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3316","3316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749426","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Cancer Strategy for England will be fully implemented by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3311","3311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749427","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the level of prescription of psychiatric drugs to children and young people in each year from 2000 to 2016.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3457","3457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749428","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will respond to the recommendations made by the UN Committee on the Rights of the Child in its Concluding Observations on the fifth periodic report of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland on the treatment of attention deficit and hyperactivity disorder and related disorders in children and young people.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3443","3443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749429","2017-07-13","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2017 to Question 1450, on organ donors, if he will review that strategy to ensure it meets the target to achieve a consent rate of over 80 per cent by 2020.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3535","3535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749430","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of health capability assessments for claimants of employment and support allowance with (a) mental health issues and (b) learning difficulties.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3462","3462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749431","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide a breakdown of how the Pharmacy Integration Fund has been spent to date.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3483","3483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749432","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3409","3409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749433","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will instigate a national review of referral-to-treatment data.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3511","3511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749434","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have died while on a waiting list for (a) heart surgery and (b) neurosurgery in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3503","3503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749435","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the provision of specialist nurses for inflammatory bowel disease.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3520","3520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749436","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many inflammatory bowel disease specialist nurses have been employed by the NHS in Leeds in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3521","3521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749437","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to HCWS232, published on 1 November 2016, when she expects to publish the joint Home Office and Department for Education Unaccompanied Children Safeguarding Strategy.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3502","3502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749438","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3410","3410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749439","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to commence sections 80 to 83 of the Policing and Crime Act 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3536","3536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749440","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to HCWS232, published on 1 November 2016, if she will place in the Library copies of the quarterly updates the Government provides to the Children's Commissioners for England, Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland on the safeguarding of unaccompanied children.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3501","3501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749441","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to incorporate the National Crime Agency and the Serious Fraud Office.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3306","3306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749442","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to merge the Civil Nuclear Constabulary, the Ministry of Defence Police and the British Transport Police.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3307","3307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749443","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to publish (a) Bishop James Jones' report into the experiences of the Hillsborough families and (b) the Government's response to that report.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3334","3334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749444","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether  she plans to continue with the reform of the police allocation formula announced in July 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3346","3346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749445","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish the review of the police core grant distribution formula.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3351","3351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749446","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-EU international students left the UK three months after completing their course in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3340","3340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749447","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has prepared its response to Bishop James Jones' report into the experiences of the Hillsborough families.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3333","3333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749448","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date she received Bishop James Jones' report on the experience of the Hillsborough families.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3352","3352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749449","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish her response to the letter of 20 June 2017 she received from the Metropolitan Police Commissioner on police resources; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3321","3321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749450","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department has had with the British Bankers' Association on the process of opening a bank account for refugees who have been granted asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3377","3377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749451","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied children have been transferred under section 69 of the Immigration Act 2016 in the last six months.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3378","3378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749452","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on allowing unaccompanied refugee children to sponsor their parents for the purpose of family reunion.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3543","3543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749453","2017-07-10","House of Commons Commission","2017-07-06","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate it has made of the cost of a change in the timetable for a decision on the proposed restoration and renewal programme for the Palace of Westminster.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3465","3465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749454","2017-07-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Palestinian Authority on the naming of a square in Jenin after Karim Younes and a square in Tulkarem after Maher Younes.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3584","3584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749455","2017-07-11","Department for International Development","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support creative industries across Africa.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3591","3591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749456","2017-07-10","Department for International Development","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the level for humanitarian support from the international community required for the people of Mosul following that city's recapture from Da'esh.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3376","3376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749457","2017-07-10","Department for International Development","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to help other government departments that spend aid achieve Good or Very Good ratings under the International Aid Transparency Initiative.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3387","3387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749458","2017-07-10","Department for International Development","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff have left or agreed settlements to leave her Department under (a) voluntary exit, (b) voluntary redundancy and (c) compulsory redundancy since 1 November 2016; and how much compensation was paid in those cases.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3365","3365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749459","2017-07-10","Department for International Development","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment on the effect on the Fairtrade scheme of the decision of Sainsbury's and other retailers to withdraw from that scheme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3300","3300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749460","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he last met Mr Justice McCloskey to discuss delays in immigration tribunals.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3322","3322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749461","2017-07-11","Cabinet Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which of the UK's Crown Dependencies have a fully functional register of beneficial ownership; and which of those dependencies does not have such a fully-functional register.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3349","3349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749462","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners waited more than 14 days for a transfer to hospital under the Mental Health Act 1983 in 2016-17.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3342","3342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749463","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff have left or agreed settlements to leave his Department under (a) voluntary exit, (b) voluntary redundancy and (c) compulsory redundancy since 1 November 2016; and how much compensation was paid in those cases.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3367","3367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749464","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reoffending rates for (a) short-term and (b) long-term prisoners were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3371","3371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749465","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders charged with possession of an offensive weapon received non-custodial sentences in each of the last three years; and what proportion of those offenders were juveniles.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3373","3373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749466","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to increase the availability of legal aid in England and Wales.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3580","3580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749467","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders charged for the possession of an offensive weapon received non-custodial sentences in each of the last three years; and what proportion of those offenders were juvenile.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3458","3458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749468","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the re-offending rates for (a) short-term and (b) long-term prisoners were in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3460","3460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749469","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which organisations have been given clearance to run educational activities on hate crime, racism or discrimination as part of prisoner rehabilitation work.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3463","3463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749470","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3411","3411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749471","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what programmes his Department sponsors across the prison system to educate prisoners against (a) racism, (b) anti-Semitism, (c) Islamophobia and (d) homophobia.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3452","3452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749472","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the savings to the public purse of out-sourcing electronic tagging for ex-offenders.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3567","3567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749473","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many electronic tags used by the Electronic Monitoring Service to monitor ex-offenders have been reported (a) faulty and (b) lost.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3566","3566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749474","2017-07-11","Leader of the House","2017-07-06","To ask the Leader of the House, when and in which House the Government plans to introduce the Courts Bill.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3491","3491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749475","2017-07-11","Leader of the House","2017-07-06","To ask the Leader of the House, when and in which House the Government plans to introduce the Patient Safety Bill.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3492","3492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749476","2017-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3412","3412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749477","2017-07-10","Prime Minister","2017-07-06","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions she has had with President Erdogan of Turkey on (a) human rights and (b) press freedom in that country.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3473","3473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749478","2017-07-10","Prime Minister","2017-07-06","To ask the Prime Minister, how many parliamentary private secretaries have undertaken travel (a) within the UK and (b) overseas with or on behalf of ministers since she became Prime Minister.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3466","3466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749479","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will discuss with Airbnb the security implications of the requirement by some hosts for guests to send the photograph page of their passport to secure a booking.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3467","3467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749480","2017-07-10","Prime Minister","2017-07-06","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions she has had with President Vladimir Putin of Russia on political prisoners in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3456","3456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749481","2017-07-11","Prime Minister","2017-07-06","To ask the Prime Minister, on what date she received Bishop James Jones' report on the experience of the Hillsborough families.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3353","3353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749482","2017-07-11","Department of Health","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on implementing the recommendations in the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3344","3344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749483","2017-07-11","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people took their own life on the rail network in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3345","3345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749484","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff have left or agreed settlements to leave his Department under (a) voluntary exit, (b) voluntary redundancy and (c) compulsory redundancy since 1 November 2016; and how much compensation was paid in those cases.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3368","3368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749485","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the trend in the number of specialist road traffic officers since 2015; and what steps his Department is taking to maintain the number of specialist road traffic officers.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3381","3381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749486","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many motorists have been penalised for using a handheld mobile telephone while driving since 1 March 2017.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3436","3436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749487","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many responses were received in the HS2 Crewe to Manchester, West Midlands to Leeds: Route Refinement Consultation 2016; and how many of those responses were (a) in support of and (b) against the new M18 route.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3500","3500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749488","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated annual income from Mersey Gateway tolls is.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3506","3506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749489","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated annual cost to the taxpayer is of reducing the Severn Bridge Toll to 3.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3505","3505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749490","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what road and rail infrastructure projects outlined in the Transport Investment Strategy published on 5 July 2017 are considered (a) England only, (b) England and Wales, (c) England, Wales and Scotland and (d) UK-wide.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3499","3499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749491","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the annual cost to the taxpayer would be of scrapping Mersey Tunnel tolls.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3507","3507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749492","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether vehicle excise duty raised from cars registered in Wales will be included in the National Road Fund.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3541","3541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749493","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria the Government uses to assess whether a transport infrastructure development is considered (a) England only, (b) England and Wales, (c) England, Wales and Scotland and (d) UK-wide.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3530","3530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749494","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the Government expects to devolve legislative powers to the Welsh Assembly to procure and manage the Wales and Borders rail franchise.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3534","3534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749495","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the automotive manufacturing industry.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3515","3515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749496","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of rail infrastructure funding identified in the Transport Investment Strategy will be spent on the Welsh rail network.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3531","3531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749497","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what mechanisms will be put in place to ensure effective consultation with the devolved administrations on proposals made in the Transport Investment Strategy.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3532","3532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749498","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations the Government has received from the Welsh Assembly on the Transport Investment Strategy.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3533","3533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749499","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the Barnett consequential the Welsh Assembly will receive with the implementation of the National Road Fund.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3542","3542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749500","2017-07-10","Wales Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3414","3414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749501","2017-07-10","Wales Office","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the timetable is for the completion of the electrification of the Cardiff to Swansea railway line.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3379","3379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749502","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what guidance the Government provides to employers on the provision of flexible hours for mothers returning to work.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3419","3419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749503","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with business organisations on the implications of maternity leave and requests for flexible working for the gender pay gap.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3420","3420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749504","2017-07-10","Women and Equalities","2017-07-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will take steps to amend same-sex marriage legislation to allow couples to convert civil partnerships to marriage.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3446","3446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749505","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he will take to eliminate inequalities in pension rights.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3448","3448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749506","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have (a) applied for and (b) received employment and support allowance for inflammatory bowel disease in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3518","3518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749507","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on advertising on social media in each month since January 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3415","3415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749508","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants with motor neurone disease are in (a) the work related activity group and (b) support group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3475","3475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749509","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure employment and support allowance and personal independence payment assessments take greater account of the complexities of inflammatory bowel disease.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3578","3578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749510","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have (a) applied for and (b) received personal independence payments support from his Department related to inflammatory bowel disease.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3579","3579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749511","2017-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date he plans to publish the list of long-term and life-limiting diseases that will be exempt from benefit re-assessments.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3587","3587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749512","2017-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is his policy to halve the disability employment gap by 2030.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3585","3585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749513","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will extend assessment rate payments to claimants of employment and support allowance who are waiting for the outcome of a mandatory reconsideration.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3527","3527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749514","2017-07-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date he plans to publish the White Paper on Work, Health and Disability.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3586","3586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749515","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of inflammatory bowel disease and its effects with employers.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3519","3519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749516","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of compulsory workplace pensions on the level of private sector job creation since 2012.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3461","3461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749517","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employees of his Department have been referred for disciplinary action as a result of factual inaccuracies in employment and support allowance and personal independence payment assessments in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3374","3374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749518","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff have left or agreed settlements to leave his Department under (a) voluntary exit, (b) voluntary redundancy and (c) compulsory redundancy since 1 November 2016; and how much compensation was paid in those cases.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3369","3369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749519","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of health capability assessments for claimants of employment and support allowance with (a) mental health issues and (b) learning difficulties.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3372","3372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749520","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of compulsory workplace pensions on the level of private sector job creation since the introduction of those pensions in 2012.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3370","3370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749521","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many women born in the 1950s and affected by the change in the state pension age have (a) taken up and (b) completed apprenticeships.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3303","3303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749522","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many women born in the 1950s and affected by the change in the state pension age have successfully taken part in the returner's scheme to return to the workplace.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3304","3304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749523","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women born in the 1950s and affected by the change in the state pension age have been able to return to employment from a position of unemployment.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3305","3305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749524","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women born in the 1950s and affected by the change in the state pension age have not been able to return to employment.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3302","3302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749525","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the performance of PIP assessors is monitored.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3568","3568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749526","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to share copies of assessors' reports with individual claimants before decisions on personal independence payment claims are made.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3565","3565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749527","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) undergraduate and (b) postgraduate students studying in the UK are of Cuban nationality.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3548","3548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749528","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision by the Higher Education Funding Council for England not to fund the Advanced Structured Testing Centre at Sheffield University on the UK steel industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3549","3549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749529","2017-07-12","HM Treasury","2017-07-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of reductions in household spending power on the economic sustainability of businesses of all sizes in (a) the retail sector and (b) the service sector.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3325","3325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749530","2017-07-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of energy prices on the viability of small and medium-sized businesses.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3324","3324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749531","2017-07-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the potential reduction in the domestic energy market consumer detriment to be achieved by implementing an extension of the pre-payment meter safeguard tariff to those eligible for Warm Home Discount who have a credit meter.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3335","3335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749532","2017-07-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department defines a vulnerable customer in the domestic energy market.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3336","3336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749533","2017-07-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has had from Ofgem on the timescale for the (a) publication of measures to protect vulnerable consumers with an extension of the pre-payment meter safeguard tariff and (b) implementation of such measures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 3337","3337"
