"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433951","2015-12-08","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academies in each local authority area were in deficit in each year since 2009-10; and what the total deficit was in academies in each such area in each of those years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18679","18679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433952","2015-12-08","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many academies were in deficit in each year since 2009-10; and what the total deficit was in academies in each such year.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18680","18680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433953","2015-12-08","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new entrants there were in undergraduate programmes by subject for Initial Teacher Training for 2015-16.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18682","18682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433954","2015-12-08","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) overall target and (b) target for each subject for new entrants to Initial Teacher Training for 2015-16 is, when the same Teacher Supply Model methodology that was applied in 2014-15 is used.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18683","18683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433955","2015-12-08","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who the Regional School Commissioners are; how many schools are located in each of the regions for which they are responsible; and how many schools in their area each commissioner has not visited since taking up that role.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18684","18684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433956","2015-12-08","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons targets and breakdown of recruitment by subject for undergraduate trainees were not included in the Initial Teacher Training census 2015-16.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18685","18685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433957","2015-12-08","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her most recent estimate is of the average annual cost to a (a) school and (b) local authority of employing a (i) teacher and (ii) classroom assistant; and what forecast she has made of the likely equivalent cost in each year from 2015-16 to 2019-20.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18686","18686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433958","2015-12-09","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has issued to schools on meetings for prayer or religious instruction for pupils during break times.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18688","18688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433959","2015-12-08","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in rural areas rated by Ofsted as inadequate became academies in 2014-15.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18643","18643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433960","2015-12-07","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to increase the role of children's centres in supporting expectant parents and improving integrated working among antenatal support services.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18617","18617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433961","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's timetable is for the implementation of the provision of postgraduate student loans of up to £10,000.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18610","18610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433962","2015-12-08","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of classroom teachers earning £65,000 or more per year are women.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18763","18763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433963","2015-12-07","Department for Education","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014 to Question 17343, what free schools her Department funded for 2014-15; how many children were enrolled at each such school in the autumn term 2014; and for how many children each such school received funding for the academic year 2014-15.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18764","18764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433964","2015-12-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what bids her Department received for the carbon capture and storage technology completion which the Government is no longer funding.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18629","18629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433965","2015-12-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much EU funding was allocated to the operation of carbon capture and storage projects which is not now available for spending on UK projects.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18630","18630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433966","2015-12-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she made of the value for money of carbon capture and storage before the Government's carbon capture and storage competition was suspended; and how much from the public purse had been spent on that competition at the time of suspension.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18631","18631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433967","2015-12-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department made of the value for money of the carbon capture and storage project bids.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18632","18632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433968","2015-12-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she had with bidders for the carbon capture and storage competition prior to the decision to withdraw funding earmarked for that competition.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18633","18633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433969","2015-12-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the Government's future plans are for carbon capture and storage.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18634","18634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433970","2015-12-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on (a) the supply chain and (b) existing infrastructure of the Government's decision to cancel the carbon capture and storage competition.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18635","18635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433971","2015-12-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she plans to publish her Department's response to the consultation on a review of the feed-in tariff scheme.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18672","18672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433972","2015-12-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she plans to publish details of how her Department plans to reform the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme to make the savings announced in the Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18670","18670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433973","2015-12-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether it is her policy that anaerobic digestion will continue to be supported under the reformed Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18671","18671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433974","2015-12-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the outcome of his call for evidence on extending permitted development rights to taller mobile telephone masts.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18661","18661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433975","2015-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with veterinary experts on the use of colistin and colistin resistance in animals, food and humans.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18673","18673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433976","2015-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps she has taken to improve the administration of the Rural Payments Agency.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18711","18711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433977","2015-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many single farm payments were issued by the Rural Payments Agency on 1 December 2015; and how many of those payments were calculated incorrectly.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18712","18712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433978","2015-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding her Department has allocated to the National Wildlife Crime Unit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18733","18733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433979","2015-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many semen collection licences her Department has issued in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18717","18717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433980","2015-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much revenue accrues to the public purse for payments received for semen collection licences.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18713","18713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433981","2015-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has formed a view on the legality of the maritime claims made by the People's Republic of China in the South China Sea as set out in the nine-dotted line map annexed to the Notes Verbales communicated to the UN Secretary-General in May 2009.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18709","18709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433982","2015-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Greek and Turkish governments on the unification of Cyprus.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18716","18716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433983","2015-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Romania on improving media freedom and media pluralism in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18599","18599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433984","2015-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of trends in media ownership in Romania.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18600","18600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433985","2015-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Romania on (a) Central Media Enterprise, (b) Adrian Sârbu and (c) Ronald Lauder.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18601","18601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433986","2015-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK is entitled to be represented before the Permanent Court of Arbitration in Philippines v. China.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18690","18690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433987","2015-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK plans to be represented before the Permanent Court of Arbitration in Philippines v. China.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18652","18652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433988","2015-12-08","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral statement of 30 November 2015, Official Report, column 33, what estimate he has made of the number of operations that were cancelled prior to the proposed industrial action on 1 December 2015 but could not be rebooked for 1 December 2015 once that proposed industrial action was postponed.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18662","18662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433989","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise public awareness of multiple myeloma and the risks presented by late diagnosis of acute myeloid leukaemia.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18669","18669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433990","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with health experts on the human health implications of the veterinary use of colistin for colistin resistance in slaughtered animals, food and humans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18674","18674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433991","2015-12-08","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will raise the issue of withdrawal of marketing authorisations for veterinary use of colistin at the next EU Employment, Social Policy, Health and Consumer Affairs Council on 7 December 2015.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18675","18675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433992","2015-12-08","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements his Department plans to put in place for new patients who wish to access drugs included in the Risk Sharing Scheme for the supply of disease modifying treatments for multiple sclerosis, glatiramer acetate and beta interferon after funding for that scheme ceases.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18681","18681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433993","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 12818, on health services: weather, what data will be (a) collected and (b) published by NHS England.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18645","18645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433994","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 12819, if he will provide an update on plans to introduce independent medical examiners to the death certification process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18646","18646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433995","2015-12-08","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether a person applying for NHS Continuing Healthcare support who is judged to be terminally ill and thus entitled to a 48-hour needs assessment by their clinical commissioning group (CCG) is able to claim the costs of any treatment over the 48-hour limit if the CCG does not make an assessment in time.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18658","18658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433996","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his oral contribution of 30 November 2015, Official Report, column 33, on NHS England collating feedback from all trusts on the effect of proposed industrial action, if he will place a copy of that feedback in the Library.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18710","18710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433997","2015-12-08","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the year 10 data for the Risk Sharing Scheme for the supply of disease modifying treatments for multiple sclerosis.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18677","18677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433998","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether an assessment has been made of the barriers preventing multiple myeloma patients accessing the most innovative treatments.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18708","18708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433999","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on the link between the speed of a person's walk and dementia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18603","18603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434000","2015-12-08","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether hospitals will incur financial penalties if they breach performance standards as a result of the suspended industrial action on 1 December 2015.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18627","18627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434001","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment (a) his Department and (b) NHS England have made of the levels of preparedness among clinical commissioning groups (CCG's) for the planned transfer of obesity surgery commissioning responsibilities to CCGs in April 2016.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18621","18621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434002","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his policy that clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) will be required to meet current national service standards for the provision of obesity surgery after the planned transfer of obesity surgery commissioning responsibilities from NHS England to CCGs in April 2016.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18622","18622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434003","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Government's response of February 2015 to the consultation entitled Arrangements for the Transfer of Commissioning Responsibilities for Renal Dialysis and Morbid Obesity Surgery Services from NHS England to Clinical Commissioning Groups, what information has been provided to clinical commissioning groups in anticipation of the transfer of responsibilities for obesity surgery in April 2016.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18623","18623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434004","2015-12-08","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to guarantee that all patients who had their operations cancelled as a result of the proposed industrial action by junior doctors will be offered another date for their operation within the next 28 days.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18641","18641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434005","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many student midwives there were in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18698","18698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434006","2015-12-08","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his oral contribution of 30 November 2015, Official Report, column 33, on the estimated number of patients who may have had a vital operation cancelled, how many patients who had such an operation cancelled had it rescheduled to a time within 24 hours of the original scheduled operation.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18754","18754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434007","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the treatment of patients with multiple myeloma is not affected by the (a) delisting of treatments from the Cancer Drugs Fund and (b) ongoing consultation on that Fund's future.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18734","18734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434008","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure the outcome of the consultation on the future of the Cancer Drugs Fund is co-ordinated with and complements the recommendations of the Accelerated Access Review to ensure improved patient access to innovative treatments.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18766","18766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434009","2015-12-08","Home Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the cost of Disclosure and Barring Service checks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18750","18750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434010","2015-12-08","Home Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the forms on her Department's website is available in Welsh.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18759","18759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434011","2015-12-08","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fatalities were caused by traffic collisions involving persons under the influence of (a) cannabis and (b) illegal drugs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18752","18752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434012","2015-12-08","Home Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the drugs advice provided by FRANK in tackling use of illegal drugs.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18753","18753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434013","2015-12-08","Home Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time was for a Disclosure and Barring Service check at (a) standard, (b) enhanced and (c) enhanced with list checks level to be conducted in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18748","18748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434014","2015-12-09","Home Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) boys and (b) girls aged (i) 11, (ii) 12, (iii) 13, (iv) 14, (v) 15, (vi) 16 and (vii) 17 were held overnight in police cells in each police station in Lancashire in each month between 1 January 2014 and 30 November 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18687","18687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434015","2015-12-07","Home Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the National Maritime Information Centre holds live records on the range of merchant shipping that is UK-owned.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18700","18700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434016","2015-12-08","Home Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to lay before Parliament a report on the steps the Government proposes to take in relation to independent child trafficking advocates, pursuant to section 48(7) of the Modern Slavery Act 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18663","18663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434017","2015-12-08","Home Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will issue a response to Early Day Motion 676, British Women and the New British Passport.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18676","18676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434018","2015-12-07","Department for International Development","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech at the UN Sustainable Development Goals Summit on 27 September  2015, what steps the Government is taking to leave no one behind.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18639","18639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434019","2015-12-07","Department for International Development","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential role for the private sector in increasing birth registration in fagile contexts.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18640","18640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434020","2015-12-07","Department for International Development","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to take account of the conclusions of the United Nations/World Health Organisation Second Global High-Level Conference on Road Safety when preparing the UK's response to the next set of Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18620","18620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434021","2015-12-07","Home Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what work her Department is undertaking with agencies outside the UN High Commissioner for Refugees system in order to assist and resettle the most vulnerable refugees.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18696","18696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434022","2015-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the forms on his Department's website is available in Welsh.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18760","18760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434023","2015-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the (a) average cost of building new prisons planned by the Government and (b) length of time it will take from conception to completion to build such a prison.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18626","18626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434024","2015-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the proposed closure of Bow County Court on access to justice for the residents of Poplar and Limehouse constituency.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18618","18618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434025","2015-12-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been made redundant by HM Courts and Tribunals Service since 31 May 2014; and what the cost to the public purse of such redundancies has been.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18689","18689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434026","2015-12-07","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department has taken to promote use of the UK Guarantees Scheme in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18724","18724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434027","2015-12-07","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the legal recognition in Northern Ireland of same-sex marriages which have been registered elsewhere in the UK.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18723","18723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434028","2015-12-07","Prime Minister","2015-12-03","To ask the Prime Minister, if the Government will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure any future decisions to deploy the armed forces requires a full debate and vote within the House.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18649","18649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434029","2015-12-07","Scotland Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps his Department has taken to promote use of the UK Guarantees Scheme in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18726","18726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434030","2015-12-07","Scotland Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2015 to Question 7426, how many events have been hosted by non-government bodies at Dover House since 21 July 2015.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18613","18613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434031","2015-12-07","Scotland Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the introduction of the Work and Health Programme in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18729","18729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434032","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the Scottish economy of devolution of corporation tax to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18730","18730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434033","2015-12-07","Scotland Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he last met with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions to discuss the rollout of universal credit across Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18728","18728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434034","2015-12-07","Scotland Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he next plans to publish a Single Departmental Plan for his Department.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18727","18727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434035","2015-12-07","Scotland Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, on what dates since 19 October 2015 Scotland Office Ministers and officials and their counterparts at UK Trade and Investment have met to discuss the Scottish steel industry; what issues affecting that industry were discussed on each occasion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18731","18731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434036","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains were cancelled on the Govia Thameslink rail line due to adverse weather conditions in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18739","18739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434037","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions Ministers have had with Govia Thameslink on improving the punctuality and reliability of that company's train service in the last six months.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18735","18735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434038","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains were cancelled on the Govia Thameslink rail line due to driver shortage in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18736","18736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434039","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains were cancelled on the Govia Thameslink rail line due to driver shortage in the most recent four time periods for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18737","18737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434040","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains were cancelled on the Govia Thameslink rail line due to driver illness in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18738","18738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434041","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to assess (a) air quality and (b) the likely effect a third runway would have on air quality around Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18715","18715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434042","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what each of the flag registers of vessels owned by company groups that qualified for inclusion in the tonnage scheme in 2014-15 was; and how many vessels in that scheme were registered under each of those flags.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18699","18699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434043","2015-12-08","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of Vauxhall Zafiras which have caught fire in the last six months; and what discussions his Department has had with Vauxhall on the number of other such cars catching fire in a similar way.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18767","18767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434044","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2015 to Question 16383, what assessment his Department has made of the levels of traffic flow and congestion within Horwich arising from the decision not to construct Junction 7 on the M61.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18604","18604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434045","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to increase UK Ship Register fees in the next financial year.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18619","18619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434046","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will introduce financial incentives for bus and coach companies to bring forward capital investment in Passenger Service Vehicles Accessibility Regulations-compliant vehicles ahead of the deadline for compliance of January 2017.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18615","18615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434047","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will implement a nationwide campaign asking people to make space for wheelchairs in wheelchair areas of buses.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18616","18616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434048","2015-12-08","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the Maritime and Coastguard Agency has been unable to provide MyCSP with accurate pension data for its staff on which pension benefit statements can be based; and by what date he expects that matter to be resolved.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18628","18628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434049","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for competition in the bus market of (a) voluntary partnership agreements and (b) statutory quality partnerships; and what account he plans to take of those implications in framing legislation on bus franchising.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18637","18637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434050","2015-12-08","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what total length of new (a) road and (b) rail was laid in rural areas between 2010 and 2015; what the cost to the public purse was of such new road and rail; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18644","18644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434051","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether special purpose vehicles are currently used to deliver any government-supported passenger rail or infrastructure operations.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18691","18691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434052","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains were cancelled on the Govia Thameslink rail line due to there being no trains available to operate services in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18740","18740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434053","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of UK seafarer (a) ratings and (b) officers were employed on category one Red Ensign Group registered vessels that qualified for the tonnage tax scheme in each year since 2000-01.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18703","18703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434054","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of UK seafarer (a) ratings and (b) officers were employed on UK registered vessels that qualified for the tonnage tax scheme in each year since 2000-01.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18704","18704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434055","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains were cancelled on the Govia Thameslink rail line due to problems with the line infrastructure in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18741","18741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434056","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of vessels that qualified for the tonnage tax scheme were registered under each flag in category one of the Red Ensign Group in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18701","18701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434057","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve reliability and punctuality of the Govia Thameslink rail line.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18742","18742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434058","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to require improvement of the punctuality and reliability of Govia Thameslink train services.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18743","18743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434059","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of UK seafarer (a) ratings and (b) officers were employed on non-UK registered vessels that qualified for the tonnage tax scheme in each year since 2000-01.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18702","18702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434060","2015-12-07","Wales Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many journeys he and his Ministers have undertaken in his Department's ministerial car in the 2015-16 session of Parliament to date.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18720","18720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434061","2015-12-07","Wales Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what official visits each of the Ministers in his Department have made since July 2014; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18721","18721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434062","2015-12-07","Wales Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps his Department has taken to promote use of the UK Guarantees Scheme in Wales.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18725","18725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434063","2015-12-07","Wales Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether he plans to amend the draft Wales Bill to enable the National Assembly for Wales to vary income tax without a referendum.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18647","18647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434064","2015-12-07","Wales Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many meetings he has held with the Chancellor of the Exchequer in the 2015-16 session of Parliament to date.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18719","18719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434065","2015-12-08","Wales Office","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many times he has visited each parliamentary constituency in Wales in an official capacity in the 2015-16 session of Parliament.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18755","18755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434066","2015-12-07","Women and Equalities","2015-12-03","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the implications for equal rights of the legal recognition in Northern Ireland of same-sex marriages registered in England, Wales or Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18732","18732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434067","2015-12-08","Women and Equalities","2015-12-03","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what her policy is on extending the time in which women may take a pregnancy and maternity discrimination case against their employers to a tribunal from three to 12 months.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18660","18660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434068","2015-12-07","Women and Equalities","2015-12-03","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with her Cabinet colleagues on the legal recognition in Northern Ireland of same-sex marriages which have been registered elsewhere in the UK.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18722","18722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434069","2015-12-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Atos assessments are carried out effectively for personal independence payment applications.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18714","18714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434070","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to ensure that 15 per cent of the three million apprenticeships his Department plans to deliver over the next five years are taken up by disabled people.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18651","18651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434071","2015-12-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2015 to Question 17942, where a claimant's income is insufficient to meet their living costs, how early an advance payment of up to 50 per cent of their universal credit award can be made once an assessment has been made.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18747","18747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433716","2015-12-04","Attorney General","2015-12-02","To ask the Attorney General, what factors the Crown Prosecution Service takes into account when assessing the reliability of evidence which is more than 30 years old.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18455","18455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433717","2015-12-07","Attorney General","2015-12-02","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2015 to Question 16871, what the budget allocated to the Specialist Fraud Division was in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18484","18484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433718","2015-12-07","Attorney General","2015-12-02","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2015 to Question 16871, how many full-time equivalent staff worked in the Specialist Fraud Division in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18485","18485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433719","2015-12-04","Attorney General","2015-12-02","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions a special adviser in the Law Officers' Departments accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18494","18494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433720","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2015 to Question 17311, what financial support his Department is providing for the Government's Productivity Plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18528","18528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433721","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to encourage (a) UK-owned and (b) UK-based private sector companies to invest in UK energy and manufacturing supply chains.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18531","18531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433722","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the effect on the UK economy of UK supply chain contracts being awarded to overseas bidders.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18533","18533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433723","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2015 to Question 18024, when he plans for the membership of the Institute for Apprenticeships to be announced.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18486","18486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433724","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Government's response will be published to the Dowling Review of Business-University Research Collaborations.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18473","18473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433725","2015-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) effect to date and (b) potential future effect on the UK skills base of the outsourcing of UK manufacturing and energy supply chain contracts to other EU member states.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18515","18515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433726","2015-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential economic effect on Scotland of Buchan Deep supply chain work being awarded to a company that will undertake the work overseas.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18518","18518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433727","2015-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential overlap between contributors to the construction industry training levy and the proposed employer apprenticeship levy; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the construction industry of that proposed levy in drawing up those proposals.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18522","18522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433728","2015-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18493","18493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433729","2015-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has conducted of the adequacy of the level of financial support offered to small businesses that have been in operation for two years or less; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18526","18526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433730","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, whether access for disabled students will be included in measures to determine whether higher education institutions deliver effective outcomes for widening access and social mobility.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18540","18540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433731","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of apprentices received (a) formal and (b) informal training in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18542","18542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433732","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of student loan borrowers with post-2012 student loan arrangements in (a) Salford and Eccles constituency, (b) the City of Salford and (c) Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18575","18575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433733","2015-12-07","Cabinet Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) full-time and (b) part-time employees earning less than £10,000 per annum.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18577","18577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433734","2015-12-04","Cabinet Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what Government property is located in Salford and Eccles constituency.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18561","18561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433735","2015-12-04","Cabinet Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18495","18495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433736","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18511","18511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433737","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many of the tax credit claims amended by Concentrix in 2014-15 resulted in a reduced tax credit award; and what the (a) smallest, (b) largest and (c) average value was of the reduction in such cases.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18536","18536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433738","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.122 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what estimate his Department has made of the effect of reducing the income disregard on the household income of a tax credit claimant family with (a) two earners and two children, (b) one earner and two children, (c) two earners and one child and (d) one earner and one child whose income rose by £5,000 during the year.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18553","18553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433739","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 26 November 2015 to Question 16850, how many (a) Notices of Underpayment and (b) financial penalties were issued to employers by HM Revenue and Customs for non-compliance with minimum wage legislation in 2014-15.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18487","18487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433740","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many completed inspections were carried out by HM Revenue and Customs as part of its duty to enforce minimum wage legislation in 2014-15.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18474","18474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433741","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints from workers were received by HM Revenue and Customs on non-compliance with minimum wage legislation in 2014-15.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18483","18483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433742","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to ensure that the status of the City of London as a world financial centre is explicitly protected during the renegotiations on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18443","18443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433743","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of expanding Pension Wise to include consideration of housing wealth as a source of retirement income.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18444","18444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433744","2015-12-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the level of the National Minimum Wage for people aged (a) 16 to 17 years, (b) 18 to 20 years and (c) 21 to 24 years in each year until 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18568","18568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433745","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to publish an update of the National Infrastructure Plan and infrastructure pipeline before the end of 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18541","18541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433746","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what modelling his Department has done to estimate the potential effect on household income for tax credit claimant families who are migrated to universal credit before 2020; and if he will place that modelling in the Library.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18559","18559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433747","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 1.123 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what estimate he has made of the effect of uprating the individual threshold in the minimum income floor for self-employed people on the household income of a tax credit claimant family with two children and one self-employed earner under the age of 25 earning the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18586","18586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433748","2015-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 1.242 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, whether the Government carried out an equality impact assessment on the policy to allow local authorities to raise council tax by two per cent to fund adult social care.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18574","18574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433749","2015-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 1.242 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what estimate he has made of the amount that the two per cent precept for adult social care would raise for each local authority if used fully.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18576","18576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433750","2015-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of how many and what proportion of homeless people (a) are ex-service personnel, (b) have mental health problems and (c) identify as LGBT.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18595","18595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433751","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what management fee was paid to each local authority in Greater Manchester for housing tenants in receipt of housing benefit in temporary accommodation in the last financial year for which information is available.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18560","18560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433752","2015-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on advertising the Right to Buy scheme in each month of 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18460","18460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433753","2015-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the Government will inform local authorities of the increased funding that will be available for housing Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18463","18463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433754","2015-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 October 2015 to Question 11444, when the regeneration strategy for Jaywick will be fully implemented; and if his Department will (a) provide additional resources to improve the (i) standard of housing and (ii) quality of life and (b) liberalise planning rules for house building in Jaywick and Brooklands.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18488","18488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433755","2015-12-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the amount of funding will be for the Starter Homes Local Authority Funding Programme in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18525","18525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433756","2015-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18496","18496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433757","2015-12-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18497","18497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433758","2015-12-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of changes in revenue from the Horserace Betting Levy arising from the activities of remote betting operators based offshore.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18529","18529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433759","2015-12-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to require newspapers and journals to publish on their websites what the questions asked, sample sizes and composition of people in terms of age, sex and ethnicity were for opinion polls cited in their publications.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18490","18490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433760","2015-12-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) funding of horseracing and (b) effect of Race Fields legislation in Australia.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18519","18519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433761","2015-12-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraphs 1.207 to 1.212 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, whether financial support will be provided to the Working Class Movement Library in Salford.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18562","18562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433762","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Financial Conduct Authority plans to publish a consultation on nuisance calls.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18538","18538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433763","2015-12-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 2.144 of the Summer Budget 2015, what progress has been made on designing the Horserace Betting Right; and when he plans to publish his proposals on that matter.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18530","18530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433764","2015-12-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information he has received from TalkTalk concerning the cause of its recent cyber-security breach and the measures it has put in place to prevent another such breach.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18544","18544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433765","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to version 4.3 of JSP 441 Defence Records Management Policy and Procedures, for what period training centres are required to maintain records in relation to (a) trainee attendance and (b) courses held; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18551","18551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433766","2015-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2015 to Question 17694, how many training courses have been completed at (a) MOD Grantown-on-Spey, (b) MOD Llanrwst, (c) MOD Fairbourne and (d) MOD Crickhowell in each year from 2010 to 2015; how many students of each service attended each such course; what the cost of each such course was per trainee; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18571","18571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433767","2015-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2015 to Question 17679, what the maintenance, improvement and development costs of (a) MOD Grantown-on-Spey, (b) MOD Llanrwst, (c) MOD Fairbourne and (d) MOD Crickhowell were in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18570","18570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433768","2015-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2015 to Question 17676, on military bases, whether those beds spaces have been consistently present and utilised in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18572","18572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433769","2015-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2015 to Question 17676, how many nights bed and breakfast has been utilised at (a) MOD Crickhowell, (b) MOD Fairbourne, (c) MOD Grantown-on-Spey and (d) MOD Llanrwst in each of the last five years; and what the cost of that provision was in each case.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18569","18569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433770","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 2 December 2015 to Questions 17676, 17682, 17679, 17694 and 17681, what statistical data was used in the assessment process to close (a) MOD Fairbourne and (b) MOD Llanrwst; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the statistical data contained in his Department's Future Development and Adventure Training review.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18552","18552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433771","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2015 to Question 17682, what the cost per trainee is of the Eagle training scheme at (a) Force Development Training Centre (FDTC) Bavaria, (b) FDTC Grantown-on-Spey, (c) FDTC Danesford/Weston on the Green/Halton and (e) overseas Eagles; and what the location is of the overseas Eagles training.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18588","18588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433772","2015-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on establishment of a Northern Ireland University Air Squadron.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18580","18580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433773","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what planning he has undertaken to ensure that any UN airstrikes in Syria are (a) co-ordinated with all participating countries and (b) do not harm UN relations with the Russian Federation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18467","18467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433774","2015-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2015 to Question 17530, what information his Department holds on which foreign armed forces British military personnel were embedded within the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18524","18524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433775","2015-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the ratio of students to instructors in Force Development and Adventure Training is; whether there is a different ratio of students to instructors for each of those activities; whether that ratio has changed in the last 10 years; whether he plans to review that ratio as a result of the Force Development and Adventure Training review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18491","18491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433776","2015-12-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the ratio of students to instructors varies across his Department's centres which provide force development and adventure training; whether risk assessments have been carried out on the student to instructor ratio in those centres; whether those risk assessments have been changed at any time in the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18535","18535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433777","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18498","18498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433778","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions a special adviser in her Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18499","18499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433779","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effect of the SEND code of practice on educational provision for children with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18478","18478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433780","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve awareness of cerebral palsy among pupils and staff working in schools.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18481","18481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433781","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of regional variations in the level of education provision for children with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18479","18479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433782","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what provisions exist to ensure that children with cerebral palsy have access to appropriate specialist education facilities.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18480","18480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433783","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve awareness of cerebral palsy among people working in children's services.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18477","18477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433784","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2015 to Question 13645, how and by whom each (a) headteacher and (b) school was recommended; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18471","18471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433785","2015-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on child protection of the recommendations of HM Inspectorate of Prisons' thematic report on Behaviour management and restraint of children in custody, published in November 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18445","18445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433786","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of decoupling AS Levels and A Levels on university admissions procedures.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18451","18451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433787","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information she holds on the proportion of A Level students who have chosen to take an AS Level in 2015-16 under the reformed AS Level and A Level system.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18452","18452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433788","2015-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information she holds on the number of countries calling for a commitment to limit global temperature increase to 1.5 degrees; what the Government's policy is on limiting the long-term global temperature increase to 1.5 degrees; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18468","18468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433789","2015-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make representations to the Indian government on ways in which the UK can assist India in moving to use cleaner sources of energy.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18450","18450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433790","2015-12-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she plans to publish a response to her Department's consultation on changes to financial support for solar PV, published on 22 July 2015.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18475","18475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433791","2015-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that supply chain contracts from the Beatrice offshore wind project will create jobs in the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18514","18514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433792","2015-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the financial value of the renewable energy sector supply chain.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18516","18516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433793","2015-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which energy companies have received public funding for renewable contracts and have contracted supply chain work to overseas companies.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18517","18517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433794","2015-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on how many occasions a special adviser in her Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18500","18500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433795","2015-12-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make an estimate of the number of UK jobs that would be created if contracts in the energy sector supply chain were awarded to UK firms.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18532","18532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433796","2015-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the implications for her polices of the Fossil Fuel Subsidy Reform Communiqué presented by the New Zealand Prime Minister John Key on behalf of the Prince of Wales' Corporate Leaders' Group to Christina Figueres, Executive Secretary of the UNFCCC, at COP 21 in Paris on 30 November 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18545","18545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433797","2015-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies on climate change of the recently published report by the Carbon Pricing Leadership Coalition, entitled Executive Guide to Carbon Pricing Leadership.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18546","18546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433798","2015-12-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions her Department has had with the devolved assemblies on best practice on insulation of historic and other older properties.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18578","18578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433799","2015-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to paragraph 2.150 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, how many of the additional homes to be protected from flooding are classified as at (a) very high, (b) high, (c) moderate, (d) low and (e) very low risk of flooding; and what estimate she has made of the number of such homes that will be in each such category after the completion of work to protect them from flooding.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18598","18598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433800","2015-12-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what timetable she proposes for deciding on the funding allocation to the National Wildlife Crime Unit from March 2016.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18534","18534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433801","2015-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on how many occasions a special adviser in her Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18501","18501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433802","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he made of the effect on (a) environmental bodies, (b) biodiversity conservation, (c) pollution prevention, (d) waste reduction and (e) public parks of the proposed reduction in the Landfill Communities Fund.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18459","18459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433803","2015-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of infractions of the Environmental Protection (Restriction of the Use of Lead Shot) (England) Regulations 1999 in the last 15 years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18456","18456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433804","2015-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what financial support her Department has provided to (a) the Convention on Migratory Species and (b) the Preventing Poisoning Working Group of the Convention on Migratory Species in the last five years; and what her policy is on continuing financial support to these organisations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18457","18457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433805","2015-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to Resolution 11.15 adopted by the Eleventh Conference of the Parties to the Convention on the Conservation of Migratory Species of Wild Animals in November 2014, what (a) assessment she has made of and (b) information her Department has received on the extent and type of poisoning risk from lead ammunition in the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18465","18465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433806","2015-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 14443, what sources of funding which are not from the Government are available for the resettlement of Chagossians in the Chagos Archipelago.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18442","18442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433807","2015-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18502","18502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433808","2015-12-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he expects that the trial will begin of Michael Misick, former Prime Minister of the Turks and Caicos Islands.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18563","18563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433809","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) target, (b) average and (c) longest time taken to approve individual funding requests are for diseases in the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18550","18550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433810","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the efficacy of anakinra for patients diagnosed with idiopathic recurrent pericarditis; and what the (a) target, (b) average and (c) longest time taken to approve that drug for use was in the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18549","18549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433811","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what type of drugs were financed by the Cancer Drugs Fund in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18597","18597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433812","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the recent review into pathways for victims of sexual assault; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18592","18592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433813","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many sexual assault referral centres offer therapeutic services for (a) adults and (b) children under 18.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18593","18593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433814","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November to Question 17518, what steps he plans to take to increase the course completion rate for people who are referred to the Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18594","18594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433815","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the obesity rate is for (a) adults and (b) children under the age of 16; and what forecast the Government has made of such rates in 2020.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18579","18579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433816","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the King's Fund's quarterly monitoring report, published in October 2015, that reductions in local authority social care budgets are adversely affecting health services.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18587","18587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433817","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to improve international cooperation on increasing the number of people on the stem cell and bone marrow registers.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18582","18582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433818","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to increase the level of stem cell donations by people of mixed ethnicity.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18583","18583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433819","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of recent progress in increasing the (a) number of people on and (b) quality of the stem cell and bone marrow registers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18584","18584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433820","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to work with the Department for Education on increasing awareness in schools of stem cell donation.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18585","18585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433821","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18503","18503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433822","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2015 to Question 16779, if he will assess the extent to which grants made by his Department to Action on Smoking and Health were used for activities designed to influence his Department, other departments or Parliament.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18543","18543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433823","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department took to promote awareness of the NHS consultation paper on the Government's Mandate to NHS England to 2020 published in October 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18482","18482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433824","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors and nurses were employed by primary care trusts and clinical commissioning groups covering the West Yorkshire area in (a) 2010 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18441","18441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433825","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of guidance from the General Medical Council on the personal liability taken on by medical professionals when prescribing off-label on the rate of off-label prescribing.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18447","18447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433826","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the General Medical Council on amending guidance related to the prescription of off-label drugs and subsequent personal liability.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18448","18448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433827","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evidence his Department holds on the prevalence of off-label prescribing among (a) specialist clinicians, (b) GPs, (c) nurses and (d) other medical professionals.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18449","18449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433828","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 17 November 2015, Official Report, column 515, on non-hospital care, on what date he commissioned Paul Johnson of the Institute for Fiscal Studies to examine pressures in the care home sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18461","18461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433829","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many items of correspondence his Department has received from (a) the Chair and (b) other members of the All Party Parliamentary Group on Smoking and Health in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18458","18458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433831","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps the Government has taken to resolve the migration situation at Calais.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18462","18462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433832","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) stolen cars, (b) untaxed cars, (c) uninsured drivers and (d) other crimes have been detected using automatic number plate recognition in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18521","18521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433833","2015-12-07","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department plans to spend on domestic counter-terrorism operations in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18527","18527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433834","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions a special adviser in her Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18504","18504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433835","2015-12-07","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people applied for British passports through the passport section of the British embassy in Dublin in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18581","18581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433836","2015-12-07","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 1.81 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, whether the protection of overall police spending includes (a) British Transport Police, (b) the Civil Nuclear Constabulary and (c) the Ministry of Defence Police.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18573","18573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433837","2015-12-07","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures her Department has put in place to provide support for Syrian refugees relocated in the UK under the vulnerable persons relocation scheme who do not speak English.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18565","18565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433838","2015-12-07","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether adult children will be included in the vulnerable persons relocation scheme along with their younger siblings and parents.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18566","18566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433839","2015-12-07","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications were initially refused in each month in 2015 to date; and how many such applications were from individuals aged under 18.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18567","18567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433840","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what protections she plans to put in place for landlords who, unwittingly and after carrying out reasonable checks, allow an illegal immigrant to rent their property.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18548","18548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433841","2015-12-07","Department for International Development","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in which countries her Department plans to spend the additional £1 billion of Government funding for humanitarian efforts in and around Syria; and how much of that spending has been allocated for each country.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18564","18564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433842","2015-12-04","Department for International Development","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, on how many occasions a special adviser in her Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18505","18505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433843","2015-12-04","Department for International Development","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of (a) 1.5, (b) 2, (c) 4 and (d) 6 degrees of global warming on (i) countries belonging to the Climate Vulnerable Forum and the Alliance of Small Island States and (ii) the achievement of the Sustainable Development Goals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18469","18469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433844","2015-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children in (a) Burnley and (b) Lancashire have mothers who are serving prison sentences.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18466","18466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433845","2015-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the letter sent in response to Question 6758, answered on 16 July 2015, what offences were committed by the 291 prisoners in the violence against the person category released on temporary licence on 25 December 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18438","18438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433846","2015-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recommendations of HM Inspectorate of Prisons' thematic report on Behaviour management and restraint of children in custody, published in November 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18446","18446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433847","2015-12-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18506","18506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433848","2015-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on maintaining former Magistrates' Courts in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015 to date.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18476","18476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433849","2015-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2015 to Question 17720, if he will take steps to ensure that magistrates' courts seek confirmation of income by means of P60s, payslips, certified accounts or letters confirming benefit entitlement when assessing the level of fines on the basis of income.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18492","18492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433850","2015-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of magistrates has resigned in each month since January 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18537","18537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433851","2015-12-07","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of prisoners with mental health problems; how many and what proportion of such prisoners are (a) men and (b) women; and how many and what proportion of such prisoners identify as LGBT.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18596","18596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433852","2015-12-04","Leader of the House","2015-12-02","To ask the Leader of the House, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Office accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18507","18507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433853","2015-12-04","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, on how many occasions a special adviser in her Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18508","18508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433854","2015-12-07","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has written to congratulate the organisers of the celebrations to commemorate the tercentenary of the Battle of Preston.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18489","18489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433855","2015-12-04","Prime Minister","2015-12-02","To ask the Prime Minister, which (a) business organisations and (b) non-governmental organisations he met during his visit to the COP 21 climate change conference in Paris on 30 November 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18547","18547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433856","2015-12-04","Scotland Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18509","18509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433857","2015-12-04","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18510","18510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433858","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what Government spending was on the Plug-in car grant in each of the last five years; and what estimate his Department has made of Government spending on that grant in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18472","18472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433859","2015-12-04","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to spread the £300 million for cycling announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 over five or six years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18523","18523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433860","2015-12-04","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of buses in England are (a) zero-emission capable, (b) Euro 4 or above and (c) hybrid diesel-electric.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18453","18453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433861","2015-12-04","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent monitoring he has undertaken of the Accessibility Action Plan; and if he will make it his policy to publish annual updates on such monitoring.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18454","18454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433862","2015-12-04","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what correspondence he has had with Vauxhall on Vauxhall Zafira car safety issues; and what steps he has taken to help deal with those issues.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18464","18464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433863","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the additional costs to retro-fit the Great Western Inter-City Express Programme fleet of electric trains with diesel engines.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18539","18539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433864","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency and test staff representatives in order to seek a resolution of the industrial disputes at that Agency.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18591","18591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433865","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department (a) holds and (b) publishes on the rating and qualifications of driving instructors.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18589","18589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433866","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons his Department no longer publishes information on the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency's rating of driving instructors; and if he will take steps to make such information routinely available.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18590","18590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433867","2015-12-04","Wales Office","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18512","18512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433868","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how he takes account of the wellbeing of children in agreeing the activities which lone parents are required to undertake as part of their action plan or claimant commitment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18470","18470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433869","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions a special adviser in his Department accompanied a Minister on an overseas trip since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18513","18513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433870","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 1.125 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what estimate he has made of the number of single claimants under 35 without dependent children living in social housing who are receiving more than the local housing allowance in housing benefit in (a) total and (b) each local authority.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18554","18554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433871","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make one of the qualifying criteria for children under three years of age to access the mobility component of the disability living allowance possession of a blue badge by either of a child's parents.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18520","18520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433872","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 1.125 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, whether the cap on housing benefit for single claimants under 35 will apply to those in receipt of disability benefits.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18555","18555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433873","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each local authority in the Greater Manchester area have been transferred from tax credits to universal credit.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18556","18556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433874","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of tax credit claimants who will be migrated to universal credit in each year to 2020-21.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18557","18557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433875","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit claimant households benefited from the income rise disregard in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18558","18558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/435932","2015-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to modernise the courts and tribunals system.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902614","902614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/435997","2015-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to increase the use of digital technology in the courts and tribunals system.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902612","902612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/435998","2015-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to reform judicial review.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902611","902611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/435999","2015-12-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what rights protected in the Human Rights Act 1998 the Government plans not to include in the proposed British Bill of Rights.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902617","902617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433418","2015-12-03","Attorney General","2015-12-01","To ask the Attorney General, how many and what proportion of prosecutions involved more than one perpetrator in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18371","18371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433419","2015-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the statement by the EU Commission of 18 June 2015 on the termination of intra-EU bilateral investment treaties, to which such treaties the UK is a party; what steps the UK is taking to terminate such treaties to which it is a party; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18402","18402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433420","2015-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the contribution of 30 November 2015 by Lord Mendelsohn, in the House of Lords, Official Report, column 937, if he will place in the Library a copy of the letter referred to on the amendment concerning UK Government Investments Limited.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18385","18385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433421","2015-12-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will extend the support package for workers affected by the closure of Sahaviriya Steel Industries UK to people employed at Cleveland Potash.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18310","18310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433422","2015-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18333","18333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433423","2015-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what provision the Government made in the conditions of the sale of Royal Mail for suitable local alternatives to be provided in the event that local sorting or collection offices were closed.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18348","18348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433424","2015-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Government sought assurances from Royal Mail that local collection offices would not be closed after the sale of that company.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18349","18349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433425","2015-12-04","Cabinet Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2015 to Question 17505, when he will publish the September half-yearly update on the job titles and pay grades of senior civil servants within his Department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18409","18409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433426","2015-12-04","Cabinet Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to update information online on civil servants earning an annual salary of over £150,000.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18440","18440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433427","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the conclusion of its thematic review of the annuities market as to whether consumers are being treated fairly in the current financial climate.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18434","18434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433428","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of his plans for HM Revenue and Customs offices in Liverpool on jobs and services in that area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18408","18408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433429","2015-12-03","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2015, whether the £30 million allocated to the City regions take the form of a cash grant from HM Treasury.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18403","18403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433430","2015-12-03","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Government's policy is on the appropriate percentage rate of return on investment for (a) schools and community groups investing in on-site solar power and (b) foreign state owned companies investing in new nuclear power in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18272","18272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433431","2015-12-03","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of HM Revenue and Customs staff are employed to collect tax on small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18305","18305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433432","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the 26 new Enterprise Zones are which were announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18313","18313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433433","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints from (a) employees and (b) third parties were received by HM Revenue and Customs' National Minimum Wage Risk Unit in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18320","18320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433434","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what total budget was allocated to HM Revenue and Customs' (a) National Minimum Wage Risk Unit, (b) National Minimum Wage compliance teams and (c) Criminal Investigations Directorate in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18321","18321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433435","2015-12-03","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons HM Revenue and Customs offices in Dundee are closing before those in the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18350","18350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433436","2015-12-03","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reasons are for the reduction in Grade 6 and 7 employees of HM Revenue and Customs in Dundee in the last decade.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18351","18351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433437","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce compensation for couples who both work in HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) in Dundee in the event that they are transferred to a HMRC regional office in another location.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18396","18396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433438","2015-12-03","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.143 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, if he will publish an impact assessment on his policy to lower motor insurance costs.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18274","18274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433439","2015-12-04","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed within HM Revenue and Customs' (a) National Minimum Wage Risk Unit, (b) National Minimum Wage compliance teams and (c) Criminal Investigations Directorate in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18319","18319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433440","2015-12-03","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18346","18346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433441","2015-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much Burnley received from the European Regional Development Fund and the European Social Fund in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18275","18275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433442","2015-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18334","18334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433443","2015-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the planning protection for Areas of Outstanding Natural Beauty; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18309","18309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433444","2015-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons he has decided to recover the planning appeals by Caudrilla Resources to build shale gas wells at Roseacre and Preston New Road.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18301","18301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433445","2015-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications have been made to councils for planning permission for change of use of a shop to betting premises since April 2015; and how many such applications have been successful.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18386","18386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433446","2015-12-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to provide additional practice guidance on applying planning policy and legislation in Areas of Outstanding Natural Beauty.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18353","18353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433447","2015-12-08","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 November 2015 to Question 15582, if he will define bus franchising in relation to the North East Devolution Deal and how it differs from a Quality Contact Scheme.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18399","18399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433448","2015-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on New Home Bonuses for district and borough councils; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18428","18428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433449","2015-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what changes are planned for local government funding over the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18430","18430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433450","2015-12-04","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his estimate is of the amount of New Home Bonuses to be granted to (a) East Northants Council, (b) the Borough Council of Wellingborough, (c) Northamptonshire County Council and (d) England in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18429","18429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433451","2015-12-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the report published by Ofcom on 1 December 2015 into broadband speeds in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18412","18412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433452","2015-12-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will reintroduce the Super Highway Broadband Voucher Scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18382","18382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433453","2015-12-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he intends to bring forward legislative proposals to replace the horserace betting levy with a horserace betting right.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18318","18318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433454","2015-12-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18335","18335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433455","2015-12-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance his Department gives to betting companies on the nature of their messages about responsible gambling required in their shop window advertising.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18387","18387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433456","2015-12-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the regulations introduced in April 2015 which ended unsupervised stakes above £50 on Fixed Odds Betting Terminals in betting shops.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18388","18388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433457","2015-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18336","18336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433458","2015-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, from where the Royal Navy will attain the remaining personnel necessary to crew the two new Queen Elizabeth Class aircraft carriers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18258","18258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433459","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what review he has conducted of the operational capacity of Islamic State in Libya; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18324","18324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433460","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2015 to Question 17694, if he will place in the Library documents his Department holds on the Force Development and Adventure Training review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18405","18405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433461","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2015 to Question 17695, how many studies have been completed under JSP507 in each year since 2005; what the title was of each such study; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18407","18407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433462","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how his Department assesses the cost per trainee for force development and adventure training; whether costs for force development are assessed separately to those for adventure training; what the cost is for (a) force development and (b) adventure training; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18406","18406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433463","2015-12-03","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2015 to Question 13645, what process was followed in the appointment of each headteacher to assist her Department on improving the provision of PSHE in schools; where each post was advertised; how many people applied for each such post; how many headteachers were short-listed for interview for those posts; whether consideration was given to each candidate's (a) political views and (b) views on (i) PSHE, (ii) contraception and (iii) abortion in the appointment process; how each candidate was appraised in that process; what criteria were adopted by each candidate; how many candidates for each such post were rejected; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18401","18401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433464","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many area reviews of further education there are which (a) have been completed, (b) are scheduled but have not yet begun, (c) are currently underway and (d) are currently underway and have met at least four times.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18432","18432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433465","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Oral Contribution of the Chancellor of Exchequer of 25 November 2015, Official Report, column 1370, how sixth form colleges that (a) have not been involved in area reviews, (b) are currently involved in area reviews and (c) have previously been involved in area reviews which have now concluded or will soon conclude will apply for academy status.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18431","18431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433466","2015-12-03","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2015 to Question 13645, what the names of each (a) head teacher and (b) school her  Department is currently working with to improve the provision of PSHE in schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18400","18400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433467","2015-12-04","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to encourage educational establishments that cater for people between 16 and 18 years old to teach the dangers of problem gambling.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18390","18390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433468","2015-12-03","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence her Department holds that pupil premium funding improves the life chances of pupils at schools which receive that funding.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18267","18267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433469","2015-12-03","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools in Lewes constituency receive pupil premium funding.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18266","18266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433470","2015-12-03","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of children who are refused admission to a state funded faith school on the grounds of differing faith or belief; and if she will work with schools and faith groups to facilitate inclusive admission policies in all state funded schools.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18302","18302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433471","2015-12-03","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants in her Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18337","18337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433472","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what policies his Department is implementing to promote active fatherhood; and if he will make it his policy that fathers be required to sign birth certificates.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18276","18276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433473","2015-12-07","Department for Education","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in each county and unitary council area in the North West are currently receiving free school meals under Part VI of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18331","18331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433474","2015-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change scenarios for keeping global temperatures below two degrees require (a) negative emissions technologies and (b) peaking of global emissions before (i) 2015 and (ii) 2020; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18352","18352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433475","2015-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what change there has been in the number of jobs in the solar industry in Northern Ireland since January 2015.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18358","18358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433476","2015-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the Paris climate change conference.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18361","18361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433477","2015-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many civil servants in her Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18338","18338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433478","2015-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make an assessment of the effect of replacing the UK's existing coal fired power stations through a combination of energy conservation, demand side measures and renewable power instead of new gas fired power stations on (a) job creation, (b) carbon emissions, (c) household energy bills, (d) long-term energy security and (e) the UK's global influence on securing international action on climate change; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18273","18273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433479","2015-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the proportion of existing fossil fuel reserves that are (a) unburnable under a scenario of keeping temperature increases to below two degrees C and (b) unburnable; and what her policy is on the proportion of primary energy supply (i) in the UK, (ii) globally that should come from oil and gas in (A) 2030 and (B) 2050; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18270","18270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433480","2015-12-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the size of the (a) solar, (b) wind, (c) offshore wind and (d) renewable heat sector is; and by what proportion she plans for these sectors to grow in the next (i) five, (ii) 10 and (iii) 20 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18271","18271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433481","2015-12-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on UK employment of (a) the early closure of renewables obligation and (b) the zero allocation into pot one of the contract for difference auction in 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18404","18404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433482","2015-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which of her Department's properties will be owned and managed by the Government Property Unit; what the annual rent will be; and what the estimated annual cost is of the services the Government Property Unit will provide to her Department.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18383","18383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433483","2015-12-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the cost was of maintaining her Department's properties in (a) London and (b) nationally in 2014-15.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18384","18384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433484","2015-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on the level of atmospheric carbon concentration required to prevent harmful ocean acidification; what assessment she has made of the effect of ocean acidification under atmospheric carbon concentration scenarios used by the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change on (a) marine species and (b) coastal populations; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18269","18269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433485","2015-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received from the professional zoo community in relation to the management of bovine TB in non-bovine farmed animals.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18260","18260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433486","2015-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to ensure that her Department's policy on the management of bovine TB in non-bovine farmed animals does not have a detrimental impact on species kept by zoos.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18257","18257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433487","2015-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what projection she has made of a global temperature increases by (a) 2050 and (b) 2100 caused by greenhouse gas emissions trajectories (i) under current trends and (ii) if all Intended Nationally Determined Contributions are delivered; what the implications of such temperature rises are in the UK for (A) coastal towns and cities, (B) extreme weather events and (C) food security; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18280","18280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433488","2015-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many civil servants in her Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18339","18339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433489","2015-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Pet Travel Scheme in tackling pet smuggling.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18292","18292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433490","2015-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many animals have entered the UK under the Pet Travel Scheme since that scheme's introduction.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18293","18293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433491","2015-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations she has received on reforms to the Pet Travel Scheme to make it harder to smuggle animals into the UK.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18289","18289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433492","2015-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18340","18340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433493","2015-12-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Prime Minister's Oral Statement of 26 November 2015, Official Report, columns 1489-94, what assessment he has made of the level of co-ordination among the 70,000 ground forces referred to as international partners fighting ISIS.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18259","18259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433494","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason UK consular services did not allow medical experts from Gaza to travel to the UK to attend the recent conference at Kingston University on trauma in war zones.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18327","18327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433495","2015-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government held discussions with Commonwealth Heads of Government at the Commonwealth Heads of Government Conference in Malta in November 2015 on increasing the proportion of the UK's trade with Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18262","18262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433496","2015-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from the Libyan Council of Deputies in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18325","18325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433497","2015-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the security risk posed by areas of the Mediterranean shoreline which are under the control of Islamic State; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18322","18322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433498","2015-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to the Libyan Council of Deputies to (a) tackle ungoverned regions and (b) support the transition to a democratic government in Libya; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18323","18323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433499","2015-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent review his Department has conducted of the security and humanitarian situation in (a) Sirte, (b) Ajdabiya, (c) Benghazi, (d) Derma and (e) Az Zawiya in Libya.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18326","18326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433500","2015-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his foreign counterparts on preventing the sale of Daesh-controlled oil; and what steps are being taken to prevent such sales.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18421","18421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433501","2015-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of how many barrels of oil Daesh sell on a daily basis; and which countries are involved in the purchase of that oil.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18420","18420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433502","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of provision of mental health services for children who have been abused.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18415","18415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433503","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there has been in prostate cancer detection rates since publication of the Report of the Prostate Cancer Audit in November 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18435","18435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433504","2015-12-03","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2015 to Question 16575, if he will review the adequacy of the number and accessibility of pharmacy facilities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18425","18425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433505","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of children who receive mental health assessments on entering care; and what assessment he has made of recent trends in such figures.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18416","18416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433506","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2015 to Question 17516, how many of the 756 training places were occupied by existing NHS psychological therapists.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18417","18417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433507","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of local authorities have a suicide prevention strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18418","18418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433508","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of local authorities have a suicide prevention group.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18419","18419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433509","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that weekday services to the NHS are not compromised as a result of a seven day service.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18380","18380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433510","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many consultants have opted out of routine weekend working through the schedule 3 paragraph 6 of the NHS consultant contract in the last year.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18381","18381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433511","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made in achieving seven day services in the NHS which provides the same consultant assessment, diagnostic tests and consultant led interventions for patients seven days a week for (a) 50 per cent of the population by 2018 and (b) 100 per cent of the population by 2020.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18377","18377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433512","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that emergency care is prioritised following the implementation of seven day services in the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18378","18378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433513","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what extra funding will be made available to deliver seven day services in the NHS; and when such funding will be made available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18379","18379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433514","2015-12-03","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he next expects to meet representatives of the care home industry to discuss local authority funding of care homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18363","18363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433515","2015-12-03","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13136, what consideration he has given to such representation made by the hon. Member for Shipley.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18364","18364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433516","2015-12-03","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 November 2015 to Question 14762, if he will place in the Library the additional information received in respect of the application.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18365","18365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433517","2015-12-03","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to amend the annual limit set on nurse educational places; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18279","18279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433518","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Better Care Fund in reducing delayed discharges from hospitals.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18329","18329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433519","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of care homes which have closed in the last two years.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18330","18330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433520","2015-12-03","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18341","18341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433521","2015-12-03","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil servants in her Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18342","18342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433522","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has conducted with its French counterpart on co-ordinating humanitarian relief efforts in Calais.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18314","18314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433523","2015-12-03","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Sri Lankans have been granted refugee status after having previously been removed to Sri Lanka following a refused application for asylum in the UK in each quarter since January 2012.","Biography information for James Berry","James Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18308","18308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433524","2015-12-03","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which parliamentary constituencies do not fall entirely within the 90 per cent coverage of the 4G replacement system being considered as sole bidder for Emergency Services as part of the Emergency Services Mobile Communications Programme.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18304","18304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433525","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assistance and advice her Department is providing to UK volunteers offering assistance to refugees in Calais.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18315","18315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433526","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with her French counterpart on securing a long-term solution to the situation in Calais.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18317","18317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433527","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what preparations her Department has made for the increased level of aid required in Calais when winter sets in.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18316","18316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433528","2015-12-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are being taken at UK border ports to tackle the illegal smuggling of puppies and other animals into the UK.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18290","18290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433529","2015-12-03","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to increase the level of co-ordination with other governmental agencies and departments to prevent the trade of puppies through UK ports.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18291","18291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433530","2015-12-07","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assistance her Department plans to permit Serco to give the Diocese of Blackburn to facilitate the settlement of Syrian refugees in Preston.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18394","18394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433531","2015-12-03","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the net contribution to the UK economy made by immigration from Australia, Canada and New Zealand in the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18261","18261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433532","2015-12-03","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will revise the bidding procurement process for the Emergency Services Mobile Communications Programme in order to increase the number of bidders for the provision of mobile services.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18303","18303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433533","2015-12-03","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to allow the free movement of citizens between the UK, Canada, Australia and New Zealand.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18264","18264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433534","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the definition of Designated Individual referred to in paragraph 53 of the Guide to Powers and Safeguards published in the Draft Investigatory Powers Bill, CM 9152, of November 2015, will include parliamentarians.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18392","18392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433535","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has been made of potential changes in local council tax required to maintain overall police spending in real terms.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18410","18410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433536","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has been made of the cost to police forces of (a) the apprenticeship levy and (b) a single tier pension.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18411","18411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433537","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on interpreters working on behalf of the UK armed forces in Iraq and Afghanistan who wish to seek resettlement in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18436","18436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433538","2015-12-04","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, whether any reduction in the formula grant will be required for the (a) £1 billion Emergency Services Communication Programme and (b) £500 million additional counter-terrorism funding.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18437","18437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433539","2015-12-03","Home Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time is for a standard Disclosure and Barring Service check.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18427","18427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433540","2015-12-03","Department for International Development","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many Syrians are temporarily displaced within Syria; and how many such people are displaced from (a) Daesh controlled areas, (b) Syrian government controlled areas and (c) other areas of conflict.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18413","18413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433541","2015-12-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of how many barrels of oil Daesh sells through Turkey on a daily basis.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18414","18414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433542","2015-12-03","Department for International Development","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to continue to spend £500 million per year on tackling malaria.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18278","18278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433543","2015-12-03","Department for International Development","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has for her Department's Future Fit Programme in each year between 2015-16 and 2019-20.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18306","18306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433544","2015-12-03","Department for International Development","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the net effect of her Department's projects on greenhouse gas emissions in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18307","18307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433545","2015-12-03","Department for International Development","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many civil servants in her Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18343","18343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433546","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18344","18344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433547","2015-12-04","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of prisoners seen by healthcare services on reception were referred to addiction services to help address problem gambling in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18389","18389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433548","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations he has received about the current political situation in Sark and the island of Brecqhou.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18263","18263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433549","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders were given a fixed term recall for (a) breaching the terms of their licence, (b) committing a further offence, (c) a combination of breaching their licence and reoffending and (d) any other reason in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18375","18375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433550","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average ratio of prison officers to prisoners is in (a) male and (b) female prisons.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18366","18366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433551","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what sentences were handed down to offenders convicted of offences involving inciting terrorism in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18367","18367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433552","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders of each offence type pleaded guilty to an offence during (a) the latest period for which information is available after 13 April 2015 and (b) the equivalent period of time before 13 April 2015 in (i) Magistrates Courts and (ii) Crown Courts.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18368","18368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433553","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders of each offence type who pleaded guilty in the latest year for which information is available had committed (a) no other offences, (b) one to five previous offences, (c) six to 15 previous offences, (d) 16 to 50 previous offences, (e) 51 to 100 previous offences and (f) over 100 previous offences.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18369","18369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433554","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of criminal court cases involved more than one perpetrator in the latest year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18370","18370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433555","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of begging in the latest period for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18372","18372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433556","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average size of a cell is in (a) male and (b) female prisons.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18373","18373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433557","2015-12-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of prisoners is per cell in (a) male and (b) female prisons.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18374","18374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433558","2015-12-04","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department is taking to consult people in Northern Ireland Assembly constituencies which will be affected by proposed changes in polling station locations.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18433","18433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433559","2015-12-03","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with (a) the NI Executive, (b) business leaders, (c) third sector representatives on the potential effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18359","18359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433560","2015-12-03","Northern Ireland Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate she has made of the amount of EU funds spent in Northern Ireland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18360","18360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433561","2015-12-04","Department for International Development","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to her oral contribution of 26 November 2015, Official Report, column 1535, what estimate has been made of the cost of reconstruction of Syria after the cessation of conflict there; what the timeframe required for reconstruction in that country will be; what countries have confirmed contributions to that reconstruction; and what the value of each such contribution will be.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18422","18422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433562","2015-12-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 26 November 2015, Official Report, column 1535, what country is responsible for the co-ordination of ground troops; and which coalition countries have agreed to the methodology referred to.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18423","18423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433563","2015-12-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 26 November 2015, Official Report, column 1535, what the estimated transition period is for stability post war.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18424","18424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433564","2015-12-08","Scotland Office","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to paragraph 39 (e) on page 12 of the North East Devolution Agreement, what discussions he has had with the First Minister of Scotland on Government support for joint initiatives between the North East and Scotland.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18332","18332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433565","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with business and tourism representatives in Northern Ireland on the Davies Commission and increased airport capacity in the south east of England.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18362","18362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433566","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18345","18345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433567","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average saving to passengers of capping regulated rail fare rises to RPI+0 until 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18288","18288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433568","2015-12-04","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2015 to Question 16092, how many UK nationals remain in Sharm el-Sheikh.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18312","18312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433569","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on his Department's policies of the recommendations of the Second Global Conference on Road Safety organised by the UN/WHO in Brasilia between 17 and 19 November 2015.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18265","18265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433570","2015-12-04","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the process is for return of passenger baggage surrendered by passengers in Sharm el-Sheikh; how long he expects it to take for all such baggage to be returned; and under what conditions the transport of the baggage was agreed.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18311","18311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433571","2015-12-04","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on introducing (a) flexible rail season tickets and (b) rail season tickets targeted at part-time workers.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18328","18328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433572","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 2065, what progress has been made on the design and planning of the A1 (M) widening scheme; when that process is expected to be completed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18426","18426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433573","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reasons for changes in the number of Blue Badges held in England since 2014.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18354","18354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433574","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on including road policing as a strategic policing requirement.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18355","18355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433575","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential of hydrogen fuel cell vehicles and electric vehicles to help the UK meet the 2050 carbon budget.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18356","18356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433576","2015-12-03","Department for Transport","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to develop (a) a hydrogen vehicle refuelling network and (b) an electric vehicle network.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18357","18357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433577","2015-12-07","Women and Equalities","2015-12-01","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she has visited (a) women's refugee shelters, (b) maternity units, (c) ante-natal groups and (d) women's groups since 15 July 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18393","18393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433578","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2015 to Question 16958, when the process of quality assuring his Department's data on universal credit will be complete; and when he will set out which statistics on universal credit will be published by his Department in the future.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18286","18286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433579","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many local housing allowance rates were set (a) at the 30th percentile, (b) within five per cent of the 30th percentile, (c) between five per cent and 10 per cent of the 30th percentile and (d) more than 10 per cent below the 30th percentile of market rents in the relevant broad market rental area in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13, (iii) 2013-14 and (iv) 2014-15.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18295","18295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433580","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many local housing allowance rates were subject to the overall caps rates for the relevant property size in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13, (c) 2013-14 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18296","18296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433581","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to bring into force section 31 of the Welfare Reform Act 2009.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18287","18287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433582","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the 130 HM Revenue and Customs staff at Caledonian House, Dundee will have a guaranteed job in the new regional HM Revenue and Customs centres in Edinburgh and Glasgow.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18395","18395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433583","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people stopped claiming (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance in the most recent month for which figures are available; and what proportion of such people ended their claim after moving into work.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18297","18297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433584","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of vacancies in each region and nation of the UK which were advertised on Universal Jobmatch were advertised as paying the National Minimum Wage in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18285","18285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433585","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what statutory provision exists to ensure that the claimant commitments of universal credit claimants with dependent children include adequate protections for the wellbeing of the children.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18294","18294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433586","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of vacancies advertised on Universal Jobmatch in the last three months which offered flexible working arrangements for lone parents.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18284","18284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433587","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what redundancy packages will be offered to HM Revenue and Customs staff at Sidlaw House and Caledonian House in Dundee.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18398","18398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433588","2015-12-07","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs staff at Sidlaw House, Dundee will have the same terms and conditions if they are transferred to the new regional centres.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18397","18397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433589","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken since 2012 to evaluate the effectiveness of the application of the work-preparation requirements which have applied to single parents who are in receipt of income support and whose youngest child is aged three or four.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18281","18281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433590","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what timetable he has set for tax credit claimants in Wythenshawe and Sale East constituency to migrate to universal credit.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18277","18277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433591","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of vacancies in each region and nation of the UK which were advertised on Universal Jobmatch in the most recent month for which figures are available were for part-time jobs.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18282","18282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433592","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many civil servants in his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18347","18347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433593","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of lone parents in receipt of (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) income support moved into work after successfully applying for a vacancy advertised on Universal Jobmatch  in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18283","18283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433594","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claims for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance made in the most recent month for which figures are available were made by a person who had been in receipt of the same benefit at any point during the proceeding 12 months.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18300","18300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433595","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has conducted research on the potential effect on the (a) rate of emigration and (b) number of pensioner returnees of unfreezing pensions.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18268","18268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433596","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who stopped claiming (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance in the most recent month for which figures are available subsequently made a new claim for working tax credits.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18298","18298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433597","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance were terminated as a result of a disallowance which followed a sanction in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18299","18299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433598","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much it cost his Department to send out winter fuel allowance payments in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18391","18391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433599","2015-12-03","HM Treasury","2015-12-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how will HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) operate in the time between closing HMRC centres in Dundee and opening new regional centres in Glasgow and Edinburgh.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18376","18376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433600","2015-12-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what transitional arrangements are in place for women affected by the planned increase in the retirement age for state pension recipients.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18439","18439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433830","2015-12-07","Department of Health","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Vaccine Damage Payment scheme.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902566","902566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/434253","2015-12-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of freezing local housing allowance on working families in privately-rented accommodation.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902578","902578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/435630","2015-12-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made on the auto-enrolment of people onto workplace pensions.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902580","902580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/435631","2015-12-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the ease of use for jobseekers and benefits claimants with learning difficulties of digital resources used in Jobcentre Plus offices.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902575","902575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/435632","2015-12-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-12-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to housing benefit announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 on people under 35.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902565","902565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433132","2015-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the different trend in the number of limited partnerships that have been registered in Scotland with Companies House compared to the rest of the UK in each year since 2008; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18099","18099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433133","2015-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies on tackling fraud and money laundering of the findings by Kroll in a report prepared for the National Bank of Moldova in April 2015 on fraud and money laundering in that country, that all but one of the limited partnerships involved had a registered place of business in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18100","18100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433134","2015-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of the science budget in the period from 2010 to 2014 was spent on neurological research.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18131","18131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433135","2015-12-02","Cabinet Office","2015-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what comparative assessment he has made of labour productivity in the South West and England.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18129","18129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433136","2015-12-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish guidance for higher education institutions on how Student Opportunity Fund monies are allocated.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18155","18155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433137","2015-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will have discussions with pub chains on training staff to identify people with suicidal tendencies in order to stop serving such people alcohol.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18209","18209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433138","2015-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support the creation of painting and decorating opportunities in the construction sector.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18208","18208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433139","2015-12-02","HM Treasury","2015-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will discuss with representatives of the insurance industry the effect on premiums of changing weather conditions.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18210","18210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433140","2015-12-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent support his Department has provided to building construction firms to ensure their bills are paid on time.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18211","18211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433141","2015-12-02","Cabinet Office","2015-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive about comparative support between Northern Ireland and the rest of the UK for charities for encouraging young people to get involved in social action.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18164","18164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433142","2015-12-03","Cabinet Office","2015-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, by when Departments are required to publish Single Departmental Plans.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18152","18152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433143","2015-12-03","Cabinet Office","2015-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress has been made on the Big Society initiative.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18153","18153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433144","2015-12-03","Cabinet Office","2015-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) redundancy and (b) voluntary exit programmes for civil servants are currently in operation in each department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18113","18113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433145","2015-12-02","Cabinet Office","2015-11-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to reduce the cost to the economy of computer hacking.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18219","18219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433146","2015-12-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on the income of an existing tax credit claimant in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20 of changes announced to tax credits and the universal credit rollout in the Summer Budget 2015 and the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18226","18226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433147","2015-12-02","HM Treasury","2015-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the benefit to the public purse of the closing of tax loopholes in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18092","18092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433148","2015-12-02","HM Treasury","2015-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether record keeping regulations relating to financial services apply to organisations offering third party data storage to banks.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18188","18188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433149","2015-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on the household income of an existing tax credit claimant family with one earner and three children in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20 of proposed changes to tax credits, assuming they are migrated to universal credit at the start of 2018 and experience a change in circumstance and lose their transitional arrangements.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18172","18172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433150","2015-12-02","HM Treasury","2015-11-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the relative competitiveness in terms of differentials in tax treatment of UK refiners and those importing petroleum products directly from European or international refiners and suppliers as opposed to internal imports in the UK.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18166","18166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433151","2015-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on the household income of an existing tax credit claimant in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20 of proposed changes to tax credits, assuming they are migrated to universal credit at the start of 2018 and experience a change in circumstance and lose their transitional arrangements.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18173","18173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433152","2015-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on the household income of an existing tax credit claimant family with two earners and two children in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20 of proposed changes to tax credits assuming they are migrated to universal credit at the start of 2018 and experience a change in circumstance and lose their transitional arrangements.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18169","18169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433153","2015-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on the income of an existing tax credit claimant in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20 of proposed changes to tax credits, assuming they are migrated to universal credit at the start of 2018.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18174","18174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433154","2015-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on the household income of an existing tax credit claimant family with two earners and three children in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20 of proposed changes to tax credits assuming they are migrated to universal credit at the start of 2018 and experience a change in circumstance and lose their transitional arrangements.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18170","18170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433155","2015-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assumptions his Department has made about the average amount of time for which people migrating from tax credits onto universal credit will have no change in circumstance that means they will lose transitional protection.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18175","18175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433156","2015-12-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on the household income of an existing tax credit claimant family with one earner and two children in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20 of proposed changes to tax credits, assuming they are migrated to universal credit at the start of 2018 and experience a change in circumstance and lose their transitional arrangements.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18171","18171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433157","2015-12-07","Department for Transport","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3 (d)(a) of the North East Devolution Agreement, what funds the Government will provide for phase 2 of the Metro.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18235","18235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433158","2015-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 42 of the North East Devolution Agreement, what the composition of the proposed Steering Group will be; what the process of escalation referred to will be; and what plans he has to report on the activities of the Steering Group to Parliament on an annual or quarterly basis.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18232","18232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/433159","2015-12-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues to local authorities to help them reduce the levels of sickness absence among employees.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 18180","18180"
